snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Gambling revenue <LOCATION>Macau</LOCATION>, world's biggest gaming hub, fell year time casinos liberalised <DATE>2001</DATE>, <LOCATION>Beijing</LOCATION> campaign conspicuous spending public officials led decline wealthy players.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T23:53:20Z,[],263,"Gambling revenue <LOCATION>Macau</LOCATION>, world's biggest gaming hub, fell year time casinos liberalised <DATE>2001</DATE>, <LOCATION>Beijing</LOCATION> campaign conspicuous spending public officials led decline wealthy players.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-macau-gambling-revenue.html,54a624b07988102023c954d7,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Macau<\/LOCATION> Annual Gambling Revenue Falls First Time Since Casino Liberalisation,print_headline:<LOCATION>Macau<\/LOCATION> Annual Gambling Revenue Falls First Time Since Casino Liberalisation}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"North Korean leader Kim J.ng Un New Year's speech <DATE>Thursday</DATE> open talks <LOCATION>Seoul</LOCATION> summit South Korean counterpart, stressed <LOCATION>North Korea</LOCATION> continue strengthen military amid atmosphere...",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T22:01:18Z,[],610,"North Korean leader Kim Jong Un New Year's speech <DATE>Thursday</DATE> open talks <LOCATION>Seoul</LOCATION> summit South Korean counterpart, stressed <LOCATION>North Korea</LOCATION> continue strengthen military amid atmosphere distrust tension diversify economy raise national standard living.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/world/asia/ap-as-nkorea-kim-jong-un.html,54a4b93a79881011bed2a429,Asia Pacific,"{main:North Korean Leader Open Summit With South,print_headline:North Korean Leader Open Summit With South}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
<LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION> announced state aid major energy project <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> drive shore strategic firms public faith banking system economic crisis deepened Western sanctions.,null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T10:29:36Z,[],781,<LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION> announced state aid major energy project <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> drive shore strategic firms public faith banking system economic crisis deepened Western sanctions.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-russia-crisis-gazprom-bk-capital.html,54a416b87988102761d6e1dd,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Russia<\/LOCATION> Ramps Up Aid Strategic Banks, Firms Crisis Deepens,print_headline:<LOCATION>Russia<\/LOCATION> Ramps Up Aid Strategic Banks, Firms Crisis Deepens}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<LOCATION>Saudi Arabia</LOCATION> is not planning to trim public salaries, wages and allowances, state-run media reported <DATE>Sunday</DATE>, just days after an earlier government statement said efforts were being made to reduce such expenditures in the face of a nearly <MONEY>$39 billion</MONEY>...",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-28T13:48:16Z,[],361,"<LOCATION>Saudi Arabia</LOCATION> is not planning to trim public salaries, wages and allowances, state-run media reported <DATE>Sunday</DATE>, just days after an earlier government statement said efforts were being made to reduce such expenditures in the face of a nearly <MONEY>$39 billion</MONEY> deficit that is largely due to falling oil prices.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/28/world/middleeast/ap-ml-saudi-arabia.html,54a0512b7988101f98e3ede7,Middle East,"{main:Saudi: Salaries Will Not Be Cut Curb Spending,print_headline:Saudi: Salaries Will Not Be Cut Curb Spending}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"The town L&#252;liang <LOCATION>Shanxi Province</LOCATION>, coal helped fuel <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>&#8217;s economic boom, center crackdown challenges close ties business government.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:China},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:11,value:Communist Party China},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Coal},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Corruption Institutional},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:4,value:Xi Jinping},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:5,value:<LOCATION>Luliang Shanxi<\/LOCATION>, <LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Economic Conditions Trends},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:Mines Mining},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:8,value:<LOCATION>Shanxi Province China<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:9,value:Xing Libin},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:10,value:Zhang Zhongsheng}]",World,"<LOCATION>Luliang</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>, rich deposits coal helped fuel country's economic boom, center Pres Xi Jinping's corruption crackdown challenging close ties business government; residents fear crackdown jobs growth, businessmen targeted alongside government Communist Party officials.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-28T00:00:00Z,[],1554,"The town L&#252;liang <LOCATION>Shanxi Province</LOCATION>, coal helped fuel <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>&#8217;s economic boom, center crackdown challenges close ties business government.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/world/asia/china-anti-corruption-campaign-takes-toll-on-luliang-shanxi.html,549f141679881001534d1f89,Asia Pacific,"{main:In Limbo, <LOCATION>City China<\/LOCATION> Faces Life After Graft,print_headline:In Limbo, <LOCATION>City China<\/LOCATION> Faces Life After Graft}","{contributor:<PERSON>Kiki Zhao<\/PERSON> contributed research from Lüliang, and <PERSON>Chen Jiehao<\/PERSON> from <LOCATION>Beijing<\/LOCATION>.,original:By <PERSON>IAN JOHNSON<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Ian,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:JOHNSON}]}",article
"A study projected job losses tied decline energy costs largest <LOCATION>Wyoming</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Oklahoma North Dakota</LOCATION>.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Layoffs Job Reductions},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:11,value:<LOCATION>Oklahoma<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:12,value:Budgets Budgeting},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Infrastructure Public Works},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Oil Petroleum Gasoline},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:States US},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:5,value:<LOCATION>Louisiana<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:6,value:<LOCATION>Alaska<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:7,value:<LOCATION>Texas<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:8,value:<LOCATION>Houston<\/LOCATION> Tex},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:9,value:<LOCATION>North Dakota<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:10,value:<LOCATION>Wyoming<\/LOCATION>}]",<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,"Experts elected officials express concerns falling oil prices strongly impact local economies nation's oil- gas-producing states; projected effects include job losses, budget deficits, freeze infrastructure-related projects.",The New York Times,[],National,2014-12-27T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/27/us/oil-web/oil-web-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/us/oil-web/oil-web-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/27/us/oil-web/oil-web-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/us/oil-web/oil-web-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/27/us/oil-web/oil-web-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/us/oil-web/oil-web-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1333,"A study projected job losses tied decline energy costs largest <LOCATION>Wyoming</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Oklahoma North Dakota</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/27/us/falling-oil-prices-have-ripple-effect-in-texas-louisiana-oklahoma.html,549d9e867988105ced788597,null,"{main:Some States See Budgets Risk Oil Price Falls,print_headline:Some States See Budgets Risk Oil Price Falls}","{contributor:<PERSON>Manny Fernandez<\/PERSON> reported <LOCATION>Houston<\/LOCATION>, <PERSON>Jeremy Alford Baton Rouge<\/PERSON>, <LOCATION>La<\/LOCATION>. <PERSON>Kirk Johnson<\/PERSON> contributed reporting <LOCATION>Seattle<\/LOCATION>.,original:By <PERSON>MANNY FERNANDEZ JEREMY ALFORD<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Manny,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:FERNANDEZ},{firstname:Jeremy,role:reported,organization:,rank:2,lastname:ALFORD}]}",article
"Eco-conscious buyers, primarily <LOCATION>North America</LOCATION>, playing increasing role <LOCATION>Costa Rica</LOCATION> market, developers sales agents.",,"[{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:1,value:Costa Rica},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Environment},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Sustainable Living}]",Great Homes & Destinations,null,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-26T11:30:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/26/greathomesanddestinations/26RECOSTA02/26RECOSTA02-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/greathomesanddestinations/26RECOSTA02/26RECOSTA02-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/26/greathomesanddestinations/26RECOSTA02/26RECOSTA02-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/greathomesanddestinations/26RECOSTA02/26RECOSTA02-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/26/greathomesanddestinations/26RECOSTA02/26RECOSTA02-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/greathomesanddestinations/26RECOSTA02/26RECOSTA02-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",996,"Eco-conscious buyers, primarily <LOCATION>North America</LOCATION>, playing increasing role <LOCATION>Costa Rica</LOCATION> market, developers sales agents.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/26/greathomesanddestinations/saving-the-earth-without-losing-a-buck.html,549bf52d7988100306691143,null,"{main:Saving Earth Without Losing Buck,print_headline:Saving Earth Without Losing Buck}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>KEVIN BRASS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Kevin,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BRASS}]}",article
"<LOCATION>Saudi Arabia</LOCATION>'s Cabinet on <DATE>Thursday</DATE> endorsed a <DATE>2015</DATE> budget that projects a slight increase in spending and a significant drop in revenues due to sliding oil prices, resulting in a nearly <MONEY>$39 billion</MONEY> deficit.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-25T08:48:46Z,[],666,"<LOCATION>Saudi Arabia</LOCATION>'s Cabinet on <DATE>Thursday</DATE> endorsed a <DATE>2015</DATE> budget that projects a slight increase in spending and a significant drop in revenues due to sliding oil prices, resulting in a nearly <MONEY>$39 billion</MONEY> deficit.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/25/world/middleeast/ap-ml-saudi-economy.html,549c16377988100306691161,Middle East,"{main:Saudi Dig Into Reserves 2015 Budget,print_headline:Saudi Dig Into Reserves 2015 Budget}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Mayor <PERSON>Bill de Blasio</PERSON> said he would attend the funerals of Officers <PERSON>Rafael Ramos</PERSON> and <PERSON>Wenjian Liu</PERSON>, whose backgrounds diverge from the <ORGANIZATION>New York Police Department</ORGANIZATION>’s Irish and Italian roots.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Funerals Memorials},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Attacks Police},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Police Department NYC},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:4,value:Liu, Wenjian 1982-2014},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:5,value:Ramos, Rafael 1974-2014},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:6,value:de Blasio, Bill},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:7,value:Murders, Attempted Murders Homicides},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:8,value:<LOCATION>New York City<\/LOCATION>}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"Funerals <LOCATION>New York City</LOCATION> <ORGANIZATION>Police Officers Wenjian Liu Rafael Ramos</ORGANIZATION> follow traditions protocols place decades, reflect diverse force; backgrounds officers reflect divergence department's Irish Italian roots past decade; Mayor de Blasio speak funerals criticism leveled police unions.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-23T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/23/nyregion/Y-FUNERAL/Y-FUNERAL-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/23/nyregion/Y-FUNERAL/Y-FUNERAL-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/23/nyregion/Y-FUNERAL/Y-FUNERAL-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/23/nyregion/Y-FUNERAL/Y-FUNERAL-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/23/nyregion/Y-FUNERAL/Y-FUNERAL-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/23/nyregion/Y-FUNERAL/Y-FUNERAL-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1245,"Mayor <PERSON>Bill de Blasio</PERSON> said he would attend the funerals of Officers <PERSON>Rafael Ramos</PERSON> and <PERSON>Wenjian Liu</PERSON>, whose backgrounds diverge from the <ORGANIZATION>New York Police Department</ORGANIZATION>’s Irish and Italian roots.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/23/nyregion/as-nypd-and-its-funerals-evolve-several-constants-remain.html,5498dc89798810035238e715,null,"{main:At <ORGANIZATION>New York Police Department Funerals<\/ORGANIZATION>, Politics, Grief Shifting Traditions,print_headline:At Police Funerals, Politics, Grief Shifting Traditions}","{contributor:<PERSON>Jeffrey E. Singer<\/PERSON> contributed reporting.,original:By <PERSON>AL BAKER J. DAVID GOODMAN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Al,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BAKER},{firstname:J.,role:reported,organization:,middlename:David,rank:2,lastname:GOODMAN}]}",article
"In heart western <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>, Belgian-Dutch-German rust belt dealt blow.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-21T05:12:53Z,[],657,"In heart western <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>, Belgian-Dutch-German rust belt dealt blow.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/21/business/21reuters-eu-investment-rustbelt-insight.html,54969d5979881029b367dedc,null,"{main:As Ford Closes, European Rust Belt Seeks New Ideas,print_headline:As Ford Closes, European Rust Belt Seeks New Ideas}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
