snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Chinese property developer <ORGANIZATION>Kaisa Group Holdings</ORGANIZATION> said it had failed to repay a <MONEY>HK$400 million 33 million pounds</MONEY> loan and warned it may default on more debt, the latest problem to hit the firm amid a downturn in the real estate sector.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T21:46:17Z,[],322,"Chinese property developer <ORGANIZATION>Kaisa Group Holdings</ORGANIZATION> said it had failed to repay a <MONEY>HK$400 million 33 million pounds</MONEY> loan and warned it may default on more debt, the latest problem to hit the firm amid a downturn in the real estate sector.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-china-kaisa-group-debt.html,54a607197988102023c95255,null,"{main:<LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION> Developer Kaisa Says Fails to Repay <MONEY>$51 Mln<\/MONEY> Loan, May Default on Others,print_headline:<LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION> Developer Kaisa Says Fails to Repay <MONEY>$51 Mln<\/MONEY> Loan, May Default on Others}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"ROSENBERG--<PERSON>Fred L.</PERSON>, died peacefully month shy 96th birthday independently living home amid friends <PERSON>Kendal Hudson Sleepy Hollow</PERSON>, NY <DATE>December 23, 2014</DATE>. Fred passed ten years day death...",null,[],Paid Death Notices,null,,[],Classified,2015-01-01T19:17:00Z,[],262,"<!-- FRED ROSENBERG --><PERSON>ROSENBERG</PERSON>--<PERSON>Fred L.</PERSON>,<br/><br/> died peacefully a month shy of his 96th birthday while independently living in his new home amid new friends at <ORGANIZATION>Kendal on Hudson</ORGANIZATION> in <LOCATION>Sleepy Hollow</LOCATION>, NY on <DATE>December 23, 2014</DATE>. Fred passed ten years to the day after the death of his beloved wife of 56 years, artist <PERSON>Joan Mattison Rosenberg</PERSON>, who never left his thoughts. <ORGANIZATION>Navy</ORGANIZATION> Lieutenant on LST 281 in a D-Day Landing, and later captain of LST 357 in the <LOCATION>Pacific</LOCATION>, <PERSON>Fred</PERSON> went on to success as textile marketing executive for leading knit firms including <ORGANIZATION>Fab Industries</ORGANIZATION>, creating many iconic fabrics such as Supersuede. An avid sportsman, he played outfield for <ORGANIZATION>Syracuse University</ORGANIZATION> in the Class of <DATE>1939</DATE>, semi- pro baseball in <LOCATION>Boston</LOCATION>, and into his 90s helped coach and took batting practice with The Kettle softball team in a <LOCATION>Central Park</LOCATION> league. Published playwright, poet, composer, and spirited performer for friends and family, <PERSON>Fred</PERSON> was a favorite piano pupil of <PERSON>Paul Creston</PERSON>, crooned with an orchestra in college, and was a lifelong student of music, literature and art. Warm, loving and spiritual, <PERSON>Fred</PERSON> is survived by his close sister <PERSON>Janet Black</PERSON> of <LOCATION>Pocasset</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>MA</LOCATION>, his dear daughter <PERSON>Vicki Rosenberg</PERSON>, his admiring son <PERSON>Eric</PERSON> and daughter-in-law <PERSON>Helen</PERSON>, and his devoted grandchildren <PERSON>Karen Rosenberg</PERSON>, <PERSON>Stuart M. Rosenberg</PERSON>, and <PERSON>Stuart</PERSON>'s wife <PERSON>Halsey Varady</PERSON>. Memorial Service <DATE>Sunday</DATE>, <DATE>January 25, 2015</DATE> at 11am at <ORGANIZATION>Temple Emanu-El</ORGANIZATION>, Fifth Avenue at 65th Street. Contributions in Fred's memory may be made to The Art Students League of <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>, attn: <PERSON>Joan M. Rosenberg</PERSON> Memorial Scholarship Fund, 215 West 57th St., <ORGANIZATION>NYC</ORGANIZATION>, NY 10019.<br><br> ",Paid Death Notice,http://www.legacy.com/Link.asp?I=LS000173695175,54a66c247988102023c95555,null,"{main:Paid Notice: Deaths  ROSENBERG, FRED}",null,article
"Beset critics buffeted economic woes, <ORGANIZATION>European Union</ORGANIZATION> chiefs forgiven thinking Pope <PERSON>Francis</PERSON> apply balm New Year address <ORGANIZATION>EU</ORGANIZATION> parliament.",null,[],Business Day,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T11:26:15Z,[],694,"Beset critics buffeted economic woes, <ORGANIZATION>European Union</ORGANIZATION> chiefs forgiven thinking Pope <PERSON>Francis</PERSON> apply balm New Year address <ORGANIZATION>EU</ORGANIZATION> parliament.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/business/ap-eu-europes-new-year.html,54a575c579881011bed2ceaa,null,"{main:Troubled <ORGANIZATION>EU<\/ORGANIZATION> Hoping Only Way Is Up 2015,print_headline:Troubled <ORGANIZATION>EU<\/ORGANIZATION> Hoping Only Way Is Up 2015}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<PERSON>Conner Lee Derek Ting</PERSON>, <LOCATION>Largo Winch</LOCATION>, maverick <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> Hedge fund trader uncanny analytic abilities, predicts unprecedented move <ORGANIZATION>Federal Reserve</ORGANIZATION> sparks investor interest <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>. <PERSON>Mark Patterson Linus Roache</PERSON>, Batman Begins,",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T10:34:47Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-supercapitalist/video-supercapitalist-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-supercapitalist/video-supercapitalist-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-supercapitalist/video-supercapitalist-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-supercapitalist/video-supercapitalist-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-supercapitalist/video-supercapitalist-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-supercapitalist/video-supercapitalist-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",37,"<PERSON>Conner Lee Derek Ting</PERSON>, <LOCATION>Largo Winch</LOCATION>, maverick <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> Hedge fund trader uncanny analytic abilities, predicts unprecedented move <ORGANIZATION>Federal Reserve</ORGANIZATION> sparks investor interest <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>. <PERSON>Mark Patterson Linus Roache</PERSON>, Batman Begins,",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003379070/supercapitalist.html,555da9e67988106d1827c88d,null,{"main":"Trailer: ‘Supercapitalist’"},"{original:Gravitas Ventures,person:[{firstname:Gravitas,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Ventures}]}",multimedia
"The Dramatists Guild Fund has awarded <MONEY>$170,000</MONEY> to dozens of nonprofit theaters across the country, from the firmly established Soho Repertory Theatre in <LOCATION>New York City</LOCATION> to the young Mo'olelo Performing Arts Company in <LOCATION>San Diego</LOCATION>.",null,[],Arts,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T10:24:57Z,[],317,"The Dramatists Guild Fund has awarded <MONEY>$170,000</MONEY> to dozens of nonprofit theaters across the country, from the firmly established Soho Repertory Theatre in <LOCATION>New York City</LOCATION> to the young Mo'olelo Performing Arts Company in <LOCATION>San Diego</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/arts/ap-us-theater-dramatists-guild-fund-.html,54a5678479881011bed2cb7f,null,"{main:Dramatists Guild Fund Announces <MONEY>$170K<\/MONEY> in Grants,print_headline:Dramatists Guild Fund Announces <MONEY>$170K<\/MONEY> in Grants}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Beset critics buffeted economic woes, <ORGANIZATION>European Union</ORGANIZATION> chiefs forgiven thinking Pope <PERSON>Francis</PERSON> apply balm New Year address <ORGANIZATION>EU</ORGANIZATION> parliament.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T07:44:52Z,[],694,"Beset critics buffeted economic woes, <ORGANIZATION>European Union</ORGANIZATION> chiefs forgiven thinking Pope <PERSON>Francis</PERSON> apply balm New Year address <ORGANIZATION>EU</ORGANIZATION> parliament.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/world/europe/ap-eu-europes-new-year-.html,54a5424279881011bed2c33b,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:Troubled <ORGANIZATION>EU<\/ORGANIZATION> Hoping Only Way Is Up 2015,print_headline:Troubled <ORGANIZATION>EU<\/ORGANIZATION> Hoping Only Way Is Up 2015}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"There's year campaigning, positioning politicking campaign president kicks <LOCATION>Iowa</LOCATION> Caucus early <DATE>2016</DATE>. Ten things year campaign...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T03:09:54Z,[],1200,"There's year campaigning, positioning politicking campaign president kicks <LOCATION>Iowa</LOCATION> Caucus early <DATE>2016</DATE>. Ten things year campaign underway shake.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/us/politics/ap-us-2016-things-to-watch.html,54a501a679881011bed2b49c,Politics,"{main:10 Things <DATE>2015<\/DATE> That Could Affect 2016 Campaign,print_headline:10 Things <DATE>2015<\/DATE> That Could Affect 2016 Campaign}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Governors political spectrum hitting roadblock bids expand Medicaid federal funds: Republican legislators adamantly oppose Obamacare.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T03:06:44Z,[],797,Governors political spectrum hitting roadblock bids expand Medicaid federal funds: Republican legislators adamantly oppose Obamacare.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/us/politics/ap-us-medicaid-politics.html,54a500ed79881011bed2b473,Politics,"{main:GOP Legislators Thwart Bids Expand Medicaid,print_headline:GOP Legislators Thwart Bids Expand Medicaid}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"On verge making partner, <PERSON>Josh Pratt</PERSON>'s life turned upside <ORGANIZATION>SEC</ORGANIZATION> investigates head multibillion-dollar hedge fund insider trading. Forced well-timed vacation asked, <PERSON>Josh</PERSON> finds Bangk",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T01:28:53Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-a-stranger-in-paradise/video-a-stranger-in-paradise-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-a-stranger-in-paradise/video-a-stranger-in-paradise-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-a-stranger-in-paradise/video-a-stranger-in-paradise-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-a-stranger-in-paradise/video-a-stranger-in-paradise-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-a-stranger-in-paradise/video-a-stranger-in-paradise-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-a-stranger-in-paradise/video-a-stranger-in-paradise-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",41,"On verge making partner, <PERSON>Josh Pratt</PERSON>'s life turned upside <ORGANIZATION>SEC</ORGANIZATION> investigates head multibillion-dollar hedge fund insider trading. Forced well-timed vacation asked, <PERSON>Josh</PERSON> finds Bangk",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003378125/a-stranger-in-paradise.html,54a4e92879881011bed2af14,null,{"main":"A Stranger In Paradise"},"{original:Freestyle Digital Media,person:[{firstname:Freestyle,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Digital,rank:1,lastname:Media}]}",multimedia
"LITVAK--<PERSON>Sheila Firestone</PERSON>. Devoted adored wife <PERSON>Harold</PERSON> 55 years. Loving mother <PERSON>Michael Maria</PERSON>, <PERSON>Cassie</PERSON>, <PERSON>Lizabeth Brad</PERSON>. The Fabulous <PERSON>Bubba Liana</PERSON>, <PERSON>Anna Lilly</PERSON>. Cherished sister <PERSON>Tina</PERSON>. Sheila lived life fullest,...",14,"[{name:persons,value:LITVAK, SHEILA}]",Paid Death Notices,null,The New York Times,[],Classified,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,[],105,"LITVAK--<PERSON>Sheila Firestone</PERSON>. Devoted and adored wife of <PERSON>Harold</PERSON> for 55 years. Loving mother of <PERSON>Michael</PERSON> and <LOCATION>Maria</LOCATION>, <PERSON>Cassie</PERSON>, <PERSON>Lizabeth</PERSON> and <PERSON>Brad</PERSON>. The Fabulous Bubba to <LOCATION>Liana</LOCATION>, <PERSON>Anna</PERSON> and <ORGANIZATION>Lilly</ORGANIZATION>. Cherished sister to <PERSON>Tina</PERSON>. Sheila lived life to its fullest, always a beacon of strength and a source of love and an inspiration to all she touched. Contributions may be made in her honor to The Dr. <PERSON>Carol Aghajanian</PERSON> Ovarian Cancer Research Fund, <ORGANIZATION>Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center</ORGANIZATION>. Funeral will be private. There will be a celebration of her life on <DATE>January 7, 2015</DATE>, 4-8pm at <ORGANIZATION>The Savoy</ORGANIZATION>, 200 East 61st St., <LOCATION>New York City</LOCATION>. 1/3",Paid Death Notice,http://query.nytimes.com/gst/fullpage.html?res=9502E5D81F3AF932A35752C0A9639D8B63,54af528a79881022e94b385a,null,"{main:Paid Notice: Deaths  LITVAK, SHEILA FIRESTONE}",null,article
