snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
Here major events arrest trial Al-Jazeera English journalists imprisoned <LOCATION>Egypt</LOCATION> year:,null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T03:07:42Z,[],655,Here major events arrest trial Al-Jazeera English journalists imprisoned <LOCATION>Egypt</LOCATION> year:,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/world/middleeast/ap-ml-egypt-al-jazeera-timeline.html,54a500e179881011bed2b46e,Middle East,"{main:A Look <LOCATION>Egypt<\/LOCATION>'s Al-Jazeera English Trial,print_headline:A Look <LOCATION>Egypt<\/LOCATION>'s Al-Jazeera English Trial}","{original:By THE ASSOC.ATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"The football coach takes baggy khakis, creating trend, moves <ORGANIZATION>University Michigan</ORGANIZATION>.",4,"[{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Harbaugh<\/PERSON>, Jim},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Fashion Apparel},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Football College},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:4,value:<PERSON>Ann Arbor<\/PERSON> Mich},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:5,value:University <LOCATION>Michigan<\/LOCATION>}]",Fashion & Style,"<PERSON>Ann Arbor</PERSON>, MI, retail stores report sudden rise popularity men's khaki pants <LOCATION>San Francisco</LOCATION> 49ers coach <PERSON>Jim Harbaugh</PERSON>, wearing baggy khakis, moved head football coach <LOCATION>University Michigan</LOCATION>.",The New York Times,[],Styles,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01KHAKI2/01KHAKI2-thumbWide-v3.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01KHAKI2/01KHAKI2-thumbWide-v3.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01KHAKI2/01KHAKI2-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:835},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01KHAKI2/01KHAKI2-articleLarge.jpg,height:835},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01KHAKI2/01KHAKI2-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01KHAKI2/01KHAKI2-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",844,"The football coach takes baggy khakis, creating trend, moves <ORGANIZATION>University Michigan</ORGANIZATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/fashion/jim-harbaugh-inspires-a-run-on-khakis-at-michigan.html,54a461a779881011bed29017,null,"{main:<PERSON>Jim Harbaugh<\/PERSON> Inspires Run Khakis <LOCATION>Michigan<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:Jeans? Coach Says You’re Out of Uniform}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>JENNIFER CONLIN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Jennifer,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:CONLIN}]}",article
"<PERSON>Ed Miliband</PERSON>, leader <LOCATION>Britain</LOCATION>'s opposition, damaged chances winning <DATE>May</DATE>'s national election steering Labour party left, Labour prime minister <PERSON>Tony Blair</PERSON> <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T06:56:40Z,[],376,"<PERSON>Ed Miliband</PERSON>, leader <LOCATION>Britain</LOCATION>'s opposition, damaged chances winning <DATE>May</DATE>'s national election steering Labour party left, Labour prime minister <PERSON>Tony Blair</PERSON> <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/world/europe/31reuters-britain-politics.html,54a3e4c97988102761d6dc26,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:Left Turn Could Cost UK's Labour <DATE>2015<\/DATE> Election, Says Ex-PM <PERSON>Blair<\/PERSON>,print_headline:Left Turn Could Cost UK's Labour <DATE>2015<\/DATE> Election, Says Ex-PM <PERSON>Blair<\/PERSON>}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"As city officials work soften <ORGANIZATION>New York Police Department</ORGANIZATION>'s image change officers engage citizens reforms training, part effort happening online.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T01:35:38Z,[],815,"As city officials work soften <ORGANIZATION>New York Police Department</ORGANIZATION>'s image change officers engage citizens reforms training, part effort happening online.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/ap-us-nypd-twitter-school.html,54a399937988102761d6d37a,null,"{main:NYPD Seeks Engage With 'Twitter School,' Blog,print_headline:NYPD Seeks Engage With 'Twitter School,' Blog}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION>&#8217;s energy minister energy giant, G.zprom, helped shape Bulgarian bill pipeline President <PERSON>Vladimir V. Putin</PERSON> sought <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION> dependent Russian gas.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Putin<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Vladimir<\/PERSON> V},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:11,value:Siderov, Volen},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:12,value:<PERSON>Oresharski<\/PERSON>, Plamen},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Natural Gas},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Pipelines},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:4,value:<LOCATION>Russia<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:5,value:<LOCATION>Bulgaria<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:6,value:Series},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:7,value:<LOCATION>Ukraine<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:8,value:Gazprom},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:9,value:<PERSON>Miller<\/PERSON>, Aleksei B},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:10,value:Oil Petroleum Gasoline}]",World,"Russian President <PERSON>Vladimir V Putin</PERSON> bullied urged <LOCATION>Bulgaria</LOCATION> years accept plan South Stream pipeline deliver natural gas southern <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>, underestimated West's response aggression <LOCATION>Ukraine</LOCATION> stopped project; serves case study <PERSON>Putin</PERSON> energy foreign-policy tool wielded tools crony capitalism <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION> home Series: <PERSON>Putin</PERSON>'s Way.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-31T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/world/jpPutin1/jpPutin1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/world/jpPutin1/jpPutin1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/world/jpPutin1/jpPutin1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:378},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/world/jpPutin1/jpPutin1-articleLarge.jpg,height:378},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/world/jpPutin1/jpPutin1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/world/jpPutin1/jpPutin1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",2801,"<LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION>&#8217;s energy minister energy giant, <ORGANIZATION>Gazprom</ORGANIZATION>, helped shape Bulgarian bill pipeline President <PERSON>Vladimir V. Putin</PERSON> sought <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION> dependent Russian gas.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/world/europe/how-putin-forged-a-pipeline-deal-that-derailed-.html,54a370c67988102761d6cfb3,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{content_kicker:<PERSON>Putin<\/PERSON>'s Way,main:How Putin Forged Pipeline Deal That Derailed,print_headline:How Putin Forged Pipeline Deal That Derailed,kicker:<PERSON>Putin<\/PERSON>'s Way}","{contributor:<PERSON>Jim Yardley<\/PERSON> reported <LOCATION>Sofia<\/LOCATION>, <PERSON>Jo Becker<\/PERSON> <LOCATION>Budapest New York<\/LOCATION>. <PERSON>Georgi Kantchev<\/PERSON> contributed reporting <LOCATION>Sofia<\/LOCATION>, <PERSON>Masha Goncharova<\/PERSON> <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION>.,original:By <PERSON>JIM YARDLEY JO BECKER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Jim,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:YARDLEY},{firstname:Jo,role:reported,organization:,rank:2,lastname:BECKER}]}",article
Scientists traced origins current epidemic toddler Guinea caught virus bats tree village.,4,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:Guinea},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:Ouamouno, Emile},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Bats},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Ebola Virus},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:6,value:EMBO Molecular Medicine Journal},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:7,value:Koch, <PERSON>Robert<\/PERSON>, Institute}]",Health,"Study published online journal EMBO Molecular Medicine <LOCATION>Berlin</LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>Robert Koch Institute</ORGANIZATION> suggests <PERSON>Emile Ouamouno</PERSON>, toddler Guinea believed case current outbreak Ebola, caught virus bats.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-31T00:00:00Z,[],505,Scientists traced origins current epidemic toddler Guinea caught virus bats tree village.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/health/source-of-ebola-outbreak-might-be-bats-study-says.html,54a342d27988102761d6cf5d,null,"{main:Source Ebola Outbreak West Africa Might Be Bats, Study Says,print_headline:Source Ebola Outbreak Might Be Bats, Study Says}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>DONALD G. McNEIL<\/PERSON> Jr,person:[{firstname:Donald,role:reported,qualifier:Jr,organization:,middlename:G.,rank:1,lastname:McNEIL}]}",article
"<PERSON>Harbaugh</PERSON>, left <LOCATION>San Francisco</LOCATION> 49ers return college coaching, expected provide jolt energy Wolverines&#8217; beleaguered football program.",,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Football College},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Coaches Managers},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:3,value:<LOCATION>San Francisco<\/LOCATION> 49ers},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:University <LOCATION>Michigan<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:5,value:<PERSON>Harbaugh<\/PERSON>, Jim}]",Sports,null,The New York Times,[],Sports,2014-12-31T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/sports/31michigan2/31michigan2-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/sports/31michigan2/31michigan2-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/sports/31michigan2/31michigan3-1419961255962-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:386},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/sports/31michigan2/31michigan3-1419961255962-articleLarge.jpg,height:386},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/sports/31michigan2/31michigan2-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/sports/31michigan2/31michigan2-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1177,"<PERSON>Harbaugh</PERSON>, left <LOCATION>San Francisco</LOCATION> 49ers return college coaching, expected provide jolt energy Wolverines&#8217; beleaguered football program.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/sports/ncaafootball/jim-harbaugh-is-michigans-next-football-coach.html,54a2f7e07988102761d6cea8,College Football,"{main:<LOCATION>Michigan<\/LOCATION> Makes It Official: <PERSON>Jim Harbaugh<\/PERSON> Is Football Coach,print_headline:<LOCATION>Michigan<\/LOCATION> Makes It Official: <PERSON>Jim Harbaugh<\/PERSON> Is Football Coach}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>JOANNE C. GERSTNER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Joanne,role:reported,organization:,middlename:C.,rank:1,lastname:GERSTNER}]}",article
"The Gambian government insisted &#8220;peace calm&#8221; prevailed gunfire erupted overnight capital, <LOCATION>Banjul</LOCATION>.",6,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Coups D'Etat Attempted Coups D'Etat},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>Gambia<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Jammeh<\/PERSON>, Yahya},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:4,value:<LOCATION>Banjul Gambia<\/LOCATION>}]",World,"<LOCATION>United States Embassy Gambia</LOCATION> reports attempted coup capital city <LOCATION>Banjul</LOCATION>, soldiers sealing government buildings main bridge gunfire erupting overnight; Gambian government issues nondescript statement denying coup attempt, <PERSON>Pres Yahya Jammeh</PERSON>, traveling country, reported planning return country <LOCATION>Chad</LOCATION>.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-31T00:00:00Z,[],660,"The Gambian government insisted &#8220;peace calm&#8221; prevailed gunfire erupted overnight capital, <LOCATION>Banjul</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/world/africa/banjul-gambia.html,54a290037988104803cc8a5e,<LOCATION>Africa</LOCATION>,"{main:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Embassy Describes Coup Attempt <LOCATION>Gambia<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Embassy Describes Coup Attempt <LOCATION>Gambia<\/LOCATION>}","{contributor:<PERSON>Alan Cowell<\/PERSON> contributed reporting <LOCATION>London<\/LOCATION>.,original:By RUKMINI CALLIMACHI,person:[{firstname:Rukmini,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:CALLIMACHI}]}",article
"A teenager accused bringing loaded gun northern <LOCATION>Utah</LOCATION> high school part plan open fire students charged misdemeanor weapons violations, sheriff's official confirmed <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T13:01:11Z,[],424,"A teenager accused bringing loaded gun northern <LOCATION>Utah</LOCATION> high school part plan open fire students charged misdemeanor weapons violations, sheriff's official confirmed <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/us/ap-us-student-with-gun.html,54a2e92f7988102761d6ce7f,null,"{main:Utah Teen Accused School Shooting Plot Charged,print_headline:Utah Teen Accused School Shooting Plot Charged}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<LOCATION>Gambia</LOCATION>'s President <PERSON>Yahya Jammeh</PERSON> returning home <LOCATION>Chad</LOCATION> late <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>, gunfire erupted presidential palace Gambian capital <LOCATION>Banjul</LOCATION> night.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T05:13:53Z,[],541,"<LOCATION>Gambia</LOCATION>'s President <PERSON>Yahya Jammeh</PERSON> returning home <LOCATION>Chad</LOCATION> late <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>, gunfire erupted presidential palace Gambian capital <LOCATION>Banjul</LOCATION> night.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/world/30reuters-gambia-security.html,54a27b5d7988104803cc8a39,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Gambia<\/LOCATION> President Says Flying Home After Gunfire Rocks Banjul,print_headline:<LOCATION>Gambia<\/LOCATION> President Says Flying Home After Gunfire Rocks Banjul}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
