snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Rigorous evidence should inform spending. Until lately, it hasn’t.",19,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:United States Politics Government},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:11,value:Research},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Federal Budget US},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:3,value:United States},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:4,value:<PERSON>Obama<\/PERSON>, Barack},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:5,value:House Representatives},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:Senate},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:7,value:Republican Party},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:8,value:Education K-12},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:9,value:Nurse-Family Partnership},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:10,value:Success All Foundation}]",Opinion,"Op-Ed article policy analyst <PERSON>Ron Haskins</PERSON> applauds <PERSON>Obama</PERSON> administration's long-term evidence-based results improving social policy; holds choice social welfare programs based rigorous evidence success; urges <ORGANIZATION>Congress</ORGANIZATION> reject Republican efforts cut <PERSON>Obama</PERSON> administration's evidence-based programs, social policy important left guesswork.",The New York Times,[],OpEd,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/opinion/01Haskins/01Haskins-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/opinion/01Haskins/01Haskins-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/opinion/01Haskins/01Haskins-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:486},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/opinion/01Haskins/01Haskins-articleLarge.jpg,height:486},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/opinion/01Haskins/01Haskins-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/opinion/01Haskins/01Haskins-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",919,"Rigorous evidence should inform spending. Until lately, it hasn’t.",Op-Ed,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/opinion/social-programs-that-work.html,54a4a21679881011bed29ed4,null,"{content_kicker:Op-Ed Contributor,main:Social Programs That Work,print_headline:Social Programs That Work,kicker:Op-Ed Contributor}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>RON HASKINS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Ron,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:HASKINS}]}",article
Trans-Atlantic transfers dominated West End fringe theaters <DATE>2014</DATE>.,,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Theater},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>London England<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Miller<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Arthur<\/PERSON>},{is_major:N,name:creative_works,rank:4,value:A Streetcar Named Desire Play},{is_major:N,name:creative_works,rank:5,value:The Crucible Play}]",Theater,null,The New York Times,[],Culture,2014-12-31T13:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/arts/international/31iht-lon31A/31iht-lon31A-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/arts/international/31iht-lon31A/31iht-lon31A-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/arts/international/31iht-lon31A/31iht-lon31A-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/arts/international/31iht-lon31A/31iht-lon31A-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/arts/international/31iht-lon31A/31iht-lon31A-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/arts/international/31iht-lon31A/31iht-lon31A-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1285,Trans-Atlantic transfers dominated West End fringe theaters <DATE>2014</DATE>.,Review,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/arts/international/american-plays-revealed-anew-on-the-london-stage.html,54a2a62a7988104803cc8a7a,null,"{content_kicker:Theater Review,main:American Plays Revealed Anew London Stage,print_headline:American Plays Revealed Anew London Stage,kicker:Theater Review}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>MATT WOLF<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Matt,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:WOLF}]}",article
No claimed responsibility suicide bomber rammed vehicle celebrated female parliamentarian <PERSON>Shukria Barakzai</PERSON>. She walked wreckage <DATE>Nov. 16</DATE> blast killed civilians wounded 20.,null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T07:12:59Z,[],795,No claimed responsibility suicide bomber rammed vehicle celebrated female parliamentarian <PERSON>Shukria Barakzai</PERSON>. She walked wreckage <DATE>Nov. 16</DATE> blast killed civilians wounded 20.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/world/asia/31reuters-afghanistan-women-insight.html,54a3e9007988102761d6dc98,Asia Pacific,"{main:As U.S.-Led Combat Mission Ends, Afghan Women Fear Oppression,print_headline:As U.S.-Led Combat Mission Ends, Afghan Women Fear Oppression}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"More 4 million people signed time re-enrolled health plans month latest sign-up period Affordable Care Act, report released <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>. A people state...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T01:31:02Z,[],213,"More 4 million people signed time re-enrolled health plans month latest sign-up period Affordable Care Act, report released <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>. A people state enrolled marketplace health plan 2015:",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/ap-us-health-overhaul-sign-ups-glance.html,54a398e27988102761d6d36b,null,"{main:A <ORGANIZATION>Look Number People Enrolled Health Plans 2015<\/ORGANIZATION>,print_headline:A <ORGANIZATION>Look Number People Enrolled Health Plans<\/ORGANIZATION> 2015}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Fewer <PERCENT>1 percent</PERCENT> state&#8217;s teachers rated ineffective year; rated appeal win case arbiter.,15,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Performance Evaluations Labor},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Teachers School Employees},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Cuomo<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Andrew<\/PERSON> M},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Education K-12},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:5,value:New York State},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:<LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION> State United Teachers}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"<LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> Gov <PERSON>Andrew M Cuomo</PERSON>'s veto legislation protect teachers receive consecutive 'ineffective' performance ratings based poor student test scores leave hundreds teachers danger termination; teacher's union pointed inadequate preparation time Common Core curriculum standards, <PERSON>Cuomo</PERSON> continues focus <DATE>2015</DATE> goal making easier remove teachers low ratings.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-31T00:00:00Z,[],807,Fewer <PERCENT>1 percent</PERCENT> state&#8217;s teachers rated ineffective year; rated appeal win case arbiter.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/nyregion/cuomo-veto-highlights-difficulties-of-firing-a-teacher.html,54a375b37988102761d6cfd1,null,"{main:Cuomo Veto Highlights Difficulties Firing Teacher,print_headline:Cuomo Veto Highlights Difficulties Firing Teacher}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>KATE TAYLOR<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Kate,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:TAYLOR}]}",article
No claimed responsibility suicide bomber rammed vehicle celebrated female parliamentarian <PERSON>Shukria Barakzai</PERSON>. She walked wreckage <DATE>Nov. 16</DATE> blast killed civilians wounded 20.,null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T16:08:21Z,[],800,No claimed responsibility suicide bomber rammed vehicle celebrated female parliamentarian <PERSON>Shukria Barakzai</PERSON>. She walked wreckage <DATE>Nov. 16</DATE> blast killed civilians wounded 20.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/world/asia/30reuters-afghanistan-women-insight.html,54a314b07988102761d6cef1,Asia Pacific,"{main:As U.S.-Led Combat Mission Ends, Afghan Women Fear Oppression,print_headline:As U.S.-Led Combat Mission Ends, Afghan Women Fear Oppression}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
A lawyer man charged sexually assaulting campers <LOCATION>Wyoming</LOCATION> decades ago <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> 94-year-old death northern <LOCATION>Michigan</LOCATION> make weekend.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T14:15:56Z,[],335,A lawyer man charged sexually assaulting campers <LOCATION>Wyoming</LOCATION> decades ago <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> 94-year-old death northern <LOCATION>Michigan</LOCATION> make weekend.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/us/ap-us-sexual-assaults-elderly-suspect.html,54a2fab47988102761d6ceab,null,"{main:Lawyer: Man Wanted Old Camp Assaults Near Death,print_headline:Lawyer: Man Wanted Old Camp Assaults Near Death}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"More 4 million people signed time re-enrolled health plans month latest sign-up period Affordable Care Act, report released <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>. A people state...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T13:24:19Z,[],214,"More 4 million people signed time re-enrolled health plans month latest sign-up period Affordable Care Act, report released <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>. A people state enrolled marketplace health plan 2015:",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/us/ap-us-health-overhaul-sign-ups-glance.html,54a2eec17988102761d6ce91,null,"{main:A <ORGANIZATION>Look Number People Enrolled Health Plans 2015<\/ORGANIZATION>,print_headline:A <ORGANIZATION>Look Number People Enrolled Health Plans<\/ORGANIZATION> 2015}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
The contractor runs nation's premier national laboratories lost <MONEY>tens millions dollars</MONEY> federal government officials call performance failure.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T04:16:48Z,[],481,The contractor runs nation's premier national laboratories lost <MONEY>tens millions dollars</MONEY> federal government officials call performance failure.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/us/ap-us-nuke-repository-los-alamos.html,54a26e067988104803cc8a13,null,"{main:Feds Dock Los Alamos Lab Performance Review,print_headline:Feds Dock Los Alamos Lab Performance Review}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Gov. <PERSON>Andrew M. Cuomo</PERSON>, administration drafted legislation, recent days make evaluation system <ORGANIZATION>New York State</ORGANIZATION> tougher.",null,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Performance Evaluations Labor},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Tests Examinations},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Education K-12},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:<LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION> State United Teachers},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:5,value:<PERSON>Cuomo<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Andrew<\/PERSON> M},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:6,value:New York State}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,null,The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-30T00:00:00Z,[],534,"Gov. <PERSON>Andrew M. Cuomo</PERSON>, administration drafted legislation, recent days make evaluation system <ORGANIZATION>New York State</ORGANIZATION> tougher.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/nyregion/cuomo-in-reversal-vetoes-bill-that-would-have-protected-teachers-from-low-ratings.html,54a2301c7988104803cc897d,null,{"main":"Cuomo Vetoes Bill That Would Protect Teachers From Low Ratings"},"{original:By <PERSON>KATE TAYLOR<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Kate,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:TAYLOR}]}",article
