snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
<PERSON>Tara Boras Tarek Arafat</PERSON> wanted larger rental apartment Upper West Side.,4,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Real Estate Housing Residential},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:2,value:Upper West Side <LOCATION>Manhattan<\/LOCATION>, NY},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Renting Leasing Real Estate}]",Real Estate,"The Hunt column on search by couple <PERSON>Tara Boras</PERSON> and <PERSON>Tarek Arafat</PERSON> for rental apartment on <LOCATION>Upper West Side</LOCATION> for under <MONEY>$3,500</MONEY> per month; found one-bedroom prewar walk-up in <LOCATION>West 90s</LOCATION> for <MONEY>$3,000</MONEY> per month.",The New York Times,[],RealEstate,2014-12-28T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/28/realestate/28HUNTMAIN/28HUNT-MAIN-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/realestate/28HUNTMAIN/28HUNT-MAIN-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/28/realestate/28HUNTMAIN/28HUNT-MAIN-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/realestate/28HUNTMAIN/28HUNT-MAIN-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/28/realestate/28HUNTMAIN/28HUNT-MAIN-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/realestate/28HUNTMAIN/28HUNT-MAIN-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",909,<PERSON>Tara Boras Tarek Arafat</PERSON> wanted larger rental apartment Upper West Side.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/realestate/room-for-people-plants-and-cats.html,549c34947988100306691184,null,"{content_kicker:The Hunt,main:Room People, Plants Cats,seo:Searching Apartment Upper West Side,print_headline:Room People, Plants Cats,kicker:The Hunt}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>JOYCE COHEN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Joyce,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:COHEN}]}",article
After 20 years spent working Christmas holidays <ORGANIZATION>Rio Ferdinand</ORGANIZATION> forgiven wanted put feet enjoy fruits long career.,null,[],Sports,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-25T05:48:30Z,[],437,After 20 years spent working Christmas holidays <ORGANIZATION>Rio Ferdinand</ORGANIZATION> forgiven wanted put feet enjoy fruits long career.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/25/sports/soccer/25reuters-soccer-england-qpr.html,549bec03798810030669113b,Soccer,"{main:QPR's Ferdinand Hoping Be Busy During Holiday Fixtures,print_headline:QPR's Ferdinand Hoping Be Busy During Holiday Fixtures}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
The Russian drama &#8220;Leviathan&#8221; turns modern-day Job Hobbesian brute seat power.,null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Movies},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:Zvyagintsev, Andrey},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:3,value:Serebryakov, <PERSON>Aleksey<\/PERSON>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:4,value:Liadova, <PERSON>Elena<\/PERSON>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:5,value:Pokhodaev, Sergey},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:6,value:<PERSON>Negin<\/PERSON>, Oleg},{is_major:Y,name:creative_works,rank:7,value:Leviathan Movie}]",Movies,"<PERSON>Manohla Dargis</PERSON> reviews movie Leviathan, directed Andrey Zvyagintsev starring <PERSON>Aleksey Serebryakov</PERSON>.",The New York Times,[],Culture,2014-12-25T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/25/arts/LEVIATHAN/LEVIATHAN-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/arts/LEVIATHAN/LEVIATHAN-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/25/arts/LEVIATHAN/LEVIATHAN-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:397},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/arts/LEVIATHAN/LEVIATHAN-articleLarge.jpg,height:397},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/25/arts/LEVIATHAN/LEVIATHAN-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/arts/LEVIATHAN/LEVIATHAN-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",792,The Russian drama &#8220;Leviathan&#8221; turns modern-day Job Hobbesian brute seat power.,Review,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/25/movies/leviathan-turns-on-a-modern-day-job.html,549b37507988100306690efb,null,"{content_kicker:Movie Review,main:Life: Poor, Nasty, Brutish Probably Short,seo:&#8216;Leviathan&#8217; Turns Modern-Day Job,print_headline:Life: Poor, Nasty, Brutish Probably Short,kicker:Movie Review | 'Leviathan'| 'Leviathan'}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>MANOHLA DARGIS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Manohla,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:DARGIS}]}",article
Some people <LOCATION>Hawaii</LOCATION> dreaming White Christmas.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-24T00:15:23Z,[],348,Some people <LOCATION>Hawaii</LOCATION> dreaming White Christmas.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/24/us/ap-us-hawaii-blizzard.html,549a4cb87988102d96d564bc,null,"{main:Blizzard Gives Hawaii Summits White Christmas,print_headline:Blizzard Gives Hawaii Summits White Christmas}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"A mix <ORGANIZATION>Gulf Coast</ORGANIZATION> thunderstorms expected travel north, predicted snowfall Great Lakes blustery conditions nation's midsection threatened <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> tangle holiday travel plans nationwide.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-23T14:33:18Z,[],577,"A mix <ORGANIZATION>Gulf Coast</ORGANIZATION> thunderstorms expected travel north, predicted snowfall Great Lakes blustery conditions nation's midsection threatened <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> tangle holiday travel plans nationwide.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/23/us/ap-us-holiday-travel.html,5499c3d97988102d96d54f6c,null,"{main:Severe Weather Could Snarl Holiday Travel,print_headline:Severe Weather Could Snarl Holiday Travel}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"The rouble hit highest levels weeks <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>, shored informal capital control measures designed head repeat inflation protests marked <LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION>'s <DATE>1998</DATE> financial crisis.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-23T02:11:13Z,[],897,"The rouble hit highest levels weeks <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>, shored informal capital control measures designed head repeat inflation protests marked <LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION>'s <DATE>1998</DATE> financial crisis.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/23/business/23reuters-russia-crisis-rouble.html,54991627798810035238e77b,null,"{main:Informal Capital Controls Arrest Russian Rouble's Slide,print_headline:Informal Capital Controls Arrest Russian Rouble's Slide}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"As focus travelers produce revenue, airlines making difficult frequent fliers accumulate miles cheaply year-end.",6,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Airlines Airplanes},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Business Travel},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Customer Relations},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:<ORGANIZATION>United Airlines<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:5,value:<ORGANIZATION>Delta Air Lines<\/ORGANIZATION>, Inc},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Frequent Flier Programs},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:Travel Vacations},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:8,value:American Airlines},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:9,value:<ORGANIZATION>US Airways Group Inc<\/ORGANIZATION>}]",Business Day,<PERSON>Joe Sharkey</PERSON> On Road column describes airlines <ORGANIZATION>United Delta</ORGANIZATION> making difficult frequent fliers achieve higher status levels year's end taking cheap flights run mileage; notes push made focus customers produce revenue.,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-23T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/23/business/Road/Road-thumbWide-v2.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/23/business/Road/Road-thumbWide-v2.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/23/business/Road/Road-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/23/business/Road/Road-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",953,"As focus travelers produce revenue, airlines making difficult frequent fliers accumulate miles cheaply year-end.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/23/business/for-frequent-flier-mileage-runs-time-is-running-out.html,5498be46798810035238e6c8,null,"{content_kicker:On Road,main:For Frequent Flier Mileage Runs, <ORGANIZATION>Time<\/ORGANIZATION> Is Running Out,print_headline:Time Is Running Out Mileage Runs Fliers,kicker:On Road}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>JOE SHARKEY<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Joe,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SHARKEY}]}",article
"Pope <PERSON>Francis</PERSON> issued blistering critique <DATE>Monday</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>Vatican</ORGANIZATION> bureaucracy serves, denouncing people lust power costs live hypocritical double lives.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-22T06:16:13Z,[],913,"Pope <PERSON>Francis</PERSON> issued blistering critique <DATE>Monday</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>Vatican</ORGANIZATION> bureaucracy serves, denouncing people lust power costs live hypocritical double lives.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/22/world/europe/ap-eu-rel-vatican-reform.html,5497fda07988104a1e0df124,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:Pope Blistering Critique Vatican Bureaucrats,print_headline:Pope Blistering Critique Vatican Bureaucrats}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Readers discuss prosperity avoidance materialism coexist.,8,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Welfare US},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Ethics Personal},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Income Inequality},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Social Conditions Trends}]",Opinion,null,The New York Times,[],Letters,2014-12-21T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/20/sunday-review/l21abundance/l21abundance-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/20/sunday-review/l21abundance/l21abundance-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/20/sunday-review/l21abundance/l21abundance-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:600},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/20/sunday-review/l21abundance/l21abundance-articleLarge.jpg,height:600},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/20/sunday-review/l21abundance/l21abundance-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/20/sunday-review/l21abundance/l21abundance-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",909,Readers discuss prosperity avoidance materialism coexist.,Letter,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/21/opinion/sunday/the-ethics-of-wealth.html,5495ce4579881029b367ddc8,<DATE>Sunday</DATE> Review,"{content_kicker:Letters,main:The Ethics Wealth,print_headline:The Ethics Wealth,kicker:Letters}",[],article
"The volume <PERSON>Norton</PERSON>&#8217;s two-part anthology includes texts <LOCATION>Hinduism</LOCATION>, Buddhism Daoism.",8,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Books Literature},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Religion Belief},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:Miles, <PERSON>Jack<\/PERSON>},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:4,value:Lopez, <PERSON>Donald<\/PERSON> S Jr},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:5,value:<PERSON>Doniger<\/PERSON>, Wendy},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:7,value:<PERSON>Robinson<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>James<\/PERSON> Jr <DATE>1939<\/DATE>-},{is_major:N,name:creative_works,rank:8,value:The Norton Anthology World Religions Book}]",Books,"<PERSON>William Dalrymple</PERSON> reviews book The Norton Anthology World Religions Volume I: <LOCATION>Hinduism</LOCATION>, Buddhism, <LOCATION>Daoism</LOCATION>, edited <PERSON>Jack Miles</PERSON>, <PERSON>Wendy Doniger</PERSON>, <PERSON>Donald S Lopez</PERSON> Jr <PERSON>James Robson</PERSON>.",The New York Times,[],BookReview,2014-12-21T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/21/books/review/sub-21dalrymple/sub-21dalrymple-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/21/books/review/sub-21dalrymple/sub-21dalrymple-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/21/books/review/sub-21dalrymple/sub-21dalrymple-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:899},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/21/books/review/sub-21dalrymple/sub-21dalrymple-articleLarge.jpg,height:899},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/21/books/review/sub-21dalrymple/sub-21dalrymple-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/21/books/review/sub-21dalrymple/sub-21dalrymple-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1167,"The volume <PERSON>Norton</PERSON>&#8217;s two-part anthology includes texts <LOCATION>Hinduism</LOCATION>, Buddhism Daoism.",Review,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/21/books/review/the-norton-anthology-of-world-religions-volume-i.html,549470e57988107c468004c5,<DATE>Sunday</DATE> Book Review,"{main:‘The Norton Anthology of World Religions: Volume I’,print_headline:Among Believers}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>WILLIAM DALRYMPLE<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:William,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:DALRYMPLE}]}",article
