snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"The relative importance genes shift years environment, study suggests.",,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Genetics Heredity},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Obesity},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Proceedings National Academy Sciences},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:4,value:<PERSON>Christakis<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Nicholas<\/PERSON> A},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Research}]",Science,null,The New York Times,[],Science,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/science/01zimmer/01zimmer-thumbWide-v2.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/science/01zimmer/01zimmer-thumbWide-v2.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/science/01zimmer/01zimmer-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:466},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/science/01zimmer/01zimmer-articleLarge.jpg,height:466},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/science/01zimmer/01zimmer-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/science/01zimmer/01zimmer-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",871,"The relative importance genes shift years environment, study suggests.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/science/gene-linked-to-obesity-hasnt-always-been-a-problem-study-finds.html,54a480b279881011bed29730,null,"{content_kicker:Matter,main:Gene Linked to Obesity Hasn’t Always Been a Problem, Study Finds,kicker:Matter}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>CARL ZIMMER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Carl,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:ZIMMER}]}",article
"The Bank <LOCATION>Portugal</LOCATION> <DATE>Wednesday 17</DATE> institutions expressed interest sale <ORGANIZATION>Novo Banco</ORGANIZATION>, bank created collapse Banco Espirito Santo <DATE>August</DATE>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T14:40:39Z,[],286,"The Bank <LOCATION>Portugal</LOCATION> <DATE>Wednesday 17</DATE> institutions expressed interest sale <ORGANIZATION>Novo Banco</ORGANIZATION>, bank created collapse Banco Espirito Santo <DATE>August</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-novobanco-sale.html,54a451c779881011bed28c78,null,"{main:Bank <LOCATION>Portugal<\/LOCATION> Says 17 Institutions Interested Novo Banco,print_headline:Bank <LOCATION>Portugal<\/LOCATION> Says 17 Institutions Interested Novo Banco}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<PERSON>Gabe Karen</PERSON>, happily married middle-aged couple, friends <PERSON>Tom Beth</PERSON>, married couple, years. In fact, <PERSON>Gabe Karen</PERSON> fixed friends place. While dinner <PERSON>Gabe Karen</PERSON>'s",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2014-12-31T13:24:07Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-dinner-with-friends/video-dinner-with-friends-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-dinner-with-friends/video-dinner-with-friends-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-dinner-with-friends/video-dinner-with-friends-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-dinner-with-friends/video-dinner-with-friends-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-dinner-with-friends/video-dinner-with-friends-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-dinner-with-friends/video-dinner-with-friends-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",44,"<PERSON>Gabe Karen</PERSON>, happily married middle-aged couple, friends <PERSON>Tom Beth</PERSON>, married couple, years. In fact, <PERSON>Gabe Karen</PERSON> fixed friends place. While dinner <PERSON>Gabe Karen</PERSON>'s",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003317358/dinner-with-friends.html,54a43f4d79881011bed28864,null,{"main":"Dinner With Friends"},"{original:HBO Video,person:[{firstname:Hbo,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Video}]}",multimedia
"Average <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> mortgage rates rose slightly week, benchmark 30-year rate stayed 19-month low.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T10:05:45Z,[],240,"Average <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> mortgage rates rose slightly week, benchmark 30-year rate stayed 19-month low.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/politics/ap-us-mortgage-rates.html,54a4111f7988102761d6e141,Politics,"{main:Average US 30-Year Mortgage Rate Edges Up <PERCENT>3.87%<\/PERCENT>,print_headline:Average US 30-Year Mortgage Rate Edges Up <PERCENT>3.87%<\/PERCENT>}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<LOCATION>Israel</LOCATION>'s economy grew estimated <PERCENT>2.6 percent</PERCENT> <DATE>2014</DATE>, slowest pace years, <DATE>summer</DATE> war dragged, expected pick pace year.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T08:58:48Z,[],365,"<LOCATION>Israel</LOCATION>'s economy grew estimated <PERCENT>2.6 percent</PERCENT> <DATE>2014</DATE>, slowest pace years, <DATE>summer</DATE> war dragged, expected pick pace year.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-israel-gdp.html,54a401a17988102761d6df7a,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Israel<\/LOCATION> Economy Grows 2.6 Percent <DATE>2014<\/DATE>, Seen Faster 2015,print_headline:<LOCATION>Israel<\/LOCATION> Economy Grows 2.6 Percent <DATE>2014<\/DATE>, Seen Faster 2015}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"- <ORGANIZATION>The United Arab Emirates Egypt</ORGANIZATION> attractive major <ORGANIZATION>Middle Eastern</ORGANIZATION> stock markets era low oil prices, latest <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION> survey regional asset managers suggests.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T00:02:01Z,[],731,"- <ORGANIZATION>The United Arab Emirates Egypt</ORGANIZATION> attractive major <ORGANIZATION>Middle Eastern</ORGANIZATION> stock markets era low oil prices, latest <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION> survey regional asset managers suggests.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-mideast-investment-survey.html,54a383c07988102761d6d0d4,null,"{main:Funds Positive <ORGANIZATION>UAE<\/ORGANIZATION>, <LOCATION>Egypt<\/LOCATION> Stocks Era Cheap Oil-Survey,print_headline:Funds Positive <ORGANIZATION>UAE<\/ORGANIZATION>, <LOCATION>Egypt<\/LOCATION> Stocks Era Cheap Oil-Survey}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
The Knicks&#8217; <PERSON>Cole Aldrich</PERSON> laugh missing tooth &#8212; bright spot team&#8217;s miserable season.,10,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Basketball},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:2,value:New York Knicks},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Aldrich<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Cole<\/PERSON>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:4,value:<PERSON>Fisher<\/PERSON>, Derek <DATE>1974<\/DATE>-}]",Sports,"<LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> Knicks center <PERSON>Cole Aldrich</PERSON> proving bright spot dark season team, starting games shooting <PERCENT>63 percent</PERCENT> field.",The New York Times,[],Sports,2014-12-31T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/sports/KNICKS/KNICKS-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/sports/KNICKS/KNICKS-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/sports/KNICKS/KNICKS-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:1280},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/sports/KNICKS/KNICKS-articleLarge.jpg,height:1280},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/sports/KNICKS/KNICKS-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/sports/KNICKS/KNICKS-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",975,The Knicks&#8217; <PERSON>Cole Aldrich</PERSON> laugh missing tooth &#8212; bright spot team&#8217;s miserable season.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/sports/basketball/the-knicks-cole-aldrich-a-bright-spot-steps-in-to-fill-the-void.html,54a363e57988102761d6cf99,Pro Basketball,"{main:The Knicks’ <PERSON>Cole Aldrich<\/PERSON>, a Bright Spot, Steps In to Fill the Void,print_headline:Not All Gloom Doom: Knicks Find Bright Spot}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>BILLY WITZ<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Billy,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:WITZ}]}",article
A passionate column looked news drew criticism.,null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Macur<\/PERSON>, Juliet},{name:persons,rank:2,value:Winston, Jameis},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:<ORGANIZATION>Florida State University<\/ORGANIZATION>},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Colleges Universities},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Sex Crimes}]",Opinion,A passionate column looked news drew criticism.,The New York Times,[],null,2014-12-30T13:30:10Z,[],966,null,Blog,http://publiceditor.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/from-a-writer-and-from-readers-strong-opinions-on-winston-rape-accusations/,54a2ef857988102761d6ce92,The Public Editor,"{main:From Writer From Readers, Strong Opinions Campus Rape Accusations,kicker:The Public Editor&#039;s Journal}","{original:By <PERSON>MARGARET SULLIVAN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Margaret,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SULLIVAN}]}",blogpost
"<ORGANIZATION>Goldman Sachs</ORGANIZATION> paid its top 121 <LOCATION>London</LOCATION> bankers about <MONEY>3 million pounds $4.7 million</MONEY> on average <DATE>last year</DATE>, far exceeding payouts at other leading banks, data released on <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> showed.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T12:44:01Z,[],327,"<ORGANIZATION>Goldman Sachs</ORGANIZATION> paid its top 121 <LOCATION>London</LOCATION> bankers about <MONEY>3 million pounds $4.7 million</MONEY> on average <DATE>last year</DATE>, far exceeding payouts at other leading banks, data released on <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> showed.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/business/30reuters-banks-britain-pay.html,54a2e4e27988102761d6ce6d,null,"{main:Goldman Tops UK Banker Pay With <MONEY>$4.7 Million<\/MONEY> Awarded for <DATE>2013<\/DATE>,print_headline:Goldman Tops UK Banker Pay With <MONEY>$4.7 Million<\/MONEY> Awarded for <DATE>2013<\/DATE>}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"An <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> Zest plane carrying 159 people overshot runway stuck muddy field <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> international airport central <LOCATION>Philippines</LOCATION> landing <LOCATION>Manila</LOCATION> windy weather, officials. There reports injuries.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T07:06:04Z,[],314,"An <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> Zest plane carrying 159 people overshot runway stuck muddy field <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> international airport central <LOCATION>Philippines</LOCATION> landing <LOCATION>Manila</LOCATION> windy weather, officials. There reports injuries.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/world/asia/ap-as-philippines-plane-overshoots-runway.html,54a2961d7988104803cc8a69,Asia Pacific,"{main:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Plane With 159 Aboard Overshoots Philippine Runway,print_headline:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Plane With 159 Aboard Overshoots Philippine Runway}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
