snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Despite illness, job loss, caring daughter severe autism financial troubles, <PERSON>Maria Maley</PERSON>, &#8220;If bills paid, I&#8217;m happy.&#8221;",23,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:New York Times Neediest Cases Fund},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Philanthropy},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:3,value:UJA-Federation of <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION>}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"Metropolitan C.uncil on Jewish Poverty, a beneficiary agency of UJA-Federation <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>, one of the organizations supported by <ORGANIZATION>The New York Times Neediest</ORGANIZATION> Cases Fund, draws <MONEY>$1,100</MONEY> to help unemployed <LOCATION>Staten Island</LOCATION> woman <PERSON>Maria Maley</PERSON> pay arrears on her rent.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-28T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/27/nyregion/27NEEDIESTMaley/27NEEDIESTMaley-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/nyregion/27NE.DIESTMaley/27NEEDIESTMaley-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/27/nyregion/27NEEDIESTMaley/27NEEDIESTMaley-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/nyregion/27NEEDIESTMaley/27NEEDIESTMaley-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/27/nyregion/27NEEDIESTMaley/27NEEDIESTMaley-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/nyregion/27NEEDIESTMaley/27NEEDIESTMaley-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",861,"Despite illness, job loss, caring daughter severe autism financial troubles, <PERSON>Maria Maley</PERSON>, &#8220;If bills paid, I&#8217;m happy.&#8221;",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/nyregion/for-staten-island-mother-her-two-daughters-needs-always-come-first.html,549f524979881001534d1fc3,null,"{content_kicker:The Neediest Cases,main:For <LOCATION>Staten Island Mother<\/LOCATION>, Her Two Daughters&#8217; Needs Always Come First,print_headline:For <LOCATION>Staten Island Mother<\/LOCATION>, Her Two Daughters’ Needs Always Come First,kicker:The Neediest Cases}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>JOHN OTIS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:John,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:OTIS}]}",article
"<PERSON>Beata Bien</PERSON>, emigrated <LOCATION>Poland</LOCATION> <DATE>1993</DATE>, abandoned boyfriend learned pregnant. Then learned cancer people.",25,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:New York Times Neediest Cases Fund},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Philanthropy},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Catholic Charities}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"Catholic Charities <LOCATION>Brooklyn Queens</LOCATION>, one of the seven agencies supported by <ORGANIZATION>The New York Times Neediest</ORGANIZATION> Cases Fund, gives <PERSON>Beata Bien</PERSON> <MONEY>$400</MONEY> to catch up on her rent.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-23T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/23/nyregion/NEEDIEST/NEEDIEST-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/23/nyregion/NEEDIEST/NEEDIEST-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/23/nyregion/NEEDIEST/NEEDIEST-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:390},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/23/nyregion/NEEDIEST/NEEDIEST-articleLarge.jpg,height:390},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/23/nyregion/NEEDIEST/NEEDIEST-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/23/nyregion/NEEDIEST/NEEDIEST-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",853,"<PERSON>Beata Bien</PERSON>, emigrated <LOCATION>Poland</LOCATION> <DATE>1993</DATE>, abandoned boyfriend learned pregnant. Then learned cancer people.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/23/nyregion/facing-cancer-and-financial-burdens-an-immigrant-finds-aid.html,5498c3f2798810035238e6db,null,"{content_kicker:The Neediest Cases,main:Facing Cancer Financial Burdens, Immigrant Finds Aid,print_headline:Help Immigrant With Cancer Bills,kicker:The Neediest Cases}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>E. C. GOGOLAK<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:E.,role:reported,organization:,middlename:C.,rank:1,lastname:GOGOLAK}]}",article
"Authorities German state <LOCATION>North Rhine-Westphalia</LOCATION> bought CD data thousand German clients Swiss bank, German newspaper Bild Sonntag <DATE>Sunday</DATE> citing sources.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-21T08:51:59Z,[],274,"Authorities German state <LOCATION>North Rhine-Westphalia</LOCATION> bought CD data thousand German clients Swiss bank, German newspaper Bild Sonntag <DATE>Sunday</DATE> citing sources.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/21/business/21reuters-germany-tax.html,5496d0ae79881029b367df1a,null,"{main:German State Buys Tax CD Containing Swiss Bank Client Data-Paper,print_headline:German State Buys Tax CD Containing Swiss Bank Client Data-Paper}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
A cab ride would-be Palestinian state's capital city reveals depressed resentful people.,,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Palestinians},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:2,value:Palestinian Authority},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:3,value:Ramallah West Bank},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Politics Government},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:5,value:<LOCATION>Israel<\/LOCATION>}]",Opinion,null,The New York Times,[],OpEd,2014-12-19T11:30:00Z,[],849,A cab ride would-be Palestinian state's capital city reveals depressed resentful people.,Op-Ed,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/19/opinion/ramallahs-mean-streets.html,5492b6e679881005eed9d4b8,null,"{content_kicker:Op-Ed Contributor,main:<LOCATION>Ramallah<\/LOCATION>’s Mean Streets,print_headline:<LOCATION>Ramallah<\/LOCATION>'s Mean Streets,kicker:Op-Ed Contributor}","{contributor:,original:By MARIAM BARGHOUTI,person:[{firstname:Mariam,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BARGHOUTI}]}",article
Property developers <LOCATION>China</LOCATION> struggling unload unsold units potential buyers decide prices continue fall.,1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Real Estate Housing Residential},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Real Estate Commercial},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Interest Rates},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Economic Conditions Trends},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:5,value:China}]",Business Day,"<LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s property market intense pressure, prices housing falling <PERCENT>1 percent 9 percent</PERCENT> months 70 mainland cities; buyers mulling prices continue drop; weak real estate prices big challenge government attempts manage economic weakness.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-19T00:00:00Z,[],1320,Property developers <LOCATION>China</LOCATION> struggling unload unsold units potential buyers decide prices continue fall.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/19/business/international/in-china-housing-market-pressure-to-sell-hesitation-to-buy.html,5492923779881005eed9d44c,International Business,"{main:<LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION>’s Housing Resists Efforts to Spur Market,print_headline:<LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION>’s Housing Resists Efforts to Spur Market}","{contributor:<PERSON>Hilda Wang<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Jonah Kessel Neil Gough<\/PERSON> contributed reporting.,original:By <PERSON>KEITH BRADSHER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Keith,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BRADSHER}]}",article
"Dutch sportscar maker <ORGANIZATION>Spyker</ORGANIZATION>, one-time owner <LOCATION>Sweden</LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>Saab</ORGANIZATION>, declared bankruptcy <DATE>Thursday</DATE>, failing secure critical bridging loan hoped refinance restructure.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-18T09:54:26Z,[],272,"Dutch sportscar maker <ORGANIZATION>Spyker</ORGANIZATION>, one-time owner <LOCATION>Sweden</LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>Saab</ORGANIZATION>, declared bankruptcy <DATE>Thursday</DATE>, failing secure critical bridging loan hoped refinance restructure.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/18/business/18reuters-spyker-bankruptcy.html,5492eb3f79881005eed9d567,null,"{main:Dutch Sportscar Maker Spyker Declared Bankrupt,print_headline:Dutch Sportscar Maker Spyker Declared Bankrupt}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
A divorce left <PERSON>Michael Stratton</PERSON> owing thousands dollars back child support payments. He working job information technology.,26,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:New York Times Neediest Cases Fund},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Philanthropy},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Community Service Society <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION>}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"Community Service Society, agencies supported The New York Times Neediest Cases Fund, buys one-month MetroCard allowing <PERSON>Michael Stratton</PERSON> commute <ORGANIZATION>Valley Stream</ORGANIZATION>, LI, IT training sessions Bronx.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-16T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/16/nyregion/16neediest/16neediest-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/16/nyregion/16neediest/16neediest-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/16/nyregion/16neediest/16neediest-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/16/nyregion/16neediest/16neediest-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/16/nyregion/16neediest/16neediest-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/16/nyregion/16neediest/16neediest-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",776,A divorce left <PERSON>Michael Stratton</PERSON> owing thousands dollars back child support payments. He working job information technology.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/16/nyregion/after-working-in-film-a-queens-man-hopes-for-a-life-in-technology.html,548fa172798810619765e98f,null,"{content_kicker:The Neediest Cases,main:After Working Film, <LOCATION>Queens<\/LOCATION> Man Hopes Life Technology,print_headline:After Time Film, <LOCATION>Queens<\/LOCATION> Man Looks Steady His Finances,kicker:The Neediest Cases}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ELEANOR STANFORD<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Eleanor,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:STANFORD}]}",article
"At 14, diagnosis lupus led <PERSON>Emie Payen</PERSON> conclude 20 years live. Despite rash health problems, coping 41 years.",28,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Philanthropy},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:2,value:New York Times Neediest Cases Fund},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Catholic Charities <LOCATION>Brooklyn<\/LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Queens<\/LOCATION>}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"Catholic Charities <LOCATION>Brooklyn</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Queens</LOCATION>, one of seven agencies supported by the <ORGANIZATION>New York Times Neediest</ORGANIZATION> Cases Fund, provides <PERSON>Emie Payen</PERSON> with <MONEY>$600</MONEY> to pay down rent arrears; <PERSON>Payen</PERSON> has struggled as a single mother with lupus and other health problems.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-11T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/11/nyregion/NEEDIEST/NEEDIEST-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/11/nyregion/NEEDIEST/NEEDIEST-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/11/nyregion/NEEDIEST/NEEDIEST-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/11/nyregion/NEEDIEST/NEEDIEST-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/<ORGANIZATION>11/nyregion/NEEDIEST/NEEDIEST-thumbStandard<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/<ORGANIZATION>11/nyregion/NEEDIEST/NEEDIEST-thumbStandard<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg,height:75}]",725,"At 14, diagnosis lupus led <PERSON>Emie Payen</PERSON> conclude 20 years live. Despite rash health problems, coping 41 years.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/11/nyregion/defying-a-short-life-expectancy.html,5488ef097988104c17459fce,null,"{content_kicker:The Neediest Cases,main:Defying Short Life Expectancy, Decades,print_headline:Defying Short Life Expectancy, Decades,kicker:The Neediest Cases}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>JOHN OTIS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:John,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:OTIS}]}",article
"British oil major <ORGANIZATION>BP</ORGANIZATION> plans to invest more than <MONEY>$12 billion 7.6 billion pounds</MONEY> in <LOCATION>Egypt</LOCATION> over the next five years, and to double its gas supplies to the local market in the next decade, the country manager of <ORGANIZATION>BP Egypt</ORGANIZATION> said on <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-09T11:24:48Z,[],280,"British oil major <ORGANIZATION>BP</ORGANIZATION> plans to invest more than <MONEY>$12 billion 7.6 billion pounds</MONEY> in <LOCATION>Egypt</LOCATION> over the next five years, and to double its gas supplies to the local market in the next decade, the country manager of <ORGANIZATION>BP Egypt</ORGANIZATION> said on <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/09/business/09reuters-egypt-bp-investment.html,548723067988101981fa0293,null,"{main:BP to Invest <MONEY>$12 Billion<\/MONEY> in <LOCATION>Egypt<\/LOCATION> Over Five Years, Boost Gas Supplies,print_headline:BP to Invest <MONEY>$12 Billion<\/MONEY> in <LOCATION>Egypt<\/LOCATION> Over Five Years, Boost Gas Supplies}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"When local officials warned striking shoe factory workers <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s <LOCATION>Pearl River Delta</LOCATION> <DATE>summer</DATE> breaking law, slight, bespectacled figure barely 5 feet 5 inches 1.65 meters tall faced.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-06T21:49:06Z,[],783,"When local officials warned striking shoe factory workers <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s <LOCATION>Pearl River Delta</LOCATION> <DATE>summer</DATE> breaking law, slight, bespectacled figure barely 5 feet 5 inches 1.65 meters tall faced.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/06/world/europe/06reuters-china-labour-lawyer-insight.html,5483c0c97988106fd483ce83,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:Labor Movement 'Concertmaster' Tests <LOCATION>Beijing<\/LOCATION>'s Boundaries,print_headline:Labor Movement 'Concertmaster' Tests <LOCATION>Beijing<\/LOCATION>'s Boundaries}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
