snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Deals worth nearly <MONEY>$3.5 trillion</MONEY> were announced, a performance favored by low interest rates and high stock prices.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Mergers, Acquisitions Divestitures}]",Business Day,"Deals worth nearly <MONEY>$3.5 trillion</MONEY> were announced, a performance favored by low interest rates and high stock prices.",The New York Times,[],Business,2015-01-01T19:32:44Z,[],525,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/deal-makers-notched-nearly-3-5-trillion-worth-in-14-best-in-7-years/,54a5e7cc7988102023c94f8e,Dealbook,"{main:Deal Makers Notched Nearly <MONEY>$3.5<\/MONEY> <ORGANIZATION>Trillion Worth<\/ORGANIZATION> in &rsquo;14, Best in 7 Years,print_headline:Deal Makers Notched Nearly <MONEY>$3.5 Trillion<\/MONEY> Worth in ’14, Best in 7 Years,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>MICHAEL J. DE<\/PERSON> LA MERCED,person:[{firstname:Michael,role:reported,organization:,middlename:J.,rank:1,lastname:DE LA MERCED}]}",blogpost
"<PERSON>William Lewis Rudolph</PERSON>, <PERSON>Krispy Kreme</PERSON> vice president helped build company, died.",null,[],Business Day,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T17:30:39Z,[],133,"<PERSON>William Lewis Rudolph</PERSON>, <PERSON>Krispy Kreme</PERSON> vice president helped build company, died.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/business/ap-us-obit-rudolph.html,54a5cb5e7988102023c94cf1,null,"{main:Former Krispy Kreme Vice President Dies 95,print_headline:Former Krispy Kreme Vice President Dies 95}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"The private equity giant, which took the British chain private in <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>’s largest buyout, will now hold <PERCENT>4.6 percent</PERCENT> of the combined <ORGANIZATION>Walgreens Boots Alliance</ORGANIZATION>.",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Pessina<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Stefano<\/PERSON>},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:Alliance Boots},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:<ORGANIZATION>Kohlberg Kravis Roberts & Co<\/ORGANIZATION>},{name:organizations,rank:3,value:Walgreen Company},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Mergers, Acquisitions Divestitures}]",Business Day,"The private equity giant, which took the British chain private in <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>’s largest buyout, will now hold <PERCENT>4.6 percent</PERCENT> of the combined <ORGANIZATION>Walgreens Boots Alliance</ORGANIZATION>.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-31T09:33:06Z,[],317,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/k-k-r-sells-last-of-alliance-boots-stake/,54a409b77988102761d6e05d,Dealbook,"{main:K.K.R. Sells Last Alliance Boots Stake,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By DEALBOOK,person:[{firstname:Dealbook,role:reported,organization:,rank:1}]}",blogpost
"Financial communications firms, accustomed advising mergers acquisitions, targets tread cautiously, <PERSON>Quentin Webb</PERSON> writes <ORGANIZATION>Reuters Breakingviews</ORGANIZATION>.",null,"[{name:organizations,rank:1,value:Publicis Groupe},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:WPP},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Mergers, Acquisitions Divestitures},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Public Relations Publicity}]",Business Day,"Financial communications firms, accustomed advising mergers acquisitions, targets tread cautiously, <PERSON>Quentin Webb</PERSON> writes <ORGANIZATION>Reuters Breakingviews</ORGANIZATION>.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-29T13:03:10Z,[],394,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/29/deal-talk-starts-to-become-part-of-the-boom/,54a197b67988104803cc8830,Dealbook,"{main:Deal Talk Starts Become Part Boom,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>QUENTIN WEBB<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Quentin,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:WEBB}]}",blogpost
"<LOCATION>Canada</LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>Ontario Teachers' Pension Plan</ORGANIZATION> said it had bought a <PERCENT>19.25 percent</PERCENT> stake in <LOCATION>Birmingham Airport</LOCATION> [BIRHLF.UL] from <LOCATION>Australia</LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>Victorian Funds Management Corporation</ORGANIZATION>, taking its investment in the British airport to <PERCENT>48.25 percent</PERCENT>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-29T03:31:21Z,[],333,"<LOCATION>Canada</LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>Ontario Teachers' Pension Plan</ORGANIZATION> said it had bought a <PERCENT>19.25 percent</PERCENT> stake in <LOCATION>Birmingham Airport</LOCATION> [BIRHLF.UL] from <LOCATION>Australia</LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>Victorian Funds Management Corporation</ORGANIZATION>, taking its investment in the British airport to <PERCENT>48.25 percent</PERCENT>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/29/business/29reuters-birmingham-airport-m-a-ontario-teachers.html,54a111bf7988101f98e3ef24,null,"{main:Ontario Teachers Raises Stake <LOCATION>Birmingham Airport<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:Ontario Teachers Raises Stake <LOCATION>Birmingham Airport<\/LOCATION>}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The board <ORGANIZATION>American Apparel Inc</ORGANIZATION> received letter British buyout firm <ORGANIZATION>Lion Capital</ORGANIZATION>, pushing explore strategic options include sale, source familiar situation <DATE>Sunday</DATE>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-28T20:24:52Z,[],263,"The board <ORGANIZATION>American Apparel Inc</ORGANIZATION> received letter British buyout firm <ORGANIZATION>Lion Capital</ORGANIZATION>, pushing explore strategic options include sale, source familiar situation <DATE>Sunday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/28/business/28reuters-american-apparel-lion-capital.html,54a0ade77988101f98e3ee6c,null,"{main:Lion Capital Sends Letter American Apparel Urging It Explore Options: Source,print_headline:Lion Capital Sends Letter American Apparel Urging It Explore Options: Source}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Unwanted calls, estate planning, career toilet parts replacement subjects tackled Shortcuts columns year.",5,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Telemarketing},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Wills Estates},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Careers Professions},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Bathrooms Toilets},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:5,value:<ORGANIZATION>NoMoRobo Telephone Science Corp<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:Federal Communications Commission},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:7,value:Federal Trade Commission}]",Your Money,"<PERSON>Alina Tugend</PERSON> Shortcuts column, reviewing columns <DATE>2014</DATE>, finds themes consumer concerns changing workplace environments dominant; offers followups columns automated telemarketing calls, estate planning, switching careers finding replacement bathroom parts.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-27T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27shortcuts-pic2/27shortcuts-pic2-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27shortcuts-pic2/27shortcuts-pic2-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27shortcuts-pic2/27shortcuts-pic2-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27shortcuts-pic2/27shortcuts-pic2-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27shortcuts-pic2/27shortcuts-pic2-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27shortcuts-pic2/27shortcuts-pic2-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1277,"Unwanted calls, estate planning, career toilet parts replacement subjects tackled Shortcuts columns year.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/27/your-money/a-year-of-shortcuts-the-fight-against-robocalls-gains-ground.html,549d9c677988105ced788592,null,"{content_kicker:Shortcuts,main:A Year Fighting Robocalls, Finding Right Parts,print_headline:A Year Fighting Robocalls, Finding Right Parts,kicker:Shortcuts}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ALINA TUGEND<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Alina,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:TUGEND}]}",article
"An agreement to sell <ORGANIZATION>Biomet</ORGANIZATION>, a medical device maker, to <ORGANIZATION>Zimmer Holdings</ORGANIZATION> for <MONEY>$13.35 billion</MONEY> may be complicated by reports that <ORGANIZATION>Biomet</ORGANIZATION> helped bribe officials in <LOCATION>Mexico</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:Justice Department},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:2,value:Securities Exchange Commission},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Bribery Kickbacks},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:4,value:<ORGANIZATION>Zimmer Holdings Inc<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:5,value:<LOCATION>Mexico<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:6,value:Biomet Incorporated},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:7,value:<LOCATION>Brazil<\/LOCATION>}]",Business Day,"An agreement to sell <ORGANIZATION>Biomet</ORGANIZATION>, a medical device maker, to <ORGANIZATION>Zimmer Holdings</ORGANIZATION> for <MONEY>$13.35 billion</MONEY> may be complicated by reports that <ORGANIZATION>Biomet</ORGANIZATION> helped bribe officials in <LOCATION>Mexico</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-23T11:09:44Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/23/business/23db-deal-pic1/23db-deal-pic1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/23/business/23db-deal-pic1/23db-deal-pic1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/23/business/23db-deal-pic1/23db-deal-pic1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/23/business/23db-deal-pic1/23db-deal-pic1-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/23/business/23db-deal-pic1/23db-deal-pic1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/23/business/23db-deal-pic1/23db-deal-pic1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1504,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/23/inquiry-into-foreign-bribes-at-biomet-hangs-over-13-billion-merger/,54999533798810035238e886,Dealbook,"{main:Inquiry Into Foreign Bribes at <ORGANIZATION>Biomet<\/ORGANIZATION> Hangs Over <MONEY>$13 Billion<\/MONEY> Merger,print_headline:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> May Blunt 2 Bribery Cases Aid Merger,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>BEN PROTESS MICHAEL J. DE<\/PERSON> LA MERCED,person:[{firstname:Ben,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:PROTESS},{firstname:Michael,role:reported,organization:,middlename:J.,rank:2,lastname:DE LA MERCED}]}",blogpost
Family Dollar delayed shareholder vote proposed acquisition Dollar Tree <DATE>Jan. 22</DATE>.,null,[],Business Day,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-23T10:59:54Z,[],227,Family Dollar delayed shareholder vote proposed acquisition Dollar Tree <DATE>Jan. 22</DATE>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/23/business/ap-us-family-dollar-dollar-tree.html,549991f6798810035238e87a,null,"{main:Family Dollar Delays Vote Dollar Tree Deal,print_headline:Family Dollar Delays Vote Dollar Tree Deal}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"TGI Fridays, casual dining restaurant chain retro American-themed setting, sold UK franchise business <ORGANIZATION>Electra Partners</ORGANIZATION> latest private equity buyout <LOCATION>Britain</LOCATION>'s eating-out market.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-23T09:45:49Z,[],374,"TGI Fridays, casual dining restaurant chain retro American-themed setting, sold UK franchise business <ORGANIZATION>Electra Partners</ORGANIZATION> latest private equity buyout <LOCATION>Britain</LOCATION>'s eating-out market.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/23/business/23reuters-tgifridays-restructuring-electra.html,54998058798810035238e841,null,"{main:TGI Fridays Sells UK Franchise Electra Private Equity Dines Out,print_headline:TGI Fridays Sells UK Franchise Electra Private Equity Dines Out}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
