snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Newly added cast &#8220;The Good Wife,&#8221; <PERSON>Matthew Goode</PERSON> building profile British actor watch.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Television},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Goode<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Matthew<\/PERSON>},{is_major:N,name:creative_works,rank:3,value:The Good Wife TV Program},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Actors Actresses}]",Arts,"Actor <PERSON>Matthew Goode</PERSON> gained fans portrayal character <PERSON>Finn Polmar</PERSON> television series The Good Wife, bringing talented British actor squarely public eye.",The New York Times,[],Culture,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/arts/JPGOODE/JPGOODE-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/arts/JPGOODE/JPGOODE-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/arts/JPGOODE/JPGOODE-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:394},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/arts/JPGOODE/JPGOODE-articleLarge.jpg,height:394},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/arts/JPGOODE/JPGOODE-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/arts/JPGOODE/JPGOODE-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1155,"Newly added cast &#8220;The Good Wife,&#8221; <PERSON>Matthew Goode</PERSON> building profile British actor watch.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/arts/television/matthew-goode-makes-mark-in-the-good-wife.html,54a47c5979881011bed29638,Television,"{main:An Actor Dashing Across <LOCATION>Atlantic<\/LOCATION>,seo:<PERSON>Matthew Goode<\/PERSON> Makes Mark In ‘The Good Wife’,print_headline:An Actor Dashing Across <LOCATION>Atlantic<\/LOCATION>}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>SARAH LYALL<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Sarah,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:LYALL}]}",article
<PERSON>Nico Muhly</PERSON> cuts striking figure travels globe.,5,"[{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:1,value:Muhly, Nico},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Music},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Fashion Apparel},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Shoes Boots},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Classical Music}]",Fashion & Style,"Encounters column; acclaimed contemporary classical music composer <PERSON>Nico Muhly</PERSON> describes penchant wearing long, dark elegant fashions performances works.",The New York Times,[],Styles,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01SUBENCOUNTERS/01SUBENCOUNTERS-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01SUBENCOUNTERS/01SUBENCOUNTERS-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01SUBENCOUNTERS/01SUBENCOUNTERS-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:401},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01SUBENCOUNTERS/01SUBENCOUNTERS-articleLarge.jpg,height:401},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01SUBENCOUNTERS/01SUBENCOUNTERS-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01SUBENCOUNTERS/01SUBENCOUNTERS-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",978,<PERSON>Nico Muhly</PERSON> cuts striking figure travels globe.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/fashion/for-a-composers-style-statement-pieces-to-play-and-wear.html,54a4751879881011bed29489,null,"{content_kicker:Encounters,main:For a Composer’s Style, Statement Pieces Play Wear,print_headline:Statement Pieces to Play and Wear,kicker:Encounters}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>CHRISTOPHER BARNARD<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Christopher,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BARNARD}]}",article
<PERSON>Jill Denny Jeff Chen</PERSON> average.,null,"[{name:subject,rank:1,value:Crossword Puzzles},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Golf}]",Crosswords/Games,<PERSON>Jill Denny Jeff Chen</PERSON> average.,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-31T22:00:19Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/crosswords/1231pitjpg/1231pitjpg-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/crosswords/1231pitjpg/1231pitjpg-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/crosswords/1231pitjpg/1231pitjpg-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:399},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/crosswords/1231pitjpg/1231pitjpg-articleLarge.jpg,height:399},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/crosswords/1231pitjpg/1231pitjpg-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/crosswords/1231pitjpg/1231pitjpg-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",951,null,Blog,http://wordplay.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/average/,54a4b92779881011bed2a423,null,"{main:Average,kicker:Wordplay}","{original:By <PERSON>DEB AMLEN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Deb,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:AMLEN}]}",blogpost
"A Winter Classic with sunglasses? With a halftime in the first period? Or delayed for a couple of hours on account of, well, gorgeous weather?",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T12:12:36Z,[],555,"A Winter Classic with sunglasses? With a halftime in the first period? Or delayed for a couple of hours on account of, well, gorgeous weather?",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/sports/hockey/ap-hkn-winter-classic-weather.html,54a42f6679881011bed28319,Hockey,"{main:Too Much Sun Could Delay Start Winter Classic,print_headline:Too Much Sun Could Delay Start Winter Classic}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"A <LOCATION>Chicago</LOCATION> driver accused sexually assaulting Uber passenger authorized drive ride-sharing company account created wife's name pick customers, company <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T12:08:10Z,[],478,"A <LOCATION>Chicago</LOCATION> driver accused sexually assaulting Uber passenger authorized drive ride-sharing company account created wife's name pick customers, company <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/ap-us-uber-driver-sexual-assault.html,54a42e0479881011bed282a7,null,"{main:Uber Didn't OK <LOCATION>Chicago<\/LOCATION> Driver Charged With Assault,print_headline:Uber Didn't OK <LOCATION>Chicago<\/LOCATION> Driver Charged With Assault}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Times critics share what they’ve been listening to lately.,null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Barenboim<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Daniel<\/PERSON>},{name:persons,rank:2,value:Cleobury, <PERSON>Stephen<\/PERSON>},{name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Gergiev<\/PERSON>, Valery},{name:persons,rank:4,value:Pahud, Emmanuel},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:Choir King's College},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:Kirov Orchestra},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Classical Music}]",Arts,Times critics share what they’ve been listening to lately.,The New York Times,[],Culture,2014-12-31T11:33:51Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/arts/artsbeat-classical/artsbeat-classical-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/arts/artsbeat-classical/artsbeat-classical-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/arts/artsbeat-classical/artsbeat-classical-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:404},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/arts/artsbeat-classical/artsbeat-classical-articleLarge.jpg,height:404},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/arts/artsbeat-classical/artsbeat-classical-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/arts/artsbeat-classical/artsbeat-classical-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",499,null,Blog,http://artsbeat.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/classical-playlist-tchaikovsky-faur-bach-and-more/,54a425d57988102761d6e6ad,null,"{main:Classical Playlist: Tchaikovsky, Faur&eacute;, <PERSON>Bach<\/PERSON> More,kicker:ArtsBeat}","{original:By THE <LOCATION>NEW YORK<\/LOCATION> TIMES,person:[],organization:The New York Times}",blogpost
<PERSON>Jim Harbaugh</PERSON> solved significant problems <LOCATION>Michigan</LOCATION>.,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T09:53:23Z,[],998,<PERSON>Jim Harbaugh</PERSON> solved significant problems <LOCATION>Michigan</LOCATION>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/sports/ncaafootball/ap-fbc-michigan-harbaugh-arrives.html,54a40e487988102761d6e0e5,College Football,"{main:<PERSON>Harbaugh<\/PERSON>'s Hit, Now Work Begins,print_headline:<PERSON>Harbaugh<\/PERSON>'s Hit, Now Work Begins}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Since returning childhood home month vacation, President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON> spent good part days cloistered people company puts ease. They're wife daughters,, trio...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T01:48:17Z,[],805,"Since returning childhood home month vacation, President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON> spent good part days cloistered people company puts ease. They're wife daughters,, trio pals friendship dates back <PERSON>Obama</PERSON>'s high school days <LOCATION>Hawaii</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/ap-us-obama-reunion.html,54a39d147988102761d6d3e5,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Hawaii<\/LOCATION> Vacation Reunites Obama Childhood Pals,print_headline:<LOCATION>Hawaii<\/LOCATION> Vacation Reunites Obama Childhood Pals}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
A reader describes special financial aid counseling children don&#8217;t live parents.,18,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Financial Aid Education},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Foster Care},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Children Childhood},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Colleges Universities}]",Opinion,null,The New York Times,[],Letters,2014-12-31T00:00:00Z,[],199,A reader describes special financial aid counseling children don&#8217;t live parents.,Letter,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/opinion/college-help-for-neediest.html,54a331837988102761d6cf3c,null,"{content_kicker:Letter,main:College Help Neediest,print_headline:College Help Neediest,kicker:Letter}",[],article
"Since returning childhood home month vacation, President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON> spent good part days cloistered people company puts ease. They're wife daughters,, trio...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T16:15:50Z,[],804,"Since returning childhood home month vacation, President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON> spent good part days cloistered people company puts ease. They're wife daughters,, trio pals friendship dates back <PERSON>Obama</PERSON>'s high school days <LOCATION>Hawaii</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/us/ap-us-obama-reunion.html,54a316d47988102761d6cefa,null,"{main:For <PERSON>Obama<\/PERSON>, Reunion With Pals Link Simpler Times,print_headline:For <PERSON>Obama<\/PERSON>, Reunion With Pals Link Simpler Times}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
