snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"A consortium led by Spanish-builder <PERSON>Sacyr</PERSON> said on <DATE>Thursday</DATE> it has won a <MONEY>$233 million 149.57 million pounds</MONEY> settlement in a dispute over cost overruns in an expansion of the <LOCATION>Panama Canal</LOCATION>, half what the group had been seeking in the lawsuit.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T15:39:04Z,[],189,"A consortium led by Spanish-builder <PERSON>Sacyr</PERSON> said on <DATE>Thursday</DATE> it has won a <MONEY>$233 million 149.57 million pounds</MONEY> settlement in a dispute over cost overruns in an expansion of the <LOCATION>Panama Canal</LOCATION>, half what the group had been seeking in the lawsuit. ",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-sacyr-panama.html,54a5b0a37988102023c94a49,null,"{main:Sacyr-Led Group Wins <MONEY>$233 Million<\/MONEY> Claim in <LOCATION>Panama<\/LOCATION> Canal Dispute,print_headline:Sacyr-Led Group Wins <MONEY>$233 Million<\/MONEY> Claim in <LOCATION>Panama<\/LOCATION> Canal Dispute}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"British retailers optimistic prospects <DATE>2015</DATE>, large majority expecting increased sales higher levels employment investment, industry survey showed <DATE>Thursday</DATE>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T19:09:02Z,[],208,"British retailers optimistic prospects <DATE>2015</DATE>, large majority expecting increased sales higher levels employment investment, industry survey showed <DATE>Thursday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-britain-retail-brc.html,54a4906079881011bed29acc,null,"{main:UK Retailers Upbeat About Prospects 2015-Industry Survey,print_headline:UK Retailers Upbeat About Prospects 2015-Industry Survey}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
A search engine called Qwant tap growing anger <ORGANIZATION>Europe Google</ORGANIZATION> holds control people surf Web.,null,"[{name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>France<\/LOCATION>},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:Qwant SAS},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Computers Internet},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Search Engines}]",Technology,A search engine called Qwant tap growing anger <ORGANIZATION>Europe Google</ORGANIZATION> holds control people surf Web.,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-31T16:34:01Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/technology/31bits-qwant/31bits-qwant-thumbWide.png},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/technology/31bits-qwant/31bits-qwant-thumbWide.png,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/technology/31bits-qwant/31bits-qwant-articleLarge.png,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:293},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/technology/31bits-qwant/31bits-qwant-articleLarge.png,height:293},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/technology/31bits-qwant/31bits-qwant-thumbStandard.png,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/technology/31bits-qwant/31bits-qwant-thumbStandard.png,height:75}]",779,null,Blog,http://bits.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/qwant-wants-to-be-alternative-to-google/,54a46be679881011bed29270,null,"{main:Qwant Wants Be Alternative Google,print_headline:,kicker:Bits}","{original:By MARK SCOTT,person:[{firstname:Mark,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SCOTT}]}",blogpost
"Administrators City Link, collapsed British parcel delivery firm, 2,300 people losing jobs bid buy business fell.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T12:40:59Z,[],124,"Administrators City Link, collapsed British parcel delivery firm, 2,300 people losing jobs bid buy business fell.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/world/europe/ap-eu-britain-city-link.html,54a435c079881011bed28539,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:UK's City Link Delivery Firm Lays Off More Than 2,300,print_headline:UK's City Link Delivery Firm Lays Off More Than 2,300}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
The German insurance giant faces responsibility lead reinsurer <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia Malaysia Airlines</ORGANIZATION>.,5,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:Allianz SE},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Aviation Accidents, Safety Disasters},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:4,value:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:5,value:<LOCATION>Malaysia<\/LOCATION> Airlines},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:<LOCATION>Malaysia<\/LOCATION> Airlines Flight 17},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:<ORGANIZATION>Malaysia Airlines<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight 370},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:8,value:Insurance}]",Business Day,"<ORGANIZATION>Allianz</ORGANIZATION> confirms main reinsurer <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION>, means company responsible part estimated hundreds <MONEY>millions dollars</MONEY> payouts major passenger jet disasters <DATE>2014</DATE>.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-30T00:00:00Z,[],926,The German insurance giant faces responsibility lead reinsurer <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia Malaysia Airlines</ORGANIZATION>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/business/international/allianz-is-to-share-in-payouts-over-3-malaysia-linked-air-disasters.html,54a1aea87988104803cc885d,International Business,"{main:Allianz Is Share Payouts Over 3 Malaysia-Linked Air Disasters,print_headline:Allianz Liable Part Air Disaster Payouts}","{contributor:<PERSON>Neil Gough<\/PERSON> contributed reporting <LOCATION>Hong Kong<\/LOCATION> <PERSON>Nicola Clark Paris<\/PERSON>.,original:By <PERSON>DAVID JOLLY<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:David,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:JOLLY}]}",article
"A script &#8220;The Wedding Ringer&#8221; moved <LOCATION>New Jersey</LOCATION> warehouse 18,000 boxes Miramax paperwork journey production.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Movies},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:Packer, Will <DATE>1974<\/DATE>-},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:Fields, Adam},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Miramax Films},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:5,value:Sony Pictures Entertainment},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:6,value:<PERSON>Hart<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Kevin<\/PERSON>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:7,value:Gad, <PERSON>Josh<\/PERSON>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:8,value:<PERSON>Garelick<\/PERSON>, Jeremy <DATE>1975<\/DATE>-},{is_major:N,name:creative_works,rank:9,value:The Wedding Ringer Movie}]",Movies,"Producers Will Packer Adam Fields describe rescued film The Wedding Ringer, Miramax production company collapsed <DATE>2009</DATE>; script film, released <DATE>January 2015</DATE> division <ORGANIZATION>Sony Pictures Entertainment</ORGANIZATION>, buried <LOCATION>New Jersey</LOCATION> warehouse 18,000 boxes Miramax paperwork.",The New York Times,[],Arts&Leisure,2014-12-28T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/28/arts/28RINGER1/28RINGER1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/arts/28RINGER1/28RINGER1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/28/arts/28RINGER1/28RINGER1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/arts/28RINGER1/28RINGER1-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/28/arts/28RINGER1/28RINGER1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/arts/28RINGER1/28RINGER1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1139,"A script &#8220;The Wedding Ringer&#8221; moved <LOCATION>New Jersey</LOCATION> warehouse 18,000 boxes Miramax paperwork journey production.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/movies/sonys-the-wedding-ringer-with-kevin-hart-has-a-tortuous-path.html,549b372e7988100306690ef7,null,"{main:Life Near Death Miramax Script,seo:<ORGANIZATION>Sony<\/ORGANIZATION>’s ‘The Wedding Ringer,’ With <PERSON>Kevin Hart<\/PERSON>, Has a Tortuous Path,print_headline:Life Near Death Miramax Script,kicker:Film}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>MICHAEL CIEPLY<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Michael,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:CIEPLY}]}",article
The F.T.C. outsourced job industry. The victim: Your privacy.,17,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Data-Mining Database Marketing},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:2,value:Federal Trade Commission},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Consumer Protection},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Privacy},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:5,value:Computers Internet},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:World Wide Web Consortium}]",Opinion,Op-Ed article telecommunications executive <ORGANIZATION>Fred B Campbell Jr</ORGANIZATION> warns rules developed industry group define <ORGANIZATION>Federal Trade Commission</ORGANIZATION>'s proposed 'Do Not Track' plan effectively free companies honoring Internet privacy requests citizens; loophole Internet giants continue collecting data web browsing habits users; accuses <ORGANIZATION>Federal Trade Commission</ORGANIZATION> abandoning responsibility consumers allowing companies make decisions left government.,The New York Times,[],OpEd,2014-12-27T00:00:00Z,[],834,The F.T.C. outsourced job industry. The victim: Your privacy.,Op-Ed,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/27/opinion/the-slow-death-of-do-not-track.html,549dfd7a7988105ced788650,null,"{content_kicker:Op-Ed Contributor,main:The Slow Death &#8216;Do Not Track&#8217;,print_headline:The Slow Death of ‘Do Not Track’,kicker:Op-Ed Contributor}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>FRED B. CAMPBELL<\/PERSON> Jr,person:[{firstname:Fred,role:reported,organization:,rank:1}]}",article
"Officials expressed concerns <ORGANIZATION>Noble Energy</ORGANIZATION>, Houston-based company, partners monopoly sector.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Israel<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Natural Gas},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Noble Energy Inc},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Delek Drilling LP},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:5,value:Avner Oil Exploration LP},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:6,value:Antitrust Laws Competition Issues},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:Oil Petroleum Gasoline},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:8,value:Tshuva, Isaac},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:9,value:<ORGANIZATION>Delek Group Ltd<\/ORGANIZATION>}]",Business Day,"<LOCATION>Israel</LOCATION>'s fledgling natural gas industry rattled antitrust officials threaten breakup American-Israeli group's hold country's gas resources; argue <ORGANIZATION>Noble Energy</ORGANIZATION>, Houston-based oil company, partners <ORGANIZATION>Delek Drilling Avner Oil Exploration</ORGANIZATION>, monopoly sector; fear group overcharge nation reliant gas.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-24T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/24/business/Israelgasjp/Israelgasjp-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/24/business/Israelgasjp/Israelgasjp-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/24/business/Israelgasjp/Israelgasjp-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/24/business/Israelgasjp/Israelgasjp-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/24/business/Israelgasjp/Israelgasjp-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/24/business/Israelgasjp/Israelgasjp-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",846,"Officials expressed concerns <ORGANIZATION>Noble Energy</ORGANIZATION>, Houston-based company, partners monopoly sector.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/24/business/international/in-israel-antitrust-regulator-reviews-natural-gas-development.html,549989a4798810035238e85f,International Business,"{main:In <LOCATION>Israel<\/LOCATION>, Antitrust Regulator Reviews Natural Gas Development,print_headline:Gas Industry Competition Scrutinized <LOCATION>Israel<\/LOCATION>}","{contributor:Isabel Kershner contributed reporting Jerusalem.,original:By <PERSON>STANLEY REED<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Stanley,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:REED}]}",article
"A group led by <ORGANIZATION>Apple</ORGANIZATION> and <ORGANIZATION>Microsoft</ORGANIZATION> has sold about 4,000 technology patents to patent management company <ORGANIZATION>RPX Corp.</ORGANIZATION> for <MONEY>$900 million</MONEY>.",null,[],Business Day,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-23T17:00:36Z,[],131,"A group led by <ORGANIZATION>Apple</ORGANIZATION> and <ORGANIZATION>Microsoft</ORGANIZATION> has sold about 4,000 technology patents to patent management company <ORGANIZATION>RPX Corp.</ORGANIZATION> for <MONEY>$900 million</MONEY>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/23/business/ap-us-patent-sale.html,5499e6727988102d96d54fcb,null,"{main:Group Led by <ORGANIZATION>Apple<\/ORGANIZATION> and <ORGANIZATION>Microsoft<\/ORGANIZATION> Sells Patents for <MONEY>$900M<\/MONEY>,print_headline:Group Led by <ORGANIZATION>Apple<\/ORGANIZATION> and <ORGANIZATION>Microsoft<\/ORGANIZATION> Sells Patents for <MONEY>$900M<\/MONEY>}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Patent risk management company <ORGANIZATION>RPX Corp</ORGANIZATION> said on <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> it would buy patents owned by <ORGANIZATION>Apple Inc</ORGANIZATION> and other firms for <MONEY>$900 million</MONEY>, helping to further scale back lawsuits over smartphone technology.",null,[],Technology,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-23T13:33:37Z,[],378,"Patent risk management company <ORGANIZATION>RPX Corp</ORGANIZATION> said on <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> it would buy patents owned by <ORGANIZATION>Apple Inc</ORGANIZATION> and other firms for <MONEY>$900 million</MONEY>, helping to further scale back lawsuits over smartphone technology.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/23/technology/23reuters-rpx-rockstar-ip.html,5499b5b97988102d96d54f48,null,"{main:RPX Buys Apple-Backed Rockstar Patents for <MONEY>$900 Million<\/MONEY>,print_headline:RPX Buys Apple-Backed Rockstar Patents for <MONEY>$900 Million<\/MONEY>}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
