snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
Small business owners <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION> 2015.,null,[],Business Day,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T13:04:30Z,[],737,Small business owners <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION> 2015.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/business/ap-us-smallbiz-small-talk.html,54a43b5479881011bed28711,null,"{main:New Year May Bring More Small Business Help From <LOCATION>Washington<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:New Year May Bring More Small Business Help From <LOCATION>Washington<\/LOCATION>}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Do international human rights treaties work protect vulnerable populations, abandoned favor measures??",null,"[{name:type_of_material,rank:1,value:News}]",Opinion,"Do international human rights treaties work protect vulnerable populations, abandoned favor measures??",The New York Times,[],null,2014-12-28T19:36:28Z,[],2903,,Blog,http://www.nytimes.com/roomfordebate/2014/12/28/have-human-rights-treaties-failed,54a0b2a27988101f98e3ee74,Room For Debate,"{main:Have Human Rights Treaties Failed??,kicker:Room For Debate}",null,blogpost
"We, Buddhists Stoics instruct, achieve distance world suffering. But it??",null,"[{name:subject,rank:1,value:Buddhism},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Pain},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Philosophy}]",Opinion,"We, Buddhists Stoics instruct, achieve distance world suffering. But it??",The New York Times,[],OpEd,2014-12-27T21:00:36Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/29/sunday-review/29STONE/29STONE-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/sunday-review/29STONE/29STONE-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/29/sunday-review/29STONE/29STONE-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:430},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/sunday-review/29STONE/29STONE-articleLarge.jpg,height:430},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/29/sunday-review/29STONE/29STONE-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/sunday-review/29STONE/29STONE-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1866,null,Blog,http://opinionator.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/27/against-invulnerability/,549f64a279881001534d1fd1,null,"{main:Against Invulnerability,kicker:The Stone}","{original:By <PERSON>TODD<\/PERSON> MAY,person:[{firstname:Todd,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:MAY}]}",blogpost
"One group potential candidates president shuffling <LOCATION>Iowa</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>New Hampshire</LOCATION> early campaign spots year. They'll hunkered statehouses <LOCATION>Midwest</LOCATION>, pushing bills...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-27T03:20:02Z,[],1051,"One group potential candidates president shuffling <LOCATION>Iowa</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>New Hampshire</LOCATION> early campaign spots year. They'll hunkered statehouses <LOCATION>Midwest</LOCATION>, pushing bills legislatures.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/27/us/ap-us-gop-2016-midwest-governors.html,549e6c997988105ced7886ce,null,"{main:Policies GOP Governors Could Find National Play,print_headline:Policies GOP Governors Could Find National Play}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"In grainy video, <PERSON>Zhang Xiuhong</PERSON> daughter ride bike country road school <DATE>spring</DATE> afternoon years ago.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-27T01:19:27Z,[],1145,"In grainy video, <PERSON>Zhang Xiuhong</PERSON> daughter ride bike country road school <DATE>spring</DATE> afternoon years ago.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/27/world/asia/ap-as-china-abducted-children.html,549e4fc77988105ced7886c6,Asia Pacific,"{main:Agonizing, Lonely Search Missing Kids <LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:Agonizing, Lonely Search Missing Kids <LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION>}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Amid churn change, champions reigned sports world, privileged tended reclaim privileges.",,"[{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Sochi Russia<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Olympic Games 2014},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:3,value:National Basketball Assn},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:World Cup 2014 Soccer},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Commonwealth Games},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:6,value:<PERSON>Woods<\/PERSON>, Tiger},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:7,value:Nadal, Rafael},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:8,value:<PERSON>Djokovic<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Novak<\/PERSON>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:9,value:<PERSON>Williams<\/PERSON>, Serena}]",Sports,null,The New York Times,[],Sports,2014-12-26T13:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/25/sports/international/26iht-sryereview26-sochi/26iht-sryereview26-sochi-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/sports/international/26iht-sryereview26-sochi/26iht-sryereview26-sochi-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/25/sports/international/26iht-sryereview26-sochi/26iht-sryereview26-sochi-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:375},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/sports/international/26iht-sryereview26-sochi/26iht-sryereview26-sochi-articleLarge.jpg,height:375},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/25/sports/international/26iht-sryereview26-sochi/26iht-sryereview26-sochi-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/sports/international/26iht-sryereview26-sochi/26iht-sryereview26-sochi-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1366,"Amid churn change, champions reigned sports world, privileged tended reclaim privileges.",Special Report,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/26/sports/international/top-stories-sports-2014.html,549c2f6b798810030669117b,International Sports,"{content_kicker:Special Report: Year Sports,main:<LOCATION>Russia<\/LOCATION> Wasn’t the Only Story in <DATE>2014<\/DATE>,print_headline:<LOCATION>Russia<\/LOCATION> Wasn't Only Story 2014}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>CHRISTOPHER CLAREY<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Christopher,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:CLAREY}]}",article
"One group potential candidates president shuffling <LOCATION>Iowa</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>New Hampshire</LOCATION> early campaign spots year. They'll hunkered statehouses <LOCATION>Midwest</LOCATION>, pushing bills...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-26T11:01:03Z,[],1051,"One group potential candidates president shuffling <LOCATION>Iowa</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>New Hampshire</LOCATION> early campaign spots year. They'll hunkered statehouses <LOCATION>Midwest</LOCATION>, pushing bills legislatures.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/26/us/ap-us-gop-2016-midwest-governors.html,549d86b27988103babf08bcc,null,"{main:Midwestern Governors Build Credentials 2016,print_headline:Midwestern Governors Build Credentials 2016}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Julio Jones needed offensive snaps dispel notion he'd decoy <LOCATION>Atlanta Falcons</LOCATION>, hampered injured hip effective.",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-22T04:31:54Z,[],695,"Julio Jones needed offensive snaps dispel notion he'd decoy <LOCATION>Atlanta Falcons</LOCATION>, hampered injured hip effective.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/22/sports/football/ap-fbn-falcons-saints-folo.html,5497e5ba7988104a1e0deeec,Pro Football,"{main:Jones' Return Helps Falcons Eliminate Saints, 30-14,print_headline:Jones' Return Helps Falcons Eliminate Saints, 30-14}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"In visit <LOCATION>Israel</LOCATION>, prospective Republican presidential candidate <PERSON>Ben Carson</PERSON> awe Jewish state, inspired ancient holy sites, impressed resilience people living perpetual conflict zone &#8212;...",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-20T03:02:11Z,[],708,"In visit <LOCATION>Israel</LOCATION>, prospective Republican presidential candidate <PERSON>Ben Carson</PERSON> awe Jewish state, inspired ancient holy sites, impressed resilience people living perpetual conflict zone &#8212; deeply disappointed President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/20/world/middleeast/ap-ml-gop-2016-carson-israel.html,54952d9c7988107c468006f7,Middle East,"{main:2016 Hopeful <PERSON>Ben Carson Pledges<\/PERSON> Support <LOCATION>Israel<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:2016 Hopeful <PERSON>Ben Carson Pledges<\/PERSON> Support <LOCATION>Israel<\/LOCATION>}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"The report’s relatively warm tone was welcomed by many — a far cry from <DATE>six years ago</DATE>, when fear, anger and mistrust greeted the announcement of the investigation of American nuns.",18,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Nuns},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:2,value:Roman Catholic Church},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:3,value:United States}]",<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,Investigation Vatican Catholic nuns began years earlier concludes positive report acknowledging accomplishments challenges women religious service.,The New York Times,[],National,2014-12-17T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/17/us/17NUNS-sub/17NUNS-sub-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/17/us/17NUNS-sub/17NUNS-sub-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/17/us/17NUNS-sub/17NUNS-sub-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:401},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/17/us/17NUNS-sub/17NUNS-sub-articleLarge.jpg,height:401},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/17/us/17NUNS-sub/17NUNS-sub-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/17/us/17NUNS-sub/17NUNS-sub-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1182,"The report’s relatively warm tone was welcomed by many — a far cry from <DATE>six years ago</DATE>, when fear, anger and mistrust greeted the announcement of the investigation of American nuns.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/17/us/vatican-report-us-nuns.html,54902ec3798810619765f689,null,"{main:Vatican Report Cites Achievements Challenges <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Nuns,print_headline:Vatican Report Cites Achievements Challenges <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Nuns}","{contributor:<PERSON>Elisabetta Povoledo<\/PERSON> contributed reporting Vatican City.,original:By <PERSON>LAURIE GOODSTEIN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Laurie,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:GOODSTEIN}]}",article
