snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
<PERSON>Troy Brouwer</PERSON> scored powerplay goal 13 seconds left regulation <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION> Capitals rang New Year thrilling 3-2 win <LOCATION>Chicago Blackhawks</LOCATION> outdoor Winter Classic <DATE>Thursday</DATE>.,null,[],Sports,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T17:10:51Z,[],424,<PERSON>Troy Brouwer</PERSON> scored powerplay goal 13 seconds left regulation <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION> Capitals rang New Year thrilling 3-2 win <LOCATION>Chicago Blackhawks</LOCATION> outdoor Winter Classic <DATE>Thursday</DATE>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/sports/hockey/01reuters-nhl-classic.html,54a5c6677988102023c94c40,Hockey,"{main:Capitals Ring New Year With Classic Win Over Blackhawks,print_headline:Capitals Ring New Year With Classic Win Over Blackhawks}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The lawyer jailed Al Jazeera journalist <PERSON>Peter Greste</PERSON> formally applied Egyptian government Australian's deportation, family <DATE>Friday</DATE>, <LOCATION>Egypt</LOCATION>'s highest court ordered retrial Greste colleagues.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T03:07:34Z,[],388,"The lawyer jailed Al Jazeera journalist <PERSON>Peter Greste</PERSON> formally applied Egyptian government Australian's deportation, family <DATE>Friday</DATE>, <LOCATION>Egypt</LOCATION>'s highest court ordered retrial Greste colleagues.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/world/middleeast/01reuters-egypt-jazeera.html,54a500db79881011bed2b46b,Middle East,"{main:Jailed Australian Journalist Seeks Presidential Deportation From <LOCATION>Egypt<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:Jailed Australian Journalist Seeks Presidential Deportation From <LOCATION>Egypt<\/LOCATION>}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
Brothers Australian Al-Jazeera English journalist held <LOCATION>Egypt</LOCATION> year <DATE>Friday</DATE> lawyers focusing deportation President <PERSON>Abdel-Fattah el-Sissi</PERSON>'s command option.,null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T01:04:21Z,[],526,Brothers Australian Al-Jazeera English journalist held <LOCATION>Egypt</LOCATION> year <DATE>Friday</DATE> lawyers focusing deportation President <PERSON>Abdel-Fattah el-Sissi</PERSON>'s command option.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/world/middleeast/ap-ml-egypt-al-jazeera.html,54a4e43679881011bed2adea,Middle East,"{main:Australian's Family Hope <LOCATION>Egypt<\/LOCATION> Will Deport Him,print_headline:Australian's Family Hope <LOCATION>Egypt<\/LOCATION> Will Deport Him}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
A law significant step forward animal welfare.,19,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Animal Abuse, Rights Welfare},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Factory Farming},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:3,value:<LOCATION>California<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Chickens},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Agriculture Farming},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Referendums},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:Pigs}]",Opinion,"Mark Bittman Op-Ed | <PERSON>Mark Bittmancolumn</PERSON> celebrates day <LOCATION>California</LOCATION>'s Prop 2, measure requires egg meat producers confine animals humane conditions; holds message Prop 2 factory farming industry consumers longer accept tortuous living conditions farm animals, expresses hope similar anti-confinement laws spread nation.",The New York Times,[],OpEd,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/11/01/opinion/bittman-circular/bittman-circular-thumbWide-v2.png},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/11/01/opinion/bittman-circular/bittman-circular-thumbWide-v2.png,height:126},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/11/01/opinion/bittman-circular/bittman-circular-thumbStandard-v2.png,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/11/01/opinion/bittman-circular/bittman-circular-thumbStandard-v2.png,height:75}]",837,A law significant step forward animal welfare.,Op-Ed,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/opinion/mark-bittman-hens-unbound.html,54a4a3f779881011bed29f40,null,"{content_kicker:Contributing Op-Ed Writer,main:Hens, Unbound,print_headline:Hens, Unbound,kicker:Op-Ed | Mark Bittman}","{contributor:,original:By MARK BITTMAN,person:[{firstname:Mark,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BITTMAN}]}",article
"Ovechkin’s goals are down, but Coach <PERSON>Barry Trotz</PERSON> says there are a hundred other ways he can help <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION>, which hosts <LOCATION>Chicago</LOCATION> on <DATE>Thursday</DATE> in the <DATE>2015</DATE> Winter Classic.",13,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Hockey, Ice},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:Ovechkin, <PERSON>Alex<\/PERSON>},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Trotz<\/PERSON>, Barry},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Washington Capitals},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:5,value:Chicago Blackhawks}]",Sports,<LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION> Capitals left wing <PERSON>Alex Ovechkin</PERSON> heads <DATE>2015</DATE> Winter classic game <ORGANIZATION>Chicago Blackhawks</ORGANIZATION> improved game coach <PERSON>Barry Trotz</PERSON>.,The New York Times,[],Sports,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/sports/capitals/capitals-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/sports/capitals/capitals-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/sports/capitals/capitals-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:392},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/sports/capitals/capitals-articleLarge.jpg,height:392},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/sports/capitals/capitals-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/sports/capitals/capitals-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",775,"Ovechkin’s goals are down, but Coach <PERSON>Barry Trotz</PERSON> says there are a hundred other ways he can help <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION>, which hosts <LOCATION>Chicago</LOCATION> on <DATE>Thursday</DATE> in the <DATE>2015</DATE> Winter Classic.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/sports/hockey/capitals-challenge-alex-ovechkin-to-play-a-more-complete-game.html,54a43f4e79881011bed28865,Hockey,"{main:Capitals Are Looking <PERSON>Alex Ovechkin<\/PERSON> Expand His Game,print_headline:Capitals Are Looking High-Scoring Ovechkin Expand His Game}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>PAT PICKENS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Pat,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:PICKENS}]}",article
"Manu Ginobili 26 points <LOCATION>San Antonio Spurs</LOCATION> avoided fourth overtime loss home <DATE>December</DATE>, escaping 95-93 victory <LOCATION>New Orleans</LOCATION> Pelicans <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T21:49:30Z,[],373,"Manu Ginobili 26 points <LOCATION>San Antonio Spurs</LOCATION> avoided fourth overtime loss home <DATE>December</DATE>, escaping 95-93 victory <LOCATION>New Orleans</LOCATION> Pelicans <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/sports/basketball/ap-bkn-pelicans-spurs.html,54a4b65a79881011bed2a380,Pro Basketball,"{main:Spurs Edge Pelicans 95-93 OT,print_headline:Spurs Edge Pelicans 95-93 OT}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"A <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> appeals court reinstated ban smoking state parks, dismissing challenge group smokers restriction enacted illegally.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T14:08:45Z,[],306,"A <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> appeals court reinstated ban smoking state parks, dismissing challenge group smokers restriction enacted illegally.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/us/31reuters-lawsuit-nysmoking.html,54a44a0d79881011bed28ab6,null,"{main:Ban Smoking <LOCATION>N.Y.<\/LOCATION> State Parks Reinstated,print_headline:Ban Smoking <LOCATION>N.Y.<\/LOCATION> State Parks Reinstated}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Accommodative monetary policy remain long global growth remains weak, <ORGANIZATION>IMF</ORGANIZATION> managing director <PERSON>Christine Lagarde</PERSON> newspaper article published <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T05:19:07Z,[],256,"Accommodative monetary policy remain long global growth remains weak, <ORGANIZATION>IMF</ORGANIZATION> managing director <PERSON>Christine Lagarde</PERSON> newspaper article published <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-imf-economy-lagarde.html,54a3ce4a7988102761d6d993,null,"{main:Anemic Growth Warrants Easy Monetary Policy: <ORGANIZATION>IMF<\/ORGANIZATION>'s Lagarde,print_headline:Anemic Growth Warrants Easy Monetary Policy: <ORGANIZATION>IMF<\/ORGANIZATION>'s Lagarde}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
<PERSON>David Perron</PERSON>'s shootout goal snapped <ORGANIZATION>Edmonton Oilers</ORGANIZATION>' nine-game losing streak 3-2 victory defending Stanley Cup champion <LOCATION>Los Angeles Kings</LOCATION> <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> night.,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T00:38:45Z,[],461,<PERSON>David Perron</PERSON>'s shootout goal snapped <ORGANIZATION>Edmonton Oilers</ORGANIZATION>' nine-game losing streak 3-2 victory defending Stanley Cup champion <LOCATION>Los Angeles Kings</LOCATION> <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> night.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/sports/hockey/ap-hkn-kings-oilers.html,54a38c397988102761d6d1f0,Hockey,"{main:<PERSON>Perron<\/PERSON>'s SO Goal Helps Oilers Snap 9-Game Skid,print_headline:<PERSON>Perron<\/PERSON>'s SO Goal Helps Oilers Snap 9-Game Skid}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<PERSON>Justin Anderson</PERSON> hit back-to-back 3-pointers fuel 12-3 run half, No. 3 <LOCATION>Virginia</LOCATION> pulled beat visiting <PERSON>Davidson</PERSON>, 83-72.",12,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Basketball College},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Davidson<\/PERSON> College},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Anderson<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Justin<\/PERSON>},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:4,value:University <LOCATION>Virginia<\/LOCATION>}]",Sports,"<LOCATION>Virginia</LOCATION> beats <PERSON>Davidson</PERSON>, 83-72; men's college basketball scores noted.",The New York Times,[],Sports,2014-12-31T00:00:00Z,[],185,"<PERSON>Justin Anderson</PERSON> hit back-to-back 3-pointers fuel 12-3 run half, No. 3 <LOCATION>Virginia</LOCATION> pulled beat visiting <PERSON>Davidson</PERSON>, 83-72.",Brief,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/sports/ncaabasketball/virginia-holds-off-pesky-davidson.html,54a3826b7988102761d6d0a7,College Basketball,"{main:<LOCATION>Virginia<\/LOCATION> Holds Off Pesky <PERSON>Davidson<\/PERSON>,print_headline:<LOCATION>Virginia<\/LOCATION> Holds Off Pesky <PERSON>Davidson<\/PERSON>}","{contributor:,original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
