snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Former <ORGANIZATION>Penn State</ORGANIZATION> assistant football coach <PERSON>Jerry Sandusky</PERSON> has lost a legal battle to restore his <MONEY>$4,900-a-month</MONEY> pension, a benefit that was canceled two years ago after he was sentenced for child molestation.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-19T11:47:26Z,[],561,"Former <ORGANIZATION>Penn State</ORGANIZATION> assistant football coach <PERSON>Jerry Sandusky</PERSON> has lost a legal battle to restore his <MONEY>$4,900-a-month</MONEY> pension, a benefit that was canceled two years ago after he was sentenced for child molestation.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/19/us/ap-us-sandusky-pension.html,5494575079881048d26b333f,null,"{main:<PERSON>Jerry Sandusky<\/PERSON> Is Denied <MONEY>$4,900-a-Month<\/MONEY> Pension,print_headline:<PERSON>Jerry Sandusky<\/PERSON> Is Denied <MONEY>$4,900-a-Month<\/MONEY> Pension}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
There quantify quickly foods make transition urban elites mainstream acceptance.,3,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Food},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Restaurants},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Cooking Cookbooks}]",The Upshot,"Fried calamari, exotic, made voyage served innovative restaurants <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> capitals gastronomy ubiquitous; foods include tuna tartare, braised short ribs, beet salad dish involving kale; chart highlights quickly foods made transition urban elites mainstream acceptance.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-08-12T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/08/12/upshot/SUB--12UP-Calamari/SUB--12UP-Calamari-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/08/12/upshot/SUB--12UP-Calamari/SUB--12UP-Calamari-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/08/12/upshot/SUB--12UP-Calamari/SUB--12UP-Calamari-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:386},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/08/12/upshot/SUB--12UP-Calamari/SUB--12UP-Calamari-articleLarge.jpg,height:386},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/08/12/upshot/SUB--12UP-Calamari/SUB--12UP-Calamari-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/08/12/upshot/SUB--12UP-Calamari/SUB--12UP-Calamari-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1072,There quantify quickly foods make transition urban elites mainstream acceptance.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/08/12/upshot/special-sauce-for-measuring-food-trends-the-fried-calamari-index.html,53e9990b79881068933b2135,null,"{content_kicker:On Menu,main:Special Sauce Measuring Food Trends: The Fried Calamari Index,print_headline:In Word Use, Seeing Dining Fads Evolve,kicker:The Upshot}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>NEIL IRWIN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Neil,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:IRWIN}]}",article
"GRUMAN--<PERSON>Jessie Christine</PERSON>. 60, <LOCATION>New York Washington</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>DC</LOCATION>, died home <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> <DATE>July 14, 2014</DATE>. Jessie born <LOCATION>Berea</LOCATION>, KY, <DATE>December 7, 1953</DATE>, grew upstate <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Montana</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Wisconsin Oregon</LOCATION>. She graduated Vassar College...",20,"[{name:persons,value:GRUMAN, JESSIE CHRISTINE}]",Paid Death Notices,null,The New York Times,[],Classified,2014-07-27T00:00:00Z,[],302,"GRUMAN--<PERSON>Jessie Christine</PERSON>. 60, <LOCATION>New York Washington</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>DC</LOCATION>, died home <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> <DATE>July 14, 2014</DATE>. Jessie born <LOCATION>Berea</LOCATION>, KY, <DATE>December 7, 1953</DATE>, grew upstate <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Montana</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Wisconsin Oregon</LOCATION>. She graduated <ORGANIZATION>Vassar College 1975</ORGANIZATION> received PhD social psychology <ORGANIZATION>Columbia University</ORGANIZATION> <DATE>1984</DATE>. In <DATE>1992</DATE>, founded <ORGANIZATION>Center Advancing Health</ORGANIZATION>, independent, nonprofit research policy institute based <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION>, <ORGANIZATION>DC</ORGANIZATION>, served president death. She author AfterShock: What Do When Doctor Gives You Someone You Love Devastating Diagnosis. Jessie received honorary doctorates <PERSON>Brown</PERSON>, <ORGANIZATION>Carnegie Mellon</ORGANIZATION>, <PERSON>Clark</PERSON>, <LOCATION>Georgetown</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>, <ORGANIZATION>Northeastern</ORGANIZATION>, <PERSON>Salve Regina</PERSON>, <ORGANIZATION>Syracuse Tulane Universities</ORGANIZATION>, <ORGANIZATION>Presidential Medal George Washington University</ORGANIZATION>. She honored Research! America, <ORGANIZATION>National Coalition Cancer Survivorship Society Behavioral Medicine</ORGANIZATION>, <DATE>2014</DATE> created <ORGANIZATION>Jessie Gruman Award Health Engagement</ORGANIZATION>. She member <ORGANIZATION>American Academy Arts Sciences Council Foreign Relations</ORGANIZATION>. She fellow <ORGANIZATION>New York Academy Medicine Society Behavioral Medicine</ORGANIZATION>. She served numerous boards advisory panels including, recently, <ORGANIZATION>Center Medical Technology Policy</ORGANIZATION>, <ORGANIZATION>Claremont School Community Global Health</ORGANIZATION>, Journal Participatory Medicine, <ORGANIZATION>Milbank Memorial Fund</ORGANIZATION>, <ORGANIZATION>Sallan Foundation VillageCare</ORGANIZATION>. She survived <PERSON>Richard Sloan</PERSON>, devoted loving husband, loving family members. Memorial services held fall <LOCATION>New York Washington</LOCATION>, DC. Memorial contributions made <ORGANIZATION>Jessie Gruman Memorial Fund Center Advancing Health</ORGANIZATION>, <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>DC</LOCATION>; VillageCare, <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>; <ORGANIZATION>Southern Center Human Rights</ORGANIZATION>, <LOCATION>Atlanta</LOCATION>; <LOCATION>City Harvest</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>.",Paid Death Notice,http://query.nytimes.com/gst/fullpage.html?res=9406E1DB173AF934A15754C0A9629D8B63,53def7c4798810168b3f6826,null,"{main:Paid Notice: Deaths  GRUMAN, JESSIE C.RISTINE}",null,article
"GRUMAN--<PERSON>Jessie Christine</PERSON>. 60, <LOCATION>New York Washington</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>DC</LOCATION>, died home <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> <DATE>July 14, 2014</DATE>. Jessie born <LOCATION>Berea</LOCATION>, KY, <DATE>December 7, 1953</DATE>, grew upstate <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Montana</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Wisconsin Oregon</LOCATION>. She graduated Vassar College...",null,[],Paid Death Notices,null,The New York Times,[],Classified,2014-07-23T02:35:15Z,[],302,"<!-- JESSIE C. GRUMAN --><<ORGANIZATION>IMG SRC</ORGANIZATION>=/Images/Cobrands/NYTimes/Photos/NYT-1000649077-GRUMANJ.1_013459.jpg lgyOrigName=NYT-1000649077-GRUMANJ.1.jpg ALIGN=LEFT vspace=4 hspace=10>GRUMAN--<PERSON>Jessie Christine</PERSON>. 60, <LOCATION>New York Washington</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>DC</LOCATION>, died home <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> <DATE>July 14, 2014</DATE>. Jessie born <LOCATION>Berea</LOCATION>, KY, <DATE>December 7, 1953</DATE>, grew upstate <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Montana</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Wisconsin Oregon</LOCATION>. She graduated <ORGANIZATION>Vassar College</ORGANIZATION>... <DATE>1975</DATE> and received a PhD in social psychology from <ORGANIZATION>Columbia University</ORGANIZATION> in <DATE>1984</DATE>. In <DATE>1992</DATE>, she founded the <ORGANIZATION>Center for Advancing Health</ORGANIZATION>, an independent, nonprofit research and policy institute based in <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>DC</LOCATION>, for which she served as president until her death. She was the author of AfterShock: What to Do When the Doctor Gives You or Someone You Love a Devastating Diagnosis. Jessie received honorary doctorates from <PERSON>Brown</PERSON>, <ORGANIZATION>Carnegie Mellon</ORGANIZATION>, <PERSON>Clark</PERSON>, <LOCATION>Georgetown</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>, <ORGANIZATION>Northeastern</ORGANIZATION>, <PERSON>Salve Regina</PERSON>, <ORGANIZATION>Syracuse</ORGANIZATION> and <ORGANIZATION>Tulane Universities</ORGANIZATION>, and the Presidential Medal of the <ORGANIZATION>George Washington University</ORGANIZATION>. She was also honored by Research! <LOCATION>America</LOCATION>, the <ORGANIZATION>National Coalition</ORGANIZATION> for Cancer Survivorship and the Society for Behavioral Medicine, which in <DATE>2014</DATE> created the <ORGANIZATION>Jessie Gruman Award for Health Engagement</ORGANIZATION>. She was a member of the <ORGANIZATION>American Academy of Arts</ORGANIZATION> and Sciences and the <ORGANIZATION>Council on Foreign Relations</ORGANIZATION>. She was a fellow of the <ORGANIZATION>New York Academy of Medicine</ORGANIZATION> and the Society for Behavioral Medicine. She served on numerous boards and advisory panels including, most recently, the <ORGANIZATION>Center for Medical Technology Policy</ORGANIZATION>, the <ORGANIZATION>Claremont School of Community and Global Health</ORGANIZATION>, the Journal of Participatory Medicine, the <ORGANIZATION>Milbank Memorial Fund</ORGANIZATION>, the <ORGANIZATION>Sallan Foundation</ORGANIZATION> and VillageCare. She is survived by <PERSON>Richard Sloan</PERSON>, her devoted and loving husband, and many loving family members. Memorial services will be held this fall in <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION>, DC. Memorial contributions may be made to the <PERSON>Jessie Gruman</PERSON> Memorial Fund at the <ORGANIZATION>Center for Advancing Health</ORGANIZATION>, <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>DC</LOCATION>; VillageCare, <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>; the <ORGANIZATION>Southern Center for Human Rights</ORGANIZATION>, <LOCATION>Atlanta</LOCATION>; <LOCATION>City Harvest</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>.<br><br> ",Paid Death Notice,http://www.legacy.com/Link.asp?I=LS000171825224,53cf79947988100eb4c3b04f,null,"{main:Paid Notice: Deaths  GRUMAN, JESSIE C.}",null,article
"GRUMAN--<PERSON>Jessie Christine</PERSON>. 60, of <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>DC</LOCATION>, died at home in <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> on <DATE>July 14, 2014</DATE>. Jessie was born in <LOCATION>Berea</LOCATION>, KY, <DATE>December 7, 1953</DATE>, and grew up in <LOCATION>upstate New York</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Montana</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Wisconsin</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Oregon</LOCATION>. She graduated from Vassar College...",14,"[{name:persons,value:GRUMAN, JESSIE CHRISTINE}]",Paid Death Notices,null,The New York Times,[],Classified,2014-07-23T00:00:00Z,[],302,"GRUMAN--<PERSON>Jessie Christine</PERSON>. 60, <LOCATION>New York Washington</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>DC</LOCATION>, died home <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> <DATE>July 14, 2014</DATE>. Jessie born <LOCATION>Berea</LOCATION>, KY, <DATE>December 7, 1953</DATE>, grew upstate <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Montana</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Wisconsin Oregon</LOCATION>. She graduated <ORGANIZATION>Vassar College 1975</ORGANIZATION> received PhD social psychology <ORGANIZATION>Columbia University</ORGANIZATION> <DATE>1984</DATE>. In <DATE>1992</DATE>, founded <ORGANIZATION>Center Advancing Health</ORGANIZATION>, independent, nonprofit research policy institute based <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION>, <ORGANIZATION>DC</ORGANIZATION>, served president death. She author AfterShock: What Do When Doctor Gives You Someone You Love Devastating Diagnosis. Jessie received honorary doctorates <PERSON>Brown</PERSON>, <ORGANIZATION>Carnegie Mellon</ORGANIZATION>, <PERSON>Clark</PERSON>, <LOCATION>Georgetown</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>, <ORGANIZATION>Northeastern</ORGANIZATION>, <PERSON>Salve Regina</PERSON>, <ORGANIZATION>Syracuse Tulane Universities</ORGANIZATION>, <ORGANIZATION>Presidential Medal George Washington University</ORGANIZATION>. She honored Research! America, <ORGANIZATION>National Coalition Cancer Survivorship Society Behavioral Medicine</ORGANIZATION>, <DATE>2014</DATE> created <ORGANIZATION>Jessie Gruman Award Health Engagement</ORGANIZATION>. She member <ORGANIZATION>American Academy Arts Sciences Council Foreign Relations</ORGANIZATION>. She fellow <ORGANIZATION>New York Academy Medicine Society Behavioral Medicine</ORGANIZATION>. She served numerous boards advisory panels including, recently, <ORGANIZATION>Center Medical Technology Policy</ORGANIZATION>, <ORGANIZATION>Claremont School Community Global Health</ORGANIZATION>, Journal Participatory Medicine, <ORGANIZATION>Milbank Memorial Fund</ORGANIZATION>, <ORGANIZATION>Sallan Foundation VillageCare</ORGANIZATION>. She survived <PERSON>Richard Sloan</PERSON>, devoted loving husband, loving family members. Memorial services held fall <LOCATION>New York Washington</LOCATION>, DC. Memorial contributions made <ORGANIZATION>Jessie Gruman Memorial Fund Center Advancing Health</ORGANIZATION>, <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>DC</LOCATION>; VillageCare, <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>; <ORGANIZATION>Southern Center Human Rights</ORGANIZATION>, <LOCATION>Atlanta</LOCATION>; <LOCATION>City Harvest</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>.",Paid Death Notice,http://query.nytimes.com/gst/fullpage.html?res=9903E5DD173AF930A15754C0A9629D8B63,53d9b1887988100f0ad908b2,null,"{main:Paid Notice: Deaths  GRUMAN, <PERSON>JESSIE CHRISTINE<\/PERSON>}",null,article
"The breast cancer patients survivors make Empire Dragon Boat Team NYC lending tenacity cleanup practice site, <LOCATION>Flushing Bay</LOCATION>.",23,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Waste Materials Disposal},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Breast Cancer},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:6,value:Empire Dragon Boat Team NYC},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Flushing Bay Queens<\/LOCATION>, NY},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Canoes Canoeing},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Water Pollution}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"Empire Dragon Boat Team NYC, group made breast cancer survivors, location polluted waters <LOCATION>Flushing Bay</LOCATION> engage strenuous team activity avenue wellness social support.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-07-11T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/07/11/nyregion/11DRAGONBOATs/11DRAGONBOAT-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/07/11/nyregion/11DRAGONBOATs/11DRAGONBOAT-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/07/11/nyregion/11DRAGONBOATs/11DRAGONBOAT-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/07/11/nyregion/11DRAGONBOATs/11DRAGONBOAT-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/07/11/nyregion/11DRAGONBOATs/11DRAGONBOATs-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/07/11/nyregion/11DRAGONBOATs/11DRAGONBOATs-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",932,"The breast cancer patients survivors make Empire Dragon Boat Team NYC lending tenacity cleanup practice site, <LOCATION>Flushing Bay</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/07/11/nyregion/cancer-survivors-apply-tenacious-spirit-to-bay-cleanup.html,53bf3fbd7988105f774f4839,null,"{main:Cancer Survivors Apply Tenacious Spirit Bay Cleanup,print_headline:Cancer Survivors Apply Tenacious Spirit Bay Cleanup}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>COREY KILGANNON<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Corey,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:KILGANNON}]}",article
Are building worse to??,null,[],Opinion,Are building worse to??,The New York Times,[],OpEd,2014-06-27T11:13:43Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/06/27/opinion/062714krugman1/062714krugman1-thumbWide.png},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/06/27/opinion/062714krugman1/062714krugman1-thumbWide.png,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/06/27/opinion/062714krugman1/062714krugman1-articleLarge.png,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:324},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/06/27/opinion/062714krugman1/062714krugman1-articleLarge.png,height:324},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/06/27/opinion/062714krugman1/062714krugman1-thumbStandard.png,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/06/27/opinion/062714krugman1/062714krugman1-thumbStandard.png,height:75}]",414,null,Blog,http://krugman.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/06/27/these-ages-of-shoddy/,53ad8a5c79881073fab4f5b8,null,"{main:These Ages Shoddy,kicker:<PERSON>Paul Krugman<\/PERSON>}","{original:By <PERSON>PAUL KRUGMAN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Paul,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:KRUGMAN}]}",blogpost
"Often low blood sugar, raised levels, pressing problem elderly patients diabetes.",null,"[{name:subject,rank:3,value:Elderly},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Elder Care},{name:subject,rank:4,value:Hypoglycemia},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Diabetes}]",Health,"Often low blood sugar, raised levels, pressing problem elderly patients diabetes.",The New York Times,[],Science,2014-06-19T05:00:56Z,[],603,null,Blog,http://newoldage.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/06/19/hypoglycemia-rising-in-older-people-with-diabetes/,53a2a74c7988101bf370ba8e,null,"{main:Hypoglycemia Rising Older People With Diabetes,kicker:The New Old Age}","{original:By <PERSON>JUDITH GRAHAM<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Judith,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:GRAHAM}]}",blogpost
The expenses of a mutual fund often tell you something that its past performance can’t.,3,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Mutual Funds},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Exchange Traded Funds},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Stocks Bonds},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:4,value:<ORGANIZATION>Morningstar Inc<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Prices Fares, Fees Rates},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:6,value:<PERSON>Kinnel<\/PERSON>, Russel},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:7,value:<ORGANIZATION>Vanguard Group Inc<\/ORGANIZATION>}]",Your Money,<PERSON>Jeff Sommer</PERSON> Strategies column holds mutual fund fees offer insight quality past performance; cites analysis Morningstar upholding wisdom funds low fees likelier outperform peers.,The New York Times,[],SundayBusiness,2014-06-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/06/01/business/01-STRA/01-STRA-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/06/01/business/01-STRA/01-STRA-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/06/01/business/01-STRA/01-STRA-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:348},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/06/01/business/01-STRA/01-STRA-articleLarge.jpg,height:348},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/06/01/business/01-STRA/01-STRA-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/06/01/business/01-STRA/01-STRA-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",983,The expenses of a mutual fund often tell you something that its past performance can’t.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/06/01/your-money/rules-of-the-fund-road-watch-the-fees-and-dont-look-back.html,5389fbc47988103c8eff03cd,null,"{content_kicker:Strategies,main:Rules of the Fund Road: Watch the Fees, and Don’t Look Back,print_headline:Rules of the Fund Road: Watch the Fees, and Don’t Look Back,kicker:Strategies}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>JEFF SOMMER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Jeff,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SOMMER}]}",article
"One 10 clinical trials adults cancer ends prematurely researchers people test treatments, scientists report.",null,[],Health,null,AP,[],null,2014-01-28T17:00:00Z,[],532,"One 10 clinical trials adults cancer ends prematurely researchers people test treatments, scientists report.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/01/28/health/ap-us-med-cancer-experiments.html,52e8293279881029dda8ea22,null,"{main:Doctors: Too Few Cancer Patients Enroll Studies,print_headline:Doctors: Too Few Cancer Patients Enroll Studies}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
