snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"<LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION>'s financial regulator running stress tests cash system stifling smaller banks' ability earn, unlike regulatory tests designed lenders capital cope...",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-29T00:11:53Z,[],636,"<LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION>'s financial regulator running stress tests cash system stifling smaller banks' ability earn, unlike regulatory tests designed lenders capital cope financial shocks.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/29/business/29reuters-japan-banking-exclusive.html,54a0e3597988101f98e3eef3,null,"{main:Exclusive-Japan's Regional Banks Face Stress Test Ultra-Low Rates,print_headline:Exclusive-Japan's Regional Banks Face Stress Test Ultra-Low Rates}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION>'s financial regulator begun stress tests regional banks determine earnings suffer long-term interest rates remain record lows <ORGANIZATION>Bank Japan</ORGANIZATION>'s loose money policy, people...",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-28T21:47:18Z,[],321,"<LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION>'s financial regulator begun stress tests regional banks determine earnings suffer long-term interest rates remain record lows <ORGANIZATION>Bank Japan</ORGANIZATION>'s loose money policy, people direct knowledge process.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/28/business/28reuters-japan-banking-exclusive.html,54a0c0e17988101f98e3ee8c,null,"{main:Exclusive-Japan's Regional Banks Face Stress Test Ultra-Low Rates,print_headline:Exclusive-Japan's Regional Banks Face Stress Test Ultra-Low Rates}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"A leftist Greek government run deficits, pursue fiscal consolidation, main opposition party's chief economy policymaker <DATE>Saturday</DATE>.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-27T16:02:42Z,[],452,"A leftist Greek government run deficits, pursue fiscal consolidation, main opposition party's chief economy policymaker <DATE>Saturday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/27/world/europe/ap-eu-greece-politics.html,549f1f4279881001534d1f8d,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:Greek Leftists Won't Run Deficits, Policymaker Says,print_headline:Greek Leftists Won't Run Deficits, Policymaker Says}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
A new fund-raising round by the <ORGANIZATION>Carlyle Group</ORGANIZATION> is just one indication of private equity’s commitment to <LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>.,null,"[{name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Brazil<\/LOCATION>},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:Advent International Corp},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:<ORGANIZATION>Carlyle Group LP<\/ORGANIZATION>},{name:organizations,rank:3,value:Gavea Investments},{name:organizations,rank:4,value:General Atlantic LLC},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Economic Conditions Trends},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Private Equity}]",Business Day,A new fund-raising round by the <ORGANIZATION>Carlyle Group</ORGANIZATION> is just one indication of private equity’s commitment to <LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>.,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-24T10:55:22Z,[],894,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/24/private-equity-funds-still-going-strong-in-brazil-despite-economic-malaise/,549ae23e7988102d96d5683a,Dealbook,"{main:Private Equity Funds Still Going Strong <LOCATION>Brazil<\/LOCATION> Despite Economic Malaise,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>VINOD SREEHARSHA<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Vinod,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SREEHARSHA}]}",blogpost
"<LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION> facing refining sector overhaul population ages shrinks economy shifts oil gas, resulting oil demand falling 2-3 percent year.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-23T00:32:05Z,[],377,"<LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION> facing refining sector overhaul population ages shrinks economy shifts oil gas, resulting oil demand falling 2-3 percent year.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/23/business/23reuters-japan-showa-shell-idemitsu-kosan.html,5498fef3798810035238e758,null,"{main:Japanese Refining Merger Talks Could Spur More Consolidation,print_headline:Japanese Refining Merger Talks Could Spur More Consolidation}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<PERSON>Edith Ramirez</PERSON>&#8217;s tenure leader commission marked effort bring regulator public eye, directing attention digital privacy transactions.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:Federal Trade Commission},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Ramirez<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Edith<\/PERSON>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Net Neutrality},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Federal Communications Commission},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:5,value:Consumer Financial Protection Bureau},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Computers Internet}]",Technology,"<ORGANIZATION>Federal Trade Commission</ORGANIZATION> chairwoman <PERSON>Edith Ramirez</PERSON> viewed soft-spoken aggressive negotiator bring agency public eye; efforts, digital privacy digital transactions, lead turf battles <ORGANIZATION>Federal Communications Commission Consumer Financial Protection Bureau</ORGANIZATION>.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-22T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/22/business/ramirez/ramirez-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/22/business/ramirez/ramirez-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/22/business/ramirez/ramirez-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:655},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/22/business/ramirez/ramirez-articleLarge.jpg,height:655},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/22/business/ramirez/ramirez-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/22/business/ramirez/ramirez-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1117,"<PERSON>Edith Ramirez</PERSON>&#8217;s tenure leader commission marked effort bring regulator public eye, directing attention digital privacy transactions.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/22/business/federal-trade-commission-raises-its-voice-under-its-soft-spoken-chairwoman.html,5497535a7988104a1e0de4b8,null,"{main:<PERSON>Edith Ramirez<\/PERSON> Is Raising the F.T.C.’s Voice,print_headline:Raising the F.T.C.’s Voice, Softly}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>EDWARD WYATT<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Edward,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:WYATT}]}",article
"Chief executives deal-making confidence back <DATE>2014</DATE>, emboldened clearer outlook businesses global value mergers acquisitions M&amp;A highest annual level <DATE>2007</DATE>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-21T03:09:15Z,[],892,"Chief executives deal-making confidence back <DATE>2014</DATE>, emboldened clearer outlook businesses global value mergers acquisitions M&amp;A highest annual level <DATE>2007</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/21/business/21reuters-m-a-global.html,5496808879881029b367deb2,null,"{main:Fear Factor Fades Global M&A Hits Seven-Year High,print_headline:Fear Factor Fades Global M&A Hits Seven-Year High}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<ORGANIZATION>Deutsche Bank</ORGANIZATION>'s co-chief executive <PERSON>Juergen Fitschen</PERSON> consolidation European retail banking market overdue, German weekly Welt Sonntag.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-20T07:22:30Z,[],230,"<ORGANIZATION>Deutsche Bank</ORGANIZATION>'s co-chief executive <PERSON>Juergen Fitschen</PERSON> consolidation European retail banking market overdue, German weekly Welt Sonntag.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/20/business/20reuters-deutsche-bank-strategy-deutsche-postbnk.html,54956ac67988107c4680073d,null,"{main:<ORGANIZATION>Deutsche Bank Co-CEO Cagey Postbank<\/ORGANIZATION> Future-Welt Am Sonntag,print_headline:<ORGANIZATION>Deutsche Bank Co-CEO Cagey Postbank<\/ORGANIZATION> Future-Welt Am Sonntag}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Next year, half chips <ORGANIZATION>Intel</ORGANIZATION> sells cloud businesses custom. The company selling tens millions thing, outfits <ORGANIZATION>Google</ORGANIZATION> Facebook special features, pay.",null,"[{name:organizations,rank:1,value:<ORGANIZATION>Intel<\/ORGANIZATION> Corporation},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Cloud Computing},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Computer Chips}]",Technology,"Next year, half chips <ORGANIZATION>Intel</ORGANIZATION> sells cloud businesses custom. The company selling tens millions thing, outfits <ORGANIZATION>Google</ORGANIZATION> Facebook special features, pay.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-19T07:00:35Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/12/technology/12bits-chip/12bits-chip-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/12/technology/12bits-chip/12bits-chip-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/12/technology/12bits-chip/12bits-chip-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/12/technology/12bits-chip/12bits-chip-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/12/technology/12bits-chip/12bits-chip-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/12/technology/12bits-chip/12bits-chip-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",792,null,Blog,http://bits.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/19/intel-betting-on-customized-commodity-chips-for-cloud-computing/,549413af79881048d26b3272,null,"{main:Intel Betting Customized Commodity Chips Cloud Computing,kicker:Bits}","{original:By <PERSON>QUENTIN HARDY<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Quentin,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:HARDY}]}",blogpost
"<ORGANIZATION>Thai Union Frozen Products</ORGANIZATION>, the world’s biggest producer of canned tuna, has agreed to buy the American company as part of a plan to double revenue.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-19T00:25:41Z,[],707,"<ORGANIZATION>Thai Union Frozen Products</ORGANIZATION>, the world’s biggest producer of canned tuna, has agreed to buy the American company as part of a plan to double revenue.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/19/business/19reuters-bumble-bee-thai-uno-frozen-acquisition.html,5493b78979881048d26b3187,null,"{main:Thai Tuna Producer to Buy <ORGANIZATION>Bumble Bee<\/ORGANIZATION> for <MONEY>$1.5 Billion<\/MONEY>,print_headline:Thai Union Frozen to Buy <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Tuna Firm <ORGANIZATION>Bumble Bee<\/ORGANIZATION> for <MONEY>$1.5 Billion<\/MONEY>}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
