snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Deals worth nearly <MONEY>$3.5 trillion</MONEY> were announced, a performance favored by low interest rates and high stock prices.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Mergers, Acquisitions Divestitures}]",Business Day,"Deals worth nearly <MONEY>$3.5 trillion</MONEY> were announced, a performance favored by low interest rates and high stock prices.",The New York Times,[],Business,2015-01-01T19:32:44Z,[],525,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/deal-makers-notched-nearly-3-5-trillion-worth-in-14-best-in-7-years/,54a5e7cc7988102023c94f8e,Dealbook,"{main:Deal Makers Notched Nearly <MONEY>$3.5<\/MONEY> <ORGANIZATION>Trillion Worth<\/ORGANIZATION> in &rsquo;14, Best in 7 Years,print_headline:Deal Makers Notched Nearly <MONEY>$3.5 Trillion<\/MONEY> Worth in ’14, Best in 7 Years,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>MICHAEL J. DE<\/PERSON> LA MERCED,person:[{firstname:Michael,role:reported,organization:,middlename:J.,rank:1,lastname:DE LA MERCED}]}",blogpost
"A federal judge north <LOCATION>Florida</LOCATION> ruled <DATE>Thursday</DATE> county clerks statewide issue marriage licenses same-sex couples request starting <DATE>Jan. 6</DATE>, effective date decision overturn <LOCATION>Florida</LOCATION>'s ban gay matrimony...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T17:53:19Z,[],388,"A federal judge north <LOCATION>Florida</LOCATION> ruled <DATE>Thursday</DATE> county clerks statewide issue marriage licenses same-sex couples request starting <DATE>Jan. 6</DATE>, effective date decision overturn <LOCATION>Florida</LOCATION>'s ban gay matrimony unconstitutional.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/us/01reuters-usa-florida-gaymarriage.html,54a5d03b7988102023c94d6c,null,"{main:Federal Judge Allows Gay Marriages Begin Across <LOCATION>Florida<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:Federal Judge Allows Gay Marriages Begin Across <LOCATION>Florida<\/LOCATION>}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"A federal judge <LOCATION>Florida</LOCATION>'s county court clerks legal duty issue marriage licenses same-sex couples, stopped short ordering.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T16:50:52Z,[],545,"A federal judge <LOCATION>Florida</LOCATION>'s county court clerks legal duty issue marriage licenses same-sex couples, stopped short ordering.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/us/ap-us-gay-marriage-florida.html,54a5c2317988102023c94bd8,null,"{main:Judge: Clerks Have Duty Issue Same-Sex Marriage Licenses,print_headline:Judge: Clerks Have Duty Issue Same-Sex Marriage Licenses}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Paramount Pictures will show the film free at <LOCATION>Selma</LOCATION>’s <ORGANIZATION>Walton Theater</ORGANIZATION> beginning <DATE>Jan. 9</DATE> as part of the movie’s national release.,null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:DuVernay, Ava},{name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Johnson<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Lyndon Baines<\/PERSON>},{name:persons,rank:3,value:King, <PERSON>Martin Luther<\/PERSON> Jr},{name:persons,rank:4,value:<PERSON>Moore<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Rob<\/PERSON>},{name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Selma<\/LOCATION> Ala},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:Paramount Pictures},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Civil Rights Movement 1954-68},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Movies}]",Arts,Paramount Pictures will show the film free at <LOCATION>Selma</LOCATION>’s <ORGANIZATION>Walton Theater</ORGANIZATION> beginning <DATE>Jan. 9</DATE> as part of the movie’s national release.,The New York Times,[],Culture,2015-01-01T15:11:01Z,[],231,null,Blog,http://artsbeat.blogs.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/selma-to-be-screened-free-in-selma/,54a5aa977988102023c949bf,null,"{main:'<LOCATION>Selma<\/LOCATION>' Be Screened Free <LOCATION>Selma<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:In <LOCATION>Selma<\/LOCATION>, Free Screening &#8216;<LOCATION>Selma<\/LOCATION>&#8217;,kicker:ArtsBeat}","{original:By <PERSON>JENNIFER SCHUESSLER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Jennifer,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SCHUESSLER}]}",blogpost
"Love triangle beautiful woman, drug dealer friend, federal agent capturing drug smugglers. Sizzling cast unpredictable drama!",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T14:20:35Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-tequila-sunrise/video-tequila-sunrise-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-tequila-sunrise/video-tequila-sunrise-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-tequila-sunrise/video-tequila-sunrise-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-tequila-sunrise/video-tequila-sunrise-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-tequila-sunrise/video-tequila-sunrise-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-tequila-sunrise/video-tequila-sunrise-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",31,"Love triangle beautiful woman, drug dealer friend, federal agent capturing drug smugglers. Sizzling cast unpredictable drama!",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003380627/tequila-sunrise.html,54a59e067988102023c946de,null,{"main":"Tequila Sunrise"},"{original:Warner Home Video,person:[{firstname:Warner,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Home,rank:1,lastname:Video}]}",multimedia
<PERSON>James Stewart</PERSON> portrays <PERSON>J. Edgar Hoover</PERSON>'s finest Vera Miles co-stars steadfast wife salute <ORGANIZATION>Federal Bureau Investigation</ORGANIZATION>. The colorful career Agent Chip <PERSON>Hardesty Stewart</PERSON> covers <DATE>1924</DATE> late '50s. Along,null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T13:56:37Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-fbi-story/video-the-fbi-story-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-fbi-story/video-the-fbi-story-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-fbi-story/video-the-fbi-story-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-fbi-story/video-the-fbi-story-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-fbi-story/video-the-fbi-story-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-fbi-story/video-the-fbi-story-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",42,<PERSON>James Stewart</PERSON> portrays <PERSON>J. Edgar Hoover</PERSON>'s finest Vera Miles co-stars steadfast wife salute <ORGANIZATION>Federal Bureau Investigation</ORGANIZATION>. The colorful career Agent Chip <PERSON>Hardesty Stewart</PERSON> covers <DATE>1924</DATE> late '50s. Along,Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003386790/the-fbi-story.html,54a598687988102023c94529,null,{"main":"The Fbi Story"},"{original:Warner Home Video,person:[{firstname:Warner,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Home,rank:1,lastname:Video}]}",multimedia
"<LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>'s President <PERSON>Dilma Rousseff</PERSON> sworn term office <DATE>Thursday</DATE>, confronting expanding kickback scandal state-run oil company, moribund economy congressional support ruling coalition.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T13:02:25Z,[],334,"<LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>'s President <PERSON>Dilma Rousseff</PERSON> sworn term office <DATE>Thursday</DATE>, confronting expanding kickback scandal state-run oil company, moribund economy congressional support ruling coalition.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/world/americas/ap-lt-brazil-inauguration.html,54a58c127988102023c94152,Americas,"{main:<LOCATION>Brazil<\/LOCATION>'s Leader Sworn In 2nd Term,print_headline:<LOCATION>Brazil<\/LOCATION>'s Leader Sworn In 2nd Term}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"For opposite reasons, undercover federal agent small time hood join forces union drug lords dirty cops.",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T12:37:50Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-breach-of-trust/video-breach-of-trust-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-breach-of-trust/video-breach-of-trust-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-breach-of-trust/video-breach-of-trust-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-breach-of-trust/video-breach-of-trust-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-breach-of-trust/video-breach-of-trust-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-breach-of-trust/video-breach-of-trust-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",25,"For opposite reasons, undercover federal agent small time hood join forces union drug lords dirty cops.",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003294622/breach-of-trust.html,54a586147988102023c93f69,null,{"main":"Breach Of Trust"},"{original:Republic Pictures Home Video,person:[{firstname:Republic,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Pictures,rank:1,lastname:Home}]}",multimedia
"The city hoping hand investigation 12-year-old boy's fatal shooting police agency, future investigations deadly use-of-force cases.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T12:19:00Z,[],361,"The city hoping hand investigation 12-year-old boy's fatal shooting police agency, future investigations deadly use-of-force cases.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/us/ap-us-cleveland-police-shoot-boy.html,54a582487988102023c93e43,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Cleveland<\/LOCATION> Seeks Outside Probe Boy's Shooting,print_headline:<LOCATION>Cleveland<\/LOCATION> Seeks Outside Probe Boy's Shooting}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"A pilot mechanic died crash helicopter <LOCATION>Arizona</LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>Cochise County Sheriff's Office</ORGANIZATION> federal investigation <DATE>Thursday</DATE> caused crash, officials.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T12:16:36Z,[],171,"A pilot mechanic died crash helicopter <LOCATION>Arizona</LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>Cochise County Sheriff's Office</ORGANIZATION> federal investigation <DATE>Thursday</DATE> caused crash, officials.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/us/01reuters-usa-helicoptercrash-arizona.html,54a581867988102023c93e10,null,"{main:Two Killed Crash Sheriff's Office Helicopter Arizona,print_headline:Two Killed Crash Sheriff's Office Helicopter Arizona}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
