snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON> praising <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> Gov. <PERSON>Mario Cuomo</PERSON> unflinching voice tolerance, fairness opportunity.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T22:40:17Z,[],132,"President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON> praising <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> Gov. <PERSON>Mario Cuomo</PERSON> unflinching voice tolerance, fairness opportunity.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/us/ap-us-obama-mario-cuomo.html,54a613c57988102023c9536a,null,"{main:<PERSON>Obama<\/PERSON> Says <PERSON>Cuomo<\/PERSON> Championed Tolerance, Opportunity,print_headline:<PERSON>Obama<\/PERSON> Says <PERSON>Cuomo<\/PERSON> Championed Tolerance, Opportunity}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Reaction death three-term Gov. <PERSON>Mario Cuomo</PERSON>, died <DATE>Thursday</DATE> hours son, <PERSON>Andrew</PERSON>, sworn term governor.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T21:41:09Z,[],744,"Reaction death three-term Gov. <PERSON>Mario Cuomo</PERSON>, died <DATE>Thursday</DATE> hours son, <PERSON>Andrew</PERSON>, sworn term governor.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/us/ap-us-obit-mario-cuomo-reaction.html,54a605bb7988102023c95235,null,"{main:What's Being Said About <PERSON>Mario Cuomo<\/PERSON>'s Death,print_headline:What's Being Said About <PERSON>Mario Cuomo<\/PERSON>'s Death}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<PERSON>Mario Cuomo</PERSON>, son Italian immigrants eloquent spokesman generation liberal Democrats terms governor <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> bring run president, died. He 82.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T21:15:05Z,[],1240,"<PERSON>Mario Cuomo</PERSON>, son Italian immigrants eloquent spokesman generation liberal Democrats terms governor <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> bring run president, died. He 82.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/us/ap-us-obit-mario-cuomo-.html,54a600187988102023c951b2,null,"{main:Ex-NY Gov. <PERSON>Mario Cuomo<\/PERSON>, Famed Oratory, Dies 82,print_headline:Ex-NY Gov. <PERSON>Mario Cuomo<\/PERSON>, Famed Oratory, Dies 82}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<PERSON>Mario Cuomo</PERSON>, three-time governor <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> leading voice Democratic Party's liberal wing turned invitations seek <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> presidency, died <DATE>Thursday</DATE>. He 82.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T20:13:45Z,[],839,"<PERSON>Mario Cuomo</PERSON>, three-time governor <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> leading voice Democratic Party's liberal wing turned invitations seek <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> presidency, died <DATE>Thursday</DATE>. He 82.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/us/01reuters-usa-politics-cuomo.html,54a5f16f7988102023c95066,null,"{main:Former <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION> Governor <PERSON>Mario Cuomo<\/PERSON> Dead 82,print_headline:Former <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION> Governor <PERSON>Mario Cuomo<\/PERSON> Dead 82}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"According recent studies, half Americans prospect good job home white picket fence, existed unachievable.",null,"[{name:type_of_material,rank:1,value:News}]",Opinion,"According recent studies, half Americans prospect good job home white picket fence, existed unachievable.",The New York Times,[],null,2015-01-01T19:32:18Z,[],2347,,Blog,http://www.nytimes.com/roomfordebate/2015/01/01/is-the-modern-american-dream-attainable,54a5e8887988102023c94f9e,Room For Debate,"{main:Is Modern American Dream Attainable??,kicker:Room For Debate}",null,blogpost
The son Russian oligarch forged strong role British media.,1,"[{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Lebedev<\/PERSON>, Evgeny},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Newspapers},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:3,value:Great <LOCATION>Britain<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:4,value:<PERSON>Lebedev<\/PERSON>, Aleksandr Y},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:5,value:<LOCATION>London<\/LOCATION> Evening Standard},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:6,value:<LOCATION>London England<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:7,value:Novaya Gazeta}]",Style,Russian-born billionaire <PERSON>Evgeny Lebedev</PERSON> immersed British media world purchasing British newspapers.,The New York Times,[],Styles,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01LEDBEDEV/01LEDBEDEV-thumbWide-v2.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01LEDBEDEV/01LEDBEDEV-thumbWide-v2.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01LEDBEDEV/01LEDBEDEV-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:827},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01LEDBEDEV/01LEDBEDEV-articleLarge.jpg,height:827},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01LEDBEDEV/01LEDBEDEV-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01LEDBEDEV/01LEDBEDEV-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1352,The son Russian oligarch forged strong role British media.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/style/the-rise-of-evgeny-lebedev.html,54a46b1479881011bed2923e,null,"{main:The Rise <PERSON>Evgeny Lebedev<\/PERSON>,print_headline:Making Himself Home}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>CHARLIE PORTER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Charlie,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:PORTER}]}",article
"Already, series unrelated policy decisions reduced ability track family change <LOCATION>America</LOCATION>.",null,"[{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:1,value:Census Bureau},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Marriages},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Divorce, Separations Annulments},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Statistics},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Social Conditions Trends},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Families Family Life},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:7,value:United States}]",The Upshot,null,The New York Times,[],Upshot,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/07/upshot/01UP-Divorce/01UP-Divorce-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/07/upshot/01UP-Divorce/01UP-Divorce-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/07/upshot/01UP-Divorce/01UP-Divorce-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:399},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/07/upshot/01UP-Divorce/01UP-Divorce-articleLarge.jpg,height:399},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/07/upshot/01UP-Divorce/01UP-Divorce-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/07/upshot/01UP-Divorce/01UP-Divorce-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1418,"Already, series unrelated policy decisions reduced ability track family change <LOCATION>America</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/upshot/census-bureaus-plan-to-cut-marriage-and-divorce-questions-has-academics-up-in-arms.html,54a420057988102761d6e4bc,null,"{content_kicker:Vanishing Data,main:Census Bureau’s Plan to Cut Marriage and Divorce Questions Has Academics Up in Arms,kicker:The Upshot}","{original:By <PERSON>JUSTIN WOLFERS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Justin,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:WOLFERS}]}",article
Excerpts recent editorials newspapers <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> abroad:,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T16:38:27Z,[],2905,Excerpts recent editorials newspapers <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> abroad:,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/ap-us-editorial-rdp.html,54a46d5379881011bed292c6,null,"{main:Editorial Roundup: Excerpts From Recent Editorials,print_headline:Editorial Roundup: Excerpts From Recent Editorials}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"In Blue Like Jazz, <PERSON>Don Allman</PERSON>, pious nineteen-year-old sophomore <LOCATION>Texas</LOCATION> junior college, impulsively decides escape evangelical upbringing life <ORGANIZATION>Pacific Northwest</ORGANIZATION> ofthe progressive campuses <LOCATION>America</LOCATION>, Reed Colleg",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2014-12-31T12:55:31Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-blue-like-jazz/video-blue-like-jazz-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-blue-like-jazz/video-blue-like-jazz-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-blue-like-jazz/video-blue-like-jazz-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-blue-like-jazz/video-blue-like-jazz-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-blue-like-jazz/video-blue-like-jazz-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-blue-like-jazz/video-blue-like-jazz-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",38,"In Blue Like Jazz, <PERSON>Don Allman</PERSON>, pious nineteen-year-old sophomore <LOCATION>Texas</LOCATION> junior college, impulsively decides escape evangelical upbringing life <ORGANIZATION>Pacific Northwest</ORGANIZATION> ofthe progressive campuses <LOCATION>America</LOCATION>, Reed Colleg",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003293757/blue-like-jazz.html,54a4389a79881011bed28624,null,{"main":"Blue Like Jazz"},"{original:Roadside Attractions,person:[{firstname:Roadside,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Attractions}]}",multimedia
An effort kill <LOCATION>California</LOCATION>'s first-in-the-nation state ban single-use plastic grocery bags advanced week bag makers spent million dollars campaign gather signatures proposed ballot initiative overturn.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T12:16:11Z,[],407,An effort kill <LOCATION>California</LOCATION>'s first-in-the-nation state ban single-use plastic grocery bags advanced week bag makers spent million dollars campaign gather signatures proposed ballot initiative overturn.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/us/31reuters-usa-california-bags.html,54a4300779881011bed2834d,null,"{main:Effort Kill <LOCATION>California<\/LOCATION>'s Ban Plastic Grocery Bags Moves Forward,print_headline:Effort Kill <LOCATION>California<\/LOCATION>'s Ban Plastic Grocery Bags Moves Forward}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
