snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
Touchdown. Turnover. Touchdown. Turnover. Touchdown.,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T01:09:31Z,[],902,Touchdown. Turnover. Touchdown. Turnover. Touchdown.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/sports/ncaafootball/ap-fbc-t25-playoff-rose-bowl.html,54a4e57c79881011bed2ae3b,College Football,"{main:Rose Bowl Rout! <ORGANIZATION>Oregon Crushes Florida State<\/ORGANIZATION> 59-20,print_headline:Rose Bowl Rout! <ORGANIZATION>Oregon Crushes Florida State<\/ORGANIZATION> 59-20}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"The ruling dealt setback Gov. <PERSON>Jan Brewer</PERSON>, Republican governors sought expand benefits state level.",12,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Arizona<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Medicaid},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:Brewer, Jan},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Patient Protection Affordable Care Act 2010},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Health Insurance Managed Care}]",<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,"<ORGANIZATION>Arizona Supreme Court</ORGANIZATION> rules lawsuit filed conservative public policy organization <ORGANIZATION>Goldwater Institute</ORGANIZATION> proceed state method expand Medicaid, assessment place <LOCATION>Arizona</LOCATION> hospitals; ruling setback <PERSON>Gov Jan Brewer</PERSON>'s signature initiative week leaves office; <PERSON>Brewer</PERSON> worked Democrats expand Medicaid benefits Affordable Care Act.",The New York Times,[],National,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/us/ARIZONA/ARIZONA-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/us/ARIZONA/ARIZONA-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/us/ARIZONA/ARIZONA-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:392},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/us/ARIZONA/ARIZONA-articleLarge.jpg,height:392},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/us/ARIZONA/ARIZONA-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/us/ARIZONA/ARIZONA-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",672,"The ruling dealt setback Gov. <PERSON>Jan Brewer</PERSON>, Republican governors sought expand benefits state level.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/us/politics/arizona-supreme-court-allows-challenge-to-states-medicaid-expansion.html,54a4821079881011bed29782,Politics,"{main:<ORGANIZATION>Arizona Supreme Court Allows Challenge to State<\/ORGANIZATION>’s Medicaid Expansion,print_headline:<ORGANIZATION>Arizona Supreme Court<\/ORGANIZATION> Allows Challenge Medicaid Growth}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>TIMOTHY WILLIAMS RICK ROJAS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Timothy,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:WILLIAMS},{firstname:Rick,role:reported,organization:,rank:2,lastname:ROJAS}]}",article
"Texas Christian, left four-team playoff, touchdown passes <PERSON>Trevone Boykin</PERSON> dominant defense win rout.",11,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Football College},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Boykin<\/PERSON>, Trevone},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Hackett<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Chris<\/PERSON>},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:4,value:University <LOCATION>Mississippi<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:5,value:Texas Christian University}]",Sports,"College Football Bowl Roundup; <ORGANIZATION>Texas Christian University</ORGANIZATION> beats <ORGANIZATION>University Mississippi</ORGANIZATION>, 42-3, Peach Bowl; bowl game scores noted.",The New York Times,[],Sports,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/sports/bowls1/bowls1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/sports/bowls1/bowls1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/sports/bowls1/bowls1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/sports/bowls1/bowls1-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/sports/bowls1/bowls1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/sports/bowls1/bowls1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",386,"Texas Christian, left four-team playoff, touchdown passes <PERSON>Trevone Boykin</PERSON> dominant defense win rout.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/sports/ncaafootball/tcu-crushes-ole-miss-in-peach-bowl.html,54a470ec79881011bed29399,College Football,"{content_kicker:<LOCATION>Texas<\/LOCATION> Christian 42, <LOCATION>Mississippi<\/LOCATION> 3,main:T.C.U. Crushes Ole Miss Peach Bowl,print_headline:Kept Out Playoff, T.C.U. Settles Rout,kicker:<LOCATION>Texas<\/LOCATION> Christian 42, <LOCATION>Mississippi<\/LOCATION> 3}","{contributor:,original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<PERSON>Kari Lehtonen</PERSON> made 32 saves 30th shutout, <PERSON>Brett Ritchie</PERSON> scored <ORGANIZATION>NHL</ORGANIZATION> game <LOCATION>Dallas</LOCATION> Stars beat <LOCATION>Arizona</LOCATION> Coyotes 6-0 <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T22:48:51Z,[],431,"<PERSON>Kari Lehtonen</PERSON> made 32 saves 30th shutout, <PERSON>Brett Ritchie</PERSON> scored <ORGANIZATION>NHL</ORGANIZATION> game <LOCATION>Dallas</LOCATION> Stars beat <LOCATION>Arizona</LOCATION> Coyotes 6-0 <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/sports/hockey/ap-hkn-coyotes-stars.html,54a4c46b79881011bed2a6b5,Hockey,"{main:<PERSON>Lehtonen<\/PERSON> Makes 32 Saves Stars' Win Over Coyotes,print_headline:<PERSON>Lehtonen<\/PERSON> Makes 32 Saves Stars' Win Over Coyotes}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<PERSON>Jenn Anderson</PERSON> scored 19, <PERSON>Tyra Buss</PERSON> grabbed career-high 15 rebounds <PERSON>Amanda Cahill</PERSON> 13 points 13 boards lead <LOCATION>Indiana</LOCATION> women past No. 24 <ORGANIZATION>Michigan State</ORGANIZATION> 70-51 <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T21:11:18Z,[],156,"<PERSON>Jenn Anderson</PERSON> scored 19, <PERSON>Tyra Buss</PERSON> grabbed career-high 15 rebounds <PERSON>Amanda Cahill</PERSON> 13 points 13 boards lead <LOCATION>Indiana</LOCATION> women past No. 24 <ORGANIZATION>Michigan State</ORGANIZATION> 70-51 <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/sports/ncaabasketball/ap-bkw-t25-michigan-st-indiana.html,54a4ad3479881011bed2a166,College Basketball,"{main:<LOCATION>Indiana<\/LOCATION> Women Roll Past No. 24 <LOCATION>Michigan<\/LOCATION> St, 70-51,print_headline:<LOCATION>Indiana<\/LOCATION> Women Roll Past No. 24 <LOCATION>Michigan<\/LOCATION> St, 70-51}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
<PERSON>Gary Patterson</PERSON> knew asked <ORGANIZATION>TCU</ORGANIZATION>'s rout <LOCATION>Mississippi</LOCATION> statement <LOCATION>Horned Frogs</LOCATION> four-team playoff.,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T16:01:32Z,[],738,<PERSON>Gary Patterson</PERSON> knew asked <ORGANIZATION>TCU</ORGANIZATION>'s rout <LOCATION>Mississippi</LOCATION> statement <LOCATION>Horned Frogs</LOCATION> four-team playoff.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/sports/ncaafootball/ap-fbc-t25-peach-bowl.html,54a464ea79881011bed290d2,College Football,"{main:No. 6 TCU Crushes No. 9 Ole Miss, 42-3 Peach,print_headline:No. 6 TCU Crushes No. 9 Ole Miss, 42-3 Peach}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Over the last four quarters, <ORGANIZATION>IBM</ORGANIZATION> has spent more than <MONEY>$23 billion</MONEY> on dividends and buybacks while revenue has shrunk. A better idea is to invest more in the business.",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:Rometty, <LOCATION>Virginia<\/LOCATION> M},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:International Business Machines Corporation},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Company Reports}]",Business Day,"Over the last four quarters, <ORGANIZATION>IBM</ORGANIZATION> has spent more than <MONEY>$23 billion</MONEY> on dividends and buybacks while revenue has shrunk. A better idea is to invest more in the business.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-31T10:39:36Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/business/dealbook/dbpix-ibm/dbpix-ibm-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/dealbook/dbpix-ibm/dbpix-ibm-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/business/dealbook/dbpix-ibm/dbpix-ibm-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/dealbook/dbpix-ibm/dbpix-ibm-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/business/dealbook/dbpix-ibm/dbpix-ibm-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/dealbook/dbpix-ibm/dbpix-ibm-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",436,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/ibm-needs-to-spend-cash-not-return-it/,54a4196b7988102761d6e283,Dealbook,"{main:IBM Needs Spend Cash, Not Return It,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>ROBERT CYRAN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Robert,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:CYRAN}]}",blogpost
"Radar data examined investigators appeared show <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> Flight QZ8501 made unbelievably steep climb crashed, possibly pushing <ORGANIZATION>Airbus</ORGANIZATION> A320's limits, source familiar probe's initial...",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T08:16:48Z,[],720,"Radar data examined investigators appeared show <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> Flight QZ8501 made unbelievably steep climb crashed, possibly pushing <ORGANIZATION>Airbus</ORGANIZATION> A320's limits, source familiar probe's initial findings.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/world/asia/31reuters-indonesia-airplane-investigation.html,54a3f7c57988102761d6de54,Asia Pacific,"{main:Data Point 'Unbelievably' Steep Climb Before <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Crash-Source,print_headline:Data Point 'Unbelievably' Steep Climb Before <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Crash-Source}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
<LOCATION>Greece</LOCATION> formally dissolved parliament <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> ahead general election <DATE>Jan. 25</DATE> cast international bailout doubt set financial markets edge euro zone grapples renewed signs weakness.,null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T06:25:59Z,[],395,<LOCATION>Greece</LOCATION> formally dissolved parliament <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> ahead general election <DATE>Jan. 25</DATE> cast international bailout doubt set financial markets edge euro zone grapples renewed signs weakness.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/world/europe/31reuters-greece-vote.html,54a3ddc17988102761d6db64,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:<LOCATION>Greece<\/LOCATION> Formally Dissolves Parliament Ahead Election,print_headline:<LOCATION>Greece<\/LOCATION> Formally Dissolves Parliament Ahead Election}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
More half Americans information restaurants decide making healthy purchase. But.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T03:21:22Z,[],900,More half Americans information restaurants decide making healthy purchase. But.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/politics/ap-us-ap-poll-calories-on-menus.html,54a3b2e37988102761d6d667,Politics,"{main:AP-GfK Poll: Americans Support Menu Labeling,print_headline:AP-GfK Poll: Americans Support Menu Labeling}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
