snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
Stocks delivered <DATE>2014</DATE>.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T11:48:36Z,[],1201,Stocks delivered <DATE>2014</DATE>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/ap-ye-financial-markets-resilient-bull-.html,54a429b67988102761d6e7f7,null,"{main:Bull Market Stocks Keeps Going 2014,print_headline:Bull Market Stocks Keeps Going 2014}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Revelers ringing year week watch day's hangover. And investors experience similar feeling early <DATE>2015</DATE> two-year run propelled <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> stocks <PERCENT>50 percent</PERCENT>.,null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T01:05:09Z,[],993,Revelers ringing year week watch day's hangover. And investors experience similar feeling early <DATE>2015</DATE> two-year run propelled <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> stocks <PERCENT>50 percent</PERCENT>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-usa-markets-2015.html,54a392887988102761d6d2aa,null,"{main:After <DATE>2014<\/DATE>'s Party, Investors <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Stock Market May Face Hangover,print_headline:After <DATE>2014<\/DATE>'s Party, Investors <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Stock Market May Face Hangover}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
Revelers ringing year week watch day's hangover. Investors experience similar feeling early <DATE>2015</DATE> two-year run propelled <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> stocks <PERCENT>50 percent</PERCENT>.,null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T01:04:37Z,[],985,Revelers ringing year week watch day's hangover. Investors experience similar feeling early <DATE>2015</DATE> two-year run propelled <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> stocks <PERCENT>50 percent</PERCENT>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-usa-markets-2015-analysis.html,54a392887988102761d6d2a9,null,"{main:After <DATE>2014<\/DATE>'s Party, Investors <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Stock Market May Face Hangover,print_headline:After <DATE>2014<\/DATE>'s Party, Investors <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Stock Market May Face Hangover}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Next signalled brighter prospects British retailers <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> solid rise Christmas sales, online, resorting discounting shopping streets.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T03:17:56Z,[],636,"Next signalled brighter prospects British retailers <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> solid rise Christmas sales, online, resorting discounting shopping streets.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/business/30reuters-next-uk-results.html,54a25ff57988104803cc8a00,null,"{main:Next Has Solid Christmas Without Cutting Prices,print_headline:Next Has Solid Christmas Without Cutting Prices}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"In classroom construction firm <ORGANIZATION>Larsen &amp; Toubro</ORGANIZATION>'s training centre Indian city <LOCATION>Mumbai</LOCATION>, instructor lifts tool shows students: Clawhandle, tells.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-29T16:29:26Z,[],811,"In classroom construction firm <ORGANIZATION>Larsen &amp; Toubro</ORGANIZATION>'s training centre Indian city <LOCATION>Mumbai</LOCATION>, instructor lifts tool shows students: Clawhandle, tells.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/29/world/asia/29reuters-india-workers.html,54a1c8917988104803cc8890,Asia Pacific,"{main:Help Wanted-India's 'Make <LOCATION>India<\/LOCATION>' Drive Lacks Skilled Labour,print_headline:Help Wanted-India's 'Make <LOCATION>India<\/LOCATION>' Drive Lacks Skilled Labour}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The Japanese company said the reorganization is meant “to centralize and speed up the decision-making process, and to step up handling” of the recalls.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-24T05:17:38Z,[],320,"The Japanese company said the reorganization is meant “to centralize and speed up the decision-making process, and to step up handling” of the recalls.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/24/world/asia/ap-as-japan-airbag-recalls.html,549a93067988102d96d567c7,Asia Pacific,"{main:Air Bag Maker Takata Shuffles Top Management,print_headline:Air Bag Maker Takata Shuffles Top Management}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Between <DATE>2003</DATE> and <DATE>2012</DATE>, <MONEY>$6.6 trillion</MONEY> was secretly and illegally funneled out of developing and emerging economies by entities that may have been involved in crime, corruption and tax evasion, according to one study.",null,"[{name:glocations,rank:1,value:China},{name:glocations,rank:2,value:United States},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:International Monetary Fund},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:World Trade Organization},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Frauds Swindling},{name:subject,rank:2,value:International Trade World Market},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Tax Evasion}]",World,"Between <DATE>2003</DATE> and <DATE>2012</DATE>, <MONEY>$6.6 trillion</MONEY> was secretly and illegally funneled out of developing and emerging economies by entities that may have been involved in crime, corruption and tax evasion, according to one study.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-23T21:45:01Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/23/world/23sino-BAKER/23sino-BAKER-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/23/world/23sino-BAKER/23sino-BAKER-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/23/world/23sino-BAKER/23sino-BAKER-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:840},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/23/world/23sino-BAKER/23sino-BAKER-articleLarge.jpg,height:840},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/23/world/23sino-BAKER/23sino-BAKER-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/23/world/23sino-BAKER/23sino-BAKER-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",933,null,Blog,http://sinosphere.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/23/q-and-a-raymond-w-baker-on-financial-fraud-in-china/,549a28d77988102d96d55c73,Asia Pacific,"{main:Q. A.: <PERSON>Raymond W. Baker<\/PERSON> Financial Fraud <LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION>,kicker:Sinosphere}","{original:By <PERSON>DAVID BARBOZA<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:David,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BARBOZA}]}",blogpost
<PERSON>Judith Rodin Rockefeller</PERSON> Foundation strength courage helped make good leader.,,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Executives Management Theory},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Rodin<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Judith<\/PERSON> S},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Rockefeller Foundation},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Philanthropy}]",Business Day,null,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-22T20:40:00Z,[],1155,<PERSON>Judith Rodin Rockefeller</PERSON> Foundation strength courage helped make good leader.,Question,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/22/business/international/a-risk-taker-who-refused-to-play-the-game.html,54978b937988104a1e0de6b9,International Business,"{content_kicker:Global Manager,main:A Risk Taker Who Refused Play Game,print_headline:A Risk Taker Who Refused Play Game,kicker:Global Manager}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>SONIA KOLESNIKOV-JESSOP<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Sonia,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:KOLESNIKOV-JESSOP}]}",article
"CNP Assurances <DATE>Monday</DATE> selling <ORGANIZATION>Barclays Bank</ORGANIZATION> <PERCENT>50 percent</PERCENT> stake <ORGANIZATION>CNP Barclays Vida Y Pensiones CNP BVP</ORGANIZATION>, <MONEY>453 million euros 356 million pounds</MONEY> including special dividend.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-22T12:06:47Z,[],72,"CNP Assurances <DATE>Monday</DATE> selling <ORGANIZATION>Barclays Bank</ORGANIZATION> <PERCENT>50 percent</PERCENT> stake <ORGANIZATION>CNP Barclays Vida Y Pensiones CNP BVP</ORGANIZATION>, <MONEY>453 million euros 356 million pounds</MONEY> including special dividend.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/22/business/22reuters-cnp-assurances-barclays-bvp.html,54984fe6798810035238e548,null,"{main:CNP Assurances Sells to Barclays Its Stake in <ORGANIZATION>BVP<\/ORGANIZATION> for <MONEY>$555 Million<\/MONEY>,print_headline:CNP Assurances Sells to Barclays Its Stake in <ORGANIZATION>BVP<\/ORGANIZATION> for <MONEY>$555 Million<\/MONEY>}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
When <PERSON>Balfour Beatty</PERSON> needed chief executive called turnaround specialist <PERSON>Leo Quinn</PERSON> revive business string profit warnings plunging share price left vulnerable circling predators.,null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-22T07:18:51Z,[],626,When <PERSON>Balfour Beatty</PERSON> needed chief executive called turnaround specialist <PERSON>Leo Quinn</PERSON> revive business string profit warnings plunging share price left vulnerable circling predators.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/22/business/22reuters-balfour-beatty-ceo-quinn.html,54980c617988104a1e0df26b,null,"{main:Balfour Beatty Pins Hopes Turnaround King Lift Fortunes,print_headline:Balfour Beatty Pins Hopes Turnaround King Lift Fortunes}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
