snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
<ORGANIZATION>Ambac Assurance Corp</ORGANIZATION> sued <ORGANIZATION>Bank of America Corp</ORGANIZATION> to recoup <MONEY>hundreds of millions of dollars</MONEY> of losses from insuring roughly <MONEY>$1.68 billion</MONEY> of securities backed at least in part by risky mortgages from the bank's <ORGANIZATION>Countrywide Home Loans</ORGANIZATION> unit.,null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T11:40:22Z,[],383,<ORGANIZATION>Ambac Assurance Corp</ORGANIZATION> sued <ORGANIZATION>Bank of America Corp</ORGANIZATION> to recoup <MONEY>hundreds of millions of dollars</MONEY> of losses from insuring roughly <MONEY>$1.68 billion</MONEY> of securities backed at least in part by risky mortgages from the bank's <ORGANIZATION>Countrywide Home Loans</ORGANIZATION> unit.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-bankofamerica-ambac-lawsuit.html,54a427987988102761d6e743,null,"{main:Ambac Sues Bank America Over Countrywide Mortgage Bonds,print_headline:Ambac Sues Bank America Over Countrywide Mortgage Bonds}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The global fast-food chain filed public tortured trappings served technology stocks., notes J.ffrey <ORGANIZATION>Goldfarb Reuters Breakingviews</ORGANIZATION>.",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Meyer<\/PERSON>, Danny},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:<ORGANIZATION>Leonard Green & Partners<\/ORGANIZATION>},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:Shake Shack},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Fast Food Industry},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Initial Public Offerings}]",Business Day,"The global fast-food chain filed public tortured trappings served technology stocks., notes <PERSON>Jeffrey Goldfarb Reuters Breakingviews</PERSON>.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-30T14:00:40Z,[],400,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/shake-shack-i-p-o-offers-healthy-profits-and-curious-metrics/,54a2f6ac7988102761d6cea1,Dealbook,"{main:Shake Shack I.P.O. Offers Healthy Profits Curious Metrics,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>JEFFREY GOLDFARB<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Jeffrey,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:GOLDFARB}]}",blogpost
"Bondholders in the casino company’s biggest unit back a bankruptcy that its parent’s merger with an affiliate could fund, says <PERSON>Quentin Webb</PERSON> of <ORGANIZATION>Reuters Breakingviews</ORGANIZATION>.",null,"[{name:organizations,rank:1,value:Caesars Entertainment Corporation},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Casinos},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Credit Debt}]",Business Day,"Bondholders in the casino company’s biggest unit back a bankruptcy that its parent’s merger with an affiliate could fund, says <PERSON>Quentin Webb</PERSON> of <ORGANIZATION>Reuters Breakingviews</ORGANIZATION>.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-22T14:13:11Z,[],403,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/22/as-caesars-deals-a-showdown-in-las-vegas-awaits/,54986da5798810035238e599,Dealbook,"{main:As Caesars Deals, Showdown Las Vegas Awaits,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>QUENTIN WEBB<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Quentin,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:WEBB}]}",blogpost
Many loans aimed higher net worth.,7,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Mortgages},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Banking Financial Institutions}]",Real Estate,"<PERSON>Lisa Prevost</PERSON> Mortgages column explains differences 'piggyback loans' offered housing crash, allowed borrowers buy homes money down; difficult qualify aimed higher-net-worth buyers; graph mortgages rates <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> region.",The New York Times,[],RealEstate,2014-12-21T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/21/realestate/21mort-graphic/21mort-graphic-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/21/realestate/21mort-graphic/21mort-graphic-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/21/realestate/21mort-graphic/21mort-graphic-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:302},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/21/realestate/21mort-graphic/21mort-graphic-articleLarge.jpg,height:302},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/21/realestate/21mort-graphic/21mort-graphic-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/21/realestate/21mort-graphic/21mort-graphic-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",598,Many loans aimed higher net worth.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/21/realestate/piggyback-loans-revisited.html,54948e047988107c4680056d,null,"{content_kicker:Mortgages,main:&#8216;Piggyback&#8217; Loans Revisited,print_headline:‘Piggyback’ Loans Revisited,kicker:Mortgages}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>LISA PREVOST<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Lisa,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:PREVOST}]}",article
"Thai Union’s ’ <MONEY>$1.51 billion</MONEY> purchase of <ORGANIZATION>Bumble Bee Seafoods</ORGANIZATION> shows a focused, low-key approach to acquisitions that has lessons for others, says <ORGANIZATION>Una Galani of Reuters Breakingviews</ORGANIZATION>.",null,"[{name:organizations,rank:1,value:<ORGANIZATION>Bumble Bee Seafoods Inc<\/ORGANIZATION>},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:Lion Capital Holdings},{name:organizations,rank:3,value:Thai Union Frozen Products PCI},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Mergers, Acquisitions Divestitures}]",Business Day,"Thai Union’s ’ <MONEY>$1.51 billion</MONEY> purchase of <ORGANIZATION>Bumble Bee Seafoods</ORGANIZATION> shows a focused, low-key approach to acquisitions that has lessons for others, says <ORGANIZATION>Una Galani of Reuters Breakingviews</ORGANIZATION>.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-19T12:58:34Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/19/business/dealbook/dbpix-tuna/dbpix-tuna-thumbWide-v2.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/19/business/dealbook/dbpix-tuna/dbpix-tuna-thumbWide-v2.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/19/business/dealbook/dbpix-tuna/dbpix-tuna-articleLarge-v2.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/19/business/dealbook/dbpix-tuna/dbpix-tuna-articleLarge-v2.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/19/business/dealbook/dbpix-tuna/dbpix-tuna-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/19/business/dealbook/dbpix-tuna/dbpix-tuna-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",355,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/19/a-food-deal-that-swims-against-the-tide/,549467ce7988107c46800492,Dealbook,"{main:A Food Deal That Swims Against Tide,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By UNA GALANI,person:[{firstname:Una,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:GALANI}]}",blogpost
Air France-KLM shares plunged <PERCENT>8 percent</PERCENT> wake airline's warning weak demand long-haul routes factors wipe hundreds millions profits year.,null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-19T11:47:15Z,[],131,Air France-KLM shares plunged <PERCENT>8 percent</PERCENT> wake airline's warning weak demand long-haul routes factors wipe hundreds millions profits year.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/19/world/europe/ap-eu-france-air-france-klm.html,5494574779881048d26b333e,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:Air France-KLM Stock Drops Profit Warning,print_headline:Air France-KLM Stock Drops Profit Warning}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
The deal add largest canned seafood producer <LOCATION>North America</LOCATION> portfolio brands includes Chicken Sea.,null,"[{name:organizations,rank:1,value:<ORGANIZATION>Bumble Bee Seafoods Inc<\/ORGANIZATION>},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:Lion Capital Holdings},{name:organizations,rank:3,value:Thai Union Frozen Products PCI},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Mergers, Acquisitions Divestitures}]",Business Day,The deal add largest canned seafood producer <LOCATION>North America</LOCATION> portfolio brands includes Chicken Sea.,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-19T08:30:33Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/19/business/dealbook/dbpix-tuna/dbpix-tuna-thumbWide-v2.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/19/business/dealbook/dbpix-tuna/dbpix-tuna-thumbWide-v2.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/19/business/dealbook/dbpix-tuna/dbpix-tuna-articleLarge-v2.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/19/business/dealbook/dbpix-tuna/dbpix-tuna-articleLarge-v2.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/19/business/dealbook/dbpix-tuna/dbpix-tuna-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/19/business/dealbook/dbpix-tuna/dbpix-tuna-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",243,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/19/thai-union-frozen-to-buy-bumble-bee-for-1-5-billion/,5494289d79881048d26b32a8,Dealbook,"{main:Thai Union Frozen to Buy <ORGANIZATION>Bumble Bee<\/ORGANIZATION> for <MONEY>$1.5 Billion<\/MONEY>,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By DEALBOOK,person:[{firstname:Dealbook,role:reported,organization:,rank:1}]}",blogpost
"The deal will allow <ORGANIZATION>Visteon</ORGANIZATION> to exit the company nearly 30 years after it was founded as a joint venture between <ORGANIZATION>Visteon</ORGANIZATION>’s former parent, <ORGANIZATION>Ford Motor</ORGANIZATION>, and the <ORGANIZATION>Mando Machinery Corporation</ORGANIZATION>.",null,"[{name:organizations,rank:1,value:Visteon Automotive Systems},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Air Conditioning},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Automobiles}]",Business Day,"The deal will allow <ORGANIZATION>Visteon</ORGANIZATION> to exit the company nearly 30 years after it was founded as a joint venture between <ORGANIZATION>Visteon</ORGANIZATION>’s former parent, <ORGANIZATION>Ford Motor</ORGANIZATION>, and the <ORGANIZATION>Mando Machinery Corporation</ORGANIZATION>.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-17T10:09:58Z,[],268,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/17/visteon-to-sell-its-stake-in-air-conditioning-venture-for-3-6-billion/,54919ece79881035eeb2f1e0,Dealbook,"{main:Visteon to Sell Its Stake in Air-Conditioning Venture for <MONEY>$3.6 Billion<\/MONEY>,print_headline:Selling Stake,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>MICHAEL J. DE<\/PERSON> LA MERCED,person:[{firstname:Michael,role:reported,organization:,middlename:J.,rank:1,lastname:DE LA MERCED}]}",blogpost
Solar firm <ORGANIZATION>REC Silicon</ORGANIZATION> expected <DATE>fourth-quarter</DATE> core earnings lower previous quarter ongoing trade dispute <LOCATION>United States China</LOCATION> hurt profits cash flow short term.,null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-17T02:09:24Z,[],154,Solar firm <ORGANIZATION>REC Silicon</ORGANIZATION> expected <DATE>fourth-quarter</DATE> core earnings lower previous quarter ongoing trade dispute <LOCATION>United States China</LOCATION> hurt profits cash flow short term.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/17/business/17reuters-rec-results-preliminary.html,54912c6279881035eeb2f08e,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Norway<\/LOCATION>'s REC Silicon Sees Negative Impact From <LOCATION>China U.S.<\/LOCATION> Dispute,print_headline:<LOCATION>Norway<\/LOCATION>'s REC Silicon Sees Negative Impact From <LOCATION>China U.S.<\/LOCATION> Dispute}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<ORGANIZATION>InterContinental Hotels Group</ORGANIZATION>, one of the world's largest hoteliers, has agreed to buy U.S.-focused <ORGANIZATION>Kimpton Hotels &amp; Restaurants</ORGANIZATION> for <MONEY>$430 million</MONEY> &#163;274.87 million to boost its exposure to the faster-growing boutique hotel sector.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-16T02:22:13Z,[],220,"<ORGANIZATION>InterContinental Hotels Group</ORGANIZATION>, one of the world's largest hoteliers, has agreed to buy U.S.-focused <ORGANIZATION>Kimpton Hotels &amp; Restaurants</ORGANIZATION> for <MONEY>$430 million</MONEY> &#163;274.87 million to boost its exposure to the faster-growing boutique hotel sector. ",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/16/business/16reuters-kimton-m-a-intercontinental.html,548fde64798810619765ef06,null,"{main:IHG Agrees <MONEY>$430 Million<\/MONEY> <ORGANIZATION>Acquisition of Boutique Kimpton<\/ORGANIZATION> Hotels,print_headline:IHG Agrees <MONEY>$430 Million<\/MONEY> <ORGANIZATION>Acquisition of Boutique Kimpton<\/ORGANIZATION> Hotels}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
