snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
Offbeat episodic account of the circulation of a <MONEY>$20</MONEY> bill into the hands of a potpourri of people.,null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T13:20:27Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-high-roller-the-stu-ungar-story/video-high-roller-the-stu-ungar-story-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-high-roller-the-stu-ungar-story/video-high-roller-the-stu-ungar-story-thumbW.de.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-high-roller-the-stu-ungar-story/video-high-roller-the-stu-ungar-story-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-high-roller-the-stu-ungar-story/video-high-roller-the-stu-ungar-story-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-high-roller-the-stu-ungar-story/video-high-roller-the-stu-ungar-story-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-high-roller-the-stu-ungar-story/video-high-roller-the-stu-ungar-story-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",18,Offbeat episodic account of the circulation of a <MONEY>$20</MONEY> bill into the hands of a potpourri of people.,Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003332477/high-roller-the-stu-ungar-story.html,54a590167988102023c94284,null,{"main":"High Roller: The <PERSON>Stu Ungar<\/PERSON> Story"},"{original:New Line Cinema,person:[]}",multimedia
"The family <PERSON>Rolando Sarraff Trujillo</PERSON> hear, suspicion extensively debriefed authorities move back society.",6,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Cuba<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Sarraff Trujillo<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Rolando<\/PERSON>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Espionage Intelligence Services},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Central Intelligence Agency},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Prisons Prisoners},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:6,value:United States},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:United States International Relations}]",World,"<PERSON>Rolando Sarraff Trujillo</PERSON>, intelligence officer freed prisoner exchange <LOCATION>Cuba</LOCATION>, contacted family released whereabouts unknown; lengthy debriefing process common cases his; American officials held captive free make phone calls.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/19/world/01spy/19SPY-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/19/world/01spy/19SPY-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/19/world/01spy/19SPY-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/19/world/01spy/19SPY-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",643,"The family <PERSON>Rolando Sarraff Trujillo</PERSON> hear, suspicion extensively debriefed authorities move back society.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/world/americas/whereabouts-of-us-spy-released-in-cuba-deal-are-unknown.html,54a4bcff79881011bed2a4ff,Americas,"{main:Whereabouts <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Spy Released <LOCATION>Cuba<\/LOCATION> Deal Are Unknown,print_headline:Whereabouts <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Spy Released <LOCATION>Cuba<\/LOCATION> Deal Are Unknown}","{contributor:<PERSON>Mark Mazzetti<\/PERSON> contributed reporting <LOCATION>Washington<\/LOCATION>, <PERSON>Michael S. Schmidt Kailua<\/PERSON>, <LOCATION>Hawaii<\/LOCATION>.,original:By <PERSON>FRANCES ROBLES<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Frances,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:ROBLES}]}",article
"New Year’s Eve can ring in healthful resolutions and new beginnings, but it can also be a risk factor for accidents, death and other dangers.",null,"[{name:subject,rank:1,value:Beans},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Champagne Wine},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Christmas},{name:subject,rank:4,value:Cork},{name:subject,rank:5,value:Deaths Fatalities},{name:subject,rank:6,value:Drunken Reckless Driving},{name:subject,rank:7,value:New Year},{name:subject,rank:8,value:Traffic Accidents Safety}]",Health,"New Year’s Eve can ring in healthful resolutions and new beginnings, but it can also be a risk factor for accidents, death and other dangers.",The New York Times,[],Science,2014-12-31T15:44:49Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/health/31well_champagne/31well_champagne-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/health/31well_champagne/31well_champagne-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/health/31well_champagne/31well_champagne-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/health/31well_champagne/31well_champagne-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/health/31well_champagne/31well_champagne-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/health/31well_champagne/31well_champagne-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1126,null,Blog,http://well.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/5-things-to-know-about-new-years-eve/,54a4609579881011bed28fda,null,"{main:5 Things Know About New Year's Eve,kicker:Well}","{original:By <PERSON>TARA PARKER-POPE<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Tara,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:PARKER-POPE}]}",blogpost
Taking stock businesses face challenges coming year.,1,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Television},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:11,value:<ORGANIZATION>Viacom Inc<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:12,value:<ORGANIZATION>Time Inc.<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:13,value:Appointments Executive Changes},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:14,value:Mergers, Acquisitions Divestitures},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:15,value:Cable Television},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Movies},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:News News Media},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:4,value:<PERSON>Dauman<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Philippe<\/PERSON> P},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:5,value:Turness, <PERSON>Deborah<\/PERSON> M},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:6,value:<PERSON>Thompson<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Mark John 1957<\/PERSON>-},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:7,value:Ripp, <PERSON>Joseph<\/PERSON> A},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:8,value:NBC News},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:9,value:Ratings Audience Measurement},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:10,value:New York Times}]",Business Day,"<PERSON>David Carr</PERSON> The Media Equation column presents Hot Seat list <DATE>2015</DATE>, companies, businesses executives face major challenges; includes movie studios, <ORGANIZATION>NBC News</ORGANIZATION> president <PERSON>Deborah Turness</PERSON>, <ORGANIZATION>Viacom</ORGANIZATION> chief executive <PERSON>Philippe Dauman</PERSON>, <ORGANIZATION>New York Times Company</ORGANIZATION> president <ORGANIZATION>Mark Thompson Time Inc.chief</ORGANIZATION> executive <PERSON>Joseph Ripp</PERSON>.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-29T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/29/business/29carr-combo/29carr-combo-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/business/29carr-combo/29carr-combo-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/29/business/29carr-combo/29carr-combo-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/business/29carr-combo/29carr-combo-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/29/business/29carr-combo/29carr-combo-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/business/29carr-combo/29carr-combo-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1495,Taking stock businesses face challenges coming year.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/29/business/media/media-companies-and-executives-on-the-hot-seat-in-2015.html,54a0b8297988101f98e3ee83,Media,"{content_kicker:The Media Equation,main:Media Companies Executives Hot Seat 2015,print_headline:On Hot Seat 2015,kicker:The Media Equation}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>DAVID CARR<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:David,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:CARR}]}",article
"Stained-glass ceiling vaults disappeared 80 years grime back display Sterling Memorial Library&#8217;s entrance hall, nave.",14,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:<ORGANIZATION>Yale University<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Libraries Librarians},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Colleges Universities},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Restoration Renovation}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"<ORGANIZATION>Yale University</ORGANIZATION>'s <MONEY>$20 million</MONEY> renovation of entrance hall of its Gothic-style <ORGANIZATION>Sterling Memorial Library</ORGANIZATION> has revealed spectacular appearance of building when it first opened in <DATE>1930</DATE>; hall, once just a passageway, has been transformed into stunning study hall.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-27T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/27/nyregion/27YALE1/27YALE1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/nyregion/27YALE1/27YALE1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/27/nyregion/27YALE1/27YALE1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/nyregion/27YALE1/27YALE1-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/27/nyregion/27YALE1/27YALE1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/nyregion/27YALE1/27YALE1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",701,"Stained-glass ceiling vaults disappeared 80 years grime back display Sterling Memorial Library&#8217;s entrance hall, nave.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/27/nyregion/yale-university-library-revives-entrance-hall.html,549e15967988105ced788672,null,"{main:A Piece Yale&#8217;s Library Is Brought Back Life,print_headline:A Piece of <ORGANIZATION>Yale<\/ORGANIZATION>’s Library Is Brought Back to Life}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>DAVID W. DUNLAP<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:David,role:reported,organization:,middlename:W.,rank:1,lastname:DUNLAP}]}",article
A tough fair puzzle <PERSON>David Phillips</PERSON>.,null,"[{name:subject,rank:1,value:Crossword Puzzles}]",Crosswords/Games,A tough fair puzzle <PERSON>David Phillips</PERSON>.,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-26T22:00:44Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/26/crosswords/1226trainjpg/1226trainjpg-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/crosswords/1226trainjpg/1226trainjpg-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/26/crosswords/1226trainjpg/1226trainjpg-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/crosswords/1226trainjpg/1226trainjpg-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/26/crosswords/1226trainjpg/1226trainjpg-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/crosswords/1226trainjpg/1226trainjpg-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1075,null,Blog,http://wordplay.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/26/drawn-in-a-forest/,549e211d7988105ced788679,null,"{main:Drawn Forest,kicker:Wordplay}","{original:By <PERSON>DEB AMLEN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Deb,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:AMLEN}]}",blogpost
"Following longstanding tradition, Gramercy Park opened public hour <DATE>Wednesday Christmas</DATE> Eve festivities.",24,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:Gramercy Park <LOCATION>Manhattan<\/LOCATION>, NY},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Christmas},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Parks Other Recreation Areas}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,<PERSON>Sarah Maslin Nir Nocturnalist</PERSON> column; exclusive <LOCATION>Gramercy Park</LOCATION> opens public hour traditional Christmas Eve event.,The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-25T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/25/nyregion/NOCTURNALIST/NOCTURNALIST-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/nyregion/NOCTURNALIST/NOCTURNALIST-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/25/nyregion/NOCTURNALIST/NOCTURNALIST-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/nyregion/NOCTURNALIST/NOCTURNALIST-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/25/nyregion/NOCTURNALIST/NOCTURNALIST-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/nyregion/NOCTURNALIST/NOCTURNALIST-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",753,"Following longstanding tradition, Gramercy Park opened public hour <DATE>Wednesday Christmas</DATE> Eve festivities.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/25/nyregion/inside-gramercy-parks-gates-one-night-less-silent-than-the-other-364.html,549b816879881003066910bd,null,"{content_kicker:Nocturnalist,main:Inside Gramercy Park’s Gates, One Night Less Silent Than the Other 364,print_headline:Inside Gramercy Gates, One Night Less Silent Than Other 364,kicker:Nocturnalist}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>SARAH MASLIN<\/PERSON> NIR,person:[{firstname:Sarah,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Maslin,rank:1,lastname:NIR}]}",article
"An American man was charged in a Ugandan court for forging currency of more than <MONEY>$190,000</MONEY> found in his Ugandan home, according to a charge sheet by a magistrate court in <LOCATION>Kampala</LOCATION>.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-23T11:21:48Z,[],257,"An American man was charged in a Ugandan court for forging currency of more than <MONEY>$190,000</MONEY> found in his Ugandan home, according to a charge sheet by a magistrate court in <LOCATION>Kampala</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/23/world/africa/ap-af-uganda-american-charged.html,549996e7798810035238e889,<LOCATION>Africa</LOCATION>,"{main:American Charged Uganda Counterfeit Dollars,print_headline:American Charged Uganda Counterfeit Dollars}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
An independent panel <DATE>Monday</DATE> clear evidence reports Asahi newspaper quoting fabricated witness accounts led international criticism <LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION>'s Asian women wartime military brothels.,null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-22T09:24:06Z,[],364,An independent panel <DATE>Monday</DATE> clear evidence reports Asahi newspaper quoting fabricated witness accounts led international criticism <LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION>'s Asian women wartime military brothels.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/22/world/asia/ap-as-japan-comfort-women-asahi-.html,549829ef7988104a1e0df507,Asia Pacific,"{main:Panel: Asahi Not Blame Criticism <LOCATION>Japan<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:Panel: Asahi Not Blame Criticism <LOCATION>Japan<\/LOCATION>}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Good morning. Here Daily Clip Report, collection articles The Times media email morning senior executives newsroom editors. The email produced <ORGANIZATION>Corporate Communications Department</ORGANIZATION> The Times.",null,[],false,"Good morning. Here Daily Clip Report, collection articles The Times media email morning senior executives newsroom editors. The email produced <ORGANIZATION>Corporate Communications Department</ORGANIZATION> The Times.",The New York Times,[],null,2014-12-18T08:25:14Z,[],221,null,Blog,http://www.nytimes.com/times-insider/2014/12/18/daily-clip-report-85/,5492d68079881005eed9d52a,false,"{main:Daily Clip Report,kicker:Times Insider}","{original:By <PERSON>JORDAN COHEN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Jordan,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:COHEN}]}",blogpost
