snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Gambling revenue <LOCATION>Macau</LOCATION>, world's biggest gaming hub, fell year time casinos liberalised <DATE>2001</DATE>, <LOCATION>Beijing</LOCATION> campaign conspicuous spending public officials led decline wealthy players.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T23:53:20Z,[],263,"Gambling revenue <LOCATION>Macau</LOCATION>, world's biggest gaming hub, fell year time casinos liberalised <DATE>2001</DATE>, <LOCATION>Beijing</LOCATION> campaign conspicuous spending public officials led decline wealthy players.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-macau-gambling-revenue.html,54a624b07988102023c954d7,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Macau<\/LOCATION> Annual Gambling Revenue Falls First Time Since Casino Liberalisation,print_headline:<LOCATION>Macau<\/LOCATION> Annual Gambling Revenue Falls First Time Since Casino Liberalisation}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"A senior Chinese diplomat sacked investigation suspected corruption, foreign ministry <DATE>Friday</DATE>, time top diplomat fallen victim sweeping campaign graft.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T23:21:45Z,[],273,"A senior Chinese diplomat sacked investigation suspected corruption, foreign ministry <DATE>Friday</DATE>, time top diplomat fallen victim sweeping campaign graft.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/world/asia/01reuters-china-corruption.html,54a61da47988102023c9543f,Asia Pacific,"{main:Senior Chinese Diplomat Sacked Corruption,print_headline:Senior Chinese Diplomat Sacked Corruption}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
<PERSON>Woody Johnson</PERSON>'s search <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> Jets' coach general manager <LOCATION>Seattle</LOCATION>.,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T22:59:30Z,[],500,<PERSON>Woody Johnson</PERSON>'s search <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> Jets' coach general manager <LOCATION>Seattle</LOCATION>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/sports/football/ap-fbn-jets-search.html,54a6180c7988102023c953c5,Pro Football,"{main:Jets <ORGANIZATION>Seattle Interview Coach<\/ORGANIZATION> G.M. Jobs,print_headline:Jets <ORGANIZATION>Seattle Interview Coach<\/ORGANIZATION>, <ORGANIZATION>GM<\/ORGANIZATION> Jobs}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Rudy Gay 21 points, rebounds assists, struggling <LOCATION>Sacramento Kings</LOCATION> handed <ORGANIZATION>Minnesota Timberwolves</ORGANIZATION> 10th straight loss 110-107 victory <DATE>Thursday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T22:45:02Z,[],492,"Rudy Gay 21 points, rebounds assists, struggling <LOCATION>Sacramento Kings</LOCATION> handed <ORGANIZATION>Minnesota Timberwolves</ORGANIZATION> 10th straight loss 110-107 victory <DATE>Thursday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/sports/basketball/ap-bkn-kings-timberwolves.html,54a615377988102023c95384,Pro Basketball,"{main:Cousins, Kings Survive Close One <LOCATION>Minnesota<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:Cousins, Kings Survive Close One <LOCATION>Minnesota<\/LOCATION>}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<PERSON>Derrick Rose</PERSON> scored 13 17 points <DATE>fourth quarter</DATE>, <ORGANIZATION>Chicago Bulls</ORGANIZATION> beat Denver Nuggets 106-101 <DATE>Thursday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T22:41:44Z,[],503,"<PERSON>Derrick Rose</PERSON> scored 13 17 points <DATE>fourth quarter</DATE>, <ORGANIZATION>Chicago Bulls</ORGANIZATION> beat Denver Nuggets 106-101 <DATE>Thursday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/sports/basketball/ap-bkn-nuggets-bulls.html,54a613cc7988102023c9536d,Pro Basketball,"{main:Rose Leads Bulls Over Nuggets 106-101,print_headline:Rose Leads Bulls Over Nuggets 106-101}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Starting 2015 themelesses, <PERSON>David Steinberg</PERSON>.",null,"[{name:subject,rank:1,value:Crossword Puzzles}]",Crosswords/Games,"Starting 2015 themelesses, <PERSON>David Steinberg</PERSON>.",The New York Times,[],Business,2015-01-01T22:00:33Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/crosswords/0101cardinaljpg/0101cardinaljpg-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/crosswords/0101cardinaljpg/0101cardinaljpg-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/crosswords/0101cardinaljpg/0101cardinaljpg-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:399},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/crosswords/0101cardinaljpg/0101cardinaljpg-articleLarge.jpg,height:399},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/crosswords/0101cardinaljpg/0101cardinaljpg-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/crosswords/0101cardinaljpg/0101cardinaljpg-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",711,null,Blog,http://wordplay.blogs.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/burning-sensation/,54a60a407988102023c9529b,null,"{main:Burning Sensation,kicker:Wordplay}","{original:By <PERSON>DEB AMLEN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Deb,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:AMLEN}]}",blogpost
"Chinese property developer <ORGANIZATION>Kaisa Group Holdings</ORGANIZATION> said it had failed to repay a <MONEY>HK$400 million 33 million pounds</MONEY> loan and warned it may default on more debt, the latest problem to hit the firm amid a downturn in the real estate sector.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T21:46:17Z,[],322,"Chinese property developer <ORGANIZATION>Kaisa Group Holdings</ORGANIZATION> said it had failed to repay a <MONEY>HK$400 million 33 million pounds</MONEY> loan and warned it may default on more debt, the latest problem to hit the firm amid a downturn in the real estate sector.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-china-kaisa-group-debt.html,54a607197988102023c95255,null,"{main:<LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION> Developer Kaisa Says Fails to Repay <MONEY>$51 Mln<\/MONEY> Loan, May Default on Others,print_headline:<LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION> Developer Kaisa Says Fails to Repay <MONEY>$51 Mln<\/MONEY> Loan, May Default on Others}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Reaction death three-term Gov. <PERSON>Mario Cuomo</PERSON>, died <DATE>Thursday</DATE> hours son, <PERSON>Andrew</PERSON>, sworn term governor.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T21:41:09Z,[],744,"Reaction death three-term Gov. <PERSON>Mario Cuomo</PERSON>, died <DATE>Thursday</DATE> hours son, <PERSON>Andrew</PERSON>, sworn term governor.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/us/ap-us-obit-mario-cuomo-reaction.html,54a605bb7988102023c95235,null,"{main:What's Being Said About <PERSON>Mario Cuomo<\/PERSON>'s Death,print_headline:What's Being Said About <PERSON>Mario Cuomo<\/PERSON>'s Death}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
<PERSON>Andrew Cuomo</PERSON> sworn term governor <DATE>Thursday</DATE> hours father died.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T21:20:05Z,[],716,<PERSON>Andrew Cuomo</PERSON> sworn term governor <DATE>Thursday</DATE> hours father died.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/us/ap-us-cuomo-inauguration.html,54a600e37988102023c951c6,null,"{main:Cuomo Begins 2nd Term Day His Father Dies,print_headline:Cuomo Begins 2nd Term Day His Father Dies}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Jameis Winston evaded <LOCATION>Oregon</LOCATION> tacklers wound throw, feet slipped Rose Bowl turf. While failed stay upright, <ORGANIZATION>Florida State</ORGANIZATION>'s star quarterback lost ball backward head comical arc,...",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T21:01:27Z,[],761,"Jameis Winston evaded <LOCATION>Oregon</LOCATION> tacklers wound throw, feet slipped Rose Bowl turf. While failed stay upright, <ORGANIZATION>Florida State</ORGANIZATION>'s star quarterback lost ball backward head comical arc, <LOCATION>Tony Washington</LOCATION> hurdled scoop score.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/sports/ncaafootball/ap-fbc-t25-rose-bowl-winstons-nightmare.html,54a5fc967988102023c95163,College Football,"{main:Winston's Woes Part Noles' Streak-Ending Loss,print_headline:Winston's Woes Part Noles' Streak-Ending Loss}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
