snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"We wrestle underlying, unresolved issues: police-community relations, functional bias policing, disparities force.",,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Police Brutality, Misconduct Shootings},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Demonstrations, Protests Riots},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Attacks Police},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:United States Politics Government},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:5,value:Brinsley, Ismaaiyl Abdullah},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:6,value:Liu, Wenjian 1982-2014},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:7,value:Ramos, Rafael 1974-2014},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:8,value:<PERSON>Byrne<\/PERSON>, Edward R 1966-88}]",Opinion,null,The New York Times,[],Editorial,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/11/01/opinion/blow-circular/blow-circular-thumbWide-v2.png},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/11/01/opinion/blow-circular/blow-circular-thumbWide-v2.png,height:126},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/11/01/opinion/blow-circular/blow-circular-thumbStandard-v2.png,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/11/01/opinion/blow-circular/blow-circular-thumbStandard-v2.png,height:75}]",1949,"We wrestle underlying, unresolved issues: police-community relations, functional bias policing, disparities force.",Op-Ed,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/opinion/charles-m-blow-look-back-to-move-forward.html,54a4beb479881011bed2a567,null,"{content_kicker:Op-Ed Columnist,main:Look Back Move Forward,kicker:Op-Ed Columnist}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>CHARLES M.<\/PERSON> BLOW,person:[{firstname:Charles,role:reported,organization:,rank:1}]}",article
Chief Justice <PERSON>John G. Roberts Jr.</PERSON> &#8220;as <DATE>2016</DATE>&#8221; annual year-end report condition federal judiciary.,14,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:Supreme Court US},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Roberts<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>John<\/PERSON> G Jr},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Computers Internet},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Archives Records}]",<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,"Supreme Court Chief Justice <PERSON>John G Roberts</PERSON> Jr, annual year-end report state federal judiciary, announces court make briefs filings electronically, early <DATE>2016</DATE>.",The New York Times,[],National,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/us/SCOTUS/SCOTUS-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/us/SCOTUS/SCOTUS-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/us/SCOTUS/SCOTUS-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:900},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/us/SCOTUS/SCOTUS-articleLarge.jpg,height:900},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/us/SCOTUS/SCOTUS-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/us/SCOTUS/SCOTUS-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",615,Chief Justice <PERSON>John G. Roberts Jr.</PERSON> &#8220;as <DATE>2016</DATE>&#8221; annual year-end report condition federal judiciary.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/us/politics/supreme-court-plans-to-provide-briefs-and-filings-electronically.html,54a4803a79881011bed29715,Politics,"{main:Supreme Court, Big Leap, Plans Put Filings Online,print_headline:High Court, Big Leap, Plans Put Filings Online}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ADAM LIPTAK<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Adam,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:LIPTAK}]}",article
"When upscale, happily unmarried <LOCATION>San Francisco</LOCATION> couple <PERSON>Kate Brad</PERSON> find socked fog Christmas morning, exotic vacation plans morph family-centric holiday,, gleefully avoided.  Out obligation-an",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2014-12-31T13:01:51Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-four-christmases/video-four-christmases-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-four-christmases/video-four-christmases-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-four-christmases/video-four-christmases-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-four-christmases/video-four-christmases-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-four-christmases/video-four-christmases-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-four-christmases/video-four-christmases-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",37,"When upscale, happily unmarried <LOCATION>San Francisco</LOCATION> couple <PERSON>Kate Brad</PERSON> find socked fog Christmas morning, exotic vacation plans morph family-centric holiday,, gleefully avoided.  Out obligation-an",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003324932/four-christmases.html,54a43a1579881011bed286a7,null,{"main":"Four Christmases"},"{original:<ORGANIZATION>Warner Bros<\/ORGANIZATION>. Pictures,person:[{firstname:Warner,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Bros}]}",multimedia
"American recording artist <PERSON>Chris Brown</PERSON> canceled New Year's Eve concert <LOCATION>Philippines</LOCATION> minute, reportedly lost passport, organizers <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T10:53:05Z,[],136,"American recording artist <PERSON>Chris Brown</PERSON> canceled New Year's Eve concert <LOCATION>Philippines</LOCATION> minute, reportedly lost passport, organizers <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/world/asia/ap-as-philippines-people-chris-brown.html,54a41c5c7988102761d6e380,Asia Pacific,"{main:<PERSON>Chris Brown<\/PERSON> Cancels Philippine Concert,print_headline:<PERSON>Chris Brown<\/PERSON> Cancels Philippine Concert}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Compensation whistle-blowers, create perverse incentives reward wrongdoing.",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:Birkenfeld, <PERSON>Bradley<\/PERSON> C},{name:persons,rank:2,value:Holder, <PERSON>Eric<\/PERSON> H Jr},{name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Madsen<\/PERSON>, Robert},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:Federal Bureau Investigation},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:Internal Revenue Service},{name:organizations,rank:3,value:Justice Department},{name:organizations,rank:4,value:Securities Exchange Commission},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Classified Information State Secrets},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Ethics Official Misconduct},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Whistle-Blowers}]",Business Day,"Compensation whistle-blowers, create perverse incentives reward wrongdoing.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-30T14:18:26Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/business/Dealprof/Dealprof-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/Dealprof/Dealprof-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/business/Dealprof/Dealprof-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:600},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/Dealprof/Dealprof-articleLarge.jpg,height:600},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/business/Dealprof/<ORGANIZATION>Dealprof-thumbStandard<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/Dealprof/<ORGANIZATION>Dealprof-thumbStandard<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg,height:75}]",1251,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/whistle-blower-awards-lure-wrongdoers-looking-to-score/,54a2fae57988102761d6ceb0,Dealbook,"{main:Whistle-Blower Awards Lure Wrongdoers Looking Score,print_headline:Whistle-Blower Awards Get Results, Also May Lure Wrongdoers,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>STEVEN DAVIDOFF SOLOMON<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Steven,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Davidoff,rank:1,lastname:SOLOMON}]}",blogpost
A team researchers pinpointed Ebola epidemic <LOCATION>West Africa</LOCATION> started &#8212; small boy playing hollowed-out tree infected bats lived.,null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T10:04:23Z,[],545,A team researchers pinpointed Ebola epidemic <LOCATION>West Africa</LOCATION> started &#8212; small boy playing hollowed-out tree infected bats lived.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/world/africa/ap-af-ebola-west-africa.html,54a2bfa77988104803cc8abc,<LOCATION>Africa</LOCATION>,"{main:First Ebola Victim May Have Been Infected Bats,print_headline:First Ebola Victim May Have Been Infected Bats}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Readers react coverage funeral Officer <PERSON>Rafael Ramos</PERSON>, officers killed gunman.",18,"[{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:1,value:Police Department NYC},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Bratton<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>William<\/PERSON> J},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:3,value:Ramos, Rafael 1974-2014},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:4,value:Liu, Wenjian 1982-2014},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:5,value:de Blasio, Bill},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:Patrolmen's Benevolent Assn}]",Opinion,null,The New York Times,[],Letters,2014-12-30T00:00:00Z,[],480,"Readers react coverage funeral Officer <PERSON>Rafael Ramos</PERSON>, officers killed gunman.",Letter,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/opinion/police-funeral-moving-words-and-a-call-for-respect.html,54a1e4da7988104803cc88c7,null,"{content_kicker:Letters,main:Police Funeral: Moving Words, Call Respect,print_headline:Police Funeral: Moving Words, Call Respect,kicker:Letters}",[],article
"For fleeting moment <DATE>spring</DATE>, epidemic sweeping <LOCATION>West Africa</LOCATION> stopped. But opportunity control virus, caused 7,800 deaths, lost.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Ebola Virus},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:11,value:Rollin, Pierre E},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:12,value:Conde, Alpha},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:13,value:Chan, <PERSON>Margaret<\/PERSON>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:14,value:Dahn, Bernice T},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:15,value:<PERSON>Duncan<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Thomas Eric<\/PERSON>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:16,value:Formenty, Pierre},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:17,value:<PERSON>Frieden<\/PERSON>, Thomas R},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:18,value:<PERSON>Johnson Sirleaf<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Ellen<\/PERSON>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:19,value:Spencer, <PERSON>Craig Allen<\/PERSON> <DATE>1981<\/DATE>-},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Epidemics},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:3,value:Africa},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:4,value:Guinea},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:5,value:<LOCATION>Liberia<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:6,value:Sierra Leone},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:7,value:Centers Disease Control Prevention},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:8,value:Doctors Without Borders},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:9,value:Samaritan's Purse},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:10,value:World Health Organization}]",Health,"Ebola epidemic <LOCATION>Africa</LOCATION>, caused 7,800 deaths began, appeared drawing close <DATE>spring</DATE> 2014 brought halt, series response missteps complicating factors; doctors experts failed adequately track disease <DATE>2014</DATE> outbreak differ previous strains catastrophic ways; addition, lack infrastructure resources, local distrust government movement tribal people borders contributed disease's spread.",The New York Times,[],Science,2014-12-30T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/24/world/africa/Ebola_Reconstruct-slide-M8BK/Ebola_Reconstruct-slide-M8BK-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/24/world/africa/Ebola_Reconstruct-slide-M8BK/Ebola_Reconstruct-slide-M8BK-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/24/world/africa/Ebola_Reconstruct-slide-M8BK/Ebola_Reconstruct-slide-M8BK-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/24/world/africa/Ebola_Reconstruct-slide-M8BK/Ebola_Reconstruct-slide-M8BK-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/24/world/africa/<ORGANIZATION>Ebola_Reconstruct-slide-M8BK/Ebola_Reconstruct-slide-M8BK-thumbStandard<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/24/world/africa/<ORGANIZATION>Ebola_Reconstruct-slide-M8BK/Ebola_Reconstruct-slide-M8BK-thumbStandard<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg,height:75}]",7596,"For fleeting moment <DATE>spring</DATE>, epidemic sweeping <LOCATION>West Africa</LOCATION> stopped. But opportunity control virus, caused 7,800 deaths, lost.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/health/how-ebola-roared-back.html,54a1ba967988104803cc8877,null,"{main:How Ebola Roared Back,print_headline:Ebola’s Deadly Escape}","{contributor:<PERSON>Kevin Sack<\/PERSON> reported <LOCATION>Atlanta<\/LOCATION>; <PERSON>Sheri Fink Liberia<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Sierra Leone<\/PERSON>, <LOCATION>Geneva New York<\/LOCATION>; <LOCATION>Pam Belluck New York<\/LOCATION>; <PERSON>Adam Nossiter<\/PERSON> Guinea. The article written Mr. <PERSON>Sack<\/PERSON>.,original:By <PERSON>KEVIN SACK<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>SHERI FINK<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>PAM BELLUCK ADAM NOSSITER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Kevin,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SACK},{firstname:Sheri,role:reported,organization:,rank:2,lastname:FINK},{firstname:Pam,role:reported,organization:,rank:3,lastname:BELLUCK},{firstname:Adam,role:reported,organization:,rank:4,lastname:NOSSITER}]}",article
Americans country days.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-29T11:25:43Z,[],836,Americans country days.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/29/us/politics/ap-us-ap-poll-civic-duty-5-things.html,54a180e47988101f98e3eff8,Politics,"{main:5 Things About Americans' Slipping Sense Duty,print_headline:5 Things About Americans' Slipping Sense Duty}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Tired hearing people grouse tuned-out, apathetic younger generation??",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-29T03:19:33Z,[],990,"Tired hearing people grouse tuned-out, apathetic younger generation??",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/29/us/politics/ap-us-ap-poll-young-volunteers.html,54a10ef67988101f98e3ef22,Politics,"{main:Young Generation No Slouches Volunteering,print_headline:Young Generation No Slouches Volunteering}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
