snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
<PERSON>Andrew Cuomo</PERSON> sworn term governor <DATE>Thursday</DATE> hours father died.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T21:20:05Z,[],716,<PERSON>Andrew Cuomo</PERSON> sworn term governor <DATE>Thursday</DATE> hours father died.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/us/ap-us-cuomo-inauguration.html,54a600e37988102023c951c6,null,"{main:Cuomo Begins 2nd Term Day His Father Dies,print_headline:Cuomo Begins 2nd Term Day His Father Dies}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Hollywood action film star <PERSON>Rafe Stoker</PERSON> has sunk <MONEY>$130,000</MONEY> of his own money into his own production, but can't find legitimate financing to complete the film. His mob-connected investor demands an exorbitant amount of collateral and a guarantee that R",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T06:57:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-hollywood-man/video-hollywood-man-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-hollywood-man/video-hollywood-man-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-hollywood-man/video-hollywood-man-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-hollywood-man/video-hollywood-man-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-hollywood-man/video-hollywood-man-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-hollywood-man/video-hollywood-man-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",40,"Hollywood action film star <PERSON>Rafe Stoker</PERSON> has sunk <MONEY>$130,000</MONEY> of his own money into his own production, but can't find legitimate financing to complete the film. His mob-connected investor demands an exorbitant amount of collateral and a guarantee that R",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003389599/hollywood-man.html,54a5361379881011bed2c074,null,{"main":"Hollywood Man"},"{original:CFS Releasing,person:[{firstname:Cfs,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Releasing}]}",multimedia
"President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON> preached economic opportunity equal access education cornerstones legacy leave. But contest host presidential library, public universities serve needy communities...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T03:07:57Z,[],822,"President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON> preached economic opportunity equal access education cornerstones legacy leave. But contest host presidential library, public universities serve needy communities fear playing field tilted pair elite, private schools seemingly endless money.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/us/ap-us-obama-library.html,54a500e879881011bed2b46f,null,"{main:Universities Competing Obama Library Site,print_headline:Universities Competing Obama Library Site}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
An Arab-Israeli Muslim woman running parliament seat member hard-line religious Jewish party aligned <LOCATION>West Bank</LOCATION> settler movement opposes Palestinian independence.,null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T02:03:01Z,[],528,An Arab-Israeli Muslim woman running parliament seat member hard-line religious Jewish party aligned <LOCATION>West Bank</LOCATION> settler movement opposes Palestinian independence.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/world/middleeast/ap-ml-israel-unlikely-candidate.html,54a4f21f79881011bed2b11a,Middle East,"{main:Iconoclast Arab Backing Israel Runs Parliament,print_headline:Iconoclast Arab Backing Israel Runs Parliament}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"A million people crammed <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>'s Times Square ushered <DATE>2015</DATE> cheers, hugs kisses glittering New Year's Eve ball descended high ton confetti wafted revelers.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T00:41:00Z,[],539,"A million people crammed <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>'s Times Square ushered <DATE>2015</DATE> cheers, hugs kisses glittering New Year's Eve ball descended high ton confetti wafted revelers.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/us/ap-us-new-years-eve-nyc.html,54a4de7379881011bed2aca1,null,"{main:Crystal Ball Drops <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION>, Ushering 2015,print_headline:Crystal Ball Drops <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION>, Ushering 2015}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<PERSON>Nick Asbury</PERSON>, a creator of the world’s most depressing datebook, on starting off the year with a fresh load of pessimism.",2,"[{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:1,value:Asbury, <PERSON>Nick<\/PERSON>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Books Literature},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Comedy Humor},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:4,value:Asbury, Sue},{is_major:Y,name:creative_works,rank:5,value:Perpetual Disappointments Diary Book}]",Home & Garden,"Q&A British author <PERSON>Nick Asbury</PERSON> explains inspiration weekly planner called <ORGANIZATION>Perpetual Disappointments Diary</ORGANIZATION>, filled demotivational quotes depressing tidbits.",The New York Times,[],Home,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/garden/01QNA1/01QNA1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/garden/01QNA1/01QNA1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/garden/01QNA1/QNA1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/garden/01QNA1/QNA1-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/garden/01QNA1/01QNA1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/garden/01QNA1/01QNA1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",813,"<PERSON>Nick Asbury</PERSON>, a creator of the world’s most depressing datebook, on starting off the year with a fresh load of pessimism.",Question,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/garden/perpetual-disappointments-diary-not-for-pollyannas.html,54a48cad79881011bed299ea,null,"{content_kicker:Q&A,main:Abandon All Hope, Ye Who Buy It,seo:Perpetual Disappointments Diary: Not Pollyannas,print_headline:Abandon All Hope, Ye Who Buy It,kicker:Q&A}","{contributor:,original:By RIMA SUQI,person:[{firstname:Rima,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SUQI}]}",article
The Eswein-Phillips family amassed million combined followers jumping simple Instagram handles @food @newyorkcity.,1,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:Instagram Inc},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:Eswein, Liz},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Social Media},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Photography}]",Style,"Profile Manhattan-based <PERSON>Sarah Phillips</PERSON> adult children, <PERSON>Liz Tom Eswein</PERSON>, collectively million followers Instagram due family's prodigious posting variety subjects.",The New York Times,[],Styles,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01SUB2INSTAGRAM/01SUB2INSTAGRAM-thumbWide-v2.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01SUB2INSTAGRAM/01SUB2INSTAGRAM-thumbWide-v2.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01SUB2INSTAGRAM/01SUB2INSTAGRAM-articleLarge-v2.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:813},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01SUB2INSTAGRAM/01SUB2INSTAGRAM-articleLarge-v2.jpg,height:813},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01SUB2INSTAGRAM/01SUB2INSTAGRAM-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01SUB2INSTAGRAM/01SUB2INSTAGRAM-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",1586,The Eswein-Phillips family amassed million combined followers jumping simple Instagram handles @food @newyorkcity.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/style/the-first-family-of-instagram.html,54a4718779881011bed293bf,null,"{main:The First Family Instagram,print_headline:The First Family Instagram}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>CAROLINE MOSS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Caroline,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:MOSS}]}",article
Excerpts recent editorials newspapers <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> abroad:,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T16:38:27Z,[],2905,Excerpts recent editorials newspapers <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> abroad:,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/ap-us-editorial-rdp.html,54a46d5379881011bed292c6,null,"{main:Editorial Roundup: Excerpts From Recent Editorials,print_headline:Editorial Roundup: Excerpts From Recent Editorials}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON> preached economic opportunity equal access education cornerstones legacy leave. But contest host presidential library, public universities serve needy communities...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T13:06:56Z,[],822,"President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON> preached economic opportunity equal access education cornerstones legacy leave. But contest host presidential library, public universities serve needy communities fear playing field tilted pair elite, private schools seemingly endless money.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/ap-us-obama-library.html,54a43c0f79881011bed28751,null,"{main:For <PERSON>Obama Library<\/PERSON>, Contest Haves Have-Nots,print_headline:For <PERSON>Obama Library<\/PERSON>, Contest Haves Have-Nots}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
The ruble's plunge offers West chance resolve <LOCATION>Ukraine</LOCATION> crisis re-engage <PERSON>Putin</PERSON>.,,"[{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Russia<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Ruble Currency},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:3,value:<LOCATION>Ukraine<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:4,value:<LOCATION>Crimea Ukraine<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Politics Government}]",Opinion,null,The New York Times,[],OpEd,2014-12-31T11:30:00Z,[],1039,The ruble's plunge offers West chance resolve <LOCATION>Ukraine</LOCATION> crisis re-engage <PERSON>Putin</PERSON>.,Op-Ed,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/opinion/rapprochement-with-russia.html,54a27e637988104803cc8a49,null,"{content_kicker:Op-Ed Contributors,main:Rapprochement With <LOCATION>Russia<\/LOCATION>???,print_headline:Rapprochement With <LOCATION>Russia<\/LOCATION>?,kicker:Op-Ed Contributors}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>HANS BINNENDIJK<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>CHRISTOPHER S. CHIVVIS OLGA OLIKER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Hans,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BINNENDIJK},{firstname:Christopher,role:reported,organization:,middlename:S.,rank:2,lastname:CHIVVIS},{firstname:Olga,role:reported,organization:,rank:3,lastname:OLIKER}]}",article
