snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"On sticky hot <DATE>Sunday August 1952</DATE>, wealthy black woman named Ruby McCollum walked colored entrance doctor's office small north <LOCATION>Florida</LOCATION> town Live Oak fatally shot white doctor, state Sen.-elect <PERSON>Clifford Leroy</PERSON>...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T11:10:34Z,[],928,"On sticky hot <DATE>Sunday August 1952</DATE>, wealthy black woman named Ruby McCollum walked colored entrance doctor's office small north <LOCATION>Florida</LOCATION> town Live Oak fatally shot white doctor, state Sen.-elect <PERSON>Clifford Leroy Adams</PERSON>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/us/ap-us-jim-crow-killing.html,54a5738e79881011bed2cddf,null,"{main:Jim Crow-Era Shooting Revisited New Documentary,print_headline:Jim Crow-Era Shooting Revisited New Documentary}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Model <PERSON>Sonni Pacheco</PERSON> filed divorce actor-husband <PERSON>Jeremy Renner</PERSON> 10 months marriage, court documents filed <LOCATION>Los Angeles</LOCATION> <DATE>Dec. 5</DATE>.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T13:21:37Z,[],115,"Model <PERSON>Sonni Pacheco</PERSON> filed divorce actor-husband <PERSON>Jeremy Renner</PERSON> 10 months marriage, court documents filed <LOCATION>Los Angeles</LOCATION> <DATE>Dec. 5</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/ap-us-people-jeremy-renner-divorce.html,54a43f9079881011bed2887e,null,"{main:<PERSON>Jeremy Renner<\/PERSON>'s Wife <PERSON>Sonni Pacheco<\/PERSON> Files Divorce,print_headline:<PERSON>Jeremy Renner<\/PERSON>'s Wife <PERSON>Sonni Pacheco<\/PERSON> Files Divorce}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"On bright New Year's Day <DATE>2010</DATE>, small group immigrants including young couple love laced donated sneakers 1,500-mile march <LOCATION>Miami Washington</LOCATION>.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T11:52:32Z,[],1157,"On bright New Year's Day <DATE>2010</DATE>, small group immigrants including young couple love laced donated sneakers 1,500-mile march <LOCATION>Miami Washington</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/ap-us-gay-immigration-activists.html,54a42a6e7988102761d6e837,null,"{main:Activists' Lives, <ORGANIZATION>Romance Nation<\/ORGANIZATION>'s Change,print_headline:Activists' Lives, <ORGANIZATION>Romance Nation<\/ORGANIZATION>'s Change}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"New state laws taking effect <DATE>Thursday</DATE> give livestock <LOCATION>California</LOCATION> living room, approve direct-to-consumer wine shipments <LOCATION>Massachusetts</LOCATION> levy ultimate punishment wannabe teen drivers <LOCATION>Nevada</LOCATION> denying licenses skip...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T01:50:55Z,[],1404,"New state laws taking effect <DATE>Thursday</DATE> give livestock <LOCATION>California</LOCATION> living room, approve direct-to-consumer wine shipments <LOCATION>Massachusetts</LOCATION> levy ultimate punishment wannabe teen drivers <LOCATION>Nevada</LOCATION> denying licenses skip school.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/ap-us-new-laws-around-the-country.html,54a39dcb7988102761d6d3fc,null,"{main:New Laws OK Wine Shipments, Ban Tiger Selfies,print_headline:New Laws OK Wine Shipments, Ban Tiger Selfies}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Can prison theater workshop prepare men life freedom??,19,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Prisons Prisoners},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Theater},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Comedy Humor}]",Opinion,"Op-Ed article writer <PERSON>Anna Clark</PERSON> describes experience leading improv theater workshop Macomb Correctional Facility <LOCATION>Michigan</LOCATION>; observes prisoners incarcerated long time emerge unfamiliar world, ways, workshop, improvise adapt.",The New York Times,[],OpEd,2014-12-31T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/opinion/31Clark/31Clark-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/opinion/31Clark/31Clark-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/opinion/31Clark/31Clark-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:994},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/opinion/31Clark/31Clark-articleLarge.jpg,height:994},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/opinion/31Clark/31Clark-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/opinion/31Clark/31Clark-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",920,Can prison theater workshop prepare men life freedom??,Op-Ed,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/opinion/inmate-improv.html,54a33ba27988102761d6cf4f,null,"{content_kicker:Op-Ed Contributor,main:Inmate Improv,print_headline:Inmate Improv,kicker:Op-Ed Contributor}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ANNA CLARK<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Anna,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:CLARK}]}",article
A federal appeals court refused reconsider decision allowing residents <LOCATION>Kansas Arizona</LOCATION> register vote federal form providing proof <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> citizenship.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-29T19:23:57Z,[],128,A federal appeals court refused reconsider decision allowing residents <LOCATION>Kansas Arizona</LOCATION> register vote federal form providing proof <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> citizenship.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/29/us/ap-us-voter-citizenship-lawsuit.html,54a1f0e27988104803cc88e0,null,"{main:Court Won't Reconsider States' Citizenship Lawsuit,print_headline:Court Won't Reconsider States' Citizenship Lawsuit}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"We have mentored a foster child through many “homes” and placements, and she has spent many holidays with us. This year, she’s bonding we hope with a new family.",null,"[{name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Los Angeles Calif<\/LOCATION>},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Children Childhood},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Foster Care},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Mentors},{name:subject,rank:4,value:Teenagers Adolescence}]",<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,"We have mentored a foster child through many “homes” and placements, and she has spent many holidays with us. This year, she’s bonding we hope with a new family.",The New York Times,[],Styles,2014-12-28T08:39:09Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/22/us/motherlode-mangrove/motherlode-mangrove-thumbWide.png},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/22/us/motherlode-mangrove/motherlode-mangrove-thumbWide.png,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/22/us/motherlode-mangrove/motherlode-mangrove-articleLarge.png,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:401},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/22/us/motherlode-mangrove/motherlode-mangrove-articleLarge.png,height:401},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/22/us/motherlode-mangrove/motherlode-mangrove-thumbStandard.png,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/22/us/motherlode-mangrove/motherlode-mangrove-thumbStandard.png,height:75}]",806,null,Blog,http://parenting.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/a-foster-teens-holiday-and-uncertain-future/,54a0087379881001534d209f,null,"{main:A Foster Teen's Holiday Uncertain Future,kicker:Motherlode}","{original:By <PERSON>SHAWNA KENNEY<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Shawna,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:KENNEY}]}",blogpost
"At <ORGANIZATION>Gem Wheelchair & Scooter Service</ORGANIZATION>, main attraction fleet motorized wheelchairs scooters, lined <PERSON>Mini Cooper</PERSON> dealership.&#160;But Gem&#8217;s true calling repair business.",3,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:Gem Wheelchair & Scooter Service <LOCATION>Queens<\/LOCATION>, NY},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>Hillcrest Queens<\/LOCATION>, NY},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Disabilities},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Jews Judaism},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Kosher Foods Products}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"Neighborhood Joint column <ORGANIZATION>Gem Wheelchair & Scooter Service Hillcrest</ORGANIZATION>, <LOCATION>Queens</LOCATION>, sells repairs mobility equipment, including operable observant Jews day rest.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-28T00:00:00Z,[],573,"At <ORGANIZATION>Gem Wheelchair & Scooter Service</ORGANIZATION>, main attraction fleet motorized wheelchairs scooters, lined <PERSON>Mini Cooper</PERSON> dealership.&#160;But Gem&#8217;s true calling repair business.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/nyregion/how-they-roll.html,549d10cf7988103babf08b2d,null,"{content_kicker:Neighborhood Joint,main:How They Roll,print_headline:How They Roll,kicker:Neighborhood Joint}","{contributor:,original:By JI HYUN LEE,person:[{firstname:Ji,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Hyun,rank:1,lastname:LEE}]}",article
"SHERMAN--<PERSON>Lillian Marion Hill</PERSON>, 86, of <LOCATION>Brooklyn</LOCATION>, NY/ <LOCATION>Trenton</LOCATION>, died at a <LOCATION>Bangor</LOCATION> hospital, <DATE>December 17, 2014</DATE>, surrounded by her loving family after a four year struggle with a heart condition and cancer. She was born <DATE>April 07, 1928</DATE>, in <LOCATION>Brooklyn</LOCATION>, NY,...",null,[],Paid Death Notices,null,The New York Times,[],Classified,2014-12-27T19:16:37Z,[],329,"<!-- LILLIAN SHERMAN -->SHERMAN--<PERSON>Lillian Marion<</PERSON>br/><br/> Hill, 86, of <LOCATION>Brooklyn</LOCATION>, NY/ <LOCATION>Trenton</LOCATION>, died at a <LOCATION>Bangor</LOCATION> hospital, <DATE>December 17, 2014</DATE>, surrounded by her loving family after a four year struggle with a heart condition and cancer. She was born <DATE>April 07, 1928</DATE>, in <LOCATION>Brooklyn</LOCATION>, <ORGANIZATION>NY</ORGANIZATION>, the daughter of <PERSON>William E.</PERSON> and <PERSON>Violet Louise Weekes</PERSON> Hill. Lillian graduated from <ORGANIZATION>Hunter College</ORGANIZATION>, class of <DATE>1949</DATE>. She received her <ORGANIZATION>M.A.</ORGANIZATION> from <ORGANIZATION>Hunter College</ORGANIZATION> in <DATE>1952</DATE>. Lillian was married to <PERSON>Allen Sherman</PERSON> in <DATE>1954</DATE>. They celebrated 60 years of marriage in <DATE>July</DATE>. Lillian received her elementary school teaching certificate in <DATE>June 1949</DATE>. She taught grades 3-6 in the <LOCATION>New York City</LOCATION> Public School system. She had a magnificent sense of devotion to the education of her children. She specialized in reading improvement and enrichment areas. Language arts and social studies were fields of special interest. Her favorite novel to share with her 5th grade classes was The Yearling. Lillian retired from teaching in <DATE>1994</DATE>. Lillian enjoyed reading, writing poetry, solving crossword puzzles, traveling and dining out with <PERSON>Allen</PERSON> in <LOCATION>New York City</LOCATION>. She is survived by her beloved husband, <PERSON>Allen Sherman</PERSON>; daughters, <PERSON>Jeanne L. Sherman</PERSON> and partner <PERSON>Joseph A. Jantzen</PERSON> of <LOCATION>Trenton</LOCATION>, ME, <PERSON>Jennifer L. Sherman</PERSON> and husband <PERSON>John P. Dineen</PERSON> of <LOCATION>Bayside</LOCATION>, NY; one granddaughter, <PERSON>Bridget T. Dineen</PERSON> of <LOCATION>Bayside</LOCATION>, NY; one brother, <PERSON>Roy E. Hill</PERSON> and wife Alma of <LOCATION>Brooklyn</LOCATION>, NY; two sisters, <PERSON>Mary Jane Fils-Aime</PERSON> and husband <PERSON>Alix</PERSON> of <LOCATION>Lakeville</LOCATION>, <ORGANIZATION>PA</ORGANIZATION>, <PERSON>Mildred A. Espino</PERSON> and husband <PERSON>Juan H. of Hawley</PERSON>, <ORGANIZATION>PA</ORGANIZATION>; and many nieces, nephews and great nieces and nephews. She was predeceased by her two brothers, <PERSON>William H. Hill</PERSON> and <PERSON>Richard Hill</PERSON>. A service of remembrance will be held 1:00- 4:00pm and 7:00-9:00pm, <DATE>December 29, 2014</DATE> at <ORGANIZATION>McLaughlin & Sons</ORGANIZATION>, <DATE>9620</DATE> 3rd Avenue, <LOCATION>Brooklyn</LOCATION>, NY. In lieu of flowers, the family suggests contributions in Lillian's memory be made to the <ORGANIZATION>SPCA</ORGANIZATION> of <LOCATION>Hancock County</LOCATION>, 141 <LOCATION>Bar Harbor Road</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Trenton</LOCATION> 04605. Services by <ORGANIZATION>Jordan-Fernald</ORGANIZATION>, 113 <ORGANIZATION>Franklin St. Ellsworth Condolences</ORGANIZATION> may be expressed at <a rel=nofollow href=www.jordanfernald.com>www.jordanfernald.com</a><br><br> ",Paid Death Notice,http://www.legacy.com/Link.asp?I=LS000173626710,549fd4a879881001534d207b,null,"{main:Paid Notice: Deaths  SHERMAN, LILLIAN}",null,article
Move farmers' markets. More 300 food hubs country providing small farms outlet sell locally raised food consumers.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-27T10:24:17Z,[],700,Move farmers' markets. More 300 food hubs country providing small farms outlet sell locally raised food consumers.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/27/us/ap-us-food-and-farm-food-hubs.html,549ed1397988105ced78871e,null,"{main:Food Hubs Link Consumers With Locally Farmed Food,print_headline:Food Hubs Link Consumers With Locally Farmed Food}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
