snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Dispensing death and clemency capriciously, killing on petulant impulse, granting pardons at whim — it’s complicated.",null,"[{name:subject,rank:1,value:Animals},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Ants},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Ethics Personal},{name:subject,rank:4,value:Insects}]",Opinion,"Dispensing death and clemency capriciously, killing on petulant impulse, granting pardons at whim — it’s complicated.",The New York Times,[],OpEd,2014-11-15T14:35:47Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/11/16/sunday-review/16MENAGERIE/16MENAGERIE-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/11/16/sunday-review/16MENAGERIE/16MENAGERIE-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/11/16/sunday-review/16MENAGERIE/16MENAGERIE-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:486},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/11/16/sunday-review/16MENAGERIE/16MENAGERIE-articleLarge.jpg,height:486},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/11/16/sunday-review/16MENAGERIE/16MENAGERIE-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/11/16/sunday-review/16MENAGERIE/16MENAGERIE-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1726,null,Blog,http://opinionator.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/11/15/on-smushing-bugs/,5467ac0379881054c64b01d4,null,"{main:On Smushing Bugs,print_headline:On Smushing Bugs,kicker:Menagerie}","{original:By <PERSON>TIM KREIDER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Tim,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:KREIDER}]}",blogpost
"In middle-grade, girl finds forward loss mother.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Books Literature},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Ehrlich<\/PERSON>, Esther}]",Books,<PERSON>Priscilla Gilman</PERSON> reviews book Nest <PERSON>Esther Ehrlich</PERSON>.,The New York Times,[],BookReview,2014-09-21T00:00:00Z,[],696,"In middle-grade, girl finds forward loss mother.",Review,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/09/21/books/review/nest-by-esther-ehrlich.html,541c52c97988100a1c6610da,<DATE>Sunday</DATE> Book Review,"{content_kicker:Children’s Books,main:Rare Bird,seo:‘Nest,’ by <PERSON>Esther Ehrlich<\/PERSON>,print_headline:Rare Bird,kicker:Children's Books}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>PRISCILLA GILMAN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Priscilla,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:GILMAN}]}",article
"<LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION>'s supreme leader <PERSON>Ayatollah Ali&#160;Khamenei</PERSON>&#160;on <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> called <LOCATION>Israel</LOCATION> rabid dog attacks <LOCATION>Gaza</LOCATION>, urged Muslims arm Palestinians enable counter termed genocide.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],null,2014-07-29T01:54:45Z,[],386,"<LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION>'s supreme leader <PERSON>Ayatollah Ali&#160;Khamenei</PERSON>&#160;on <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> called <LOCATION>Israel</LOCATION> rabid dog attacks <LOCATION>Gaza</LOCATION>, urged Muslims arm Palestinians enable counter termed genocide.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/07/29/world/middleeast/29reuters-mideast-gaza-iran-khamenei.html,53d737e97988104972f05013,Middle East,"{main:Iran Leader Calls <LOCATION>Israel<\/LOCATION> 'Rabid Dog', Urges Arms Palestinians,print_headline:Iran Leader Calls <LOCATION>Israel<\/LOCATION> 'Rabid Dog', Urges Arms Palestinians}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"There poisonous view conservatives poor deficient character, cash.",17,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Poverty},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:2,value:Republican Party},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:3,value:United States},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:4,value:<PERSON>Bush<\/PERSON>, Jeb},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:5,value:Ryan, <PERSON>Paul<\/PERSON> D Jr}]",Opinion,"Charles M Blow Op-Ed column criticizes view conservatives poor suffer lack character; notes Rep <PERSON>Paul Ryan Florida Gov Jeb Bush</PERSON>, Republicans, offered examples view gathering <ORGANIZATION>Manhattan Institute</ORGANIZATION>.",The New York Times,[],Editorial,2014-05-19T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/05/19/opinion/19blowchart/19blowchart-thumbWide.gif},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/05/19/opinion/19blowchart/19blowchart-thumbWide.gif,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/05/19/opinion/19blowchart/19blowchart-articleLarge.gif,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:278},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/05/19/opinion/19blowchart/19blowchart-articleLarge.gif,height:278},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/05/19/opinion/19blowchart/19blowchart-thumbStandard.gif,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/05/19/opinion/19blowchart/19blowchart-thumbStandard.gif,height:75}]",757,"There poisonous view conservatives poor deficient character, cash.",Op-Ed,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/05/19/opinion/blow-poverty-is-not-a-state-of-mind.html,537952f67988100a0ee14674,null,"{content_kicker:Op-Ed Columnist,main:Poverty Is Not State Mind,print_headline:Poverty Is Not State Mind,kicker:Op-Ed Columnist}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>CHARLES M.<\/PERSON> BLOW,person:[{firstname:Charles,role:reported,organization:,rank:1}]}",article
