snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"There smart reasons <PERSON>Hillary Clinton</PERSON>, Iron Lady <DATE>2008</DATE>, campaign grandmother-in-chief.",3,"[{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Clinton<\/PERSON>, Hillary Rodham},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Presidential Election 2016},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Women Girls},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Stand With Hillary},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Gender}]",Opinion,Frank <PERSON>Bruni</PERSON> Op-Ed column marvels Web video posted 'super PAC' Stand With Hillary supporting <PERSON>Hillary Clinton</PERSON>'s as-yet unannounced <DATE>2016</DATE> presidential bid; observes video suggests <PERSON>Clinton</PERSON> focus gender place greater emphasis making history <DATE>2008</DATE>; contends smart <PERSON>Clinton</PERSON> mitigate big vulnerabilities.,The New York Times,[],Editorial,2014-12-07T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/07/sunday-review/07bruni/07bruni-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/07/sunday-review/07bruni/07bruni-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/07/sunday-review/07bruni/07bruni-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:670},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/07/sunday-review/07bruni/07bruni-articleLarge.jpg,height:670},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/07/sunday-review/07bruni/07bruni-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/07/sunday-review/07bruni/07bruni-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1105,"There smart reasons <PERSON>Hillary Clinton</PERSON>, Iron Lady <DATE>2008</DATE>, campaign grandmother-in-chief.",Op-Ed,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/07/opinion/sunday/frank-bruni-hillary-2-0-would-be-hillary-xx.html,548361a47988106fd483c51f,<DATE>Sunday</DATE> Review,"{content_kicker:Op-Ed Columnist,main:Hillary 2.0 Would Be Hillary XX,print_headline:Hillary 2.0 Would Be Hillary XX,kicker:Op-Ed Columnist}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>FRANK BRUNI<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Frank,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BRUNI}]}",article
The Chinese comedy “The Breakup Guru” opens the heart of a man who makes his living shutting down relationships.,null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:6,value:Movies},{is_major:N,name:creative_works,rank:1,value:The Breakup Guru Movie},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Deng Chao<\/PERSON>},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:4,value:Yu Baimei}]",Movies,"<PERSON>Andy Webster</PERSON> reviews film The Breakup Guru, directed <PERSON>Deng Chao Yu Baimei</PERSON>.",The New York Times,[],Weekend,2014-06-27T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/06/27/arts/27BREAKUP/27BREAKUP-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/06/27/arts/27BREAKUP/27BREAKUP-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/06/27/arts/27BREAKUP/27BREAKUP-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/06/27/arts/27BREAKUP/27BREAKUP-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/06/27/arts/27BREAKUP/27BREAKUP-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/06/27/arts/27BREAKUP/27BREAKUP-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",247,The Chinese comedy “The Breakup Guru” opens the heart of a man who makes his living shutting down relationships.,Review,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/06/27/movies/the-breakup-guru-starring-deng-chao.html,53aca17279881073fab4f349,null,"{content_kicker:Movie Review,main:A Matchmaker Reverse,seo:‘The Breakup Guru,’ Starring <PERSON>Deng Chao<\/PERSON>,print_headline:The Breakup Guru,kicker:Movie Review | 'The Breakup Guru'| 'The Breakup Guru'}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ANDY WEBSTER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Andy,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:WEBSTER}]}",article
A married immigrant Londoner 70s ready.,null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Books Literature},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:Evaristo, Bernardine}]",Books,Ellery <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION> reviews book Mr <PERSON>Loverman Bernardine Evaristo</PERSON>.,The New York Times,[],BookReview,2014-06-15T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/06/15/books/review/15WASHINGTON/15WASHINGTON-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/06/15/books/review/15WASHINGTON/15WASHINGTON-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/06/15/books/review/15WASHINGTON/15WASHINGTON-articleLarge-v4.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:465},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/06/15/books/review/15WASHINGTON/15WASHINGTON-articleLarge-v4.jpg,height:465},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/06/15/books/review/15WASHINGTON/15WASHINGTON-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/06/15/books/review/15WASHINGTON/15WASHINGTON-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",636,A married immigrant Londoner 70s ready.,Review,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/06/15/books/review/mr-loverman-by-bernardine-evaristo.html,539b18f57988106c3c7768d8,<DATE>Sunday</DATE> Book Review,"{main:Late Bloomer,seo:‘Mr. Loverman,’ by <PERSON>Bernardine Evaristo<\/PERSON>,print_headline:Late Bloomer}","{contributor:,original:By ELLERY <LOCATION>WASHINGTON<\/LOCATION>,person:[{firstname:Ellery,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:<LOCATION>WASHINGTON<\/LOCATION>}]}",article
"The avant-garde opera composer <PERSON>Robert Ashley</PERSON> died <DATE>March</DATE>, presence strongly felt presentations <ORGANIZATION>Whitney Biennial</ORGANIZATION> recent re-envisionings work.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Music},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:2,value:Ashley, <PERSON>Robert<\/PERSON> 1930-2014},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Whitney Biennial},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Whitney Museum American Art}]",Arts,<PERSON>Steve Smith</PERSON> reflects late avant-garde opera composer <PERSON>Robert Ashley</PERSON>'s presence strongly felt presentations <ORGANIZATION>Whitney Biennial</ORGANIZATION> recent re-envisionings work.,The New York Times,[],Culture,2014-04-15T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/04/15/arts/15ASHLEY/15ASHLEY-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/04/15/arts/15ASHLEY/15ASHLEY-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/04/15/arts/15ASHLEY/15ASHLEY-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/04/15/arts/15ASHLEY/15ASHLEY-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/04/15/arts/15ASHLEY/15ASHLEY-thumbStandard-v3.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/04/15/arts/15ASHLEY/15ASHLEY-thumbStandard-v3.jpg,height:75}]",861,"The avant-garde opera composer <PERSON>Robert Ashley</PERSON> died <DATE>March</DATE>, presence strongly felt presentations <ORGANIZATION>Whitney Biennial</ORGANIZATION> recent re-envisionings work.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/04/15/arts/music/robert-ashleys-work-lives-on-at-the-whitney-biennial.html,534c50fd7988107dedc8d7d5,Music,"{content_kicker:Critic’s Notebook,main:Still Sensing Presence Departed Composer,seo:<PERSON>Robert Ashley<\/PERSON>’s Work Lives On at the Whitney Biennial,print_headline:Still Sensing Presence Departed Composer,kicker:Critic’s Notebook}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>STEVE SMITH<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Steve,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SMITH}]}",article
"The Times live-blogged the <ORGANIZATION>86th Academy Awards</ORGANIZATION>, with interviews from the red carpet and backstage, video updates from <PERSON>David Carr</PERSON> and <PERSON>A. O. Scott</PERSON>, live commentary during the telecast, reviews of the night’s best and worst looks and star turns,...",null,[],Arts,"The Times live-blogged the <ORGANIZATION>86th Academy Awards</ORGANIZATION>, with interviews from the red carpet and backstage, video updates from <PERSON>David Carr</PERSON> and <PERSON>A. O. Scott</PERSON>, live commentary during the telecast, reviews of the night’s best and worst looks and star turns, social media features and more.",The New York Times,[],Culture,2014-03-02T15:26:56Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/03/03/arts/oscar-gravity/oscar-gravity-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/03/03/arts/oscar-gravity/oscar-gravity-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/03/03/arts/oscar-gravity/oscar-gravity-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:349},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/03/03/arts/oscar-gravity/oscar-gravity-articleLarge.jpg,height:349},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/03/03/arts/oscar-gravity/oscar-gravity-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/03/03/arts/oscar-gravity/oscar-gravity-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",9905,null,Blog,http://carpetbagger.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/03/02/live-coverage-of-the-86th-academy-awards/,5313942a79881059936a5ba1,Movies,"{main:Oscars 2014: '12 Years A Slave' Is Best Picture 'Gravity' Wins Seven Awards,kicker:Carpetbagger}","{original:By THE <LOCATION>NEW YORK<\/LOCATION> TIMES,person:[],organization:The New York Times}",blogpost
