snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"<LOCATION>South Korea</LOCATION>'s manufacturing activity shrank fourth consecutive month <DATE>December</DATE> slower pace, private-sector survey showed <DATE>Friday</DATE>, adding signs economy slowly regaining footing heading <DATE>2015</DATE>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T19:03:32Z,[],250,"<LOCATION>South Korea</LOCATION>'s manufacturing activity shrank fourth consecutive month <DATE>December</DATE> slower pace, private-sector survey showed <DATE>Friday</DATE>, adding signs economy slowly regaining footing heading <DATE>2015</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-southkorea-economy-pmi.html,54a5e0717988102023c94ee3,null,"{main:<LOCATION>South Korea<\/LOCATION> <DATE>December<\/DATE> Factory Activity Shrinks Fourth Month Slower Pace-PMI,print_headline:<LOCATION>South Korea<\/LOCATION> <DATE>December<\/DATE> Factory Activity Shrinks Fourth Month Slower Pace-PMI}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"AM LOVE tells story wealthy <PERSON>Recchi</PERSON> family <LOCATION>Milan</LOCATION>, lives rapidly changing. The family patriarch surprised family shared ownership massive industrial company son <PERSON>Tancredi Delbono</PERSON>,",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T11:47:06Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-i-am-love/video-i-am-love-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-i-am-love/video-i-am-love-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-i-am-love/video-i-am-love-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-i-am-love/video-i-am-love-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-i-am-love/video-i-am-love-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-i-am-love/video-i-am-love-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",41,"AM LOVE tells story wealthy <PERSON>Recchi</PERSON> family <LOCATION>Milan</LOCATION>, lives rapidly changing. The family patriarch surprised family shared ownership massive industrial company son <PERSON>Tancredi Delbono</PERSON>,",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003340131/i-am-love.html,54a57a2479881011bed2cfae,null,{"main":"I Am Love"},"{original:Magnolia Pictures,person:[{firstname:Magnolia,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Pictures}]}",multimedia
The year expected bring rising chicken egg prices <LOCATION>U.S. California</LOCATION> starts requiring farmers house hens cages space move stretch wings.,null,[],Business Day,null,AP,[],Business,2015-01-01T10:32:26Z,[],626,The year expected bring rising chicken egg prices <LOCATION>U.S. California</LOCATION> starts requiring farmers house hens cages space move stretch wings.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/us/ap-us-chicken-cage-california-law.html,54a568e579881011bed2cbce,null,"{main:More Room Chickens Likely Means Costlier Eggs,print_headline:More Room Chickens Likely Means Costlier Eggs}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<PERSON>Monika</PERSON>, <ORGANIZATION>Tonik Dasha</ORGANIZATION> grew housing project outskirts small industrial city. Now childhood friends adults, struggling feelings desire loneliness, longing failure. Though ad",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T06:14:11Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-something-like-happiness/video-something-like-happiness-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-something-like-happiness/video-something-like-happiness-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-something-like-happiness/video-something-like-happiness-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:348},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-something-like-happiness/video-something-like-happiness-articleLarge.jpg,height:348},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-something-like-happiness/video-something-like-happiness-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-something-like-happiness/video-something-like-happiness-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",41,"<PERSON>Monika</PERSON>, <ORGANIZATION>Tonik Dasha</ORGANIZATION> grew housing project outskirts small industrial city. Now childhood friends adults, struggling feelings desire loneliness, longing failure. Though ad",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003377770/something-like-happiness.html,54a52c0679881011bed2be37,null,{"main":"Something Like Happiness"},"{original:Film Movement,person:[{firstname:Film,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Movement}]}",multimedia
"At vast skating rink <LOCATION>Moscow</LOCATION>'s Gorky Park, Russians forward <DATE>2015</DATE> smooth ice, country's economic political difficulties. The ruble sunk, tensions West,...",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T03:57:16Z,[],796,"At vast skating rink <LOCATION>Moscow</LOCATION>'s Gorky Park, Russians forward <DATE>2015</DATE> smooth ice, country's economic political difficulties. The ruble sunk, tensions West, troubles produced surge national pride.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/world/europe/ap-eu-russia-new-year-mood.html,54a50cd779881011bed2b733,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:Russians Optimistic 2015 Despite It All,print_headline:Russians Optimistic 2015 Despite It All}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s factory activity sputtered <DATE>December</DATE>, underlining challenges facing country's manufacturers fight rising costs softening demand cooling economy.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T00:37:48Z,[],762,"<LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s factory activity sputtered <DATE>December</DATE>, underlining challenges facing country's manufacturers fight rising costs softening demand cooling economy.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-china-economy-pmi.html,54a4ddba79881011bed2ac73,null,"{main:China <DATE>December<\/DATE> Factory PMIs Suggest Economy Cooling Further, More Stimulus Expected,print_headline:China <DATE>December<\/DATE> Factory PMIs Suggest Economy Cooling Further, More Stimulus Expected}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Building loft <LOCATION>Portland</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Ore.</LOCATION>, suffused local character treasured flaws.",6,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Portland<\/LOCATION> Ore},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Interior Design Furnishings},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Lofts},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:4,value:Childs, <PERSON>Joan<\/PERSON> S <DATE>1949<\/DATE>-},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Real Estate Housing Residential},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:6,value:<PERSON>Zaret<\/PERSON>, Jerry <DATE>1943<\/DATE>-}]",Home & Garden,<PERSON>Joan Childs</PERSON> husband <PERSON>Jerry Zaret</PERSON> share transformation <LOCATION>Portland</LOCATION> industrial space <ORGANIZATION>Ford Model</ORGANIZATION> T factory spacious loft-like home.,The New York Times,[],Home,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/garden/20150101-LOCATION-slide-OF9V/20150101-LOCATION-slide-OF9V-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/garden/20150101-LOCATION-slide-OF9V/20150101-LOCATION-slide-OF9V-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/garden/20150101-LOCATION-slide-OF9V/20150101-LOCATION-slide-OF9V-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/garden/20150101-LOCATION-slide-OF9V/20150101-LOCATION-slide-OF9V-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/garden/20150101-LOCATION-slide-OF9V/20150101-LOCATION-slide-OF9V-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/garden/20150101-LOCATION-slide-OF9V/20150101-LOCATION-slide-OF9V-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",654,"Building loft <LOCATION>Portland</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Ore.</LOCATION>, suffused local character treasured flaws.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/garden/the-imperfectionists.html,54a48ee479881011bed29a74,null,"{content_kicker:On Location,main:The Imperfectionists,print_headline:The Imperfectionists,kicker:On Location}","{contributor:,original:By AMARA HOLSTEIN,person:[{firstname:Amara,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:HOLSTEIN}]}",article
"&#8220;Ways Modernism,&#8221; exhibition <LOCATION>Vienna</LOCATION>, contrasting styles early Modernist architects.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Hoffmann<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Josef<\/PERSON>},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:Loos, Adolf},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Architecture},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Austrian Museum of Applied Arts / Contemporary Art <LOCATION>Vienna<\/LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Austria<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Art}]",Arts,"<PERSON>Alice Rawsthorn</PERSON> Critic's Notebook on exhibit Ways to Modernism: <PERSON>Josef Hoffmann</PERSON>, <PERSON>Adolf Loos</PERSON> and Their Impact at <ORGANIZATION>MAK</ORGANIZATION>, Austrian Museum of Applied Arts/Contemporary Art in <LOCATION>Vienna</LOCATION>; exhibit compares competing visions of modernist architects <PERSON>Hoffman</PERSON> and Loos at time when new generation is paying attention to their work.",The New York Times,[],Culture,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/arts/MODERNISM/MODERNISM-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/arts/MODERNISM/MODERNISM-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/arts/MODERNISM/MODERNISM-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:448},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/arts/MODERNISM/MODERNISM-articleLarge.jpg,height:448},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/arts/MODERNISM/MODERNISM-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/arts/MODERNISM/MODERNISM-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1061,"&#8220;Ways Modernism,&#8221; exhibition <LOCATION>Vienna</LOCATION>, contrasting styles early Modernist architects.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/arts/design/josef-hoffmann-and-adolf-loos-contrasting-modernist-architects.html,54a46a4279881011bed2920d,Art & Design,"{content_kicker:Critic’s Notebook,main:Two Architects, Two Visions, One Diptych Early Modernism,seo:<PERSON>Josef Hoffmann Adolf Loos<\/PERSON>, Contrasting Modernist Architects,print_headline:Two Architects, Two Modernist Visions,kicker:Critic’s Notebook}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ALICE RAWSTHORN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Alice,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:RAWSTHORN}]}",article
"The <ORGANIZATION>Standard & Poor&#8217;</ORGANIZATION>s 500-stock index ended year 11.4 higher, double analysts expected beginning year.",,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Nasdaq Composite Index},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Standard & Poor's 500-Stock Index},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Stocks Bonds},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Dow Jones Stock Average}]",Business Day,null,The New York Times,[],Business,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,[],515,"The <ORGANIZATION>Standard & Poor&#8217;</ORGANIZATION>s 500-stock index ended year 11.4 higher, double analysts expected beginning year.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/business/daily-stock-market-activity.html,54a413507988102761d6e182,null,"{main:Market Ends Strong Year With Modest Decline,print_headline:Market Ends Strong Year With Modest Decline}","{contributor:,original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"The fine biggest Chinese pollution case signal officials crack businesses degraded <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>&#8217;s land, water air.",10,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:China},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:11,value:Wuxi Fu'an <ORGANIZATION>Chemical Plant Taixing Fu'an Chemical Co Ltd<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:12,value:Taizhou City Environmental Protection Assn},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:13,value:<ORGANIZATION>Zhenqing Chemical Taixing Zhenqing Chemical Co Ltd<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Water Pollution},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Fines Penalties},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Environment},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Suits Litigation Civil},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Agriculture Farming},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:7,value:Jiangsu Changlong Chemical Co},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:8,value:Jiangsu Shimeikang Pharmaceutical Co},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:9,value:Kam Taixing Chemical Co Jinhui Co},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:10,value:Shenlong Gong Division}]",World,Chinese provincial court upholds lower court verdict imposing fines totaling around <MONEY>$26 million</MONEY> on six companies convicted of dumping waste acid into water; pollution is growing concern in <LOCATION>China</LOCATION> and environmental protection laws are becoming stronger.,The New York Times,[],Foreign,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,[],673,"The fine biggest Chinese pollution case signal officials crack businesses degraded <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>&#8217;s land, water air.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/world/asia/chinese-court-orders-6-companies-to-pay-26-million-for-polluting.html,54a3ee097988102761d6dd37,Asia Pacific,"{main:Fines Total <MONEY>$26 Million<\/MONEY> for Polluters in <LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:Fines Total <MONEY>$26 Million<\/MONEY> for Polluters in <LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION>}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>EDWARD WONG<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Edward,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:WONG}]}",article
