snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"DISH Networks Inc <DATE>Thursday</DATE> make The Interview, controversial <ORGANIZATION>Sony Pictures Entertainment</ORGANIZATION> film fictitious assassination North Korean leader <PERSON>Kim Jong Un</PERSON>, pay-per-view option starting Jan 2.",null,[],Arts,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T14:13:13Z,[],173,"DISH Networks Inc <DATE>Thursday</DATE> make The Interview, controversial <ORGANIZATION>Sony Pictures Entertainment</ORGANIZATION> film fictitious assassination North Korean leader <PERSON>Kim Jong Un</PERSON>, pay-per-view option starting Jan 2.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/arts/01reuters-dish-theinterview.html,54a59cea7988102023c94688,null,"{main:DISH Network Make 'The Interview' Available January 2,print_headline:DISH Network Make 'The Interview' Available January 2}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Scaffolding around the exterior of the Broad in <LOCATION>Los Angeles</LOCATION> has been removed, though the museum’s opening date remains somewhat nebulous.",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Diller<\/PERSON>, Elizabeth},{name:glocations,rank:1,value:Los Angeles Calif},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Diller Scofidio<\/PERSON> & Renfro},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Architecture},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Art},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Museums}]",Arts,"Scaffolding around the exterior of the Broad in <LOCATION>Los Angeles</LOCATION> has been removed, though the museum’s opening date remains somewhat nebulous.",The New York Times,[],Culture,2014-12-31T17:21:43Z,[],282,null,Blog,http://artsbeat.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/broad-museum-shows-its-face/,54a479be79881011bed2959f,null,"{main:Broad Museum Shows Its Face,print_headline:Broad Museum Shows Its Face,kicker:ArtsBeat}","{original:By <PERSON>WILLIAM GRIMES<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:William,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:GRIMES}]}",blogpost
"<ORGANIZATION>Sony Pictures Entertainment</ORGANIZATION> added viewing options provocative comedy The Interview, making film <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> pay television operators doubling number independent theaters show movie.",null,[],Arts,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T13:45:40Z,[],376,"<ORGANIZATION>Sony Pictures Entertainment</ORGANIZATION> added viewing options provocative comedy The Interview, making film <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> pay television operators doubling number independent theaters show movie.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/arts/31reuters-northkorea-cyberattack-sony.html,54a4446a79881011bed28a1e,null,"{main:<ORGANIZATION>Sony<\/ORGANIZATION>'s 'Interview' Lands Pay TV 580 Theaters,print_headline:<ORGANIZATION>Sony<\/ORGANIZATION>'s 'Interview' Lands Pay TV 580 Theaters}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
<ORGANIZATION>Ambac Assurance Corp</ORGANIZATION> sued <ORGANIZATION>Bank of America Corp</ORGANIZATION> to recoup <MONEY>hundreds of millions of dollars</MONEY> of losses from insuring roughly <MONEY>$1.68 billion</MONEY> of securities backed at least in part by risky mortgages from the bank's <ORGANIZATION>Countrywide Home Loans</ORGANIZATION> unit.,null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T11:40:22Z,[],383,<ORGANIZATION>Ambac Assurance Corp</ORGANIZATION> sued <ORGANIZATION>Bank of America Corp</ORGANIZATION> to recoup <MONEY>hundreds of millions of dollars</MONEY> of losses from insuring roughly <MONEY>$1.68 billion</MONEY> of securities backed at least in part by risky mortgages from the bank's <ORGANIZATION>Countrywide Home Loans</ORGANIZATION> unit.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-bankofamerica-ambac-lawsuit.html,54a427987988102761d6e743,null,"{main:Ambac Sues Bank America Over Countrywide Mortgage Bonds,print_headline:Ambac Sues Bank America Over Countrywide Mortgage Bonds}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The <PERSON>Baltimore Ravens</PERSON>' security director accused groping woman pressing team's stadium <DATE>December</DATE> game, police court documents obtained <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>The Associated Press</ORGANIZATION>.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T00:52:00Z,[],835,"The <PERSON>Baltimore Ravens</PERSON>' security director accused groping woman pressing team's stadium <DATE>December</DATE> game, police court documents obtained <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>The Associated Press</ORGANIZATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/ap-fbn-ravens-security-director-charged.html,54a38fbc7988102761d6d256,null,"{main:Ravens Security Head Accused Groping Stadium,print_headline:Ravens Security Head Accused Groping Stadium}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"In <LOCATION>Cuba</LOCATION>, artists cut supplies Internet celebrated coterie international buyers, pipeline grow.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Art},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>Cuba<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Embargoes Sanctions},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:4,value:<PERSON>Garaicoa<\/PERSON>, Carlos},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:5,value:<PERSON>Lopez<\/PERSON>, Kadir}]",Arts,Thriving arts scene <LOCATION>Cuba</LOCATION> years attracted international attention lack real market makes difficult artists survive; hope thawing relations <ORGANIZATION>United</ORGANIZATION> states bring positive change.,The New York Times,[],Culture,2014-12-30T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/30/arts/JPARTCUBA2/JPARTCUBA2-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/arts/JPARTCUBA2/JPARTCUBA2-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/30/arts/JPARTCUBA2/JPARTCUBA2-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:368},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/arts/JPARTCUBA2/JPARTCUBA2-articleLarge.jpg,height:368},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/30/arts/JPARTCUBA2/JPARTCUBA2-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/arts/JPARTCUBA2/JPARTCUBA2-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1413,"In <LOCATION>Cuba</LOCATION>, artists cut supplies Internet celebrated coterie international buyers, pipeline grow.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/arts/cubas-art-scene-awaits-a-travel-boom.html,54a1e05a7988104803cc88be,Art & Design,"{main:<LOCATION>Cuba<\/LOCATION>&#8217;s Art Scene Awaits Travel Boom,print_headline:<LOCATION>Cuba<\/LOCATION>’s Art Scene Awaits a Travel Boom}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>VICTORIA BURNETT<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Victoria,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BURNETT}]}",article
"<ORGANIZATION>Sony Pictures</ORGANIZATION> said The Interview has earned more than <MONEY>$15 million 9.64 million pounds</MONEY> in online sales and another <MONEY>$2.8 million</MONEY> in theatres, an impressive return made possible by the publicity surrounding the cyberattack blamed on <LOCATION>North Korea</LOCATION>.",null,[],Arts,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-29T03:59:39Z,[],621,"<ORGANIZATION>Sony Pictures</ORGANIZATION> said The Interview has earned more than <MONEY>$15 million 9.64 million pounds</MONEY> in online sales and another <MONEY>$2.8 million</MONEY> in theatres, an impressive return made possible by the publicity surrounding the cyberattack blamed on <LOCATION>North Korea</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/29/arts/29reuters-northkorea-cyberattack-sony-downloads.html,54a118cf7988101f98e3ef3b,null,"{main:<ORGANIZATION>Sony<\/ORGANIZATION>'s 'The Interview' Makes <MONEY>$18 Million<\/MONEY> in Opening Weekend,print_headline:<ORGANIZATION>Sony<\/ORGANIZATION>'s 'The Interview' Makes <MONEY>$18 Million<\/MONEY> in Opening Weekend}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<ORGANIZATION>Sony Pictures</ORGANIZATION> said <ORGANIZATION>The Interview</ORGANIZATION> has earned more than <MONEY>$15 million</MONEY> in online sales and another <MONEY>$2.8 million</MONEY> in theaters, an impressive return made possible by the publicity surrounding the cyberattack blamed on <LOCATION>North Korea</LOCATION>.",null,[],Arts,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-28T17:50:03Z,[],618,"<ORGANIZATION>Sony Pictures</ORGANIZATION> said The Interview has earned more than <MONEY>$15 million</MONEY> in online sales and another <MONEY>$2.8 million</MONEY> in theaters, an impressive return made possible by the publicity surrounding the cyberattack blamed on <LOCATION>North Korea</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/28/arts/28reuters-northkorea-cyberattack-sony-downloads.html,54a0895f7988101f98e3ee35,null,"{main:<ORGANIZATION>Sony<\/ORGANIZATION>'s 'The Interview' Makes <MONEY>$18 Million<\/MONEY> in Opening Weekend,print_headline:<ORGANIZATION>Sony<\/ORGANIZATION>'s 'The Interview' Makes <MONEY>$18 Million<\/MONEY> in Opening Weekend}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Prompted record low interest rates, British government planning pay debts racked hundreds years.",14,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:Great <LOCATION>Britain<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Government Bonds},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Credit Debt},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:European Sovereign Debt Crisis <DATE>2010<\/DATE>-},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:5,value:<PERSON>Osborne<\/PERSON>, George}]",World,"Great <LOCATION>Britain</LOCATION> announced plans pay debts accrued hundreds years, dating back <DATE>1720</DATE>, due record low interest rates; move underscores government debt passed generation generation.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-28T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/28/world/BRITAIN/BRITAIN-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/world/BRITAIN/BRITAIN-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/28/world/BRITAIN/BRITAIN-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/world/BRITAIN/BRITAIN-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/28/world/BRITAIN/BRITAIN-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/world/BRITAIN/BRITAIN-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",893,"Prompted record low interest rates, British government planning pay debts racked hundreds years.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/world/that-debt-from-1720-britains-payment-is-coming.html,549ed3f67988105ced788726,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:That Debt From 1720? Britain&#8217;s Payment Is Coming ,print_headline:That Debt From 1720? <LOCATION>Britain<\/LOCATION>’s Payment Is Coming}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>STEPHEN<\/PERSON> CASTLE,person:[{firstname:Stephen,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:CASTLE}]}",article
The Th&#233;&#226;tre <ORGANIZATION>Royal de la Monnaie</ORGANIZATION>&#8217;s announcement tighter budget force end dance programming sets concern.,7,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Dancing},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:2,value:Theatre Royal de la Monnaie <LOCATION>Brussels<\/LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Belgium<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Morris<\/PERSON>, Mark}]",Arts,"Several prominent choreographers, including <PERSON>Mark Morris</PERSON>, speak elimination dance programming <LOCATION>Belgium</LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>Theatre Royal de la Monnaie</ORGANIZATION>, source cutting-edge music dance productions.",The New York Times,[],Culture,2014-12-27T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/27/arts/submorris1/submorris1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/arts/submorris1/submorris1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/27/arts/submorris1/submorris1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:496},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/arts/submorris1/submorris1-articleLarge.jpg,height:496},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/27/arts/submorris1/submorris1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/arts/submorris1/submorris1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",968,The Th&#233;&#226;tre <ORGANIZATION>Royal de la Monnaie</ORGANIZATION>&#8217;s announcement tighter budget force end dance programming sets concern.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/27/arts/dance/dance-leaders-decry-cuts-in-belgium.html,549dc7007988105ced7885ed,Dance,"{main:Dance Leaders Deplore Cuts <LOCATION>Belgium<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:Dance Leaders Deplore Cuts <LOCATION>Belgium<\/LOCATION>}","{contributor:,original:By ROSLYN SULCAS,person:[{firstname:Roslyn,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SULCAS}]}",article
