snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
<ORGANIZATION>Computer Sciences Corp.</ORGANIZATION> says it will pay <MONEY>$190 million</MONEY> and restate three years of financial results in a proposed settlement with the <ORGANIZATION>Securities and Exchange Commission</ORGANIZATION>.,null,[],Business Day,null,A.,[],None,2014-12-29T19:16:09Z,[],129,<ORGANIZATION>Computer Sciences Corp.</ORGANIZATION> says it will pay <MONEY>$190 million</MONEY> and restate three years of financial results in a proposed settlement with the <ORGANIZATION>Securities and Exchange Commission</ORGANIZATION>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/29/business/ap-us-computer-sciences-sec.html,54a1ef757988104803cc88de,null,"{main:Computer Sciences to Pay <MONEY>$190M<\/MONEY> in <ORGANIZATION>SEC<\/ORGANIZATION> Settlement,print_headline:Computer Sciences to Pay <MONEY>$190M<\/MONEY> in <ORGANIZATION>SEC<\/ORGANIZATION> Settlement}","{original:By THE ASSO.IATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Congress stint budget support make <ORGANIZATION>Secret Service</ORGANIZATION> job.,18,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:Secret Service},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Editorials},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:White House Building <LOCATION>Washington<\/LOCATION>, DC}]",Opinion,"Editorial cites bipartisan review highlighting number gaps shortcomings presidential security; points report, prompted <DATE>September</DATE> incident man scaled <ORGANIZATION>White House</ORGANIZATION> fence, paints picture <ORGANIZATION>Secret Service</ORGANIZATION> insular stretched thin; urges <ORGANIZATION>Congress</ORGANIZATION> stint budget important agency.",The New York Times,[],Editorial,2014-12-29T00:00:00Z,[],345,Congress stint budget support make <ORGANIZATION>Secret Service</ORGANIZATION> job.,Editorial,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/29/opinion/alarming-gaps-in-presidential-protection.html,54a0b3787988101f98e3ee76,null,"{content_kicker:Editorial,main:Alarming Gaps Presidential Protection,print_headline:Alarming Gaps Presidential Protection,kicker:Editorial}","{contributor:,original:By THE EDITORIAL BOARD,person:[],organization:THE EDITORIAL BOARD}",article
"Former hostages Syrian rebel commanders offered information believed free American captives, officials uninterested.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Terrorism},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Kidnapping Hostages},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Islamic State Iraq <LOCATION>Syria<\/LOCATION> ISIS},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:4,value:<LOCATION>Syria<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:5,value:<PERSON>Foley<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>James<\/PERSON> 1973-2014},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:6,value:Abo Aljoud, Louai},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:7,value:Kassig, <PERSON>Peter Edward<\/PERSON> 1988-2014},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:8,value:Sotloff, <PERSON>Steven<\/PERSON> J},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:9,value:United States International Relations},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:10,value:Federal Bureau Investigation}]",World,"Former hostages Syrian rebel commanders offered information believed helped free J.mes Foley Americans hostages officials uninterested; relatives victims, retired law enforcement officials, interpretation hostage negotiation policy changed Sept 11 terrorist attacks warn 'no ransom' policy closes options.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-28T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/27/world/28hostage/28hostage-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/world/28hostage/28hostage-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/27/world/28hostage/28hostage-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/world/28hostage/28hostage-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/27/world/28hostage/28hostage-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/world/28hostage/28hostage-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",4027,"Former hostages Syrian rebel commanders offered information believed free American captives, officials uninterested.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/world/middleeast/the-cost-of-the-us-ban-on-paying-for-hostages.html,549f5faa79881001534d1fcb,Middle East,"{main:The Cost <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Ban Paying Hostages,print_headline:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Policy No Ransom Closes Off Other Options}","{contributor:<PERSON>Eric Schmitt<\/PERSON> contributed reporting <LOCATION>Washington<\/LOCATION>, <PERSON>Michael S. Schmidt<\/PERSON> <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION>.,original:By RUKMINI CALLIMACHI,person:[{firstname:Rukmini,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:CALLIMACHI}]}",article
Here’s how The Times’s editorial board reacted to the year’s biggest news events as they unfolded.,,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Two Thousand Fourteen},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:11,value:Executive Orders Memorandums},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:12,value:Torture},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:13,value:Marijuana},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:14,value:Minimum Wage},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:15,value:Automobile Safety Features Defects},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:16,value:Recalls Bans Products},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:17,value:Same-Sex Marriage, Civil Unions Domestic Partnerships},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:18,value:Holder, <PERSON>Eric<\/PERSON> H Jr},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:19,value:Abortion},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:20,value:Women's Rights},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Editorials},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:21,value:Global Warming},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:3,value:<LOCATION>Cuba<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Police Brutality, Misconduct Shootings},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:5,value:Islamic State Iraq <LOCATION>Syria<\/LOCATION> ISIS},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:United States Politics Government},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:7,value:<LOCATION>Ukraine<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:8,value:<PERSON>Putin<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Vladimir<\/PERSON> V},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:9,value:Ebola Virus},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:10,value:Immigration Emigration}]",Opinion,null,The New York Times,[],Editorial,2014-12-28T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/23/opinion/mostest-protest/mostest-protest-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/23/opinion/mostest-protest/mostest-protest-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/23/opinion/mostest-protest/mostest-protest-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/23/opinion/mostest-protest/mostest-protest-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/23/opinion/mostest-protest/mostest-protest-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/23/opinion/mostest-protest/mostest-protest-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1235,Here’s how The Times’s editorial board reacted to the year’s biggest news events as they unfolded.,Editorial,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/opinion/torture-race-marijuana-and-12-other-big-issues-of-2014.html,549f2ccf79881001534d1fa9,null,"{content_kicker:Editorial,main:Torture, Race, Marijuana 12 Other Big Issues 2014,kicker:Editorial}","{contributor:,original:By THE EDITORIAL BOARD,person:[],organization:THE EDITORIAL BOARD}",article
"<LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION>'s Cabinet approved <MONEY>3.5 trillion yen $29 billion</MONEY> in fresh stimulus <DATE>Saturday</DATE> for the ailing economy, pledging to get growth back on track and restore the country's precarious public finances.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-27T05:47:03Z,[],665,"<LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION>'s Cabinet approved <MONEY>3.5 trillion yen $29 billion</MONEY> in fresh stimulus <DATE>Saturday</DATE> for the ailing economy, pledging to get growth back on track and restore the country's precarious public finances.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/27/world/asia/ap-as-japan-economy.html,549e8f067988105ced7886ea,Asia Pacific,"{main:<LOCATION>Japan<\/LOCATION>'s Abe Unleashes Stimulus Plan Spur Growth,print_headline:<LOCATION>Japan<\/LOCATION>'s Abe Unleashes Stimulus Plan Spur Growth}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"A selected guide cultural events children, teenagers families <LOCATION>New York City</LOCATION>.",32,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Museums},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Children Childhood},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Culture Arts}]",Arts,null,The New York Times,[],Weekend,2014-12-26T00:00:00Z,[],3892,"A selected guide cultural events children, teenagers families <LOCATION>New York City</LOCATION>.",Schedule,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/26/arts/spare-times-for-children-for-dec-26-jan-1.html,549c9b5b7988103babf08a7e,null,"{main:Spare Times Children <DATE>Dec. 26-Jan<\/DATE>. 1,print_headline:Spare Times: For Children}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>LAUREL GRAEBER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Laurel,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:GRAEBER}]}",article
"A selected, critical guide visual arts <LOCATION>New York City</LOCATION>.",25,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Art},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Museums}]",Arts,null,The New York Times,[],Weekend,2014-12-26T00:00:00Z,[],5269,"A selected, critical guide visual arts <LOCATION>New York City</LOCATION>.",Schedule,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/26/arts/design/museum-gallery-listings-for-dec-26-jan-1.html,549c98247988103babf08a78,Art & Design,"{main:Museum &amp; <ORGANIZATION>Gallery Listings Dec.<\/ORGANIZATION> 26-Jan. 1,print_headline:The Listings: Art}",[],article
"The past year’s developments are dots on a map, worthy of attention but hard to assemble into a narrative that says much more than ‘stuck.’",,"[{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Guantanamo Bay Naval Base Cuba<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Habeas Corpus},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Edwards<\/PERSON>, Harry T},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:4,value:<PERSON>Obama<\/PERSON>, Barack},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:5,value:Supreme Court US},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:6,value:<PERSON>Breyer<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Stephen<\/PERSON> G},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:7,value:<PERSON>Bush<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>George<\/PERSON> W},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:8,value:Hussain, Abdul al-Qader Ahmed},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:9,value:Ali, <PERSON>Abdul Razak<\/PERSON>}]",Opinion,null,The New York Times,[],Editorial,2014-12-25T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/11/01/opinion/greenhouse-circular/greenhouse-circular-thumbWide-v2.png},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/11/01/opinion/greenhouse-circular/greenhouse-circular-thumbWide-v2.png,height:126},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/11/01/opinion/greenhouse-circular/greenhouse-circular-thumbStandard-v2.png,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/11/01/opinion/greenhouse-circular/greenhouse-circular-thumbStandard-v2.png,height:75}]",1524,"The past year’s developments are dots on a map, worthy of attention but hard to assemble into a narrative that says much more than ‘stuck.’",Op-Ed,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/25/opinion/guantnamo-dreams.html,549b4b047988100306690f1a,null,"{content_kicker:Contributing Op-Ed Writer,main:Guantánamo Dreams,kicker:Op-Ed | <PERSON>Linda Greenhouse<\/PERSON>| <PERSON>Linda Greenhouse<\/PERSON>}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>LINDA<\/PERSON> GREENHOUSE,person:[{firstname:Linda,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:GREENHOUSE}]}",article
"Also, force-quit apps Windows 8.1.",6,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:iOS Operating System},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Windows Operating System},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Computers Internet},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:iPhone},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Mobile Applications},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Web Browsers},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:Smartphones}]",Technology,"Personal Tech Q&A clearing space update iPhone's iOS, force-quitting apps Windows 8.1 mouse keyboard, Tip Week altering size individual elements web pages web browsers.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-25T00:00:00Z,[],619,"Also, force-quit apps Windows 8.1.",Question,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/25/technology/personaltech/trying-to-update-an-overloaded-iphone.html,549b24c97988100306690eae,Personal Tech,"{content_kicker:Q&A,main:Trying Update Overloaded iPhone,print_headline:Trying Update Overloaded iPhone,kicker:Q&A}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>J. D. BIERSDORFER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:J.,role:reported,organization:,rank:1}]}",article
"<PERSON>Ava DuVernay</PERSON>&#8217;s film &#8220;<LOCATION>Selma</LOCATION>&#8221; civil rights demonstrators <DATE>March 1965</DATE> Alabama bridge era black Americans, progress made promises unkept.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Movies},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:DuVernay, Ava},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Oyelowo<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>David<\/PERSON>},{is_major:Y,name:creative_works,rank:4,value:Selma Movie}]",Movies,"A O <PERSON>Scott</PERSON> reviews movie <LOCATION>Selma</LOCATION>, directed <PERSON>Ava DuVernay</PERSON> starring <PERSON>David Oyelowo</PERSON>.",The New York Times,[],Culture,2014-12-25T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/25/arts/SELMA/SELMA-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/arts/SELMA/SELMA-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/25/arts/SELMA/SELMA-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:382},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/arts/SELMA/SELMA-articleLarge.jpg,height:382},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/25/arts/SELMA/SELMA-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/arts/SELMA/SELMA-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1370,"<PERSON>Ava DuVernay</PERSON>&#8217;s film &#8220;<LOCATION>Selma</LOCATION>&#8221; civil rights demonstrators <DATE>March 1965</DATE> Alabama bridge era black Americans, progress made promises unkept.",Review,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/25/arts/in-selma-king-is-just-one-of-the-heroes.html,549a95b17988102d96d567c8,null,"{content_kicker:Movie Review,main:A 50-Mile <DATE>March<\/DATE>, Nearly 50 Years Later,seo:In &#8216;<LOCATION>Selma<\/LOCATION>,&#8217; King Is Just One Many Heroes,print_headline:A 50-Mile <DATE>March<\/DATE>, Nearly 50 Years Later,kicker:Movie Review | '<LOCATION>Selma<\/LOCATION>'| 'Selma'}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>A. O. SCOTT<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:A.,role:reported,organization:,middlename:O.,rank:1,lastname:SCOTT}]}",article
