snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"The economy finally emerged financial crisis recession 2007-9, long stagnation middle-class incomes continues.",10,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:United States Economy},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Income Inequality},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:United States Politics Government},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Corporate Taxes},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:5,value:Infrastructure Public Works},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Labor Jobs},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:Taxation}]",<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,"Political Memo; bipartisan economists seemingly frustrated persistent, generation-long stagnation middle-class incomes; Democrats Republicans big policy shifts address trend, Democrats pushing heavy investment infrastructure spending Republicans calling overhauling energy policy corporate tax code.",The New York Times,[],National,2014-12-30T00:00:00Z,[],1081,"The economy finally emerged financial crisis recession 2007-9, long stagnation middle-class incomes continues.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/us/politics/for-solution-to-income-stagnation-republicans-and-democrats-revise-their-playbooks.html,54a1f9067988104803cc88eb,Politics,"{content_kicker:Political Memo,main:For Solution Income Stagnation, Republicans Democrats Revise Their Playbooks,print_headline:For Solution Income Stagnation, Parties Revise Their Playbooks,kicker:Political Memo}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>JOHN HARWOOD<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:John,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:HARWOOD}]}",article
The <ORGANIZATION>Financial Reporting Council</ORGANIZATION> said that it would review <ORGANIZATION>PricewaterhouseCoopers</ORGANIZATION>’ role in reporting to British regulators on the bank’s compliance with client asset rules after <ORGANIZATION>Barclays</ORGANIZATION> was fined <MONEY>$58.9 million</MONEY> in <DATE>September</DATE> for failing to properly...,null,"[{name:glocations,rank:1,value:Great <LOCATION>Britain<\/LOCATION>},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:<ORGANIZATION>Barclays PLC<\/ORGANIZATION>},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:Financial Conduct Authority Great <LOCATION>Britain<\/LOCATION>},{name:organizations,rank:3,value:PricewaterhouseCoopers},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Fines Penalties},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Regulation Deregulation Industry}]",Business Day,The <ORGANIZATION>Financial Reporting Council</ORGANIZATION> said that it would review <ORGANIZATION>PricewaterhouseCoopers</ORGANIZATION>’ role in reporting to British regulators on the bank’s compliance with client asset rules after <ORGANIZATION>Barclays</ORGANIZATION> was fined <MONEY>$58.9 million</MONEY> in <DATE>September</DATE> for failing to properly segregate client assets.,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-22T07:58:32Z,[],227,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/22/corporate-governance-watchdog-to-examine-barclays-auditor/,549815fb7988104a1e0df348,Dealbook,"{main:Corporate Governance Watchdog Examine Barclays' Auditor,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>CHAD BRAY<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Chad,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BRAY}]}",blogpost
"<PERSON>Sergei Pugachev</PERSON>, a Russian tycoon once dubbed the cashier to the <ORGANIZATION>Kremlin</ORGANIZATION>, failed in a bid on <DATE>Friday</DATE> to overturn a British court order which froze <MONEY>$2 billion</MONEY> of his assets in a case linked to the insolvency of Russian bank Mezhprombank.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-19T09:31:47Z,[],364,"<PERSON>Sergei Pugachev</PERSON>, a Russian tycoon once dubbed the cashier to the <ORGANIZATION>Kremlin</ORGANIZATION>, failed in a bid on <DATE>Friday</DATE> to overturn a British court order which froze <MONEY>$2 billion</MONEY> of his assets in a case linked to the insolvency of Russian bank Mezhprombank.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/19/business/19reuters-britain-russia-pugachev.html,5494378579881048d26b32c7,null,"{main:Russian Tycoon Pugachev Loses UK Asset Freeze Appeal,print_headline:Russian Tycoon Pugachev Loses UK Asset Freeze Appeal}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
How young Iranian refugee quit boardrooms <LOCATION>London</LOCATION> risky stake land birth.,,"[{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:1,value:Iran},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Economic Conditions Trends},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Social Conditions Trends}]",Opinion,null,The New York Times,[],Editorial,2014-12-13T13:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/13/opinion/13cohen/13cohen-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/13/opinion/13cohen/13cohen-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/13/opinion/13cohen/13cohen-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:473},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/13/opinion/13cohen/13cohen-articleLarge.jpg,height:473},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/13/opinion/13cohen/13cohen-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/13/opinion/13cohen/13cohen-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1628,How young Iranian refugee quit boardrooms <LOCATION>London</LOCATION> risky stake land birth.,Op-Ed,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/13/opinion/roger-cohen-the-way-back-to-iran.html,548b719679881004157bb7a1,null,"{content_kicker:Op-Ed Columnist,main:The Way Back <LOCATION>Iran<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:The Way Back <LOCATION>Iran<\/LOCATION>,kicker:Op-Ed Columnist}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ROGER COHEN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Roger,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:COHEN}]}",article
Retirees covered financially troubled multiemployer pensions benefits cut congressional spending deal government running.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-11T03:26:53Z,[],903,Retirees covered financially troubled multiemployer pensions benefits cut congressional spending deal government running.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/11/us/politics/ap-us-congress-pensions-qa.html,548956047988104c1745a912,Politics,"{main:Multiemployer Pensions Could Face Cuts,print_headline:Multiemployer Pensions Could Face Cuts}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Retirees covered financially troubled multiemployer pensions benefits cut congressional spending deal government running.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-10T17:59:42Z,[],903,Retirees covered financially troubled multiemployer pensions benefits cut congressional spending deal government running.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/10/us/politics/ap-us-congress-pensions-qa.html,5488d1317988104c17459eee,Politics,"{main:Deal Allow Multiemployer Pension Benefits Cuts,print_headline:Deal Allow Multiemployer Pension Benefits Cuts}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"The <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> government on <DATE>Monday</DATE> sued <ORGANIZATION>Deutsche Bank AG</ORGANIZATION>, seeking to recoup more than <MONEY>$190 million</MONEY> from the German bank over alleged tax fraud more than 14 years ago.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-08T15:39:48Z,[],349,"The <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> government on <DATE>Monday</DATE> sued <ORGANIZATION>Deutsche Bank AG</ORGANIZATION>, seeking to recoup more than <MONEY>$190 million</MONEY> from the German bank over alleged tax fraud more than 14 years ago.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/08/business/08reuters-deutschebank-lawsuit.html,54860d427988101981f9ea28,null,"{main:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Sues <ORGANIZATION>Deutsche Bank<\/ORGANIZATION> for Alleged Tax Fraud, Seeks <MONEY>$190 Million<\/MONEY>,print_headline:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Sues <ORGANIZATION>Deutsche Bank<\/ORGANIZATION> for Alleged Tax Fraud, Seeks <MONEY>$190 Million<\/MONEY>}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
The report extra money ensure banks survive repeat global financial crisis.,,"[{is_major:N,name:unknown,rank:1,value:}]",Business Day,null,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-08T11:30:00Z,[],499,The report extra money ensure banks survive repeat global financial crisis.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/08/business/international/report-calls-for-australia-banks-to-set-aside-more-capital.html,548412667988106fd483d6bb,International Business,"{main:Report Calls <LOCATION>Australia<\/LOCATION> Banks Set Aside More Capital,print_headline:Report Calls <LOCATION>Australia<\/LOCATION> Banks Set Aside More Capital}","{contributor:,original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Multiemployer pension plans, involving unionized workers, common industries coal mining, trucking construction. But they&#8217;re running money.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Pensions Retirement Plans},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Retirement},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:401k, 403b 457 Plans},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Labor Jobs}]",Business Day,"<ORGANIZATION>Floyd Norris High & Low Finance</ORGANIZATION> column notes annual report released <ORGANIZATION>Pension Benefit Guaranty Corporation</ORGANIZATION> shows multiemployer pension plans run money years; warns absent legislation, pensions retired workers eliminated; laments political system unwilling taxpayer-supported solution.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-05T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/05/business/Norris/<ORGANIZATION>Norris-thumbWide<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/05/business/Norris/<ORGANIZATION>Norris-thumbWide<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/05/business/Norris/Norris-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:833},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/05/business/Norris/Norris-articleLarge.jpg,height:833},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/05/business/Norris/<ORGANIZATION>Norris-thumbStandard<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/05/business/Norris/<ORGANIZATION>Norris-thumbStandard<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg,height:75}]",1194,"Multiemployer pension plans, involving unionized workers, common industries coal mining, trucking construction. But they&#8217;re running money.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/05/business/without-new-laws-endangered-pensions-may-die.html,5480e8ae7988103739e172c4,null,"{content_kicker:High & Low Finance,main:A Strategy Pensions Risk Extinction,print_headline:A Strategy Pensions Risk Extinction,kicker:High &amp; Low Finance}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>FLOYD NORRIS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Floyd,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:NORRIS}]}",article
"<LOCATION>China</LOCATION> <DATE>Sunday</DATE> issued draft regulations introduce bank deposit insurance system time, latest series steps fully liberalise interest rates banks compete wholly commercial basis.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-11-30T05:03:00Z,[],578,"<LOCATION>China</LOCATION> <DATE>Sunday</DATE> issued draft regulations introduce bank deposit insurance system time, latest series steps fully liberalise interest rates banks compete wholly commercial basis.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/11/30/business/30reuters-china-cenbank-deposits.html,547aeba97988101f1558b0fc,null,"{main:China Launches Draft Rules Insurance Bank Deposits,print_headline:China Launches Draft Rules Insurance Bank Deposits}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
