snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Chinese property developer <ORGANIZATION>Kaisa Group Holdings</ORGANIZATION> said it had failed to repay a <MONEY>HK$400 million 33 million pounds</MONEY> loan and warned it may default on more debt, the latest problem to hit the firm amid a downturn in the real estate sector.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T21:46:17Z,[],322,"Chinese property developer <ORGANIZATION>Kaisa Group Holdings</ORGANIZATION> said it had failed to repay a <MONEY>HK$400 million 33 million pounds</MONEY> loan and warned it may default on more debt, the latest problem to hit the firm amid a downturn in the real estate sector.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-china-kaisa-group-debt.html,54a607197988102023c95255,null,"{main:<LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION> Developer Kaisa Says Fails to Repay <MONEY>$51 Mln<\/MONEY> Loan, May Default on Others,print_headline:<LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION> Developer Kaisa Says Fails to Repay <MONEY>$51 Mln<\/MONEY> Loan, May Default on Others}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<ORGANIZATION>Hyundai Motor Co</ORGANIZATION> affiliate <ORGANIZATION>Kia Motors Corp</ORGANIZATION> forecast sales year grow slowest pace <DATE>2003</DATE>, hampered capacity constraints weaker yen give Japanese rivals edge key markets.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T18:11:36Z,[],387,"<ORGANIZATION>Hyundai Motor Co</ORGANIZATION> affiliate <ORGANIZATION>Kia Motors Corp</ORGANIZATION> forecast sales year grow slowest pace <DATE>2003</DATE>, hampered capacity constraints weaker yen give Japanese rivals edge key markets.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-hyundai-motor-kia-motors-sales.html,54a5d48a7988102023c94dd6,null,"{main:Hyundai-Kia See <DATE>2015<\/DATE> Sales Growth Weakest 12 Years,print_headline:Hyundai-Kia See <DATE>2015<\/DATE> Sales Growth Weakest 12 Years}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Gunmen attacked truck carrying Kenyan soldiers border <LOCATION>Somalia</LOCATION> <DATE>Thursday</DATE>, wounding, police, assault bore hallmarks <LOCATION>Somalia</LOCATION>'s Islamist militant group al Shabaab.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T14:45:16Z,[],332,"Gunmen attacked truck carrying Kenyan soldiers border <LOCATION>Somalia</LOCATION> <DATE>Thursday</DATE>, wounding, police, assault bore hallmarks <LOCATION>Somalia</LOCATION>'s Islamist militant group al Shabaab.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/world/africa/01reuters-kenya-attacks.html,54a5a41a7988102023c948b1,<LOCATION>Africa</LOCATION>,"{main:Three Kenyan Soldiers Wounded Gun Attack Near Somali Border,print_headline:Three Kenyan Soldiers Wounded Gun Attack Near Somali Border}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
Detective Shaft Africa track slave-trading operation entangled international scheme corruption murder. His pursuit ruthless slave traders non-stop fight save skin.,null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T10:21:37Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/06/movies/video-shaft-in-africa/video-shaft-in-africa-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/06/movies/video-shaft-in-africa/video-shaft-in-africa-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/06/movies/video-shaft-in-africa/video-shaft-in-africa-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/06/movies/video-shaft-in-africa/video-shaft-in-africa-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/06/movies/video-shaft-in-africa/video-shaft-in-africa-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/06/movies/video-shaft-in-africa/video-shaft-in-africa-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",38,Detective Shaft Africa track slave-trading operation entangled international scheme corruption murder. His pursuit ruthless slave traders non-stop fight save skin.,Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003372997/shaft-in-africa.html,54a5660679881011bed2cb2b,null,{"main":"Shaft In <LOCATION>Africa<\/LOCATION>"},"{original:Warner Home Video,person:[{firstname:Warner,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Home,rank:1,lastname:Video}]}",multimedia
"<LOCATION>Italy</LOCATION>'s 89-year-old President <PERSON>Giorgio Napolitano</PERSON> <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> step age, leaving Prime Minister <PERSON>Matteo Renzi</PERSON> facing delicate political challenge replace.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T04:46:46Z,[],467,"<LOCATION>Italy</LOCATION>'s 89-year-old President <PERSON>Giorgio Napolitano</PERSON> <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> step age, leaving Prime Minister <PERSON>Matteo Renzi</PERSON> facing delicate political challenge replace.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/world/europe/01reuters-italy-president-resignation.html,54a5180479881011bed2b9b6,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:<LOCATION>Italy<\/LOCATION> President Says He Will Step Down Soon,print_headline:<LOCATION>Italy<\/LOCATION> President Says He Will Step Down Soon}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"On verge making partner, <PERSON>Josh Pratt</PERSON>'s life turned upside <ORGANIZATION>SEC</ORGANIZATION> investigates head multibillion-dollar hedge fund insider trading. Forced well-timed vacation asked, <PERSON>Josh</PERSON> finds Bangk",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T01:28:53Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-a-stranger-in-paradise/video-a-stranger-in-paradise-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-a-stranger-in-paradise/video-a-stranger-in-paradise-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-a-stranger-in-paradise/video-a-stranger-in-paradise-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-a-stranger-in-paradise/video-a-stranger-in-paradise-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-a-stranger-in-paradise/video-a-stranger-in-paradise-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-a-stranger-in-paradise/video-a-stranger-in-paradise-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",41,"On verge making partner, <PERSON>Josh Pratt</PERSON>'s life turned upside <ORGANIZATION>SEC</ORGANIZATION> investigates head multibillion-dollar hedge fund insider trading. Forced well-timed vacation asked, <PERSON>Josh</PERSON> finds Bangk",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003378125/a-stranger-in-paradise.html,54a4e92879881011bed2af14,null,{"main":"A Stranger In Paradise"},"{original:Freestyle Digital Media,person:[{firstname:Freestyle,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Digital,rank:1,lastname:Media}]}",multimedia
"We wrestle underlying, unresolved issues: police-community relations, functional bias policing, disparities force.",,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Police Brutality, Misconduct Shootings},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Demonstrations, Protests Riots},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Attacks Police},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:United States Politics Government},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:5,value:Brinsley, Ismaaiyl Abdullah},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:6,value:Liu, Wenjian 1982-2014},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:7,value:Ramos, Rafael 1974-2014},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:8,value:<PERSON>Byrne<\/PERSON>, Edward R 1966-88}]",Opinion,null,The New York Times,[],Editorial,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/11/01/opinion/blow-circular/blow-circular-thumbWide-v2.png},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/11/01/opinion/blow-circular/blow-circular-thumbWide-v2.png,height:126},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/11/01/opinion/blow-circular/blow-circular-thumbStandard-v2.png,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/11/01/opinion/blow-circular/blow-circular-thumbStandard-v2.png,height:75}]",1949,"We wrestle underlying, unresolved issues: police-community relations, functional bias policing, disparities force.",Op-Ed,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/opinion/charles-m-blow-look-back-to-move-forward.html,54a4beb479881011bed2a567,null,"{content_kicker:Op-Ed Columnist,main:Look Back Move Forward,kicker:Op-Ed Columnist}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>CHARLES M.<\/PERSON> BLOW,person:[{firstname:Charles,role:reported,organization:,rank:1}]}",article
"With creepy ballads unhappy tales, <PERSON>Michael Daves</PERSON> brought <ORGANIZATION>All-Star Bluegrass Throwdown Bell House Brooklyn</ORGANIZATION> <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Music},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:2,value:<ORGANIZATION>Bell House Brooklyn<\/ORGANIZATION>, NY, Bar},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Daves<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Michael<\/PERSON>}]",Arts,"<PERSON>Jon Pareles</PERSON> reviews All-Star Bluegrass Throwdown, music event organized guitarist singer <ORGANIZATION>Michael Daves Bell House Brooklyn</ORGANIZATION>.",The New York Times,[],Culture,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/arts/SUB-BLUEGRASS/SUB-BLUEGRASS-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/arts/SUB-BLUEGRASS/SUB-BLUEGRASS-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/arts/SUB-BLUEGRASS/SUB-BLUEGRASS-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:401},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/arts/SUB-BLUEGRASS/SUB-BLUEGRASS-articleLarge.jpg,height:401},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/arts/SUB-BLUEGRASS/SUB-BLUEGRASS-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/arts/SUB-BLUEGRASS/SUB-BLUEGRASS-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",579,"With creepy ballads unhappy tales, <PERSON>Michael Daves</PERSON> brought <ORGANIZATION>All-Star Bluegrass Throwdown Bell House Brooklyn</ORGANIZATION> <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.",Review,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/arts/michael-daves-brings-bluegrass-to-the-bell-house.html,54a4772a79881011bed2950a,Music,"{content_kicker:Music Review,main:Gather &#8217;Round, Y&#8217;all, It&#8217;s Bluegrass Time,seo:<PERSON>Michael Daves<\/PERSON> Brings Bluegrass Bell House,print_headline:Gather ’Round, Y’all, It’s Bluegrass Time,kicker:Music Review}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>JON PARELES<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Jon,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:PARELES}]}",article
"The <ORGANIZATION>Standard & Poor&#8217;</ORGANIZATION>s 500-stock index ended year 11.4 higher, double analysts expected beginning year.",,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Nasdaq Composite Index},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Standard & Poor's 500-Stock Index},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Stocks Bonds},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Dow Jones Stock Average}]",Business Day,null,The New York Times,[],Business,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,[],515,"The <ORGANIZATION>Standard & Poor&#8217;</ORGANIZATION>s 500-stock index ended year 11.4 higher, double analysts expected beginning year.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/business/daily-stock-market-activity.html,54a413507988102761d6e182,null,"{main:Market Ends Strong Year With Modest Decline,print_headline:Market Ends Strong Year With Modest Decline}","{contributor:,original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"CARR--<PERSON>Peter F., Jr.</PERSON>, beloved son, devoted loyal father, loving brother treasured friend, died <DATE>December 26, 2014</DATE> suspected heart attack. He 69. Peter born <DATE>October 20</DATE>, 1945 <PERSON>Peter F. Carr</PERSON>, Sr. <PERSON>Helen B. Carr</PERSON> nee Trainer...",null,[],Paid Death Notices,null,The New York Times,[],Classified,2014-12-31T19:17:27Z,[],248,"<!-- PETER CARR -->CARR--<PERSON>Peter F., Jr.</PERSON>, beloved son, devoted and loyal father, loving brother and treasured friend, died on <DATE>December 26, 2014</DATE> of a suspected heart attack. He was 69. <PERSON>Peter</PERSON> was born <DATE>October 20, 1945</DATE> to <PERSON>Peter F. Carr</PERSON>, Sr. and <PERSON>Helen B. Carr</PERSON> nee Trainer in <LOCATION>Pawtucket</LOCATION>, RI. He attended <ORGANIZATION>St. Pius X Prep Seminary</ORGANIZATION>, Seminary of the <ORGANIZATION>Immaculate Conception</ORGANIZATION> and <ORGANIZATION>Fordham University</ORGANIZATION>. Peter retired from his position as an institutional sales trader at <ORGANIZATION>Stephens Inc.</ORGANIZATION> in <LOCATION>Little Rock</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>AR</LOCATION>, where he spent the majority of his professional career. <PERSON>Peter</PERSON>, known to many friends as <PERSON>Pete</PERSON>, was an avid and voracious reader. He loved horses and was lifelong devotee of horse racing, an interest he shared with many close friends. <PERSON>Peter</PERSON> is survived by his son <PERSON>Kevin</PERSON>, mother <PERSON>Helen</PERSON> of <LOCATION>Southampton</LOCATION>, NY, sister <PERSON>Karen</PERSON> and her wife <PERSON>Yvette Christofilis</PERSON> of <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>, sister <ORGANIZATION>Sharon of Southampton</ORGANIZATION>, NY and many dear friends and relatives. <PERSON>Peter</PERSON> was predeceased by his father <PERSON>Peter</PERSON>, Sr. in <DATE>1985</DATE>. <PERSON>Peter</PERSON>, like his father, was cherished by all who knew him. There will be a Funeral Mass at <ORGANIZATION>The Catholic Church of St. John The Baptist</ORGANIZATION> in <LOCATION>Hot Springs</LOCATION>, AR, on <DATE>December 31, 2014</DATE> at 10am. A graveside memorial service in <LOCATION>Coventry</LOCATION>, RI. will be announced at a future date. In lieu of flowers, contributions can be made to American Diabetes <a rel=nofollow href=www.diabetes.org>www.diabetes.org</a> <ORGANIZATION>American Heart Association</ORGANIZATION>, <a rel=nofollow href=www.heart.org>www.heart.org</a> or<br/><br/> Group For The East End, <a rel=nofollow href=www.groupfortheeastend.org>www.groupfortheeastend.org</a> For <PERSON>Peter</PERSON>, a small act of kindness would be the gift most appreciated.<br><br> ",Paid Death Notice,http://www.legacy.com/Link.asp?I=LS000173684841,54a51aa279881011bed2ba4a,null,"{main:Paid Notice: Deaths  CARR, PETER}",null,article
