snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Hollywood action film star <PERSON>Rafe Stoker</PERSON> has sunk <MONEY>$130,000</MONEY> of his own money into his own production, but can't find legitimate financing to complete the film. His mob-connected investor demands an exorbitant amount of collateral and a guarantee that R",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T06:57:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-hollywood-man/video-hollywood-man-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-hollywood-man/video-hollywood-man-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-hollywood-man/video-hollywood-man-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-hollywood-man/video-hollywood-man-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-hollywood-man/video-hollywood-man-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-hollywood-man/video-hollywood-man-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",40,"Hollywood action film star <PERSON>Rafe Stoker</PERSON> has sunk <MONEY>$130,000</MONEY> of his own money into his own production, but can't find legitimate financing to complete the film. His mob-connected investor demands an exorbitant amount of collateral and a guarantee that R",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003389599/hollywood-man.html,54a5361379881011bed2c074,null,{"main":"Hollywood Man"},"{original:CFS Releasing,person:[{firstname:Cfs,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Releasing}]}",multimedia
"<LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION>'s potential demotion 'junk' credit status <DATE>January</DATE>, crunch review <LOCATION>Italy</LOCATION>'s debt end <DATE>March</DATE> reappraisal <LOCATION>Britain</LOCATION> election key dates <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>'s <DATE>2015</DATE> credit rating calendar.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T12:06:15Z,[],451,"<LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION>'s potential demotion 'junk' credit status <DATE>January</DATE>, crunch review <LOCATION>Italy</LOCATION>'s debt end <DATE>March</DATE> reappraisal <LOCATION>Britain</LOCATION> election key dates <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>'s <DATE>2015</DATE> credit rating calendar.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-ratings-europe-calendar.html,54a42d3879881011bed28264,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Russia<\/LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Italy Britain<\/LOCATION> Draw Credit-Rating Scrutiny 2015,print_headline:<LOCATION>Russia<\/LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Italy Britain<\/LOCATION> Draw Credit-Rating Scrutiny 2015}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Today, years bankruptcy, <ORGANIZATION>Yellowstone Club</ORGANIZATION> thriving.",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Blixseth<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Timothy<\/PERSON> L},{name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Byrne<\/PERSON>, Samuel T},{name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Chernin<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Peter<\/PERSON> A},{name:persons,rank:4,value:Gates, Bill},{name:persons,rank:5,value:<PERSON>Weiskopf<\/PERSON>, Tom},{name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Montana<\/LOCATION>},{name:glocations,rank:2,value:Yellowstone National Park},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:Credit <ORGANIZATION>Suisse Group AG<\/ORGANIZATION>},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:Yellowstone Club},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Bankruptcies},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Real Estate Housing Residential},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Skiing}]",Business Day,"Today, years bankruptcy, <ORGANIZATION>Yellowstone Club</ORGANIZATION> thriving.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-31T09:00:28Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/26/business/26YELLOWSTONE-3/26YELLOWSTONE-3-thumbWide-v2.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/business/26YELLOWSTONE-3/26YELLOWSTONE-3-thumbWide-v2.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/26/business/26YELLOWSTONE-3/26YELLOWSTONE-3-articleLarge-v2.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/business/26YELLOWSTONE-3/26YELLOWSTONE-3-articleLarge-v2.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/26/business/26YELLOWSTONE-3/26YELLOWSTONE-3-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/business/26YELLOWSTONE-3/26YELLOWSTONE-3-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",1719,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/huge-ski-resort-for-the-rich-is-bouncing-back/,54a401c67988102761d6df7e,Dealbook,"{main:Huge Ski Resort Rich Is Bouncing Back,print_headline:Apr&egrave;s-Bankruptcy,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>SARAH MAX<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Sarah,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:MAX}]}",blogpost
The wife man killed prosecutor&#8217;s wife revenge plot pleaded guilty <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> counts capital murder sentenced 40 years prison.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T10:16:23Z,[],274,The wife man killed prosecutor&#8217;s wife revenge plot pleaded guilty <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> counts capital murder sentenced 40 years prison.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/us/30reuters-usa-texas-districtattorney.html,54a2c2697988104803cc8ac1,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Texas<\/LOCATION> Woman Pleads Guilty Revenge Murder Prosecutors,print_headline:<LOCATION>Texas<\/LOCATION> Woman Pleads Guilty Revenge Murder Prosecutors}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
Congress stint budget support make <ORGANIZATION>Secret Service</ORGANIZATION> job.,18,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:Secret Service},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Editorials},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:White House Building <LOCATION>Washington<\/LOCATION>, DC}]",Opinion,"Editorial cites bipartisan review highlighting number gaps shortcomings presidential security; points report, prompted <DATE>September</DATE> incident man scaled <ORGANIZATION>White House</ORGANIZATION> fence, paints picture <ORGANIZATION>Secret Service</ORGANIZATION> insular stretched thin; urges <ORGANIZATION>Congress</ORGANIZATION> stint budget important agency.",The New York Times,[],Editorial,2014-12-29T00:00:00Z,[],345,Congress stint budget support make <ORGANIZATION>Secret Service</ORGANIZATION> job.,Editorial,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/29/opinion/alarming-gaps-in-presidential-protection.html,54a0b3787988101f98e3ee76,null,"{content_kicker:Editorial,main:Alarming Gaps Presidential Protection,print_headline:Alarming Gaps Presidential Protection,kicker:Editorial}","{contributor:,original:By THE EDITORIAL BOARD,person:[],organization:THE EDITORIAL BOARD}",article
"Camel racing part Arabian culture generations, widespread robots jockeys giving sport modern twist.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Camels},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:2,value:United Arab Emirates},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Robots Robotics},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Jockeys, Drivers Trainers},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:5,value:Abu Dhabi United Arab Emirates}]",Sports,Ancient Arabian tradition camel racing modern twist robotic jockeys.,The New York Times,[],Sports,2014-12-28T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/28/sports/28camelracing1/28camelracing1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/sports/28camelracing1/28camelracing1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/28/sports/28camelracing1/28camelracing1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:401},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/sports/28camelracing1/28camelracing1-articleLarge.jpg,height:401},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/28/sports/28camelracing1/28camelracing1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/sports/28camelracing1/28camelracing1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1847,"Camel racing part Arabian culture generations, widespread robots jockeys giving sport modern twist.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/sports/camel-racing-in-the-united-arab-emirates-is-a-blend-of-centuries-old-traditions-and-modern-technology.html,549dab527988105ced7885b6,null,"{main:Sprinting Over Dirt, With Robot Hump,seo:Camel Racing Blends Centuries-Old Traditions Modern Technology,print_headline:Sprinting Over Dirt, With Robot Hump}","{contributor:<PERSON>Hala Droubi<\/PERSON> contributed reporting.,original:By <PERSON>SAM BORDEN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Sam,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BORDEN}]}",article
"To children bilingual, travel writer investigates options public school programs home day camps abroad.",5,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Travel Vacations},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:11,value:<LOCATION>Italy<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>Tuscany Italy<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Language Languages},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:International Baccalaureate},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:5,value:Jaumont, Fabrice},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Bilingual Education},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:French Language},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:8,value:Italian Language},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:9,value:Spanish Language},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:10,value:Camps Camping}]",Travel,<PERSON>Danielle Pergament</PERSON> travel article shares experience taking children <LOCATION>Tuscany</LOCATION> month learn Italian 'true citizens world.',The New York Times,[],Travel,2014-12-28T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/28/travel/28-LANGUAGE/28-LANGUAGE-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/travel/28-LANGUAGE/28-LANGUAGE-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/28/travel/28-LANGUAGE/28-LANGUAGE-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:258},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/travel/28-LANGUAGE/28-LANGUAGE-articleLarge.jpg,height:258},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/28/travel/28-LANGUAGE/28-LANGUAGE-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/travel/28-LANGUAGE/28-LANGUAGE-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",1067,"To children bilingual, travel writer investigates options public school programs home day camps abroad.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/travel/making-language-immersion-fun-for-the-kids.html,549d92197988103babf08be6,null,"{content_kicker:Personal Journeys,main:Making Language Immersion Fun Kids,print_headline:Travel Plus Summer Camp Equals Language Immersion,kicker:Personal Journeys}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>DANIELLE PERGAMENT<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Danielle,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:PERGAMENT}]}",article
"President <PERSON>Vladimir V. Putin</PERSON> <LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION>, wields virtually unchallenged power reward class oligarchs, instrument punish oppose.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Putin<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Vladimir<\/PERSON> V},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>Russia<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Series},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:4,value:Yevtushenkov, <PERSON>Vladimir<\/PERSON> P},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Political Prisoners},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:Bashneft OAO},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:7,value:<PERSON>Lebedev<\/PERSON>, Aleksandr Y},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:8,value:Pugachev, <PERSON>Sergei<\/PERSON>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:9,value:<PERSON>Sechin<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Igor<\/PERSON> I},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:10,value:Rosneft}]",World,"Russian Pres Vladimir V <PERSON>Putin</PERSON> developed political economic system rewards class oligarchs severely punishes challenge <ORGANIZATION>Kremlin</ORGANIZATION>'s interests; latest case fate <PERSON>Vladimir P Yevtushenkov</PERSON>, longstanding loyalty <PERSON>Putin</PERSON>, punished public humiliating manner, lifetime fortune oil company <ORGANIZATION>Bashneft</ORGANIZATION> returned state Series: <PERSON>Putin</PERSON>'s Way.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-27T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/27/world/JP-PUTIN-1/JP-PUTIN-1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/world/JP-PUTIN-1/JP-PUTIN-1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/27/world/JP-PUTIN-1/JP-PUTIN-1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:394},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/world/JP-PUTIN-1/JP-PUTIN-1-articleLarge.jpg,height:394},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/27/world/JP-PUTIN-1/JP-PUTIN-1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/world/JP-PUTIN-1/JP-PUTIN-1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",2855,"President <PERSON>Vladimir V. Putin</PERSON> <LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION>, wields virtually unchallenged power reward class oligarchs, instrument punish oppose.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/27/world/even-loyalty-no-guarantee-against-putin.html,549e10cd7988105ced788670,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{content_kicker:<PERSON>Putin<\/PERSON>'s Way,main:Even Loyalty No Guarantee Against Putin,print_headline:Even Loyalty No Guarantee Against Putin,kicker:<PERSON>Putin<\/PERSON>'s Way}","{contributor:<PERSON>Steven Lee Myers<\/PERSON> reported <LOCATION>Moscow<\/LOCATION>, <PERSON>Jo Becker<\/PERSON> <LOCATION>Paris New York<\/LOCATION>. <PERSON>Andrew Roth<\/PERSON> contributed reporting <LOCATION>Moscow<\/LOCATION>, <PERSON>Masha Goncharova<\/PERSON> <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION>.,original:By <PERSON>STEVEN LEE MYERS JO BECKER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Steven,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Lee,rank:1,lastname:MYERS},{firstname:Jo,role:reported,organization:,rank:2,lastname:BECKER}]}",article
"A suspected <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> drone fired missiles compounds <LOCATION>Pakistan</LOCATION>'s <LOCATION>North Waziristan</LOCATION> tribal region <DATE>Friday</DATE>, killing alleged militants, security forces killed alleged planner deadly recent attack school, Pakistani...",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-26T01:44:03Z,[],352,"A suspected <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> drone fired missiles compounds <LOCATION>Pakistan</LOCATION>'s <LOCATION>North Waziristan</LOCATION> tribal region <DATE>Friday</DATE>, killing alleged militants, security forces killed alleged planner deadly recent attack school, Pakistani officials.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/26/world/asia/ap-as-pakistan.html,549d049e7988103babf08b1e,Asia Pacific,"{main:US Missile Strikes Kill 7 Militants NW <LOCATION>Pakistan<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:US Missile Strikes Kill 7 Militants NW <LOCATION>Pakistan<\/LOCATION>}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"With crackdown payday lenders, subprime borrowers increasingly auto title loans, high interest rates lead repossession financial ruin.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Automobiles},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Series},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Credit Debt},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:ACE Cash Express},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:Center Responsible Lending}]",Business Day,"With crackdown payday lenders, subprime borrowers increasingly auto title loans, high interest rates lead repossession financial ruin.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-25T12:13:48Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/25/business/dbpix-subprime-1/dbpix-subprime-1-thumbWide-v2.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/business/dbpix-subprime-1/dbpix-subprime-1-thumbWide-v2.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/25/business/dbpix-subprime-1/dbpix-subprime-1-articleLarge-v2.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/business/dbpix-subprime-1/dbpix-subprime-1-articleLarge-v2.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/25/business/dbpix-subprime-1/dbpix-subprime-1-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/business/dbpix-subprime-1/dbpix-subprime-1-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",2192,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/25/dipping-into-auto-equity-devastates-many-borrowers/,549c46247988103babf08a10,Dealbook,"{main:Rise Loans Linked Cars Is Hurting Poor,print_headline:Surge Loans Linked Cars Is Hurting Poor,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>JESSICA SILVER-GREENBERG MICHAEL CORKERY<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Jessica,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SILVER-GREENBERG},{firstname:Michael,role:reported,organization:,rank:2,lastname:CORKERY}]}",blogpost
