snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
<PERSON>D.J. Balentine</PERSON> scored 17 points <LOCATION>Evansville</LOCATION> back 16 beat No. 23 <LOCATION>Northern Iowa</LOCATION> 52-49 <DATE>Thursday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T22:51:45Z,[],316,<PERSON>D.J. Balentine</PERSON> scored 17 points <LOCATION>Evansville</LOCATION> back 16 beat No. 23 <LOCATION>Northern Iowa</LOCATION> 52-49 <DATE>Thursday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/sports/ncaabasketball/ap-bkc-t25-northern-iowa-evansville.html,54a616be7988102023c953a0,College Basketball,"{main:<LOCATION>Evansville<\/LOCATION> Rallies Past No. 23 <LOCATION>Northern Iowa<\/LOCATION> 52-49,print_headline:<LOCATION>Evansville<\/LOCATION> Rallies Past No. 23 <LOCATION>Northern Iowa<\/LOCATION> 52-49}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Deals worth nearly <MONEY>$3.5 trillion</MONEY> were announced, a performance favored by low interest rates and high stock prices.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Mergers, Acquisitions Divestitures}]",Business Day,"Deals worth nearly <MONEY>$3.5 trillion</MONEY> were announced, a performance favored by low interest rates and high stock prices.",The New York Times,[],Business,2015-01-01T19:32:44Z,[],525,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/deal-makers-notched-nearly-3-5-trillion-worth-in-14-best-in-7-years/,54a5e7cc7988102023c94f8e,Dealbook,"{main:Deal Makers Notched Nearly <MONEY>$3.5<\/MONEY> <ORGANIZATION>Trillion Worth<\/ORGANIZATION> in &rsquo;14, Best in 7 Years,print_headline:Deal Makers Notched Nearly <MONEY>$3.5 Trillion<\/MONEY> Worth in ’14, Best in 7 Years,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>MICHAEL J. DE<\/PERSON> LA MERCED,person:[{firstname:Michael,role:reported,organization:,middlename:J.,rank:1,lastname:DE LA MERCED}]}",blogpost
"PERKINS--<PERSON>J. Stuart</PERSON>, 86, President <ORGANIZATION>Volkswagen America, Inc.</ORGANIZATION>, passed <DATE>December 25</DATE>, <LOCATION>2014 Sarasota</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Florida</LOCATION>. He preceded death wife 60 years, <PERSON>Valerie</PERSON>, parents, sister brother. He survived...",null,[],Paid Death Notices,null,,[],Classified,2015-01-01T19:17:02Z,[],173,"<!-- J  PERKINS --><<ORGANIZATION>IMG SRC</ORGANIZATION>=/Images/Cobrands/NYTimes/Photos/NYT-0001943718-PERKINSJS_22_006102515.1_191658.jpg lgyOrigName=NYT-0001943718-PERKINSJS_22_006102515.1.jpg ALIGN=LEFT vspace=4 hspace=10>PERKINS--<PERSON>J. Stuart</PERSON>,<br/><br/> 86, former President of <ORGANIZATION>Volkswagen of America, Inc.</ORGANIZATION>, passed away on <DATE>December 25, 2014</DATE> in <LOCATION>Sarasota</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Florida</LOCATION>. He was preceded in death by his wife of 60 years, <PERSON>Valerie</PERSON>, also his parents, sister and brother. He is survived by his daughter, <PERSON>Sarah Perkins Cortese</PERSON>, and her husband, <PERSON>John Richard Cortese</PERSON>, both of <LOCATION>Sarasota</LOCATION>. <PERSON>Stuart Perkins</PERSON> was born in <LOCATION>London</LOCATION> in <DATE>1928</DATE> and was one of <ORGANIZATION>Volkswagen</ORGANIZATION>'s first three <PERSON>U. S.</PERSON> employees when the American sales office was established in <DATE>1955</DATE>. In <DATE>1964</DATE> he was appointed vice president and general manager and became president in <DATE>1965</DATE>. During his tenure as president, he enjoyed great success in expanding <ORGANIZATION>Volkswagen</ORGANIZATION>'s dealership network and increasing sales figures in this country to nearly 600,000 vehicles in <DATE>1970</DATE>. A <ORGANIZATION>Celebration of Life Service</ORGANIZATION> will take place <DATE>January 10th 2015</DATE> at Church Of The Palms in <LOCATION>Sarasota</LOCATION> at 2pm. In lieu of flowers donations can be made to SPARCC of <LOCATION>Sarasota</LOCATION>, <ORGANIZATION>All Faiths Food Bank</ORGANIZATION>, Church of The Palms or Temple <PERSON>Beth Sholom Preschool Sarasota</PERSON> attn: <PERSON>Vickie Inglese</PERSON>.<br><br> ",Paid Death Notice,http://www.legacy.com/Link.asp?I=LS000173695176,54a66c237988102023c95553,null,"{main:Paid Notice: Deaths  PERKINS, J.}",null,article
"The euro started year 29-month lows <LOCATION>Asia</LOCATION> head head <ORGANIZATION>European Central Bank</ORGANIZATION> fanned expectations bolder steps stimulus month, underlining <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> dollar's rate advantage.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T19:10:02Z,[],546,"The euro started year 29-month lows <LOCATION>Asia</LOCATION> head head <ORGANIZATION>European Central Bank</ORGANIZATION> fanned expectations bolder steps stimulus month, underlining <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> dollar's rate advantage.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-markets-global.html,54a5e2847988102023c94f13,null,"{main:Euro Starts New Year New Lows, Oil Tries Bounce,print_headline:Euro Starts New Year New Lows, Oil Tries Bounce}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<LOCATION>South Korea</LOCATION>'s manufacturing activity shrank fourth consecutive month <DATE>December</DATE> slower pace, private-sector survey showed <DATE>Friday</DATE>, adding signs economy slowly regaining footing heading <DATE>2015</DATE>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T19:03:32Z,[],250,"<LOCATION>South Korea</LOCATION>'s manufacturing activity shrank fourth consecutive month <DATE>December</DATE> slower pace, private-sector survey showed <DATE>Friday</DATE>, adding signs economy slowly regaining footing heading <DATE>2015</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-southkorea-economy-pmi.html,54a5e0717988102023c94ee3,null,"{main:<LOCATION>South Korea<\/LOCATION> <DATE>December<\/DATE> Factory Activity Shrinks Fourth Month Slower Pace-PMI,print_headline:<LOCATION>South Korea<\/LOCATION> <DATE>December<\/DATE> Factory Activity Shrinks Fourth Month Slower Pace-PMI}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"European Central Bank President <PERSON>Mario Draghi</PERSON> risk central bank fulfilling mandate preserving price stability higher half year ago, reiterated readiness act early year...",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T15:13:24Z,[],437,"European Central Bank President <PERSON>Mario Draghi</PERSON> risk central bank fulfilling mandate preserving price stability higher half year ago, reiterated readiness act early year.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-ecb-policy-draghi.html,54a5aaf87988102023c949cd,null,"{main:Draghi: Risk <ORGANIZATION>ECB<\/ORGANIZATION> Failing Its Mandate Higher Than Six Months Ago-Paper,print_headline:Draghi: Risk <ORGANIZATION>ECB<\/ORGANIZATION> Failing Its Mandate Higher Than Six Months Ago-Paper}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
A lady bank robber cell block boss she's prison.,null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T14:40:50Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/01/23/movies/video-ladies-they-talk-about/video-ladies-they-talk-about-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/01/23/movies/video-ladies-they-talk-about/video-ladies-they-talk-about-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/01/23/movies/video-ladies-they-talk-about/video-ladies-they-talk-about-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/01/23/movies/video-ladies-they-talk-about/video-ladies-they-talk-about-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/01/23/movies/video-ladies-they-talk-about/video-ladies-they-talk-about-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/01/23/movies/video-ladies-they-talk-about/video-ladies-they-talk-about-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",14,A lady bank robber cell block boss she's prison.,Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003348052/ladies-they-talk-about.html,54a5a2c57988102023c94855,null,{"main":"Ladies They Talk About"},"{original:Warner Home Video,person:[{firstname:Warner,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Home,rank:1,lastname:Video}]}",multimedia
Al Pacino <PERSON>John Cazale</PERSON> play hapless bank robbers heads wrong.,null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T14:32:39Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-dog-day-afternoon/video-dog-day-afternoon-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-dog-day-afternoon/video-dog-day-afternoon-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-dog-day-afternoon/video-dog-day-afternoon-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-dog-day-afternoon/video-dog-day-afternoon-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-dog-day-afternoon/video-dog-day-afternoon-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-dog-day-afternoon/video-dog-day-afternoon-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",21,Al Pacino <PERSON>John Cazale</PERSON> play hapless bank robbers heads wrong.,Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003317981/dog-day-afternoon.html,54a5a0dc7988102023c947c0,null,{"main":"Dog Day Afternoon"},"{original:Artists Entertainment Complex,person:[{firstname:Artists,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Entertainment,rank:1,lastname:Complex}]}",multimedia
A young <ORGANIZATION>FBI</ORGANIZATION> recruit infiltrates gang surfing Southern Californian bank robbers. Idiotic story redeemed exciting action scenes!,null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T14:26:24Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-point-break/video-point-break-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-point-break/video-point-break-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-point-break/video-point-break-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-point-break/video-point-break-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-point-break/video-point-break-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-point-break/video-point-break-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",21,A young <ORGANIZATION>FBI</ORGANIZATION> recruit infiltrates gang surfing Southern Californian bank robbers. Idiotic story redeemed exciting action scenes!,Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003364587/point-break.html,54a59f6a7988102023c9474b,null,{"main":"Point Break"},"{original:Twentieth Century Fox Home Entertainment,person:[{firstname:Twentieth,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Century,rank:1,lastname:Fox}]}",multimedia
"Lawman <PERSON>J.D. Cahill</PERSON> stand bad-guy army. But widower father, insecure footing raising sons. Particularly suspects boys involved bank robbery - killings. Filmed location high",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T13:58:21Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-cahill-us-marshal/video-cahill-us-marshal-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-cahill-us-marshal/video-cahill-us-marshal-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-cahill-us-marshal/video-cahill-us-marshal-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-cahill-us-marshal/video-cahill-us-marshal-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-cahill-us-marshal/video-cahill-us-marshal-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-cahill-us-marshal/video-cahill-us-marshal-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",45,"Lawman <PERSON>J.D. Cahill</PERSON> stand bad-guy army. But widower father, insecure footing raising sons. Particularly suspects boys involved bank robbery - killings. Filmed location high",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003301619/cahill-us-marshal.html,54a598d27988102023c94549,null,"{main:<PERSON>Cahill<\/PERSON>, <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Marshal}","{original:Warner Home Video,person:[{firstname:Warner,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Home,rank:1,lastname:Video}]}",multimedia
