snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"According recent studies, half Americans prospect good job home white picket fence, existed unachievable.",null,"[{name:type_of_material,rank:1,value:News}]",Opinion,"According recent studies, half Americans prospect good job home white picket fence, existed unachievable.",The New York Times,[],null,2015-01-01T19:32:18Z,[],2347,,Blog,http://www.nytimes.com/roomfordebate/2015/01/01/is-the-modern-american-dream-attainable,54a5e8887988102023c94f9e,Room For Debate,"{main:Is Modern American Dream Attainable??,kicker:Room For Debate}",null,blogpost
"In <DATE>2012</DATE>, InDinero had spent nearly all of the <MONEY>$1.2 million</MONEY> it had raised from investors. Today, it has just under <MONEY>$3 million</MONEY> in annual sales.",3,"[{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:1,value:Mah, <PERSON>Jessica<\/PERSON>},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:2,value:inDinero Inc},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Accounting Accountants},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Small Business},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Start-ups},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Careers Professions}]",Business Day,"<PERSON>Jessica Mah</PERSON>, entrepreneur who has rescued her startup InDinero from insolvency it faced in <DATE>2009</DATE>, discusses how she turned things around for her company, which now has <MONEY>$3 million</MONEY> in annual sales.",The New York Times,[],Business,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/business/01sbiz-pic1/01sbiz-pic1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/business/01sbiz-pic1/01sbiz-pic1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/business/01sbiz-pic1/01sbiz-pic1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:394},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/business/01sbiz-pic1/01sbiz-pic1-articleLarge.jpg,height:394},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/business/01sbiz-pic1/01sbiz-pic1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/business/01sbiz-pic1/01sbiz-pic1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1239,"In <DATE>2012</DATE>, InDinero had spent nearly all of the <MONEY>$1.2 million</MONEY> it had raised from investors. Today, it has just under <MONEY>$3 million</MONEY> in annual sales.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/business/smallbusiness/a-reversal-for-indinero-a-once-struggling-accounting-software-start-up.html,54a4149a7988102761d6e1a4,Small Business,"{content_kicker:Conversations,main:A Reversal InDinero, Once-Struggling Accounting Software Start-Up,print_headline:Fortunes Reverse Once-Struggling Accounting Software Start-Up,kicker:Conversations}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ADRIANA GARDELLA<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Adriana,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:GARDELLA}]}",article
The <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> extolled leading opium dealer&#8217;s imprisonment sign Afghan authorities establish law order. Then man paid millions escape.,4,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:Afghanistan},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:11,value:Karzai, Ahmed Wali},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:12,value:<PERSON>Ghani<\/PERSON>, Ashraf},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Drug Abuse Traffic},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Bribery Kickbacks},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Corruption Institutional},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:6,value:Prisons Prisoners},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:7,value:Kandahar Afghanistan},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:8,value:Opium},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:9,value:Taliban},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:10,value:Karzai, Hamid}]",World,"Afghan drug kingpin <PERSON>Haji Lal Jan Ishaqzai</PERSON>, incarceration evidence country's willingness tackle opium trafficking, released prison bribing wide array people criminal justice system; transactions common widely acknowledged <LOCATION>Afghanistan</LOCATION>.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/world/31escape/31escape-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/world/31escape/31escape-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/world/31escape/31escape-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/world/31escape/31escape-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/world/31escape/31escape-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/world/31escape/31escape-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1110,The <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> extolled leading opium dealer&#8217;s imprisonment sign Afghan authorities establish law order. Then man paid millions escape.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/world/asia/bribes-free-drug-kingpin-in-afghanistan-where-cash-often-overrules-justice.html,54a40cbc7988102761d6e0b5,Asia Pacific,"{main:Bribery Frees Drug <LOCATION>Kingpin Afghanistan<\/LOCATION>, Where Cash Often Overrules Justice,print_headline:Bribery Frees Drug <LOCATION>Kingpin Afghanistan<\/LOCATION>, Where Cash Often Overrules Justice}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>JOSEPH GOLDSTEIN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Joseph,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:GOLDSTEIN}]}",article
"The head remuneration committee scandal-hit British grocer <ORGANIZATION>Tesco PLC</ORGANIZATION>, <PERSON>Stuart Chambers</PERSON>, set step, <ORGANIZATION>Tesco</ORGANIZATION> <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T16:45:49Z,[],124,"The head remuneration committee scandal-hit British grocer <ORGANIZATION>Tesco PLC</ORGANIZATION>, <PERSON>Stuart Chambers</PERSON>, set step, <ORGANIZATION>Tesco</ORGANIZATION> <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-tesco-stuartchambers.html,54a46f5079881011bed29335,null,"{main:<ORGANIZATION>Tesco Remuneration Committee Head<\/ORGANIZATION> Step Down,print_headline:Tesco Remuneration Committee Head Step Down}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
Excerpts recent editorials newspapers <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> abroad:,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T16:38:27Z,[],2905,Excerpts recent editorials newspapers <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> abroad:,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/ap-us-editorial-rdp.html,54a46d5379881011bed292c6,null,"{main:Editorial Roundup: Excerpts From Recent Editorials,print_headline:Editorial Roundup: Excerpts From Recent Editorials}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<PERSON>Tripp Foy</PERSON>'s sing-song chant rang sentimental oldie die-hard farmers clinging selling tobacco, small procession buyers shadowed long rows reddish-brown leaf piled bales.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T03:52:35Z,[],978,"<PERSON>Tripp Foy</PERSON>'s sing-song chant rang sentimental oldie die-hard farmers clinging selling tobacco, small procession buyers shadowed long rows reddish-brown leaf piled bales.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/ap-us-old-fashioned-tobacco-sales.html,54a3b9ef7988102761d6d73f,null,"{main:Tobacco Auction System Is All Snuffed Out,print_headline:Tobacco Auction System Is All Snuffed Out}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<LOCATION>China</LOCATION> <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> published detailed plans reform fiscal reporting system, step dealing massive debts accrued local governments recent years reallocating budgetary control back central government.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T03:20:35Z,[],405,"<LOCATION>China</LOCATION> <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> published detailed plans reform fiscal reporting system, step dealing massive debts accrued local governments recent years reallocating budgetary control back central government.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-china-fiscalreform.html,54a3b23b7988102761d6d64d,null,"{main:China Details Fiscal Reform Plans Improve Budget Management,print_headline:China Details Fiscal Reform Plans Improve Budget Management}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Mexican crude oil sailing <LOCATION>U.S. East Coast</LOCATION> highest rate decade, customs data reviewed <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION>, sign deepening discounts crack open markets domestic shale inundates <LOCATION>Texas</LOCATION>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T02:31:15Z,[],890,"Mexican crude oil sailing <LOCATION>U.S. East Coast</LOCATION> highest rate decade, customs data reviewed <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION>, sign deepening discounts crack open markets domestic shale inundates <LOCATION>Texas</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-mexico-crude-usa.html,54a3a6ea7988102761d6d501,null,"{main:Exclusive: <LOCATION>Mexico<\/LOCATION>'s Light Crude, Shunned <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Shale, Sails East,print_headline:Exclusive: <LOCATION>Mexico<\/LOCATION>'s Light Crude, Shunned <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Shale, Sails East}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"When Xi Jinping wanted deliver political message <LOCATION>Hong Kong</LOCATION> protesters demanding free elections threatening streets, summoned tycoons dominate city&#8217;s economy. The words Chinese leader...",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T00:30:59Z,[],2444,"When Xi Jinping wanted deliver political message <LOCATION>Hong Kong</LOCATION> protesters demanding free elections threatening streets, summoned tycoons dominate city&#8217;s economy. The words Chinese leader <DATE>September 22</DATE> meeting <LOCATION>Beijing</LOCATION> uncompromising surprising. He entertain demand full universal suffrage <LOCATION>Hong Kong</LOCATION>, people attended.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-hongkong-china-economy-specialreport.html,54a38aca7988102761d6d1c4,null,"{main:Special Report: The <ORGANIZATION>Mainland<\/ORGANIZATION>'s Colonization <LOCATION>Hong Kong<\/LOCATION> Economy,print_headline:Special Report: The <ORGANIZATION>Mainland<\/ORGANIZATION>'s Colonization Hong Kong Economy}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Small businesses stepping farmers connect local markets marketing, transportation, logistics services.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Agriculture Farming},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Local Food},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Small Business},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Fresh Connection, The},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:E-Commerce},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Start-ups},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:Venture Capital},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:8,value:<PERSON>Jaffe<\/PERSON>, Mark},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:9,value:Red Tomato Inc},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:10,value:Fair Food Network}]",Business Day,"Many small businesses, trucking firm <ORGANIZATION>Fresh Connection</ORGANIZATION>, coming forefront supply local farmers customers marketing, transportation, logistics services; services meeting growing demand meat produce farmed locally; Fresh Connection delivery services farms <LOCATION>New York City</LOCATION>.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-31T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/business/31farms-webadd1/31farms-webadd1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/31farms-webadd1/31farms-webadd1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/business/31farms-webadd1/31farms-webadd1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/31farms-webadd1/31farms-webadd1-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/business/31farms-webadd1/31farms-webadd1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/31farms-webadd1/31farms-webadd1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1509,"Small businesses stepping farmers connect local markets marketing, transportation, logistics services.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/business/start-ups-rise-to-close-a-gap-for-farmers.html,54a3626d7988102761d6cf96,null,"{main:Start-Ups Rise Close Gap Farmers,print_headline:Start-Ups Rise Close Gap Farmers}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>STEPHANIE STROM<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Stephanie,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:STROM}]}",article
