snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"The young Russian pianist <PERSON>Daniil Trifonov</PERSON> returned <PERSON>Avery Fisher Hall</PERSON> program Rimsky-K.rsakov, <ORGANIZATION>Rachmaninoff Tchaikovsky New York Philharmonic</ORGANIZATION>.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Music},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:New Year},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:3,value:New York Philharmonic},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:4,value:<PERSON>Trifonov<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Daniil<\/PERSON>},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:5,value:Reeves, Dianne},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:7,value:<PERSON>Avery Fisher<\/PERSON> Hall},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:8,value:Classical Music}]",Arts,"<PERSON>Zachary Woolfe</PERSON> reviews <LOCATION>New York Philharmonic</LOCATION>'s New Year's Eve concert, featuring Russian pianist <PERSON>Daniil Trifonov</PERSON> jazz singer <PERSON>Dianne Reeves</PERSON> conducted <ORGANIZATION>Juanjo Mena</ORGANIZATION>, <PERSON>Avery Fisher Hall</PERSON>.",The New York Times,[],Culture,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/arts/TRIFONOV/TRIFONOV-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/arts/TRIFONOV/TRIFONOV-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/arts/TRIFONOV/TRIFONOV-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/arts/TRIFONOV/TRIFONOV-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/arts/TRIFONOV/TRIFONOV-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/arts/TRIFONOV/TRIFONOV-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",497,"The young Russian pianist <PERSON>Daniil Trifonov</PERSON> returned <PERSON>Avery Fisher Hall</PERSON> program Rimsky-Korsakov, <ORGANIZATION>Rachmaninoff Tchaikovsky New York Philharmonic</ORGANIZATION>.",Review,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/arts/music/trifonov-and-the-philharmonic-together-again-at-avery-fisher.html,54a45a0079881011bed28e5b,Music,"{content_kicker:Music Review,main:Focus, Flexibility Calm Lucidity,seo:Trifonov Philharmonic, Together Again <PERSON>Avery Fisher<\/PERSON>,print_headline:Focus, Flexibility Calm Lucidity,kicker:Music Review}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ZACHARY WOOLFE<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Zachary,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:WOOLFE}]}",article
"Recommendations for the new year, including a vow to drink rosé in winter, seafood delivered to your door and more.",3,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Cooking Cookbooks},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Alcoholic Beverages},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Food},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Coffee},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Seafood},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:6,value:<LOCATION>Kennedy<\/LOCATION>, Diana},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:7,value:Gracious Home}]",Food,"Florence Fabricant Front Burner column offers suggestions culinary New Year's resolutions, including vow drink rose winter.",The New York Times,[],Dining,2014-12-31T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/dining/31BURNER5/31BURNER5-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/dining/31BURNER5/31BURNER5-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/dining/31BURNER5/31BURNER5-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/dining/31BURNER5/31BURNER5-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/dining/31BURNER5/31BURNER5-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/dining/31BURNER5/31BURNER5-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",592,"Recommendations for the new year, including a vow to drink rosé in winter, seafood delivered to your door and more.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/dining/learning-mexican-cooking-from-diana-kennedy.html,54a199497988104803cc8832,null,"{content_kicker:Front Burner,main:Learning Mexican Cooking From <PERSON>Diana Kennedy<\/PERSON>}","{contributor:,original:By FLORENCE FABRICANT,person:[{firstname:<LOCATION>Florence<\/LOCATION>,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:FABRICANT}]}",article
Developer <PERSON>Richard Green</PERSON> place build upscale homes heavily polluted land electronic components plant mountains <LOCATION>Asheville</LOCATION>. All needed permit.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-29T00:01:00Z,[],2140,Developer <PERSON>Richard Green</PERSON> place build upscale homes heavily polluted land electronic components plant mountains <LOCATION>Asheville</LOCATION>. All needed permit.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/29/us/ap-us-superfund-subdivision.html,54a0e1517988101f98e3eeee,null,"{main:An Old Plant, Tainted Land, Worried Homeowners,print_headline:An Old Plant, Tainted Land, Worried Homeowners}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<LOCATION>India</LOCATION> sought cooperation <LOCATION>Bhutan</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Myanmar Bangladesh</LOCATION> offensive tribal militant group shot dead 80 people <LOCATION>Assam</LOCATION> state week, officials <DATE>Friday</DATE>.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-26T03:02:23Z,[],368,"<LOCATION>India</LOCATION> sought cooperation <LOCATION>Bhutan</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Myanmar Bangladesh</LOCATION> offensive tribal militant group shot dead 80 people <LOCATION>Assam</LOCATION> state week, officials <DATE>Friday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/26/world/asia/26reuters-india-attacks.html,549d16e17988103babf08b2f,Asia Pacific,"{main:<LOCATION>India<\/LOCATION> Seeks Help From <LOCATION>Bhutan<\/LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Myanmar<\/LOCATION> Hunt Down Militants,print_headline:<LOCATION>India<\/LOCATION> Seeks Help From <LOCATION>Bhutan<\/LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Myanmar<\/LOCATION> Hunt Down Militants}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<PERSON>Laura Benanti</PERSON>, singing cabaret New Year&#8217;s Eve 54 Below, unguarded, self-deprecating wit.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Benanti<\/PERSON>, Laura},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:2,value:54 Below <LOCATION>Manhattan<\/LOCATION>, NY, Restaurant},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Music}]",Arts,"Actress <PERSON>Laura Benanti</PERSON>, perform cabaret act New Years Eve 54 Below, small dedicated.",The New York Times,[],Weekend,2014-12-26T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/26/arts/26BENANTI/26BENANTI-thumbWide-v2.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/arts/26BENANTI/26BENANTI-thumbWide-v2.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/26/arts/26BENANTI/26BENANTI-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:450},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/arts/26BENANTI/26BENANTI-articleLarge.jpg,height:450},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/26/arts/26BENANTI/26BENANTI-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/arts/26BENANTI/26BENANTI-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",1491,"<PERSON>Laura Benanti</PERSON>, singing cabaret New Year&#8217;s Eve 54 Below, unguarded, self-deprecating wit.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/26/arts/music/laura-benanti-takes-on-54-below-and-her-career.html,549c7af67988103babf08a47,Music,"{main:Working People New Year&#8217;s Eve,seo:<PERSON>Laura Benanti<\/PERSON> Takes On 54 Below Her Career,print_headline:Working for the People on New Year’s Eve}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>DAVE ITZKOFF<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Dave,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:ITZKOFF}]}",article
"<LOCATION>India</LOCATION> deployed military helicopters hunt tribal militants northeastern state <LOCATION>Assam</LOCATION> <DATE>Thursday</DATE> rebels killed 75 people week, deadliest remote area years.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-25T03:47:37Z,[],369,"<LOCATION>India</LOCATION> deployed military helicopters hunt tribal militants northeastern state <LOCATION>Assam</LOCATION> <DATE>Thursday</DATE> rebels killed 75 people week, deadliest remote area years.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/25/world/asia/25reuters-india-attacks.html,549bcfe37988100306691106,Asia Pacific,"{main:<LOCATION>India<\/LOCATION>'s Military Hunts Rebels After Deadly Attacks Remote State,print_headline:<LOCATION>India<\/LOCATION>'s Military Hunts Rebels After Deadly Attacks Remote State}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
A leak major Russian oil pipeline caused spill Black Sea port <LOCATION>Tuapse</LOCATION> <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> officials stormy weather hampering efforts assess respond mishap.,null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-24T05:40:29Z,[],277,A leak major Russian oil pipeline caused spill Black Sea port <LOCATION>Tuapse</LOCATION> <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> officials stormy weather hampering efforts assess respond mishap.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/24/world/europe/24reuters-russia-oil-spill.html,549a98a27988102d96d567cd,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:Oil Spills Into Black Sea Near Russian Port After Pipeline Leak,print_headline:Oil Spills Into Black Sea Near Russian Port After Pipeline Leak}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
Television highlights.,9,[],Arts,null,The New York Times,[],Culture,2014-12-24T00:00:00Z,[],755,Television highlights.,Schedule,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/24/arts/television/whats-on-tv-wednesday.html,549a56687988102d96d566ec,Television,"{main:What’s on TV <DATE>Wednesday<\/DATE>,print_headline:What’s On TV <DATE>Wednesday<\/DATE>}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>BRANDON K. THORP<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Brandon,role:reported,organization:,middlename:K.,rank:1,lastname:THORP}]}",article
"Questions put hyphens trivial, pedantic. But small errors distract readers focused substance reporting.",null,[],null,"Questions put hyphens trivial, pedantic. But small errors distract readers focused substance reporting.",The New York Times,[],null,2014-12-23T08:00:26Z,[],2284,null,Blog,http://afterdeadline.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/23/tricky-little-things-2/,54996941798810035238e815,null,"{main:Tricky Little Things,kicker:After Deadline}","{original:By <PERSON>PHILIP B. CORBETT<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Philip,role:reported,organization:,rank:1}]}",blogpost
A hedge fund owns stake parent company restaurant chain shift smaller portions food.,null,"[{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:1,value:Olive Garden Italian Restaurants},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Calories},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Starboard Value LP},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Pasta},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Restaurants},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Cooking Cookbooks}]",The Upshot,null,The New York Times,[],Upshot,2014-12-23T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/24/upshot/23UP-Olive-Garden/23UP-Olive-Garden-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/24/upshot/23UP-Olive-Garden/23UP-Olive-Garden-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/24/upshot/23UP-Olive-Garden/23UP-Olive-Garden-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:403},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/24/upshot/23UP-Olive-Garden/23UP-Olive-Garden-articleLarge.jpg,height:403},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/24/upshot/23UP-Olive-Garden/23UP-Olive-Garden-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/24/upshot/23UP-Olive-Garden/23UP-Olive-Garden-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",296,A hedge fund owns stake parent company restaurant chain shift smaller portions food.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/23/upshot/a-dispute-over-portion-size-at-olive-garden.html,5498531a798810035238e555,null,"{content_kicker:Counting Calories,main:A Dispute Over Portion Size Olive Garden,kicker:The Upshot}","{original:By <PERSON>JOSH BARRO<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Josh,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BARRO}]}",article
