snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"When <LOCATION>Missouri</LOCATION> played season, <ORGANIZATION>Tigers</ORGANIZATION> stopped run ran. <LOCATION>Minnesota</LOCATION> found Tigers successful.",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T16:33:05Z,[],703,"When <LOCATION>Missouri</LOCATION> played season, <ORGANIZATION>Tigers</ORGANIZATION> stopped run ran. <LOCATION>Minnesota</LOCATION> found Tigers successful.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/sports/ncaafootball/ap-fbc-t25-citrus-bowl.html,54a5be147988102023c94b7d,College Football,"{main:No. 16 <LOCATION>Missouri<\/LOCATION> Rumbles Past <LOCATION>Minnesota<\/LOCATION>, 33-17,print_headline:No. 16 <LOCATION>Missouri<\/LOCATION> Rumbles Past <LOCATION>Minnesota<\/LOCATION>, 33-17}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Cleveland Cavaliers forward LeBron <PERSON>James</PERSON> expected action weeks receives treatment strained left knee lower back pain, <ORGANIZATION>National Basketball Association NBA</ORGANIZATION> team <DATE>Thursday</DATE>.",null,[],Sports,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T15:50:13Z,[],118,"Cleveland Cavaliers forward LeBron <PERSON>James</PERSON> expected action weeks receives treatment strained left knee lower back pain, <ORGANIZATION>National Basketball Association NBA</ORGANIZATION> team <DATE>Thursday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/sports/basketball/01reuters-nba-cavaliers-james.html,54a5b3697988102023c94a87,Pro Basketball,"{main:James Miss Two Weeks With Strained Knee Back Pain,print_headline:James Miss Two Weeks With Strained Knee Back Pain}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The year <ORGANIZATION>College Football Playoff</ORGANIZATION> changed postseason. One thing stays intact: New Year's Day packed anticipated bowl games, including national semifinals. Here's viewing guide...",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T01:11:12Z,[],1392,"The year <ORGANIZATION>College Football Playoff</ORGANIZATION> changed postseason. One thing stays intact: New Year's Day packed anticipated bowl games, including national semifinals. Here's viewing guide games times EST:",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/sports/ncaafootball/ap-fbc-bowl-viewing-guide.html,54a4e58a79881011bed2ae40,College Football,"{main:New Year's Day <DATE>2015<\/DATE> Bowl Viewing Guide,print_headline:New Year's Day <DATE>2015<\/DATE> Bowl Viewing Guide}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Top-ranked <LOCATION>South Carolina</LOCATION> ready &#8212; hardest &#8212; stretch season opens <ORGANIZATION>Southeastern Conference</ORGANIZATION> play week.,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T17:32:49Z,[],631,Top-ranked <LOCATION>South Carolina</LOCATION> ready &#8212; hardest &#8212; stretch season opens <ORGANIZATION>Southeastern Conference</ORGANIZATION> play week.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/sports/ncaabasketball/ap-bkw-t25-scarolina-sec-start.html,54a479f279881011bed295ad,College Basketball,"{main:No. 1 <LOCATION>South Carolina<\/LOCATION> Women Prepped <ORGANIZATION>SEC<\/ORGANIZATION> Start,print_headline:No. 1 <LOCATION>South Carolina<\/LOCATION> Women Prepped <ORGANIZATION>SEC<\/ORGANIZATION> Start}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Sterling Gibbs 25 points assists lead Seton Hall No. 15 St. <PERSON>John</PERSON>'s 78-67 <LOCATION>Big East</LOCATION> opener teams <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>.,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T16:05:28Z,[],482,Sterling Gibbs 25 points assists lead Seton Hall No. 15 St. <PERSON>John</PERSON>'s 78-67 <LOCATION>Big East</LOCATION> opener teams <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/sports/ncaabasketball/ap-bkc-t25-st-johns-seton-hall.html,54a465a379881011bed290fd,College Basketball,"{main:<PERSON>Gibbs Sparks Seton Hall<\/PERSON> Past No. 15 St. <PERSON>John<\/PERSON>'s,print_headline:<PERSON>Gibbs Sparks Seton Hall<\/PERSON> Past No. 15 St. <PERSON>John<\/PERSON>'s}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Frank <PERSON>Kaminsky</PERSON> 18 points 14 rebounds, <PERSON>Nigel Hayes</PERSON> scored 21 points No. 4 <LOCATION>Wisconsin</LOCATION> shot blistering <PERCENT>63 percent</PERCENT> field beat <ORGANIZATION>Penn State</ORGANIZATION> 89-72 <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>.",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T15:14:35Z,[],442,"Frank <PERSON>Kaminsky</PERSON> 18 points 14 rebounds, <PERSON>Nigel Hayes</PERSON> scored 21 points No. 4 <LOCATION>Wisconsin</LOCATION> shot blistering <PERCENT>63 percent</PERCENT> field beat <ORGANIZATION>Penn State</ORGANIZATION> 89-72 <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/sports/ncaabasketball/ap-bkc-t25-penn-st-wisconsin.html,54a4599279881011bed28e42,College Basketball,"{main:<PERSON>Kaminsky<\/PERSON>, No. 4 <ORGANIZATION>Badgers Overwhelm Penn State<\/ORGANIZATION> 89-72,print_headline:<PERSON>Kaminsky<\/PERSON>, No. 4 Badgers Overwhelm Penn State 89-72}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"As Americans trimmed tree week hung stockings care, viewers turned TV screens. During week reruns, total prime-time viewership Big Four networks dipped <PERCENT>25 percent</PERCENT> week.",null,[],Business Day,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T13:15:13Z,[],336,"As Americans trimmed tree week hung stockings care, viewers turned TV screens. During week reruns, total prime-time viewership Big Four networks dipped <PERCENT>25 percent</PERCENT> week.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/business/ap-us-nielsens.html,54a43e3279881011bed28802,null,"{main:A Week Reruns, Christmas Saw Dip TV Viewing,print_headline:A Week Reruns, Christmas Saw Dip TV Viewing}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
<LOCATION>Auburn Wisconsin</LOCATION> began season aspirations competing inaugural College Football Playoff.,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T12:38:49Z,[],662,<LOCATION>Auburn Wisconsin</LOCATION> began season aspirations competing inaugural College Football Playoff.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/sports/ap-t25-outback-bowl.html,54a4355879881011bed284fc,null,"{main:Alvarez: Badgers Eager Face Tigers Outback,print_headline:Alvarez: Badgers Eager Face Tigers Outback}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"The Big 12 plenty positive statistics, winning teams, back claim nation's top basketball conference.",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T09:54:49Z,[],677,"The Big 12 plenty positive statistics, winning teams, back claim nation's top basketball conference.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/sports/ncaabasketball/ap-bkc-big-12-league-play.html,54a40f037988102761d6e0fa,College Basketball,"{main:Big 12 Can Back Up Claim Top Basketball League,print_headline:Big 12 Can Back Up Claim Top Basketball League}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Every <DATE>March</DATE> nation's darlings.,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T08:56:34Z,[],648,Every <DATE>March</DATE> nation's darlings.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/sports/ncaabasketball/ap-bkc-usual-suspects.html,54a400f37988102761d6df66,College Basketball,"{main:NCAA Contenders Includes 'Little Guys',print_headline:NCAA Contenders Includes 'Little Guys'}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
