snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"<PERSON>Harrison Ford</PERSON>, <PERSON>Brendan Fraser Keri Russell</PERSON> star Extraordinary Measures CBS Films, film division <ORGANIZATION>CBS Corporation NYSE</ORGANIZATION>: CBS.A <ORGANIZATION>CBS</ORGANIZATION>.  The project, wrapped principal photography mid-June <DATE>2009</DATE>, film",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2014-12-31T12:32:44Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-extraordinary-measures/video-extraordinary-measures-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-extraordinary-measures/video-extraordinary-measures-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-extraordinary-measures/video-extraordinary-measures-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-extraordinary-measures/video-extraordinary-measures-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-extraordinary-measures/video-extraordinary-measures-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-extraordinary-measures/video-extraordinary-measures-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",38,"<PERSON>Harrison Ford</PERSON>, <PERSON>Brendan Fraser Keri Russell</PERSON> star Extraordinary Measures CBS Films, film division <ORGANIZATION>CBS Corporation NYSE</ORGANIZATION>: CBS.A <ORGANIZATION>CBS</ORGANIZATION>.  The project, wrapped principal photography mid-June <DATE>2009</DATE>, film",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003322081/extraordinary-measures.html,54a4334179881011bed28463,null,{"main":"Extraordinary Measures"},"{original:CBS Films,person:[{firstname:Cbs,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Films}]}",multimedia
"<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> stocks fell <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> crude oil prices continued descent, <ORGANIZATION>S&amp;P</ORGANIZATION> closed straight year double-digit gains.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T07:37:22Z,[],560,"<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> stocks fell <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> crude oil prices continued descent, <ORGANIZATION>S&amp;P</ORGANIZATION> closed straight year double-digit gains.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-markets-stocks-usa.html,54a3eea47988102761d6dd4a,null,"{main:Wall St. Lower Finishes Year With Solid Gains,print_headline:Wall St. Lower Finishes Year With Solid Gains}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> stocks fell <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> investors engaged profit-taking pull major indexes record levels, trend modest moves low volume continued heading final trading day year.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T06:57:06Z,[],477,"<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> stocks fell <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> investors engaged profit-taking pull major indexes record levels, trend modest moves low volume continued heading final trading day year.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/business/30reuters-markets-stocks-usa.html,54a293477988104803cc8a62,null,"{main:Wall St. Pulls Back From Record; Utilities Slump,print_headline:Wall St. Pulls Back From Record; Utilities Slump}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
Stocks moved substantially traded heavily <DATE>Monday</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>New York Stock Exchange Nasdaq</ORGANIZATION> Stock Market:,null,[],Business Day,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-29T16:54:19Z,[],212,Stocks moved substantially traded heavily <DATE>Monday</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>New York Stock Exchange Nasdaq</ORGANIZATION> Stock Market:,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/29/business/ap-us-financial-markets-stocks.html,54a1ce3a7988104803cc889a,null,"{main:Manitowoc Gilead Are Big Market Movers,print_headline:Manitowoc Gilead Are Big Market Movers}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> stocks changed thin trading <DATE>Monday</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>S&amp;P</ORGANIZATION> 500 notched latest record high, gains curbed early rally energy prices lost momentum.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-29T06:57:58Z,[],463,"<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> stocks changed thin trading <DATE>Monday</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>S&amp;P</ORGANIZATION> 500 notched latest record high, gains curbed early rally energy prices lost momentum.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/29/business/29reuters-markets-stocks-usa.html,54a142457988101f98e3ef82,null,"{main:Wall Street Little Changed S&P Hits Record,print_headline:Wall Street Little Changed S&P Hits Record}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
Stocks moved substantially traded heavily <DATE>Friday</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>New York Stock Exchange Nasdaq</ORGANIZATION> Stock Market:,null,[],Business Day,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-26T16:24:39Z,[],218,Stocks moved substantially traded heavily <DATE>Friday</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>New York Stock Exchange Nasdaq</ORGANIZATION> Stock Market:,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/26/business/ap-us-financial-markets-stocks.html,549dd29b7988105ced78860d,null,"{main:Yamana Gold Ocwen Are Big Market Movers,print_headline:Yamana Gold Ocwen Are Big Market Movers}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> stocks ended higher <DATE>Friday</DATE>, <ORGANIZATION>Dow S&amp;P</ORGANIZATION> 500 closing records broad rally, trading light market participants Christmas holiday.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-26T07:35:52Z,[],506,"<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> stocks ended higher <DATE>Friday</DATE>, <ORGANIZATION>Dow S&amp;P</ORGANIZATION> 500 closing records broad rally, trading light market participants Christmas holiday.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/26/business/26reuters-markets-stocks-usa.html,549d56d77988103babf08b80,null,"{main:Wall Street Ends Record Second Straight Weekly Gain,print_headline:Wall Street Ends Record Second Straight Weekly Gain}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
Stocks moved substantially traded heavily <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>New York Stock Exchange Nasdaq</ORGANIZATION> Stock Market:,null,[],Business Day,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-24T13:37:15Z,[],250,Stocks moved substantially traded heavily <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>New York Stock Exchange Nasdaq</ORGANIZATION> Stock Market:,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/24/business/ap-us-financial-markets-stocks.html,549b083a7988100306690e2d,null,"{main:Taser Walgreen Are Big Market Movers,print_headline:Taser Walgreen Are Big Market Movers}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> stocks closed flat short session <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> investors found reasons push major indexes sixth straight day gains strength biotechs bullish labor market data.,null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-24T07:41:42Z,[],484,<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> stocks closed flat short session <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> investors found reasons push major indexes sixth straight day gains strength biotechs bullish labor market data.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/24/business/24reuters-markets-stocks-usa.html,549ab4c07988102d96d567f2,null,"{main:Wall St. Ends Flat Short Session, Dow Ekes Out Record Close,print_headline:Wall St. Ends Flat Short Session, Dow Ekes Out Record Close}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> stocks rose <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>, Dow closing 18,000 time <ORGANIZATION>S&amp;P</ORGANIZATION> 500 ending record unexpectedly strong report economic growth.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-23T07:42:44Z,[],508,"<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> stocks rose <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>, Dow closing 18,000 time <ORGANIZATION>S&amp;P</ORGANIZATION> 500 ending record unexpectedly strong report economic growth.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/23/business/23reuters-markets-stocks-usa.html,5499637f798810035238e80b,null,"{main:Dow Ends Above 18,000 First Time Strong GDP Report,print_headline:Dow Ends Above 18,000 First Time Strong GDP Report}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
