snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T13:23:23Z,[],677,,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/ap-us-rel-religion-briefs.html,54a43f8e79881011bed2887c,null,"{main:Religion News Brief,print_headline:Religion News Brief}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Lawyers 40 military personnel civilians killed wounded attack <LOCATION>Fort Hood</LOCATION> military post <ORGANIZATION>Texas Army</ORGANIZATION> psychologist filed petition <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>Pentagon</ORGANIZATION> incident declared act terrorism.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T16:15:48Z,[],311,Lawyers 40 military personnel civilians killed wounded attack <LOCATION>Fort Hood</LOCATION> military post <ORGANIZATION>Texas Army</ORGANIZATION> psychologist filed petition <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>Pentagon</ORGANIZATION> incident declared act terrorism.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/us/30reuters-usa-texas-forthood.html,54a316c67988102761d6cef9,null,"{main:Victims <LOCATION>Fort Hood Shooting Texas<\/LOCATION> Seek 'Terrorism' Declaration,print_headline:Victims <LOCATION>Fort Hood Shooting Texas<\/LOCATION> Seek 'Terrorism' Declaration}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> imposed sanctions <DATE>Monday</DATE> Russians alleged human rights abuses, including officials involved cover-up death lawyer died prison exposing large-scale corruption.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-29T17:25:22Z,[],292,"The <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> imposed sanctions <DATE>Monday</DATE> Russians alleged human rights abuses, including officials involved cover-up death lawyer died prison exposing large-scale corruption.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/29/world/europe/29reuters-usa-russia-sanctions.html,54a1d5377988104803cc88ad,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Adds Four More Russians Human Rights Sanctions List,print_headline:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Adds Four More Russians Human Rights Sanctions List}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
An Egyptian court <DATE>Monday</DATE> banned annual festival honor Moroccan rabbi regularly attended hundreds Jewish pilgrims.,null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-29T07:41:05Z,[],458,An Egyptian court <DATE>Monday</DATE> banned annual festival honor Moroccan rabbi regularly attended hundreds Jewish pilgrims.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/29/world/middleeast/ap-ml-egypt-jewish-festival.html,54a14c1f7988101f98e3ef8e,Middle East,"{main:<LOCATION>Egypt<\/LOCATION> Court Bans Festival Honoring Revered Moroccan Rabbi,print_headline:<LOCATION>Egypt<\/LOCATION> Court Bans Festival Honoring Revered Moroccan Rabbi}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Roche Holding AG <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> health regulators approved Ebola test emergency response world's worst outbreak disease <LOCATION>West Africa</LOCATION>.,null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-29T07:12:33Z,[],181,Roche Holding AG <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> health regulators approved Ebola test emergency response world's worst outbreak disease <LOCATION>West Africa</LOCATION>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/29/world/africa/29reuters-health-ebola-roche.html,54a145c77988101f98e3ef87,<LOCATION>Africa</LOCATION>,"{main:<ORGANIZATION>FDA<\/ORGANIZATION> Approves Roche Ebola Test Emergency Use,print_headline:<ORGANIZATION>FDA<\/ORGANIZATION> Approves Roche Ebola Test Emergency Use}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
Developer <PERSON>Richard Green</PERSON> place build upscale homes heavily polluted land electronic components plant mountains <LOCATION>Asheville</LOCATION>. All needed permit.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-29T00:01:00Z,[],2140,Developer <PERSON>Richard Green</PERSON> place build upscale homes heavily polluted land electronic components plant mountains <LOCATION>Asheville</LOCATION>. All needed permit.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/29/us/ap-us-superfund-subdivision.html,54a0e1517988101f98e3eeee,null,"{main:An Old Plant, Tainted Land, Worried Homeowners,print_headline:An Old Plant, Tainted Land, Worried Homeowners}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Developer <PERSON>Richard Green</PERSON> place build upscale homes heavily polluted land electronic components plant mountains <LOCATION>Asheville</LOCATION>. All needed permit.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-29T00:01:00Z,[],874,Developer <PERSON>Richard Green</PERSON> place build upscale homes heavily polluted land electronic components plant mountains <LOCATION>Asheville</LOCATION>. All needed permit.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/29/us/ap-us-superfund-subdivision-abridged.html,54a0e1527988101f98e3eef0,null,"{main:An Old Plant, Tainted Land, Worried Homeowners,print_headline:An Old Plant, Tainted Land, Worried Homeowners}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Coverage funeral Officer Ramos, shot dead patrol partner sat car.",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:Ramos, Rafael 1974-2014},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Attacks Police}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"Coverage funeral Officer Ramos, shot dead patrol partner sat car.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-27T09:27:57Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/28WAKEBLOG2/28WAKEBLOG2-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/28WAKEBLOG2/28WAKEBLOG2-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/28WAKEBLOG2/28WAKEBLOG2-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/28WAKEBLOG2/28WAKEBLOG2-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/28WAKEBLOG2/28WAKEBLOG2-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/28WAKEBLOG2/28WAKEBLOG2-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",2436,null,Blog,http://cityroom.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/27/latest-updates-from-the-funeral-of-officer-rafael-ramos/,549ed29c7988105ced788722,null,"{main:Updates From Funeral N.Y.P.D. Officer Rafael Ramos,kicker:City Room}","{original:By THE <LOCATION>NEW YORK<\/LOCATION> TIMES,person:[],organization:The New York Times}",blogpost
"Officers <PERSON>Rafael Ramos Wenjian Liu</PERSON> lifted highest designation detective <ORGANIZATION>Police Department</ORGANIZATION>, augment benefits families.",13,"[{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:1,value:Liu, Wenjian 1982-2014},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:Ramos, Rafael 1974-2014},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Police Department NYC},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Attacks Police},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:5,value:Murders, Attempted Murders Homicides}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"<LOCATION>New York City</LOCATION> Police Officers <PERSON>Rafael Ramos Wenjian Liu</PERSON>, shot killed targeted attack, posthumously promoted rank first-grade detective.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-27T00:00:00Z,[],225,"Officers <PERSON>Rafael Ramos Wenjian Liu</PERSON> lifted highest designation detective <ORGANIZATION>Police Department</ORGANIZATION>, augment benefits families.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/27/nyregion/two-officers-killed-in-ambush-are-posthumously-promoted-to-detectives.html,549e0efd7988105ced78866e,null,"{main:Two Officers Killed Ambush Are Posthumously Promoted Detectives,print_headline:2 Are Promoted Detectives Posthumously}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>BENJAMIN MUELLER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Benjamin,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:MUELLER}]}",article
"The <ORGANIZATION>Southern District</ORGANIZATION> has been partying all fall to celebrate its 225th anniversary, but some say its claim to be the country’s first federal district court is false advertising.",23,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Federal Courts US},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:2,value:Cabranes, Jose A},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Jacobs<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Dennis<\/PERSON> G},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:4,value:<PERSON>Rakoff<\/PERSON>, Jed S},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:5,value:<LOCATION>New York City<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:6,value:<PERSON>Duane<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>James<\/PERSON> 1733-97}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"<ORGANIZATION>United States District Court Manhattan</ORGANIZATION> celebrates 225th anniversary, calling country's sitting court, assertion disputed justices nation's 13 courts enjoy equal claim.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-26T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/26/nyregion/y-ANNIVERSARY/y-ANNIVERSARY-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/nyregion/y-ANNIVERSARY/y-ANNIVERSARY-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/26/nyregion/y-ANNIVERSARY/y-ANNIVERSARY-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/nyregion/y-ANNIVERSARY/y-ANNIVERSARY-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/26/nyregion/y-ANNIVERSARY/y-ANNIVERSARY-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/nyregion/y-ANNIVERSARY/y-ANNIVERSARY-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1254,"The <ORGANIZATION>Southern District</ORGANIZATION> has been partying all fall to celebrate its 225th anniversary, but some say its claim to be the country’s first federal district court is false advertising.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/26/nyregion/a-new-york-court-celebrates-its-status-as-the-nations-oldest-but-others-arent-so-sure.html,549cccaa7988103babf08ac9,null,"{main:Judges Playfully Dispute Whether <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION>’s Federal Court Is the Oldest,print_headline:Judges Playfully Dispute Whether <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION>’s Federal Court Is the Oldest}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>BENJAMIN WEISER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Benjamin,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:WEISER}]}",article
