snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
Factbox Asian Cup qualifiers <LOCATION>North Korea</LOCATION>.,null,[],Sports,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T03:42:27Z,[],380,Factbox Asian Cup qualifiers <LOCATION>North Korea</LOCATION>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/sports/soccer/01reuters-soccer-asia-northkorea-profile.html,54a5094b79881011bed2b65f,Soccer,"{main:Profile <LOCATION>North Korea<\/LOCATION> Team 2015 Asian Cup,print_headline:Profile <LOCATION>North Korea<\/LOCATION> Team 2015 Asian Cup}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
Ndamukong Suh happy suspension lifted <DATE>Sunday</DATE>'s playoff game <LOCATION>Dallas</LOCATION>.,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T12:57:47Z,[],630,Ndamukong Suh happy suspension lifted <DATE>Sunday</DATE>'s playoff game <LOCATION>Dallas</LOCATION>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/sports/football/ap-fbn-lions-suh.html,54a439ec79881011bed2869a,Pro Football,"{main:Suh Won't Discuss Incident With <PERSON>Rodgers<\/PERSON>,print_headline:Suh Won't Discuss Incident With <PERSON>Rodgers<\/PERSON>}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<LOCATION>Djibouti</LOCATION>'s government <ORGANIZATION>Union National Salvation USNopposition</ORGANIZATION> coalition signed agreement pave opposition lawmakers make parliamentary appearance, reforms country's electoral...",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T04:40:50Z,[],331,"<LOCATION>Djibouti</LOCATION>'s government <ORGANIZATION>Union National Salvation USNopposition</ORGANIZATION> coalition signed agreement pave opposition lawmakers make parliamentary appearance, reforms country's electoral body.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/world/africa/31reuters-djibouti-politics.html,54a3c5277988102761d6d886,<LOCATION>Africa</LOCATION>,"{main:<LOCATION>Djibouti<\/LOCATION> Government Reaches Deal Bring Opposition Into Parliament,print_headline:<LOCATION>Djibouti<\/LOCATION> Government Reaches Deal Bring Opposition Into Parliament}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<LOCATION>West Virginia</LOCATION> flipped statistics <LOCATION>Virginia</LOCATION> Tech <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>, easily out-shooting Hokies 3-point range.",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T16:32:31Z,[],608,"<LOCATION>West Virginia</LOCATION> flipped statistics <LOCATION>Virginia</LOCATION> Tech <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>, easily out-shooting Hokies 3-point range.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/sports/ncaabasketball/ap-bkc-t25-virginia-tech-west-virginia.html,54a31a657988102761d6cf04,College Basketball,"{main:No. 17 <LOCATION>West Virginia Routs Virginia<\/LOCATION> Tech 82-51,print_headline:No. 17 <LOCATION>West Virginia Routs Virginia<\/LOCATION> Tech 82-51}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
The intense social pressure Bangladeshi women marry young wastes talent blights lives.,,"[{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Bangladesh<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Marriages},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Women Girls},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Social Conditions Trends}]",Opinion,null,The New York Times,[],Editorial,2014-12-30T11:30:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2013/10/04/opinion/Anan-contributor/contributors-images-slide-1OZF-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2013/10/04/opinion/Anan-contributor/contributors-images-slide-1OZF-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2013/10/04/opinion/Anan-contributor/contributors-images-slide-1OZF-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:600},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2013/10/04/opinion/Anan-contributor/contributors-images-slide-1OZF-articleLarge.jpg,height:600},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2013/10/04/opinion/Anan-contributor/contributors-images-slide-1OZF-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2013/10/04/opinion/Anan-contributor/contributors-images-slide-1OZF-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",968,The intense social pressure Bangladeshi women marry young wastes talent blights lives.,Op-Ed,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/opinion/anam-the-curse-of-early-marriage.html,54a12c1c7988101f98e3ef64,null,"{content_kicker:Contributing Op-Ed | Tahmima AnamWriter,main:The Curse Early Marriage,print_headline:The Curse Early Marriage,kicker:Op-Ed | Tahmima Anam}","{contributor:,original:By TAHMIMA ANAM,person:[{firstname:Tahmima,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:ANAM}]}",article
"In <LOCATION>Cuba</LOCATION>, artists cut supplies Internet celebrated coterie international buyers, pipeline grow.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Art},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>Cuba<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Embargoes Sanctions},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:4,value:<PERSON>Garaicoa<\/PERSON>, Carlos},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:5,value:<PERSON>Lopez<\/PERSON>, Kadir}]",Arts,Thriving arts scene <LOCATION>Cuba</LOCATION> years attracted international attention lack real market makes difficult artists survive; hope thawing relations <ORGANIZATION>United</ORGANIZATION> states bring positive change.,The New York Times,[],Culture,2014-12-30T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/30/arts/JPARTCUBA2/JPARTCUBA2-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/arts/JPARTCUBA2/JPARTCUBA2-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/30/arts/JPARTCUBA2/JPARTCUBA2-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:368},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/arts/JPARTCUBA2/JPARTCUBA2-articleLarge.jpg,height:368},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/30/arts/JPARTCUBA2/JPARTCUBA2-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/arts/JPARTCUBA2/JPARTCUBA2-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1413,"In <LOCATION>Cuba</LOCATION>, artists cut supplies Internet celebrated coterie international buyers, pipeline grow.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/arts/cubas-art-scene-awaits-a-travel-boom.html,54a1e05a7988104803cc88be,Art & Design,"{main:<LOCATION>Cuba<\/LOCATION>&#8217;s Art Scene Awaits Travel Boom,print_headline:<LOCATION>Cuba<\/LOCATION>’s Art Scene Awaits a Travel Boom}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>VICTORIA BURNETT<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Victoria,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BURNETT}]}",article
No sports world heard <DATE>2014</DATE> Associated Press Female Athlete Year <DATE>August</DATE>.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-29T13:04:28Z,[],795,No sports world heard <DATE>2014</DATE> Associated Press Female Athlete Year <DATE>August</DATE>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/29/us/ap-ye-female-athlete-of-the-year.html,54a1982b7988104803cc8831,null,"{main:Davis Wins AP Female Athlete Year Honors,print_headline:Davis Wins AP Female Athlete Year Honors}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Though global cricket community reeling death Australian <PERSON>Phillip Hughes</PERSON>, significant events <DATE>2014</DATE> occurred field.",,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Cricket Game},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>Australia<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:3,value:England},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:4,value:<LOCATION>New Zealand<\/LOCATION>}]",Sports,null,The New York Times,[],Sports,2014-12-29T11:30:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/29/sports/29iht-cricket29-1/29iht-cricket29-1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/sports/29iht-cricket29-1/29iht-cricket29-1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/29/sports/29iht-cricket29-1/29iht-cricket29-1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:450},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/sports/29iht-cricket29-1/29iht-cricket29-1-articleLarge.jpg,height:450},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/29/sports/29iht-cricket29-1/29iht-cricket29-1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/sports/29iht-cricket29-1/29iht-cricket29-1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",848,"Though global cricket community reeling death Australian <PERSON>Phillip Hughes</PERSON>, significant events <DATE>2014</DATE> occurred field.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/29/sports/cricket/both-on-the-field-and-off-2014-was-an-eventful-year-in-the-world-of-cricket.html,54a0271979881001534d20ba,Cricket,"{main:Both Field Off, <DATE>2014<\/DATE> Was Eventful Year World Cricket,print_headline:Both Field Off, <DATE>2014<\/DATE> Was Eventful Year World Cricket}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>HUW RICHARDS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Huw,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:RICHARDS}]}",article
"Cardale Jones strolled hotel ballroom owned place. Decked gray <ORGANIZATION>Ohio State</ORGANIZATION> sweatsuit, seat podium smoothly answered question, throwing charming smile, well-timed...",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-28T19:33:49Z,[],892,"Cardale Jones strolled hotel ballroom owned place. Decked gray <ORGANIZATION>Ohio State</ORGANIZATION> sweatsuit, seat podium smoothly answered question, throwing charming smile, well-timed quip.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/28/sports/ncaafootball/ap-fbc-t25-sugar-bowl-mystery-man.html,54a0a2077988101f98e3ee53,College Football,"{main:Jones: <ORGANIZATION>Ohio State<\/ORGANIZATION>'s Mystery Man Sugar Bowl,print_headline:Jones: <ORGANIZATION>Ohio State<\/ORGANIZATION>'s Mystery Man Sugar Bowl}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<ORGANIZATION>Ohio State</ORGANIZATION> quarterback Cardale Jones opened season stuck Heisman candidate talented throw name mix,. <LOCATION>Alabama</LOCATION>'s <PERSON>Blake Sims</PERSON> succeeded Heisman finalist, outdueled heralded challenger...",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-28T13:39:54Z,[],852,"<ORGANIZATION>Ohio State</ORGANIZATION> quarterback Cardale Jones opened season stuck Heisman candidate talented throw name mix,. <LOCATION>Alabama</LOCATION>'s <PERSON>Blake Sims</PERSON> succeeded Heisman finalist, outdueled heralded challenger emerged Crimson Tide's offensive leader.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/28/sports/ncaafootball/ap-fbc-qb-tale-of-the-tape-jones-sims.html,54a04f157988101f98e3ede6,College Football,"{main:Sugar Bowl: Jones, <PERSON>Sims<\/PERSON> Rise Unexpected Stars,print_headline:Sugar Bowl: Jones, <PERSON>Sims<\/PERSON> Rise Unexpected Stars}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
