snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
<PERSON>D.J. Balentine</PERSON> scored 17 points <LOCATION>Evansville</LOCATION> back 16 beat No. 23 <LOCATION>Northern Iowa</LOCATION> 52-49 <DATE>Thursday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T22:51:45Z,[],316,<PERSON>D.J. Balentine</PERSON> scored 17 points <LOCATION>Evansville</LOCATION> back 16 beat No. 23 <LOCATION>Northern Iowa</LOCATION> 52-49 <DATE>Thursday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/sports/ncaabasketball/ap-bkc-t25-northern-iowa-evansville.html,54a616be7988102023c953a0,College Basketball,"{main:<LOCATION>Evansville<\/LOCATION> Rallies Past No. 23 <LOCATION>Northern Iowa<\/LOCATION> 52-49,print_headline:<LOCATION>Evansville<\/LOCATION> Rallies Past No. 23 <LOCATION>Northern Iowa<\/LOCATION> 52-49}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<LOCATION>Libya</LOCATION> made progress extinguishing fire oil storage tanks country's biggest oil port, <PERSON>Es Sider</PERSON>, raging week, member firefighting crew <DATE>Thursday</DATE>.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T17:22:06Z,[],285,"<LOCATION>Libya</LOCATION> made progress extinguishing fire oil storage tanks country's biggest oil port, <PERSON>Es Sider</PERSON>, raging week, member firefighting crew <DATE>Thursday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/world/africa/01reuters-libya-security.html,54a5c9337988102023c94cc1,<LOCATION>Africa</LOCATION>,"{main:<LOCATION>Libya<\/LOCATION> Sees More Progress Extinguishing Fire Eastern Oil Terminal,print_headline:<LOCATION>Libya<\/LOCATION> Sees More Progress Extinguishing Fire Eastern Oil Terminal}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"As <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> combat operations formally ended, military families sensed forgotten.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Afghanistan War 2001-14},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:United States Defense Military Forces},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Veterans},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:4,value:Afghanistan},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:5,value:Fort Hood Tex},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:6,value:Killeen Tex},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:7,value:<PERSON>Morris<\/PERSON>, Ramon S 1977-2014}]",<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,"Many American troops remain involved operations <LOCATION>Afghanistan</LOCATION>, official end war, soldiers families continue grapple injuries, mental trauma loss loved ones; scaled-down Operation Resolute Support continue bringing troops overseas train advise Afghan forces, sense mission fades; troops, veterans close feel forgotten.",The New York Times,[],National,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/us/JP-SOLDIER1/JP-SOLDIER1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/us/JP-SOLDIER1/JP-SOLDIER1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/us/JP-SOLDIER1/JP-SOLDIER1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/us/JP-SOLDIER1/JP-SOLDIER1-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/us/JP-SOLDIER1/JP-SOLDIER1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/us/JP-SOLDIER1/JP-SOLDIER1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1428,"As <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> combat operations formally ended, military families sensed forgotten.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/us/mission-ends-but-sacrifices-are-not-over-for-us-soldiers.html,54a4ac7f79881011bed2a13b,null,"{main:Mission Ends <LOCATION>Afghanistan<\/LOCATION>, Sacrifices Are Not Over <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Soldiers,print_headline:Mission Ends, Sacrifices Not Over}","{contributor:<PERSON>Andy Lehren<\/PERSON> contributed reporting <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION>.,original:By <PERSON>DAVE PHILIPPS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Dave,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:PHILIPPS}]}",article
"Manu Ginobili 26 points <LOCATION>San Antonio Spurs</LOCATION> avoided fourth overtime loss home <DATE>December</DATE>, escaping 95-93 victory <LOCATION>New Orleans</LOCATION> Pelicans <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T21:49:30Z,[],373,"Manu Ginobili 26 points <LOCATION>San Antonio Spurs</LOCATION> avoided fourth overtime loss home <DATE>December</DATE>, escaping 95-93 victory <LOCATION>New Orleans</LOCATION> Pelicans <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/sports/basketball/ap-bkn-pelicans-spurs.html,54a4b65a79881011bed2a380,Pro Basketball,"{main:Spurs Edge Pelicans 95-93 OT,print_headline:Spurs Edge Pelicans 95-93 OT}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Naz Long made 3-pointers scored season-high 24 points No. 9 <ORGANIZATION>Iowa State</ORGANIZATION> cruised past <ORGANIZATION>Mississippi Valley State</ORGANIZATION> 83-33 <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T21:07:31Z,[],379,Naz Long made 3-pointers scored season-high 24 points No. 9 <ORGANIZATION>Iowa State</ORGANIZATION> cruised past <ORGANIZATION>Mississippi Valley State</ORGANIZATION> 83-33 <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/sports/ncaabasketball/ap-bkc-t25-mvsu-iowa-st.html,54a4ac8c79881011bed2a13e,College Basketball,"{main:No. 9 <LOCATION>Iowa<\/LOCATION> St Routs <LOCATION>Mississippi Valley<\/LOCATION> St 83-33,print_headline:No. 9 <LOCATION>Iowa<\/LOCATION> St Routs <LOCATION>Mississippi Valley<\/LOCATION> St 83-33}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Argentine President <PERSON>Cristina Fernandez</PERSON> chose unexpected theme year-end message country: change policy state-run airline passengers carry notoriously-pampered lapdogs flights.,null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T14:53:46Z,[],314,Argentine President <PERSON>Cristina Fernandez</PERSON> chose unexpected theme year-end message country: change policy state-run airline passengers carry notoriously-pampered lapdogs flights.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/world/americas/31reuters-argentina-lapdogs.html,54a4549e79881011bed28d1c,Americas,"{main:<LOCATION>Argentina<\/LOCATION> Start 2015 With Lapdogs Flying High,print_headline:<LOCATION>Argentina<\/LOCATION> Start 2015 With Lapdogs Flying High}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Cyprus' president reunification talks restart, <LOCATION>Turkey</LOCATION> respects ethnically divided island's sovereign exploit offshore gas reserves.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T12:24:15Z,[],132,"Cyprus' president reunification talks restart, <LOCATION>Turkey</LOCATION> respects ethnically divided island's sovereign exploit offshore gas reserves.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/world/europe/ap-eu-cyprus-turkey.html,54a4324479881011bed2840e,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:Cyprus Says Turkey Must Stop 'Bullying' Over Gas,print_headline:Cyprus Says Turkey Must Stop 'Bullying' Over Gas}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
The replace daily caps foreign-exchange positions weekly limits establish standards foreign-exchange positions banks hold.,,"[{is_major:N,name:unknown,rank:1,value:}]",Business Day,null,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-31T11:30:00Z,[],427,The replace daily caps foreign-exchange positions weekly limits establish standards foreign-exchange positions banks hold.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/business/international/china-to-relax-rules-on-renminbi-trading-by-banks.html,54a274ee7988104803cc8a1e,International Business,"{main:China Relax Rules Renminbi Trading Banks,print_headline:China Relax Rules Renminbi Trading Banks}","{contributor:,original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<LOCATION>Libya</LOCATION> made progress fire largest oil port destroyed days country's oil production damage storage tanks hamper efforts resume exports, officials industry insiders.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T09:26:28Z,[],642,"<LOCATION>Libya</LOCATION> made progress fire largest oil port destroyed days country's oil production damage storage tanks hamper efforts resume exports, officials industry insiders.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/world/africa/31reuters-libya-security.html,54a407f47988102761d6e032,<LOCATION>Africa</LOCATION>,"{main:<LOCATION>Libya<\/LOCATION> Containing Es Sider Oil Fire Export Resumption Question,print_headline:<LOCATION>Libya<\/LOCATION> Containing Es Sider Oil Fire Export Resumption Question}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<PERSON>Marreese Speights</PERSON> scored 23 points, <PERSON>Stephen Curry</PERSON> added 13 points assists, <ORGANIZATION>Golden State Warriors</ORGANIZATION> beat <LOCATION>Philadelphia</LOCATION> 76ers 126-86 <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T01:00:01Z,[],410,"<PERSON>Marreese Speights</PERSON> scored 23 points, <PERSON>Stephen Curry</PERSON> added 13 points assists, <ORGANIZATION>Golden State Warriors</ORGANIZATION> beat <LOCATION>Philadelphia</LOCATION> 76ers 126-86 <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/sports/basketball/ap-bkn-76ers-warriors.html,54a391d97988102761d6d295,Pro Basketball,"{main:Warriors Keep Rolling, Topple 76ers 126-86,print_headline:Warriors Keep Rolling, Topple 76ers 126-86}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
