snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
Cable movie <LOCATION>Texas</LOCATION> highschool principal finds romance Mexican custodian. Fine performances make worthwhile!,null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T02:41:25Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-crazy-from-the-heart/video-crazy-from-the-heart-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-crazy-from-the-heart/video-crazy-from-the-heart-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-crazy-from-the-heart/video-crazy-from-the-heart-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:348},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-crazy-from-the-heart/video-crazy-from-the-heart-articleLarge.jpg,height:348},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-crazy-from-the-heart/video-crazy-from-the-heart-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-crazy-from-the-heart/video-crazy-from-the-heart-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",19,Cable movie <LOCATION>Texas</LOCATION> highschool principal finds romance Mexican custodian. Fine performances make worthwhile!,Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003313641/crazy-from-the-heart.html,54a4fa2779881011bed2b2ea,null,{"main":"Crazy From The Heart"},"{original:Turner Home Entertainment,person:[{firstname:Turner,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Home,rank:1,lastname:Entertainment}]}",multimedia
"<LOCATION>Saudi Arabia</LOCATION>'s elderly <LOCATION>King Abdullah</LOCATION> bin Abdulaziz admitted hospital <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> medical tests, state media, citing royal court statement, suffered source breathing difficulties.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T04:35:24Z,[],336,"<LOCATION>Saudi Arabia</LOCATION>'s elderly <LOCATION>King Abdullah</LOCATION> bin Abdulaziz admitted hospital <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> medical tests, state media, citing royal court statement, suffered source breathing difficulties.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/world/middleeast/31reuters-saudi-king.html,54a3c3c07988102761d6d85f,Middle East,"{main:Saudi King Undergoing Medical Tests Riyadh Hospital-Royal Court,print_headline:Saudi King Undergoing Medical Tests Riyadh Hospital-Royal Court}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<ORGANIZATION>Time Mother Nature</ORGANIZATION> threatening dismantle Alamo. Not original, replica 18th-century Spanish mission Old West movie set <PERSON>John Wayne</PERSON> built Oscar-nominated <DATE>1960</DATE> movie decades tourist mecca film...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-26T11:46:57Z,[],660,"<ORGANIZATION>Time Mother Nature</ORGANIZATION> threatening dismantle Alamo. Not original, replica 18th-century Spanish mission Old West movie set <PERSON>John Wayne</PERSON> built Oscar-nominated <DATE>1960</DATE> movie decades tourist mecca film production site.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/26/us/ap-us-travel-john-waynes-alamo.html,549d91ec7988103babf08be4,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Texas<\/LOCATION> Movie Set Used <PERSON>John Wayne<\/PERSON> Fading Away,print_headline:<LOCATION>Texas<\/LOCATION> Movie Set Used <PERSON>John Wayne<\/PERSON> Fading Away}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<ORGANIZATION>Time Mother Nature</ORGANIZATION> threatening dismantle Alamo. Not original, replica 18th-century Spanish mission Old West movie set <PERSON>John Wayne</PERSON> built Oscar-nominated <DATE>1960</DATE> movie decades tourist mecca film...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-26T01:43:42Z,[],660,"<ORGANIZATION>Time Mother Nature</ORGANIZATION> threatening dismantle Alamo. Not original, replica 18th-century Spanish mission Old West movie set <PERSON>John Wayne</PERSON> built Oscar-nominated <DATE>1960</DATE> movie decades tourist mecca film production site.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/26/us/ap-us-john-waynes-alamo.html,549d03e07988103babf08b1c,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Texas<\/LOCATION> Movie Set Used <PERSON>John Wayne<\/PERSON> Fading Away,print_headline:<LOCATION>Texas<\/LOCATION> Movie Set Used <PERSON>John Wayne<\/PERSON> Fading Away}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Secretary State <PERSON>John Kerry</PERSON> ending <DATE>2014</DATE> started, frustrated efforts push <LOCATION>Israel</LOCATION> Palestinians peace.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-22T02:23:23Z,[],924,"Secretary State <PERSON>John Kerry</PERSON> ending <DATE>2014</DATE> started, frustrated efforts push <LOCATION>Israel</LOCATION> Palestinians peace.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/22/us/politics/ap-us-united-states-israel-palestinians.html,5497c77c7988104a1e0dec38,Politics,"{main:US Renews Elusive Push Mideast Peace,print_headline:US Renews Elusive Push Mideast Peace}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Secretary State <PERSON>John Kerry</PERSON> ending <DATE>2014</DATE> started, frustrated efforts push <LOCATION>Israel</LOCATION> Palestinians peace.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-21T08:13:57Z,[],924,"Secretary State <PERSON>John Kerry</PERSON> ending <DATE>2014</DATE> started, frustrated efforts push <LOCATION>Israel</LOCATION> Palestinians peace.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/21/us/politics/ap-us-united-states-israel-palestinians.html,5496c84879881029b367df11,Politics,"{main:2014 Frustrates US Hopes Israeli-Palestinian Peace,print_headline:2014 Frustrates US Hopes Israeli-Palestinian Peace}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"A <LOCATION>California</LOCATION> man accused killing wife, abducting sons engaging police highway standoff acted self-defense wife stab, lawyer <DATE>Monday</DATE>.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-15T17:23:15Z,[],361,"A <LOCATION>California</LOCATION> man accused killing wife, abducting sons engaging police highway standoff acted self-defense wife stab, lawyer <DATE>Monday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/15/us/ap-us-missing-family.html,548f5ff2798810619765e354,null,"{main:Not Guilty Plea <LOCATION>California<\/LOCATION> Missing Family Case,print_headline:Not Guilty Plea <LOCATION>California<\/LOCATION> Missing Family Case}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
A <LOCATION>California</LOCATION> man accused abducting sons engaging police highway standoff booked jail <DATE>Friday</DATE> investigation wife's death kidnapping.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-12T04:03:48Z,[],422,A <LOCATION>California</LOCATION> man accused abducting sons engaging police highway standoff booked jail <DATE>Friday</DATE> investigation wife's death kidnapping.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/12/us/ap-us-missing-family.html,548ab06e7988102fcc130e85,null,"{main:Man Who Fled With 4 Sons Arrested Wife's Death,print_headline:Man Who Fled With 4 Sons Arrested Wife's Death}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"We deep forest crowded Australian paperback trees, air thick humidity eerily silent save screeching tropical birds, <PERSON>Marcus</PERSON> shouts: Look, crocodiles!&#160; &#160; As <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION> photojournalist, I'm trained...",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-10T03:57:29Z,[],762,"We are deep in a forest crowded by Australian paperback trees, the air thick with humidity but eerily silent save for the screeching of tropical birds, when <PERSON>Marcus</PERSON> shouts: Look, crocodiles!&#160; &#160; As a <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION> photojournalist, I'm a trained observer, but I can't see any crocs. I can't see anything beyond mud and what little water is left in the small billabong.&#160; &#160; Aboriginal hunters <PERSON>Marcus and Roy</PERSON>, a father and son team, take off running past a herd of water buffalo and by the time I catch up <PERSON>Roy</PERSON> is standing ankle-deep in murky water, his shotgun pointed at the surface.&#160; &#160; Hang on a minute: wasn't your son pointing at crocodiles in that water ten seconds ago? Is this safe?",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/10/world/asia/10reuters-australia-aborigine-widerimage.html,54880b80798810726e2d3c04,Asia Pacific,"{main:Hunting Pictures, Crocodiles, Remote Aboriginal Country,print_headline:Hunting Pictures, Crocodiles, Remote Aboriginal Country}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The bride, works Planned Parenthood, groom, special assistant President <PERSON>Obama</PERSON>, marry <LOCATION>Puerto Rico</LOCATION>.",25,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Weddings Engagements}]",Fashion & Style,null,The New York Times,[],Society,2014-12-07T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/07/fashion/weddings/07BERGERjpg/07BERGERjpg-thumbWide-v2.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/07/fashion/weddings/07BERGERjpg/07BERGERjpg-thumbWide-v2.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/07/fashion/weddings/07BERGERjpg/07BERGERjpg-articleLarge-v2.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:355},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/07/fashion/weddings/07BERGERjpg/07BERGERjpg-articleLarge-v2.jpg,height:355},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/07/fashion/weddings/07BERGERjpg/07BERGERjpg-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/07/fashion/weddings/07BERGERjpg/07BERGERjpg-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",249,"The bride, works Planned Parenthood, groom, special assistant President <PERSON>Obama</PERSON>, marry <LOCATION>Puerto Rico</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/07/fashion/weddings/stacy-berger-and-marlon-marshall.html,5483e25e7988106fd483d11a,Weddings,"{main:<PERSON>Stacy Berger Marlon Marshall<\/PERSON>,print_headline:<PERSON>Stacy Berger<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Marlon Marshall<\/PERSON>}",[],article
