snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Rescue teams coast <LOCATION>Borneo</LOCATION> found bodies debris <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> plane disappeared <DATE>Sunday</DATE>, remained unknown plane.",4,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Aviation Accidents, Safety Disasters},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:3,value:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:4,value:<LOCATION>Indonesia<\/LOCATION>}]",World,"Search rescue officials found bodies debris <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501 coast southwestern <LOCATION>Borneo</LOCATION>; plane's crash undetermined, officials suggest survivors found.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-31T00:00:00Z,[],960,"Rescue teams coast <LOCATION>Borneo</LOCATION> found bodies debris <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> plane disappeared <DATE>Sunday</DATE>, remained unknown plane.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/world/asia/airasia-8501-jet-missing-indonesia.html,54a260c17988104803cc8a01,Asia Pacific,"{main:Searchers Pull AirAsia Plane Debris and Bodies From <LOCATION>Java<\/LOCATION> Sea,print_headline:Searchers Pull Jet Debris Bodies From <LOCATION>Java<\/LOCATION> Sea}","{contributor:<PERSON>Tom McCawley<\/PERSON> contributed reporting <LOCATION>Jakarta<\/LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Indonesia<\/LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Austin Ramzy Hong Kong<\/LOCATION>.,original:By <PERSON>THOMAS FULLER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Thomas,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:FULLER}]}",article
"<LOCATION>Greece</LOCATION>'s splintered political landscape means small, parties determine winner elections month cobble lasting government avoid financial crisis.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T12:57:41Z,[],835,"<LOCATION>Greece</LOCATION>'s splintered political landscape means small, parties determine winner elections month cobble lasting government avoid financial crisis.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/world/europe/30reuters-greece-vote-politics.html,54a2e8657988102761d6ce79,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:Small Parties Play Outsized Role Greek Election,print_headline:Small Parties Play Outsized Role Greek Election}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Federal wildlife officials compare DNA gray wolf accidently shot <LOCATION>Utah</LOCATION> wolf spotted wandering Grand Canyon year, <ORGANIZATION>U.S. Fish Wildlife Service</ORGANIZATION>.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T12:38:08Z,[],502,"Federal wildlife officials compare DNA gray wolf accidently shot <LOCATION>Utah</LOCATION> wolf spotted wandering Grand Canyon year, <ORGANIZATION>U.S. Fish Wildlife Service</ORGANIZATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/us/ap-us-gray-wolf-killed.html,54a2e3837988102761d6ce6a,null,"{main:Tests See <LOCATION>Arizona Gray Wolf Killed Utah<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:Tests See <LOCATION>Arizona Gray Wolf Killed Utah<\/LOCATION>}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Investigators <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> flight crashed sea <LOCATION>Indonesia</LOCATION> focusing timing crew's request climb higher altitude avoid bad weather factor tragedy, source close probe...",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T10:04:37Z,[],841,"Investigators <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> flight crashed sea <LOCATION>Indonesia</LOCATION> focusing timing crew's request climb higher altitude avoid bad weather factor tragedy, source close probe.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/world/asia/30reuters-indonesia-airplane-investigation-exclusive.html,54a2bf997988104803cc8ab8,Asia Pacific,"{main:Exclusive: <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Crash Probe Focuses Timing Request Climb, Weather,print_headline:Exclusive: <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Crash Probe Focuses Timing Request Climb, Weather}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Investigators <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> flight crashed sea <LOCATION>Indonesia</LOCATION> focussing timing crew's request climb higher altitude avoid bad weather factor tragedy, source close probe...",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T10:04:33Z,[],841,"Investigators <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> flight crashed sea <LOCATION>Indonesia</LOCATION> focussing timing crew's request climb higher altitude avoid bad weather factor tragedy, source close probe.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/world/asia/30reuters-indonesia-airplane-investigation.html,54a2bf997988104803cc8ab9,Asia Pacific,"{main:Exclusive-AirAsia Crash Probe Focuses Timing Request Climb, Weather,print_headline:Exclusive-AirAsia Crash Probe Focuses Timing Request Climb, Weather}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
The Premier League's managerial firing Christmas week <PERSON>Neil Warnock</PERSON> Crystal Palace.,,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Soccer},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:2,value:English Premier League},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Chelsea Soccer Team},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Atletico Madrid Soccer Team},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:5,value:Real Madrid Soccer Team},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:<LOCATION>Milan<\/LOCATION> Soccer Team}]",Sports,null,The New York Times,[],Sports,2014-12-29T13:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/29/sports/29iht-Soccer29-2/29iht-Soccer29-2-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/sports/29iht-Soccer29-2/29iht-Soccer29-2-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/29/sports/29iht-Soccer29-2/29iht-Soccer29-2-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:419},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/sports/29iht-Soccer29-2/29iht-Soccer29-2-articleLarge.jpg,height:419},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/29/sports/29iht-Soccer29-2/29iht-Soccer29-2-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/sports/29iht-Soccer29-2/29iht-Soccer29-2-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",999,The Premier League's managerial firing Christmas week <PERSON>Neil Warnock</PERSON> Crystal Palace.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/29/sports/soccer/as-january-nears-premier-league-coaches-and-players-pack-up.html,54a053bb7988101f98e3edea,Soccer,"{content_kicker:Global Soccer,main:As <DATE>January Nears<\/DATE>, Premier League Coaches Players Pack Up,print_headline:As <DATE>January<\/DATE> Nears, Coaches Players Pack Up}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ROB HUGHES<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Rob,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:HUGHES}]}",article
"Police <LOCATION>Texas</LOCATION> responding suicide home suburban <LOCATION>Fort Worth</LOCATION> found bodies man, women girl inside residence, officials <DATE>Monday</DATE>.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-29T10:24:41Z,[],173,"Police <LOCATION>Texas</LOCATION> responding suicide home suburban <LOCATION>Fort Worth</LOCATION> found bodies man, women girl inside residence, officials <DATE>Monday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/29/us/29reuters-usa-texas-deaths.html,54a172cc7988101f98e3efd0,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Texas<\/LOCATION> Police Investigate Deaths Four People <LOCATION>Fort Worth Area<\/LOCATION> Home,print_headline:<LOCATION>Texas<\/LOCATION> Police Investigate Deaths Four People Fort Worth Area Home}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Should no survivors be found aboard the missing <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> flight, Malaysian carriers, or their subsidiaries, will have been involved in the world’s three deadliest aviation disasters this year.",8,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Malaysia<\/LOCATION> Airlines},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Aviation Accidents, Safety Disasters},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:<LOCATION>Malaysia<\/LOCATION> Airlines Flight 17},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:5,value:<ORGANIZATION>Malaysia Airlines<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight 370},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:7,value:<LOCATION>Malaysia<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:8,value:<LOCATION>Indonesia<\/LOCATION>}]",World,"<LOCATION>Malaysia</LOCATION> airlines, subsidiaries, involved world's deadliest aviation disasters <DATE>2014</DATE>, survivors found aboard <LOCATION>Indonesia</LOCATION> <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501; combined total 537 people board <ORGANIZATION>Malaysia Airlines</ORGANIZATION> Flight 370, missing Indian Ocean <DATE>March 8</DATE>, Flight 17, crashed <LOCATION>Ukraine</LOCATION> <DATE>July 17</DATE>.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-29T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/29/world/29malaysia/29malaysia-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/world/29malaysia/29malaysia-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/29/world/29malaysia/29malaysia-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:412},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/world/29malaysia/29malaysia-articleLarge.jpg,height:412},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/29/world/29malaysia/29malaysia-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/world/29malaysia/29malaysia-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",624,"Should no survivors be found aboard the missing <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> flight, Malaysian carriers, or their subsidiaries, will have been involved in the world’s three deadliest aviation disasters this year.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/29/world/asia/2014-proves-a-grim-year-in-malaysian-aviation.html,54a08e8b7988101f98e3ee3d,Asia Pacific,"{main:2014 Proves Grim Year Malaysian Aviation,print_headline:2014 Proves Grim Year Malaysian Aviation, With Links Three Air Calamities}","{contributor:<PERSON>Emma G. Fitzsimmons<\/PERSON> contributed reporting <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION>.,original:By <PERSON>MICHAEL FORSYTHE<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Michael,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:FORSYTHE}]}",article
"More 100 distraught relatives passengers aboard missing Flight QZ8501 hunkered makeshift crisis center <LOCATION>Indonesia</LOCATION>'s <LOCATION>Surabaya airport East Java</LOCATION> <DATE>Sunday</DATE>, waiting anxiously news.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-28T13:15:28Z,[],301,"More 100 distraught relatives passengers aboard missing Flight QZ8501 hunkered makeshift crisis center <LOCATION>Indonesia</LOCATION>'s <LOCATION>Surabaya airport East Java</LOCATION> <DATE>Sunday</DATE>, waiting anxiously news.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/28/world/asia/28reuters-indonesia-airplane-airport.html,54a0495d7988101f98e3eddd,Asia Pacific,"{main:Restless Night Awaits Relatives Passengers Missing <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Plane,print_headline:Restless Night Awaits Relatives Passengers Missing <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Plane}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> plane missing <DATE>Sunday</DATE> young commercial aircraft standards. It worked hard lacks real time engine diagnostics, accordance role short-haul aircraft.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-28T05:58:22Z,[],561,"The <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> plane missing <DATE>Sunday</DATE> young commercial aircraft standards. It worked hard lacks real time engine diagnostics, accordance role short-haul aircraft.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/28/world/europe/28reuters-indonesia-airplane-airbus.html,549fe2b479881001534d2083,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:Missing <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Plane Young, Basic, Hard-Working,print_headline:Missing <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Plane Young, Basic, Hard-Working}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
