snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
Small business owners <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION> 2015.,null,[],Business Day,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T13:04:30Z,[],737,Small business owners <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION> 2015.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/business/ap-us-smallbiz-small-talk.html,54a43b5479881011bed28711,null,"{main:New Year May Bring More Small Business Help From <LOCATION>Washington<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:New Year May Bring More Small Business Help From <LOCATION>Washington<\/LOCATION>}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"The global fast-food chain filed public tortured trappings served technology stocks., notes <PERSON>Jeffrey Goldfarb Reuters Breakingviews</PERSON>.",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Meyer<\/PERSON>, Danny},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:<ORGANIZATION>Leonard Green & Partners<\/ORGANIZATION>},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:Shake Shack},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Fast Food Industry},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Initial Public Offerings}]",Business Day,"The global fast-food chain filed public tortured trappings served technology stocks., notes <PERSON>Jeffrey Goldfarb Reuters Breakingviews</PERSON>.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-30T14:00:40Z,[],400,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/shake-shack-i-p-o-offers-healthy-profits-and-curious-metrics/,54a2f6ac7988102761d6cea1,Dealbook,"{main:Shake Shack I.P.O. Offers Healthy Profits Curious Metrics,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>JEFFREY GOLDFARB<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Jeffrey,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:GOLDFARB}]}",blogpost
"The Greek Parliament <DATE>Monday</DATE> failed avert early general election, reviving toxic debate austerity cure continent&#8217;s economic woes.",8,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Greece<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>Europe<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:3,value:Dimas, Stavros},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Elections}]",World,"Greek Parliament fails stop early general election, restarting acerbic debate austerity solution <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>'s economic troubles; governments investors prepare economic turmoil.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-30T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/29/world/europe/30GREECE1/30GREECE1-thumbWide-v3.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/world/europe/30GREECE1/30GREECE1-thumbWide-v3.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/29/world/europe/30GREECE1/30GREECE1-articleLarge-v2.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:399},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/world/europe/30GREECE1/30GREECE1-articleLarge-v2.jpg,height:399},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/29/world/europe/30GREECE1/30GREECE1-thumbStandard-v3.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/world/europe/30GREECE1/30GREECE1-thumbStandard-v3.jpg,height:75}]",1045,"The Greek Parliament <DATE>Monday</DATE> failed avert early general election, reviving toxic debate austerity cure continent&#8217;s economic woes.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/world/europe/greece-early-elections.html,54a132647988101f98e3ef6f,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:<LOCATION>Europe<\/LOCATION> Braces Economic Fallout Greece Heads Early Elections,print_headline:<LOCATION>Europe<\/LOCATION> Braces Economic Fallout Greece Heads Early Elections}","{contributor:<PERSON>Niki Kitsantonis<\/PERSON> reported <LOCATION>Athens<\/LOCATION>, <PERSON>James Kanter Brussels<\/PERSON>. Reporting contributed <PERSON>Alan Cowell<\/PERSON> <LOCATION>London<\/LOCATION>, <PERSON>David Jolly Paris<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Alison Smale Berlin Jack Ewing Vilnius<\/PERSON>, <LOCATION>Lithuania<\/LOCATION>.,original:By <PERSON>NIKI KITSANTONIS JAMES KANTER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Niki,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:KITSANTONIS},{firstname:James,role:reported,organization:,rank:2,lastname:KANTER}]}",article
"<LOCATION>Britain</LOCATION>'s economy relied heavily spending households growth quarter fall take-home incomes, underscoring challenges recovery sounder footing.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-23T04:57:05Z,[],498,"<LOCATION>Britain</LOCATION>'s economy relied heavily spending households growth quarter fall take-home incomes, underscoring challenges recovery sounder footing.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/23/business/23reuters-britain-economy.html,54993cd2798810035238e7be,null,"{main:British Economy Relying More Consumer Spending, Investment Sags,print_headline:UK Households Drive Economy, Current Account Deeper Red}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The rouble hit highest levels weeks <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>, shored informal capital control measures designed head repeat inflation protests marked <LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION>'s <DATE>1998</DATE> financial crisis.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-23T02:11:13Z,[],897,"The rouble hit highest levels weeks <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>, shored informal capital control measures designed head repeat inflation protests marked <LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION>'s <DATE>1998</DATE> financial crisis.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/23/business/23reuters-russia-crisis-rouble.html,54991627798810035238e77b,null,"{main:Informal Capital Controls Arrest Russian Rouble's Slide,print_headline:Informal Capital Controls Arrest Russian Rouble's Slide}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Bondholders in the casino company’s biggest unit back a bankruptcy that its parent’s merger with an affiliate could fund, says <PERSON>Quentin Webb</PERSON> of <ORGANIZATION>Reuters Breakingviews</ORGANIZATION>.",null,"[{name:organizations,rank:1,value:Caesars Entertainment Corporation},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Casinos},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Credit Debt}]",Business Day,"Bondholders in the casino company’s biggest unit back a bankruptcy that its parent’s merger with an affiliate could fund, says <PERSON>Quentin Webb</PERSON> of <ORGANIZATION>Reuters Breakingviews</ORGANIZATION>.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-22T14:13:11Z,[],403,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/22/as-caesars-deals-a-showdown-in-las-vegas-awaits/,54986da5798810035238e599,Dealbook,"{main:As Caesars Deals, Showdown Las Vegas Awaits,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>QUENTIN WEBB<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Quentin,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:WEBB}]}",blogpost
<LOCATION>Germany</LOCATION>'s <PERSON>Gerry Weber</PERSON> agreed buy fashion group <PERSON>Hallhuber</PERSON> announced <DATE>Monday</DATE> plans return menswear market part expansion strategy.,null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-22T12:47:05Z,[],309,<LOCATION>Germany</LOCATION>'s <PERSON>Gerry Weber</PERSON> agreed buy fashion group <PERSON>Hallhuber</PERSON> announced <DATE>Monday</DATE> plans return menswear market part expansion strategy.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/22/business/22reuters-hallhuber-m-a-gerry.html,549859b9798810035238e563,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Germany<\/LOCATION>'s <PERSON>Gerry Weber Buys Hallhuber<\/PERSON>, Eyes Menswear,print_headline:<LOCATION>Germany<\/LOCATION>'s <PERSON>Gerry Weber Buys Hallhuber<\/PERSON>, Eyes Menswear}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION>'s tensions <LOCATION>West Ukraine</LOCATION> slump ruble echoing French Alps &#8212; businesses, time ski season.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-22T09:28:21Z,[],1083,"<LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION>'s tensions <LOCATION>West Ukraine</LOCATION> slump ruble echoing French Alps &#8212; businesses, time ski season.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/22/us/ap-eu-travel-europe-russia-tourism-troubles.html,54982b5d7988104a1e0df52c,null,"{main:Tourism Suffers <DATE>Winter<\/DATE> EU-Russia Discontent,print_headline:Tourism Suffers Winter EU-Russia Discontent}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"A big oil price slide hurt <LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION>'s attempts rescue battered living standards, economic pain soften stance nuclear talks end aid allies <LOCATION>Syria</LOCATION>, matters ruling clerics strategic priorities.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-22T06:14:26Z,[],811,"A big oil price slide hurt <LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION>'s attempts rescue battered living standards, economic pain soften stance nuclear talks end aid allies <LOCATION>Syria</LOCATION>, matters ruling clerics strategic priorities.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/22/world/middleeast/22reuters-iran-economy.html,5497fd9f7988104a1e0df123,Middle East,"{main:Budget Pressure Unlikely Deflect Iran From Nuclear Goals,print_headline:Budget Pressure Unlikely Deflect Iran From Nuclear Goals}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION>'s tensions <LOCATION>West Ukraine</LOCATION> slump ruble echoing French Alps &#8212; businesses, time ski season.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-21T06:29:31Z,[],1083,"<LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION>'s tensions <LOCATION>West Ukraine</LOCATION> slump ruble echoing French Alps &#8212; businesses, time ski season.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/21/world/europe/ap-eu-europe-russia-tourism-troubles.html,5496afa579881029b367deeb,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:Tourism Suffers <DATE>Winter<\/DATE> EU-Russia Discontent,print_headline:Tourism Suffers Winter EU-Russia Discontent}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
