snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"DISH Networks Inc <DATE>Thursday</DATE> make The Interview, controversial <ORGANIZATION>Sony Pictures Entertainment</ORGANIZATION> film fictitious assassination North Korean leader <PERSON>Kim Jong Un</PERSON>, pay-per-view option starting Jan 2.",null,[],Arts,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T14:13:13Z,[],173,"DISH Networks Inc <DATE>Thursday</DATE> make The Interview, controversial <ORGANIZATION>Sony Pictures Entertainment</ORGANIZATION> film fictitious assassination North Korean leader <PERSON>Kim Jong Un</PERSON>, pay-per-view option starting Jan 2.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/arts/01reuters-dish-theinterview.html,54a59cea7988102023c94688,null,"{main:DISH Network Make 'The Interview' Available January 2,print_headline:DISH Network Make 'The Interview' Available January 2}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
Dwyane Wade angry. Just.,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T12:39:32Z,[],715,Dwyane Wade angry. Just.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/sports/basketball/ap-bkn-heat-wades-year.html,54a5871e7988102023c93fca,Pro Basketball,"{main:Dwyane Wade Looking Ahead After Year Change,print_headline:Dwyane Wade Looking Ahead After Year Change}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Beset critics buffeted economic woes, <ORGANIZATION>European Union</ORGANIZATION> chiefs forgiven thinking Pope <PERSON>Francis</PERSON> apply balm New Year address <ORGANIZATION>EU</ORGANIZATION> parliament.",null,[],Business Day,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T11:26:15Z,[],694,"Beset critics buffeted economic woes, <ORGANIZATION>European Union</ORGANIZATION> chiefs forgiven thinking Pope <PERSON>Francis</PERSON> apply balm New Year address <ORGANIZATION>EU</ORGANIZATION> parliament.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/business/ap-eu-europes-new-year.html,54a575c579881011bed2ceaa,null,"{main:Troubled <ORGANIZATION>EU<\/ORGANIZATION> Hoping Only Way Is Up 2015,print_headline:Troubled <ORGANIZATION>EU<\/ORGANIZATION> Hoping Only Way Is Up 2015}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Palestinian President <PERSON>Mahmoud Abbas</PERSON> entered confrontation <LOCATION>Israel</LOCATION> signing <ORGANIZATION>International Criminal Court</ORGANIZATION>.,null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T10:40:03Z,[],846,Palestinian President <PERSON>Mahmoud Abbas</PERSON> entered confrontation <LOCATION>Israel</LOCATION> signing <ORGANIZATION>International Criminal Court</ORGANIZATION>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/world/middleeast/01reuters-palestinians-israel-abbas.html,54a56b0279881011bed2cc49,Middle East,"{main:Abbas Trades Stalemate Confrontation ICC Move,print_headline:Abbas Trades Stalemate Confrontation ICC Move}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Set future, Frank, retired cat burglar, grown kids concerned longer live. They tempted place nursing home <PERSON>Frank</PERSON>'s son chooses option: man's wishes, bu",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T08:58:02Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/03/03/movies/video-frank/video-frank-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/03/03/movies/video-frank/video-frank-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/03/03/movies/video-frank/video-frank-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/03/03/movies/video-frank/video-frank-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/03/03/movies/video-frank/video-frank-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/03/03/movies/video-frank/video-frank-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",47,"Set future, Frank, retired cat burglar, grown kids concerned longer live. They tempted place nursing home <PERSON>Frank</PERSON>'s son chooses option: man's wishes, bu",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003369625/frank.html,54a5527179881011bed2c6cf,null,{"main":"Frank"},"{original:<PERSON>Samuel Goldwyn<\/PERSON> Films,person:[{firstname:Samuel,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Goldwyn,rank:1,lastname:Films}]}",multimedia
"Beset critics buffeted economic woes, <ORGANIZATION>European Union</ORGANIZATION> chiefs forgiven thinking Pope <PERSON>Francis</PERSON> apply balm New Year address <ORGANIZATION>EU</ORGANIZATION> parliament.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T07:44:52Z,[],694,"Beset critics buffeted economic woes, <ORGANIZATION>European Union</ORGANIZATION> chiefs forgiven thinking Pope <PERSON>Francis</PERSON> apply balm New Year address <ORGANIZATION>EU</ORGANIZATION> parliament.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/world/europe/ap-eu-europes-new-year-.html,54a5424279881011bed2c33b,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:Troubled <ORGANIZATION>EU<\/ORGANIZATION> Hoping Only Way Is Up 2015,print_headline:Troubled <ORGANIZATION>EU<\/ORGANIZATION> Hoping Only Way Is Up 2015}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Brothers Australian Al-Jazeera English journalist held <LOCATION>Egypt</LOCATION> year <DATE>Friday</DATE> lawyers focusing deportation President <PERSON>Abdel-Fattah el-Sissi</PERSON>'s command option.,null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T01:04:21Z,[],526,Brothers Australian Al-Jazeera English journalist held <LOCATION>Egypt</LOCATION> year <DATE>Friday</DATE> lawyers focusing deportation President <PERSON>Abdel-Fattah el-Sissi</PERSON>'s command option.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/world/middleeast/ap-ml-egypt-al-jazeera.html,54a4e43679881011bed2adea,Middle East,"{main:Australian's Family Hope <LOCATION>Egypt<\/LOCATION> Will Deport Him,print_headline:Australian's Family Hope <LOCATION>Egypt<\/LOCATION> Will Deport Him}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"The Yellow Jackets finished 452 rushing yards win Bulldogs, improving 2-8 bowl games past 10 seasons.",,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Football College},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Orange Bowl Football Game},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:3,value:<ORGANIZATION>Georgia Institute Technology<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:University <LOCATION>Mississippi<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:5,value:Prescott, Dak <DATE>1993<\/DATE>-}]",Sports,null,The New York Times,[],Sports,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/02/sports/01orangebowl1/01orangebowl1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/02/sports/01orangebowl1/01orangebowl1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/02/sports/01orangebowl1/01orangebowl1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:429},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/02/sports/01orangebowl1/01orangebowl1-articleLarge.jpg,height:429},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/02/sports/01orangebowl1/01orangebowl1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/02/sports/01orangebowl1/01orangebowl1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",492,"The Yellow Jackets finished 452 rushing yards win Bulldogs, improving 2-8 bowl games past 10 seasons.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/sports/ncaafootball/georgia-tech-runs-past-mississippi-state-in-orange-bowl.html,54a4dcf079881011bed2ac46,College Football,"{content_kicker:<LOCATION>Georgia<\/LOCATION> Tech 49, <LOCATION>Mississippi<\/LOCATION> State 34,main:<ORGANIZATION>Georgia Tech Runs Past Mississippi State<\/ORGANIZATION> Orange Bowl,kicker:<LOCATION>Georgia<\/LOCATION> Tech 49, <LOCATION>Mississippi<\/LOCATION> State 34}","{contributor:,original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
<PERSON>Flora Grubb</PERSON> introduces minimal steel holders air plants.,3,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Flowers Plants},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Interior Design Furnishings},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:4,value:<LOCATION>San Francisco Calif<\/LOCATION>}]",Home & Garden,"<PERSON>Flora Grubb</PERSON> designs <LOCATION>Thigmotrope Perch</LOCATION>, steel stand display air plants.",The New York Times,[],Home,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/garden/01CURR_DECOR/01CURR_DECOR-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/garden/01CURR_DECOR/01CURR_DECOR-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/garden/01CURR_DECOR/01CURR_DECOR-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:683},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/garden/01CURR_DECOR/01CURR_DECOR-articleLarge.jpg,height:683},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/garden/01CURR_DECOR/01CURR_DECOR-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/garden/01CURR_DECOR/01CURR_DECOR-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",143,<PERSON>Flora Grubb</PERSON> introduces minimal steel holders air plants.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/garden/what-lies-beneath-takes-a-gulp-of-air.html,54a48cd179881011bed299f5,null,"{content_kicker:Décor,main:What Lies Beneath Takes Gulp Air,print_headline:What Lies Beneath Takes Gulp Air,kicker:Décor}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>TIM McKEOUGH<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Tim,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:McKEOUGH}]}",article
Co-washing products gain traction beauty industry.,3,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Hair},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Shampoos Hair Products}]",Fashion & Style,"Beauty industry begun offer wide range 'co-washing' hair products, cleansing conditioners clean hair foam, gentler shampoo alternative women curly color-treated hair.",The New York Times,[],Styles,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01SKIN1/01SKIN1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01SKIN1/01SKIN1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01SKIN1/01SKIN1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:600},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01SKIN1/01SKIN1-articleLarge.jpg,height:600},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01SKIN1/01SKIN1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/fashion/01SKIN1/01SKIN1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",787,Co-washing products gain traction beauty industry.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/fashion/no-shampoo-regimens-replace-the-suds.html,54a2ce977988104803cc8adf,null,"{content_kicker:Skin Deep,main:No-Shampoo Regimens Replace Suds,print_headline:No-Shampoo Regimens Replace Suds,kicker:Skin Deep}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>MARISA MELTZER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Marisa,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:MELTZER}]}",article
