snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"From Bâtard to <ORGANIZATION>Russ &amp; Daughters Cafe</ORGANIZATION>, the restaurants that brought a fresh perspective to the dining scene this year.",4,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Restaurants},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:11,value:Bar Bolonat <LOCATION>Manhattan<\/LOCATION>, NY, Restaurant},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:12,value:Manhattan NYC},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:13,value:Brooklyn NYC},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:2,value:Batard <LOCATION>Manhattan<\/LOCATION>, NY, Restaurant},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Russ & Daughters Cafe <LOCATION>Manhattan<\/LOCATION>, NY, Restaurant},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Simone, The <LOCATION>Manhattan<\/LOCATION>, NY, Restaurant},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:5,value:Cherche Midi <LOCATION>Manhattan<\/LOCATION>, NY, Restaurant},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:<PERSON>Ivan Ramen Manhattan<\/PERSON>, NY, Restaurant},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:7,value:<LOCATION>Delaware Hudson Brooklyn<\/LOCATION>, NY, Restaurant},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:8,value:Contra <LOCATION>Manhattan<\/LOCATION>, NY, Restaurant},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:9,value:Dirty French <LOCATION>Manhattan<\/LOCATION>, NY, Restaurant},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:10,value:Gato <LOCATION>Manhattan<\/LOCATION>, NY, Restaurant}]",Food,<PERSON>Pete Wells</PERSON> identifies 10 restaurants <LOCATION>New York City</LOCATION> 2014.,The New York Times,[],Dining,2014-12-31T00:00:00Z,[],1984,"From Bâtard to <ORGANIZATION>Russ &amp; Daughters Cafe</ORGANIZATION>, the restaurants that brought a fresh perspective to the dining scene this year.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/dining/nyc-best-new-restaurants-2014.html,549d62e77988103babf08b8c,null,"{content_kicker:Restaurants,main:The 10 Best New Restaurants 2014,print_headline:Gazing Beyond Stars,kicker:Restaurants}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>PETE WELLS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Pete,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:WELLS}]}",article
"Every week, combined total 28 planes roll assembly lines <ORGANIZATION>Airbus</ORGANIZATION>, <ORGANIZATION>Boeing</ORGANIZATION>, <ORGANIZATION>Bombardier Embraer</ORGANIZATION> factories &#8212; fastest production rate history commercial aviation. Most aircraft feed insatiable demand...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T10:03:21Z,[],1166,"Every week, combined total 28 planes roll assembly lines <ORGANIZATION>Airbus</ORGANIZATION>, <ORGANIZATION>Boeing</ORGANIZATION>, <ORGANIZATION>Bombardier Embraer</ORGANIZATION> factories &#8212; fastest production rate history commercial aviation. Most aircraft feed insatiable demand <LOCATION>Asia</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/us/ap-as-travel-indonesia-plane-pilot-shortage.html,54a2bfa07988104803cc8abb,null,"{main:Rapid Growth Leaves Asian Airlines Searching Pilots,print_headline:Rapid Growth Leaves Asian Airlines Searching Pilots}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Every week, combined total 28 planes roll assembly lines <ORGANIZATION>Airbus</ORGANIZATION>, <ORGANIZATION>Boeing</ORGANIZATION>, <ORGANIZATION>Bombardier Embraer</ORGANIZATION> factories &#8212; fastest production rate history commercial aviation. Most aircraft feed insatiable demand...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T01:02:03Z,[],1166,"Every week, combined total 28 planes roll assembly lines <ORGANIZATION>Airbus</ORGANIZATION>, <ORGANIZATION>Boeing</ORGANIZATION>, <ORGANIZATION>Bombardier Embraer</ORGANIZATION> factories &#8212; fastest production rate history commercial aviation. Most aircraft feed insatiable demand <LOCATION>Asia</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/us/ap-as-indonesia-plane-pilot-shortage.html,54a2412e7988104803cc89b1,null,"{main:Rapid Growth Leaves Asian Airlines Searching Pilots,print_headline:Rapid Growth Leaves Asian Airlines Searching Pilots}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"New books technology experts examine consumer-ranking techniques widespread, offer advice people protect.",3,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Credit Scores},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Books Literature},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Privacy},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Data-Mining Database Marketing},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:5,value:<PERSON>Fertik<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Michael<\/PERSON>},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:6,value:Pasquale, Frank},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:7,value:<PERSON>Thompson<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>David<\/PERSON> C <DATE>1979<\/DATE>-},{is_major:N,name:creative_works,rank:8,value:The Black Box Society: The Secret Algorithms That Control Money Information Book},{is_major:N,name:creative_works,rank:9,value:The Reputation Economy: How Optimize Your Digital Footprint A World Where Your Reputation Is Your Most Valuable Asset Book}]",Technology,Natasha Singer Technophobia column cites nonfiction books reveal companies secretly rank score consumers; notes The Reputation Economy: How Optimize Your Digital Footprint A World Where Your Reputation Is Your Most Valuable Asset <PERSON>Michael Fertik David Thompson</PERSON> The Black Box Society: The <ORGANIZATION>Secret Algorithms That Control Money Information Frank Pasquale</ORGANIZATION> differ substantially advising people protect.,The New York Times,[],SundayBusiness,2014-12-28T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/28/business/28-TECHNO/28-TECHNO-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/business/28-TECHNO/28-TECHNO-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/28/business/28-TECHNO/28-TECHNO-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:412},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/business/28-TECHNO/28-TECHNO-articleLarge.jpg,height:412},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/28/business/28-TECHNO/28-TECHNO-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/business/28-TECHNO/28-TECHNO-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1033,"New books technology experts examine consumer-ranking techniques widespread, offer advice people protect.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/technology/the-scoreboards-where-you-cant-see-your-score.html,549ecfcf7988105ced788713,null,"{content_kicker:Technophoria,main:The Scoreboards Where You Can’t See Your Score,print_headline:The Scoreboards Where You Can’t See Your Score,kicker:Technophoria}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>NATASHA<\/PERSON> SINGER,person:[{firstname:Natasha,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SINGER}]}",article
"Amid churn change, champions reigned sports world, privileged tended reclaim privileges.",,"[{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Sochi Russia<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Olympic Games 2014},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:3,value:National Basketball Assn},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:World Cup 2014 Soccer},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Commonwealth Games},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:6,value:<PERSON>Woods<\/PERSON>, Tiger},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:7,value:Nadal, Rafael},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:8,value:<PERSON>Djokovic<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Novak<\/PERSON>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:9,value:<PERSON>Williams<\/PERSON>, Serena}]",Sports,null,The New York Times,[],Sports,2014-12-26T13:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/25/sports/international/26iht-sryereview26-sochi/26iht-sryereview26-sochi-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/sports/international/26iht-sryereview26-sochi/26iht-sryereview26-sochi-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/25/sports/international/26iht-sryereview26-sochi/26iht-sryereview26-sochi-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:375},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/sports/international/26iht-sryereview26-sochi/26iht-sryereview26-sochi-articleLarge.jpg,height:375},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/25/sports/international/26iht-sryereview26-sochi/26iht-sryereview26-sochi-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/sports/international/26iht-sryereview26-sochi/26iht-sryereview26-sochi-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1366,"Amid churn change, champions reigned sports world, privileged tended reclaim privileges.",Special Report,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/26/sports/international/top-stories-sports-2014.html,549c2f6b798810030669117b,International Sports,"{content_kicker:Special Report: Year Sports,main:<LOCATION>Russia<\/LOCATION> Wasn’t the Only Story in <DATE>2014<\/DATE>,print_headline:<LOCATION>Russia<\/LOCATION> Wasn't Only Story 2014}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>CHRISTOPHER CLAREY<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Christopher,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:CLAREY}]}",article
"In an interview, Mr. <PERSON>Lurie</PERSON> shared some of his thoughts about <ORGANIZATION>AT&T</ORGANIZATION>’s future and the state of the wireless industry and those “supercookies.”",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Lurie<\/PERSON>, Glenn},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:<ORGANIZATION>AT&T Inc<\/ORGANIZATION>},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Customer Relations},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Discount Selling},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Wireless Communications}]",Technology,"In an interview, Mr. <PERSON>Lurie</PERSON> shared some of his thoughts about <ORGANIZATION>AT&T</ORGANIZATION>’s future and the state of the wireless industry and those “supercookies.”",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-26T07:00:40Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/26/technology/26bits-lurie/26bits-lurie-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/technology/26bits-lurie/26bits-lurie-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/26/technology/26bits-lurie/26bits-lurie-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:453},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/technology/26bits-lurie/26bits-lurie-articleLarge.jpg,height:453},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/26/technology/26bits-lurie/26bits-lurie-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/technology/26bits-lurie/26bits-lurie-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",855,null,Blog,http://bits.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/26/a-conversation-with-glenn-lurie-att-mobilitys-new-chief/,549d4f037988103babf08b79,null,"{main:A Conversation With <PERSON>Glenn Lurie<\/PERSON>, <ORGANIZATION>AT&T Mobility<\/ORGANIZATION>'s New Chief,kicker:Bits}","{original:By <PERSON>BRIAN X. CHEN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Brian,role:reported,organization:,middlename:X.,rank:1,lastname:CHEN}]}",blogpost
"<PERSON>Udo J.ergens</PERSON>, Austrian-born star dominated pop music German-speaking world sold 100 million records career spanning decades, died <DATE>Sunday</DATE>. He 80 years.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-21T13:55:24Z,[],631,"<PERSON>Udo Juergens</PERSON>, Austrian-born star dominated pop music German-speaking world sold 100 million records career spanning decades, died <DATE>Sunday</DATE>. He 80 years.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/21/world/europe/ap-eu-switzerland-obit-juergens.html,549718687988104a1e0de463,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:German-Language Pop Superstar <PERSON>Udo Juergens<\/PERSON> Dies,print_headline:German-Language Pop Superstar <PERSON>Udo Juergens<\/PERSON> Dies}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"New books <PERSON>Hassan Daoud</PERSON>, <PERSON>Salar Abdoh</PERSON>, <PERSON>Assaf Gavron Kader Abdolah</PERSON>.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Books Literature},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:Abdoh, Salar},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:Daoud, Hassan},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:4,value:<PERSON>Gavron<\/PERSON>, Assaf},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:5,value:Abdolah, Kader}]",Books,"Pauls Toutonghi reviews books The <PERSON>Penguin</PERSON>'s Song <PERSON>Hassan Daoud</PERSON>, <ORGANIZATION>Tehran Twilight Salar Abdoh</ORGANIZATION>, The <PERSON>Hilltop Assaf Gavron</PERSON> The King Kader Abdolah.",The New York Times,[],BookReview,2014-12-21T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/21/books/review/1221-bks-Short/1221-bks-Short-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/21/books/review/1221-bks-Short/1221-bks-Short-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/21/books/review/1221-bks-Short/1221-bks-Short-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:150},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/21/books/review/1221-bks-Short/1221-bks-Short-articleLarge.jpg,height:150},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/21/books/review/1221-bks-Short/1221-bks-Short-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/21/books/review/1221-bks-Short/1221-bks-Short-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1042,"New books <PERSON>Hassan Daoud</PERSON>, <PERSON>Salar Abdoh</PERSON>, <PERSON>Assaf Gavron Kader Abdolah</PERSON>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/21/books/review/the-penguins-song-by-hassan-daoud-and-more.html,5494562979881048d26b3337,<DATE>Sunday</DATE> Book Review,"{content_kicker:The Shortlist,main:Middle Eastern Fiction,seo:'The Penguin's Song' <PERSON>Hassan Daoud<\/PERSON>, More,print_headline:Middle Eastern Fiction,kicker:The Shortlist}","{contributor:,original:By PAULS TOUTONGHI,person:[{firstname:Pauls,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:TOUTONGHI}]}",article
"A week Christmas, <LOCATION>Alaska</LOCATION>'s largest city postcard wonderland, place expect equipment making snow.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-19T02:24:56Z,[],571,"A week Christmas, <LOCATION>Alaska</LOCATION>'s largest city postcard wonderland, place expect equipment making snow.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/19/us/ap-us-alaska-weird-weather.html,5493d2fb79881048d26b31e9,null,"{main:Weird Weather Lingers <LOCATION>Alaska<\/LOCATION>'s Largest City,print_headline:Weird Weather Lingers <LOCATION>Alaska<\/LOCATION>'s Largest City}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Here’s a different way to look at our situation: If we had another dollar to invest in acquiring customers, we could make <MONEY>$8</MONEY> back on that investment in a year.",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Moore<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Robert<\/PERSON> J},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:RJMetrics Inc},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Advertising Marketing},{name:subject,rank:2,value:E-Commerce},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Small Business},{name:subject,rank:4,value:Start-ups},{name:subject,rank:5,value:Venture Capital}]",Business Day,"Here’s a different way to look at our situation: If we had another dollar to invest in acquiring customers, we could make <MONEY>$8</MONEY> back on that investment in a year.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-16T07:00:36Z,[],995,null,Blog,http://boss.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/16/why-it-makes-sense-for-some-companies-to-burn-cash/,54901f4a798810619765f512,Small Business,"{main:Why It Makes Sense Some Companies Burn Cash,kicker:You&#039;re Boss}","{original:By <PERSON>ROBERT J. MOORE<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Robert,role:reported,organization:,middlename:J.,rank:1,lastname:MOORE}]}",blogpost
