snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"- The United Arab E.irates <LOCATION>Egypt</LOCATION> attractive major <ORGANIZATION>Middle Eastern</ORGANIZATION> stock markets era low oil prices, latest <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION> survey regional asset managers suggests.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T00:02:01Z,[],731,"- <ORGANIZATION>The United Arab Emirates Egypt</ORGANIZATION> attractive major <ORGANIZATION>Middle Eastern</ORGANIZATION> stock markets era low oil prices, latest <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION> survey regional asset managers suggests.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-mideast-investment-survey.html,54a383c07988102761d6d0d4,null,"{main:Funds Positive <ORGANIZATION>UAE<\/ORGANIZATION>, <LOCATION>Egypt<\/LOCATION> Stocks Era Cheap Oil-Survey,print_headline:Funds Positive <ORGANIZATION>UAE<\/ORGANIZATION>, <LOCATION>Egypt<\/LOCATION> Stocks Era Cheap Oil-Survey}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Governments <LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Peru Venezuela</LOCATION> load debt ignore danger signs.",9,"[{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>South America<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Economic Conditions Trends},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:3,value:<LOCATION>Peru<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:4,value:<LOCATION>Venezuela<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:5,value:<LOCATION>Brazil<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:6,value:Latin America}]",World,"<LOCATION>South America</LOCATION> Memo; boom prices commodities oil, minerals crops ended <LOCATION>South America</LOCATION>, evidence countries including <LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Peru Venezuela</LOCATION> position avoid bust; measure external debt foreign reserves low region.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-30T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/30/world/30latin-4/30latin-4-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/world/30latin-4/30latin-4-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/30/world/30latin-4/30latin-4-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/world/30latin-4/30latin-4-articleL.rge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/30/world/30latin-4/30latin-4-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/world/30latin-4/30latin-4-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1282,"Governments <LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Peru Venezuela</LOCATION> load debt ignore danger signs.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/world/americas/an-economic-boom-recedes-but-south-america-might-avert-the-bust.html,54a1fa727988104803cc88f0,Americas,"{content_kicker:South America Memo,main:An Economic Boom Recedes, <LOCATION>South America<\/LOCATION> Might Avert Bust,print_headline:A Boom Recedes, Transformed Continent Might Avert Bust,kicker:South America Memo}","{contributor:<PERSON>Andrea Zarate<\/PERSON> contributed reporting.,original:By <PERSON>WILLIAM NEUMAN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:William,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:NEUMAN}]}",article
Clemson quarterback <PERSON>Cole Stoudt</PERSON> moments <DATE>2014</DATE> season hard forget.,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-29T21:09:41Z,[],721,Clemson quarterback <PERSON>Cole Stoudt</PERSON> moments <DATE>2014</DATE> season hard forget.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/29/sports/ncaafootball/ap-fbc-russell-athletic-bowl.html,54a20a2f7988104803cc8905,College Football,"{main:Clemson Routs Oklahoma Russell Athletic Bowl,print_headline:Clemson Routs Oklahoma Russell Athletic Bowl}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
A woman&#8217;s successful fight sick pay offers <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>&#8217;s mayor delivered promise uplift struggling families.,13,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Paid Time Off},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:de Blasio, Bill},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:3,value:<LOCATION>New York City<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Labor Jobs}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"<PERSON>Rachel L Swarns</PERSON> The Working Life column examines <LOCATION>New York City Mayor Bill de Blasio</LOCATION>'s year office experience <PERSON>Sharme Cagle</PERSON>; notes <PERSON>Cagle</PERSON>, licensed practical nurse, beneficiary de <ORGANIZATION>Blasio</ORGANIZATION>'s major policy move, expansion paid sick leave; points policy initiatives.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-29T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/29/nyregion/29WORKINGweb/29WORKINGweb-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/nyregion/29WORKINGweb/29WORKINGweb-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/29/nyregion/29WORKINGweb/29WORKINGweb-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:401},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/nyregion/29WORKINGweb/29WORKINGweb-articleLarge.jpg,height:401},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/29/nyregion/29WORKINGweb/29WORKINGweb-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/nyregion/29WORKINGweb/29WORKINGweb-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",886,A woman&#8217;s successful fight sick pay offers <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>&#8217;s mayor delivered promise uplift struggling families.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/22/nyregion/measuring-de-blasios-first-year-by-a-broken-toe-and-a-360-check.html,5496fa4679881029b367df41,null,"{content_kicker:The Working Life,main:Measuring Mayor de Blasio’s First Year by a <ORGANIZATION>Broken Toe<\/ORGANIZATION> and a <MONEY>$360<\/MONEY> Check,print_headline:Measuring the Mayor’s First Year by a <ORGANIZATION>Broken Toe<\/ORGANIZATION> and a <MONEY>$360<\/MONEY> Check,kicker:The Working Life}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>RACHEL L. SWARNS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Rachel,role:reported,organization:,middlename:L.,rank:1,lastname:SWARNS}]}",article
"Despite illness, job loss, caring daughter severe autism financial troubles, <PERSON>Maria Maley</PERSON>, &#8220;If bills paid, I&#8217;m happy.&#8221;",23,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:New York Times Neediest Cases Fund},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Philanthropy},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:3,value:UJA-Federation <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION>}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"Metropolitan Council on Jewish Poverty, a beneficiary agency of UJA-Federation <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>, one of the organizations supported by <ORGANIZATION>The New York Times Neediest</ORGANIZATION> Cases Fund, draws <MONEY>$1,100</MONEY> to help unemployed <LOCATION>Staten Island</LOCATION> woman <PERSON>Maria Maley</PERSON> pay arrears on her rent.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-28T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/27/nyregion/27NEEDIESTMaley/27NEEDIESTMaley-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/nyregion/27NEEDIESTMaley/27NEEDIESTMaley-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/27/nyregion/27NEEDIESTMaley/27NEEDIESTMaley-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/nyregion/27NEEDIESTMaley/27NEEDIESTMaley-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/27/nyregion/27NEEDIESTMaley/27NEEDIESTMaley-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/nyregion/27NEEDIESTMaley/27NEEDIESTMaley-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",861,"Despite illness, job loss, caring daughter severe autism financial troubles, <PERSON>Maria Maley</PERSON>, &#8220;If bills paid, I&#8217;m happy.&#8221;",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/nyregion/for-staten-island-mother-her-two-daughters-needs-always-come-first.html,549f524979881001534d1fc3,null,"{content_kicker:The Neediest Cases,main:For <LOCATION>Staten Island Mother<\/LOCATION>, Her Two Daughters&#8217; Needs Always Come First,print_headline:For <LOCATION>Staten Island Mother<\/LOCATION>, Her Two Daughters’ Needs Always Come First,kicker:The Neediest Cases}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>JOHN OTIS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:John,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:OTIS}]}",article
"For <LOCATION>Harlem</LOCATION> family 10 sons daughters home, UJA-Federation <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> made sleeping accommodations lot easier.",25,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:New York Times Neediest Cases Fund},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>Harlem Manhattan<\/LOCATION>, NY},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:3,value:UJA-Federation of <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION>}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"Educational Alliance, part of UJA-Federation of <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>, one of the seven organizations supported by <ORGANIZATION>The New York Times Neediest</ORGANIZATION> Cases Fund, draws <MONEY>$2,700</MONEY> from fund to pay for beds, futons and home office equipment for <PERSON>Julia</PERSON> and <ORGANIZATION>Tarcisio Coraizaca</ORGANIZATION> and their seven children.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-26T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/26/nyregion/NEEDIEST/NEEDIEST-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/nyregion/NEEDIEST/NEEDIEST-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/26/nyregion/NEEDIEST/NEEDIEST-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/nyregion/NEEDIEST/NEEDIEST-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/26/nyregion/NEEDIEST/NEEDIEST-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/nyregion/NEEDIEST/NEEDIEST-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",649,"For <LOCATION>Harlem</LOCATION> family 10 sons daughters home, UJA-Federation <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> made sleeping accommodations lot easier.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/26/nyregion/improving-the-bedtime-arithmetic-for-a-large-family.html,549ccd8c7988103babf08aca,null,"{content_kicker:The Neediest Cases,main:Improving Bedtime Arithmetic Large Family,print_headline:Improving Bedtime Arithmetic Large Family,kicker:The Neediest Cases}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>SANDRA E. GARCIA<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Sandra,role:reported,organization:,middlename:E.,rank:1,lastname:GARCIA}]}",article
"Activists praised <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> government's decision remove <LOCATION>Gambia</LOCATION> trade agreement response human rights abuses, including law signed <DATE>October</DATE> imposes life imprisonment homosexual acts.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-24T14:11:43Z,[],301,"Activists praised <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> government's decision remove <LOCATION>Gambia</LOCATION> trade agreement response human rights abuses, including law signed <DATE>October</DATE> imposes life imprisonment homosexual acts.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/24/world/africa/ap-af-gambia-us-trade-agreement.html,549b10b17988100306690e81,<LOCATION>Africa</LOCATION>,"{main:US Removes Gambia From Trade Agreement,print_headline:US Removes Gambia From Trade Agreement}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
The newly elected president <LOCATION>Tunisia</LOCATION> faces deep-seated economic problems takes power country blazed trail Arab Spring.,null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-24T05:38:09Z,[],501,The newly elected president <LOCATION>Tunisia</LOCATION> faces deep-seated economic problems takes power country blazed trail Arab Spring.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/24/world/middleeast/ap-ml-tunisia-economic-challenges.html,549a97f47988102d96d567cc,Middle East,"{main:Economy Dominates In-Tray <LOCATION>New Tunisia<\/LOCATION> President,print_headline:Economy Dominates In-Tray <LOCATION>New Tunisia<\/LOCATION> President}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Jameis Winston cleared violating student code conduct, woman accused raping spoke powerfully university hearing.",9,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Football College},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:Winston, Jameis},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Sex Crimes},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:4,value:Harding, Major B},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:5,value:<ORGANIZATION>Florida State University<\/ORGANIZATION>}]",Sports,<PERSON>Juliet Macur</PERSON> Sports The Times column holds <ORGANIZATION>Florida State University</ORGANIZATION> complicit clearing quarterback <PERSON>Jameis Winston</PERSON> rape allegation 2012; notes student conduct hearing transcript obtained The <ORGANIZATION>New York Times</ORGANIZATION> upholds accuser's story; states supported <ORGANIZATION>Florida State</ORGANIZATION>'s football program past couple years feel dirty.,The New York Times,[],Sports,2014-12-24T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/24/sports/Y-JP-MACUR/Y-JP-MACUR-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/24/sports/Y-JP-MACUR/Y-JP-MACUR-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/24/sports/Y-JP-MACUR/Y-JP-MACUR-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:384},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/24/sports/Y-JP-MACUR/Y-JP-MACUR-articleLarge.jpg,height:384},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/24/sports/Y-JP-MACUR/Y-JP-MACUR-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/24/sports/Y-JP-MACUR/Y-JP-MACUR-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",813,"Jameis Winston cleared violating student code conduct, woman accused raping spoke powerfully university hearing.",Text,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/24/sports/ncaafootball/transcript-of-jameis-winston-hearing-reveals-accusers-words-and-florida-states-complicity.html,549a29ce7988102d96d55cab,College Football,"{content_kicker:Sports The Times,main:Transcript of Winston Hearing Reveals Accuser’s Words, and <ORGANIZATION>Florida State<\/ORGANIZATION>’s Complicity,print_headline:Accuser’s Words, and <ORGANIZATION>Florida State<\/ORGANIZATION>’s Complicity,kicker:Sports The Times}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>JULIET MACUR<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Juliet,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:MACUR}]}",article
"Instead narrowing gender gaps, technology industry created vast <ORGANIZATION>Stanford University</ORGANIZATION>&#8217;s pioneering class <DATE>1994</DATE>.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,The New York Times,[],National,2014-12-23T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/01/us/stanford-94-photos-slide-M8SO/stanford-94-photos-slide-M8SO-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/01/us/stanford-94-photos-slide-M8SO/stanford-94-photos-slide-M8SO-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/01/us/stanford-94-photos-slide-M8SO/stanford-94-photos-slide-M8SO-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/01/us/stanford-94-photos-slide-M8SO/stanford-94-photos-slide-M8SO-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/01/us/stanford-94-photos-slide-M8SO/stanford-94-photos-slide-M8SO-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/01/us/stanford-94-photos-slide-M8SO/stanford-94-photos-slide-M8SO-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",5528,"Instead narrowing gender gaps, technology industry created vast <ORGANIZATION>Stanford University</ORGANIZATION>&#8217;s pioneering class <DATE>1994</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/23/us/stanfords-women-won-just-a-sliver-of-silicon-valley-.html,549969a6798810035238e817,null,"{main:A Gender Gap More Powerful Than Internet,seo:Stanford’s Women Won Just a Sliver of Silicon Valley,print_headline:A Gender Gap More Powerful Than Internet}","{contributor:Madeleine Han contributed research. Stanford Quad yearbook photos <DATE>1994<\/DATE> Will Kim, <PERSON>Victor Cheng Vincent Ho<\/PERSON>.,original:By <PERSON>JODI KANTOR<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Jodi,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:KANTOR}]}",article
