snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Rep. <PERSON>Joe Kennedy</PERSON> wrapping term <ORGANIZATION>Congress</ORGANIZATION>, remains committed bread butter local constituent services batting talk future higher office.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T12:58:39Z,[],646,"<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Rep. <PERSON>Joe Kennedy</PERSON> wrapping term <ORGANIZATION>Congress</ORGANIZATION>, remains committed bread butter local constituent services batting talk future higher office.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/us/ap-us-kennedy-first-year.html,54a58b707988102023c9411b,null,"{main:AP Interview: Rep. <PERSON>Kennedy<\/PERSON> Reflects First Term,print_headline:AP Interview: Rep. <PERSON>Kennedy<\/PERSON> Reflects First Term}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Lawyers 40 military personnel civilians killed wounded attack <LOCATION>Fort Hood</LOCATION> military post <ORGANIZATION>Texas Army</ORGANIZATION> psychologist filed petition <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>Pentagon</ORGANIZATION> incident declared act terrorism.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T16:15:48Z,[],311,Lawyers 40 military personnel civilians killed wounded attack <LOCATION>Fort Hood</LOCATION> military post <ORGANIZATION>Texas Army</ORGANIZATION> psychologist filed petition <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>Pentagon</ORGANIZATION> incident declared act terrorism.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/us/30reuters-usa-texas-forthood.html,54a316c67988102761d6cef9,null,"{main:Victims <LOCATION>Fort Hood Shooting Texas<\/LOCATION> Seek 'Terrorism' Declaration,print_headline:Victims <LOCATION>Fort Hood Shooting Texas<\/LOCATION> Seek 'Terrorism' Declaration}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
Taking America permanent war footing proving harder President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON> suggested.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T12:00:16Z,[],989,Taking America permanent war footing proving harder President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON> suggested.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/us/politics/ap-us-wars-end-abridged.html,54a2db117988102761d6ce56,Politics,"{main:US Off War Footing Year's End, Wars Go On,print_headline:US Off War Footing Year's End, Wars Go On}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Taking America permanent war footing proving harder President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON> suggested.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T11:54:38Z,[],1840,Taking America permanent war footing proving harder President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON> suggested.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/us/politics/ap-us-wars-end.html,54a2d9a67988104803cc8afb,Politics,"{main:US Off War Footing Year's End, Wars Go On,print_headline:US Off War Footing Year's End, Wars Go On}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"The main <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> export authority telling oil companies exporting lightly processed form crude oil called condensate formal permission, people familiar discussions.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T07:06:29Z,[],702,"The main <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> export authority telling oil companies exporting lightly processed form crude oil called condensate formal permission, people familiar discussions.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/business/30reuters-usa-crude-exports-exclusive.html,54a296187988104803cc8a68,null,"{main:Exclusive: <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Agency Gives Quiet Nod Light Oil Exports-Sources,print_headline:Exclusive: <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Agency Gives Quiet Nod Light Oil Exports-Sources}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
Distant neighborhoods hot. Rent regulation question.,1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Real Estate Housing Residential},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>New York City<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:3,value:Grand Concourse Bronx, NY},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Airbnb},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Renting Leasing Real Estate}]",Real Estate,"Real estate experts speculate year ahead <LOCATION>New York City</LOCATION>'s residential market; hottest issues include battle illegal bed-and-breakfast rentals, fate affordable housing rise neighborhoods missed housing boom city.",The New York Times,[],RealEstate,2014-12-28T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/28/realestate/28SUBCOVER/28SUBCOVER-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/realestate/28SUBCOVER/28SUBCOVER-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/28/realestate/28SUBCOVER/28SUBCOVER-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:416},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/realestate/28SUBCOVER/28SUBCOVER-articleLarge.jpg,height:416},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/28/realestate/28SUBCOVER/28SUBCOVER-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/realestate/28SUBCOVER/28SUBCOVER-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",2095,Distant neighborhoods hot. Rent regulation question.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/realestate/new-york-airbnb-and-rent-regulation-will-be-hot-topics.html,549d686b7988103babf08b92,null,"{main:What’s Up Next in <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION>?,seo:Airbnb Rent Regulation Will Be Hot Topics,print_headline:What’s Up Next?}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>RONDA KAYSEN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Ronda,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:KAYSEN}]}",article
Advocates worry prosecutors apply sweeping law decreed military-backed president tool fight terrorism.,4,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Egypt<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Human Rights Human Rights Violations},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:Sisi, <PERSON>Abdel Fattah<\/PERSON> el-},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Nonprofit Organizations}]",World,"Rights activists <LOCATION>Egypt</LOCATION> law enacted military-backed <PERSON>Pres Abdel Fattah</PERSON> el-Sisi sign <LOCATION>Egypt</LOCATION> repressive police state; law, intended fight terrorism, imposes potential life sentence crime interpreted harmful country.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-27T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/27/world/EGYPT/EGYPT-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/world/EGYPT/EGYPT-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/27/world/EGYPT/EGYPT-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:418},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/world/EGYPT/EGYPT-articleLarge.jpg,height:418},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/27/world/EGYPT/EGYPT-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/world/EGYPT/EGYPT-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1338,Advocates worry prosecutors apply sweeping law decreed military-backed president tool fight terrorism.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/27/world/middleeast/human-rights-groups-in-egypt-brace-for-crackdown-under-new-law.html,549e03c17988105ced78865f,Middle East,"{main:Human Rights Groups Egypt Brace Crackdown Under New Law,print_headline:Human Rights Groups Egypt Brace Crackdown Under New Law}","{contributor:<PERSON>Merna Thomas<\/PERSON> contributed reporting.,original:By <PERSON>DAVID D. KIRKPATRICK<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:David,role:reported,organization:,rank:1}]}",article
"While tens thousands immigrants living country illegally gearing apply long-sought driver's license <LOCATION>California</LOCATION> starting <DATE>Jan. 2</DATE>, urged.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-26T10:26:23Z,[],764,"While tens thousands immigrants living country illegally gearing apply long-sought driver's license <LOCATION>California</LOCATION> starting <DATE>Jan. 2</DATE>, urged.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/26/us/ap-us-immigrants-drivers-licenses.html,549d7eef7988103babf08bb7,null,"{main:<LOCATION>California<\/LOCATION> Gears Up Migrant Driver's Licenses,print_headline:<LOCATION>California<\/LOCATION> Gears Up Migrant Driver's Licenses}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Continuing Christmas Eve tradition, Gov. <PERSON>Jerry Brown</PERSON> issued pardons 105 people <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>, retracting man hours learning disclosed recent discipline financial regulators, spokesman.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-24T23:13:53Z,[],696,"Continuing Christmas Eve tradition, Gov. <PERSON>Jerry Brown</PERSON> issued pardons 105 people <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>, retracting man hours learning disclosed recent discipline financial regulators, spokesman.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/24/us/ap-us-governor-pardons.html,549b8f3979881003066910d9,null,"{main:<LOCATION>California<\/LOCATION>'s Governor Issues 105 Pardons, Retracts 1,print_headline:<LOCATION>California<\/LOCATION>'s Governor Issues 105 Pardons, Retracts 1}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
The newly elected president <LOCATION>Tunisia</LOCATION> faces deep-seated economic problems takes power country blazed trail Arab Spring.,null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-24T05:38:09Z,[],501,The newly elected president <LOCATION>Tunisia</LOCATION> faces deep-seated economic problems takes power country blazed trail Arab Spring.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/24/world/middleeast/ap-ml-tunisia-economic-challenges.html,549a97f47988102d96d567cc,Middle East,"{main:Economy Dominates In-Tray <LOCATION>New Tunisia<\/LOCATION> President,print_headline:Economy Dominates In-Tray <LOCATION>New Tunisia<\/LOCATION> President}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
