snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"<PERSON>Jim Caviezel</PERSON> stars golf legend <PERSON>Bobby Jones</PERSON>, icon retired competition tender age 28.",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T14:31:41Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-bobby-jones-stroke-of-genius/video-bobby-jones-stroke-of-genius-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-bobby-jones-stroke-of-genius/video-bobby-jones-stroke-of-genius-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-bobby-jones-stroke-of-genius/video-bobby-jones-stroke-of-genius-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-bobby-jones-stroke-of-genius/video-bobby-jones-stroke-of-genius-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-bobby-jones-stroke-of-genius/video-bobby-jones-stroke-of-genius-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-bobby-jones-stroke-of-genius/video-bobby-jones-stroke-of-genius-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",20,"<PERSON>Jim Caviezel</PERSON> stars golf legend <PERSON>Bobby Jones</PERSON>, icon retired competition tender age 28.",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003293940/bobby-jones-stroke-of-genius.html,54a5a0a67988102023c947ae,null,"{main:<PERSON>Bobby Jones<\/PERSON>, Stroke Of Genius}","{original:Sony Pictures Home Entertainment,person:[{firstname:Sony,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Pictures,rank:1,lastname:Home}]}",multimedia
"An official selection of <ORGANIZATION>Cannes Critics Week</ORGANIZATION> and winner of the Special Jury Prize at <ORGANIZATION>SXSW</ORGANIZATION>, THE MYTH OF THE AMERICAN SLEEPOVER is a youthful and tender coming-of-age drama from first-time writer/director <PERSON>David Robert Mitchell</PERSON>. In the tradition of fre",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T11:16:57Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-myth-of-the-american-sleepover/video-the-myth-of-the-american-sleepover-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-myth-of-the-american-sleepover/video-the-myth-of-the-american-sleepover-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-myth-of-the-american-sleepover/video-the-myth-of-the-american-sleepover-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-myth-of-the-american-sleepover/video-the-myth-of-the-american-sleepover-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-myth-of-the-american-sleepover/video-the-myth-of-the-american-sleepover-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-myth-of-the-american-sleepover/video-the-myth-of-the-american-sleepover-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",40,"An official selection of <ORGANIZATION>Cannes Critics Week</ORGANIZATION> and winner of the Special Jury Prize at <ORGANIZATION>SXSW</ORGANIZATION>, THE MYTH OF THE AMERICAN SLEEPOVER is a youthful and tender coming-of-age drama from first-time writer/director <PERSON>David Robert Mitchell</PERSON>. In the tradition of fre",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003394220/the-myth-of-the-american-sleepover.html,54a573aa79881011bed2ce15,null,{"main":"The Myth Of The American Sleepover"},"{original:Sundance Selects,person:[{firstname:Sundance,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Selects}]}",multimedia
"Lou tender story relationship 11-year-old <PERSON>Lou</PERSON> grandfather. Not long <PERSON>Lou</PERSON>'s father walks life, irascible befuddled grandfather crashes. But <PERSON>Doyle</PERSON> stay, <PERSON>Lou</PERSON> discovers,",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T10:53:42Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-lou/video-lou-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-lou/video-lou-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-lou/video-lou-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-lou/video-lou-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-lou/video-lou-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-lou/video-lou-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",41,"Lou tender story relationship 11-year-old <PERSON>Lou</PERSON> grandfather. Not long <PERSON>Lou</PERSON>'s father walks life, irascible befuddled grandfather crashes. But <PERSON>Doyle</PERSON> stay, <PERSON>Lou</PERSON> discovers,",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003351279/lou.html,54a56d8979881011bed2ccdc,null,{"main":"Lou"},"{original:Warner Home Video,person:[{firstname:Warner,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Home,rank:1,lastname:Video}]}",multimedia
"<PERSON>Mosquita Mari</PERSON> coming age story focuses tender friendship young Chicanas. <PERSON>Yolanda Mari</PERSON> growing <LOCATION>Huntington Park</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Los Angeles</LOCATION> loyalty thing: family. Growing immigrant househ",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T10:34:25Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-mosquita-y-mari/video-mosquita-y-mari-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-mosquita-y-mari/video-mosquita-y-mari-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-mosquita-y-mari/video-mosquita-y-mari-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-mosquita-y-mari/video-mosquita-y-mari-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-mosquita-y-mari/video-mosquita-y-mari-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-mosquita-y-mari/video-mosquita-y-mari-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",44,"<PERSON>Mosquita Mari</PERSON> coming age story focuses tender friendship young Chicanas. <PERSON>Yolanda Mari</PERSON> growing <LOCATION>Huntington Park</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Los Angeles</LOCATION> loyalty thing: family. Growing immigrant househ",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003355956/mosquita-y-mari.html,54a5690a79881011bed2cbd5,null,{"main":"Mosquita Y <PERSON>Mari<\/PERSON>"},"{original:Wolfe Releasing,person:[{firstname:Wolfe,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Releasing}]}",multimedia
"<LOCATION>Italy</LOCATION>'s 89-year-old President <PERSON>Giorgio Napolitano</PERSON> <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> step age, leaving Prime Minister <PERSON>Matteo Renzi</PERSON> facing delicate political challenge replace.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T04:46:46Z,[],467,"<LOCATION>Italy</LOCATION>'s 89-year-old President <PERSON>Giorgio Napolitano</PERSON> <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> step age, leaving Prime Minister <PERSON>Matteo Renzi</PERSON> facing delicate political challenge replace.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/world/europe/01reuters-italy-president-resignation.html,54a5180479881011bed2b9b6,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:<LOCATION>Italy<\/LOCATION> President Says He Will Step Down Soon,print_headline:<LOCATION>Italy<\/LOCATION> President Says He Will Step Down Soon}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The inspiration minestrone bag <ORGANIZATION>Rancho Gordo Royal Corona</ORGANIZATION> beans I pantry. Royal Coronas large white European runner beans similar Greek gigandes bigger, richer sturdier. They...",null,[],null,null,du_recipe,[],null,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:[],subtype:thumbnail,width:75,rank:1,credit:<PERSON>Andrew Scrivani<\/PERSON> The New York Times,type:image,url:images/2015/01/10/science/recipehealthminestrone/recipehealthminestrone-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75},{legacy:[],subtype:large,width:600,rank:1,credit:<PERSON>Andrew Scrivani<\/PERSON> The New York Times,type:image,url:images/2015/01/10/science/recipehealthminestrone/recipehealthminestrone-articleLarge.jpg,height:400}]",318,"The inspiration for this minestrone was a bag of <ORGANIZATION>Rancho Gordo Royal Corona</ORGANIZATION> beans that I have had in my pantry for a while. Royal Coronas are large white European runner beans that are similar to Greek gigandes but bigger, richer and sturdier. They are about twice the size of a lima bean and, unlike many other large white beans, the skin doesn’t slip off when you soak them. If you substitute limas I would not soak the beans, but if you use the Royal Coronas, do soak them to shorten the cooking time. The beans are downright meaty and the soup is a hearty one. I didn’t even feel the need to add pasta or rice to this substantial minestrone.",Recipe,http://cooking.nytimes.com/recipes/1017113-minestrone-with-giant-white-beans-and-winter-squash,54aff3c079881022e94b3a5b,null,"{name:Minestrone With Giant White Beans Winter Squash,main:Easy Vegetable Soups Cold Winter Nights}","{original:<PERSON>Martha Rose Shulman<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Martha,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Rose,rank:1,lastname:Shulman}]}",recipe
"Hold onto your chard stalks! Recently I came upon a recipe in a Provençal cookbook for a gratin made with chard stalks and celeriac. I used the combination for a purée, which I served at Thanksgiving dinner to great acclaim. I took the same idea...",null,[],null,null,du_recipe,[],null,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:[],subtype:thumbnail,width:75,rank:1,credit:<PERSON>Andrew Scrivani<\/PERSON> The New York Times,type:image,url:images/2015/01/10/science/recipehealthchard/recipehealthchard-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75},{legacy:[],subtype:large,width:600,rank:1,credit:<PERSON>Andrew Scrivani<\/PERSON> The New York Times,type:image,url:images/2015/01/10/science/recipehealthchard/recipehealthchard-articleLarge.jpg,height:400}]",157,"Hold onto your chard stalks! Recently I came upon a recipe in a Provençal cookbook for a gratin made with chard stalks and celeriac. I used the combination for a purée, which I served at Thanksgiving dinner to great acclaim. I took the same idea and made it into a blended soup, this time adding a potato and a bunch of leeks for added flavor and body. The soup is incredibly satisfying, but quite light.",Recipe,http://cooking.nytimes.com/recipes/1017112-chard-stalk-celeriac-and-leek-soup,54aff34779881022e94b3a53,null,"{name:Chard Stalk, Celeriac Leek Soup,main:Easy Vegetable Soups Cold Winter Nights}","{original:<PERSON>Martha Rose Shulman<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Martha,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Rose,rank:1,lastname:Shulman}]}",recipe
"From director La Mujer de <ORGANIZATION>Mi Hermano My Brother</ORGANIZATION>'s Wife, writer <ORGANIZATION>Voces Inocentes Innocent Voices Mancora</ORGANIZATION>, tender pulsating road-trip drama delicately traces shifting emotional boundaries dis",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2014-12-31T22:31:47Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/04/22/movies/video-mancora/video-mancora-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/04/22/movies/video-mancora/video-mancora-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/04/22/movies/video-mancora/video-mancora-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:348},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/04/22/movies/video-mancora/video-mancora-articleLarge.jpg,height:348},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/04/22/movies/video-mancora/video-mancora-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/04/22/movies/video-mancora/video-mancora-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",38,"From director La Mujer de <ORGANIZATION>Mi Hermano My Brother</ORGANIZATION>'s Wife, writer <ORGANIZATION>Voces Inocentes Innocent Voices Mancora</ORGANIZATION>, tender pulsating road-trip drama delicately traces shifting emotional boundaries dis",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003353058/mancora.html,54a4bfa779881011bed2a5a1,null,{"main":"Mancora"},"{original:Maya Entertainment,person:[{firstname:Maya,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Entertainment}]}",multimedia
"<LOCATION>Italy</LOCATION>'s 89-year-old President <PERSON>Giorgio Napolitano</PERSON> <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> step age, leaving Prime Minister <PERSON>Matteo Renzi</PERSON> facing delicate political challenge replace.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T14:52:52Z,[],467,"<LOCATION>Italy</LOCATION>'s 89-year-old President <PERSON>Giorgio Napolitano</PERSON> <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> step age, leaving Prime Minister <PERSON>Matteo Renzi</PERSON> facing delicate political challenge replace.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/world/europe/31reuters-italy-president-resignation.html,54a4549779881011bed28d18,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:<LOCATION>Italy<\/LOCATION> President Says He Will Step Down Soon,print_headline:<LOCATION>Italy<\/LOCATION> President Says He Will Step Down Soon}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Acclaimed Kazakh documentarian <PERSON>Sergey Dvortsevoy</PERSON>'s narrative feature gorgeous melange tender comedy, ethnographic drama wildlife extravaganza. Following Russian naval service, young dreamer Asa returns sister's nomadic",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2014-12-31T13:18:26Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-tulpan/video-tulpan-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-tulpan/video-tulpan-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-tulpan/video-tulpan-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:348},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-tulpan/video-tulpan-articleLarge.jpg,height:348},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-tulpan/video-tulpan-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-tulpan/video-tulpan-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",34,"Acclaimed Kazakh documentarian <PERSON>Sergey Dvortsevoy</PERSON>'s narrative feature gorgeous melange tender comedy, ethnographic drama wildlife extravaganza. Following Russian naval service, young dreamer Asa returns sister's nomadic",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003405404/tulpan.html,54a43df779881011bed287ef,null,{"main":"Tulpan"},"{original:Zeitgeist Films,person:[{firstname:Zeitgeist,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Films}]}",multimedia
