snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"A Moonbase commander crew exiled run lonely lunar garbage dump. Trouble inmates escape orbiting prison satellite, steal deadly nuclear weapons hidden garbage, order win",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T12:16:28Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-moonbase/video-moonbase-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-moonbase/video-moonbase-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-moonbase/video-moonbase-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-moonbase/video-moonbase-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-moonbase/video-moonbase-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-moonbase/video-moonbase-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",45,"A Moonbase commander crew exiled run lonely lunar garbage dump. Trouble inmates escape orbiting prison satellite, steal deadly nuclear weapons hidden garbage, order win",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003355722/moonbase.html,54a580f27988102023c93ded,null,{"main":"Moonbase"},"{original:Live Home Video,person:[{firstname:Live,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Home,rank:1,lastname:Video}]}",multimedia
"Filmed years, WASTE LAND renowned artist <PERSON>Vik Muniz</PERSON> journeys home base <LOCATION>Brooklyn</LOCATION> native <LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION> world's largest garbage dump, J.rdim Gramacho, located outskirts <ORGANIZATION>Rio de Janeiro</ORGANIZATION>. There",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T00:59:08Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/04/14/movies/video-waste-land/video-waste-land-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/04/14/movies/video-waste-land/video-waste-land-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/04/14/movies/video-waste-land/video-waste-land-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/04/14/movies/video-waste-land/video-waste-land-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/04/14/movies/video-waste-land/video-waste-land-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/04/14/movies/video-waste-land/video-waste-land-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",42,"Filmed years, WASTE LAND renowned artist <PERSON>Vik Muniz</PERSON> journeys home base <LOCATION>Brooklyn</LOCATION> native <LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION> world's largest garbage dump, <PERSON>Jardim Gramacho</PERSON>, located outskirts <ORGANIZATION>Rio de Janeiro</ORGANIZATION>. There",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003408710/waste-land.html,54a4e22f79881011bed2ad7a,null,{"main":"Waste Land"},"{original:ArtHouse Films,person:[{firstname:Arthouse,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Films}]}",multimedia
A World War II Russian secret weapon missing found present day <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> agent Bulgarian ammunition dump. Then hell breaks loose action-packed zombie war film.,null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2014-12-31T12:58:06Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-code-red/video-code-red-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-code-red/video-code-red-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-code-red/video-code-red-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-code-red/video-code-red-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-code-red/video-code-red-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-code-red/video-code-red-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",36,A World War II Russian secret weapon missing found present day <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> agent Bulgarian ammunition dump. Then hell breaks loose action-packed zombie war film.,Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003312261/code-red.html,54a4393279881011bed2865a,null,{"main":"C.de Red"},"{original:Entertainment One,person:[{firstname:Entertainment,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:One}]}",multimedia
Interviews suggest that <ORGANIZATION>Sony</ORGANIZATION> — slow to realize the depths of its peril — let its troubles deepen by mounting a public defense only after enormous damage had been done.,1,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:Sony Pictures Entertainment},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:11,value:Computers Internet},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Cyberwarfare},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Lynton<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Michael<\/PERSON>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Movies},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:5,value:<LOCATION>North Korea<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:<ORGANIZATION>Sony<\/ORGANIZATION> Corporation},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:7,value:<PERSON>Pascal<\/PERSON>, Amy},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:8,value:<LOCATION>Los Angeles Calif<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:creative_works,rank:9,value:The Interview Movie},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:10,value:Computer Security}]",Business Day,<ORGANIZATION>Sony Pictures</ORGANIZATION> executives acknowledge studio slow realize depths security breach problems worsen defending publicly colossal damage occurred; company's decision treat attack internal affair reflects Hollywood habit executive imperturbability chief executive <PERSON>Michael Lynton</PERSON>.,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-31T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/business/jpSONY1/jpSONY1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/jpSONY1/jpSONY1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/business/jpSONY1/jpSONY1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:396},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/jpSONY1/jpSONY1-articleLarge.jpg,height:396},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/business/jpSONY1/jpSONY1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/jpSONY1/jpSONY1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",2702,Interviews suggest that <ORGANIZATION>Sony</ORGANIZATION> — slow to realize the depths of its peril — let its troubles deepen by mounting a public defense only after enormous damage had been done.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/business/media/sony-attack-first-a-nuisance-swiftly-grew-into-a-firestorm-.html,54a35ce17988102761d6cf89,Media,"{main:Sony Cyberattack, <ORGANIZATION>First Nuisance<\/ORGANIZATION>, Swiftly Grew Into Firestorm,print_headline:<ORGANIZATION>Sony Attack<\/ORGANIZATION>, <ORGANIZATION>First Nuisance<\/ORGANIZATION>, Swiftly Grew Into Firestorm}","{contributor:<PERSON>Michael S. Schmidt<\/PERSON> contributed reporting <PERSON>Honolulu Michael D. Shear<\/PERSON> <LOCATION>Washington<\/LOCATION>.,original:By <PERSON>MICHAEL CIEPLY BROOKS BARNES<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Michael,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:CIEPLY},{firstname:Brooks,role:reported,organization:,rank:2,lastname:BARNES}]}",article
"An <ORGANIZATION>Air Force</ORGANIZATION> staff sergeant’s injuries from a chemical round led the <ORGANIZATION>Army</ORGANIZATION> to urge lifelong monitoring of such cases, but he says he was not tracked after retiring.",1,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:United States Defense Military Forces},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Biological Chemical Warfare},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Veterans},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:5,value:Mould, <PERSON>Daniel<\/PERSON> W <DATE>1969<\/DATE>-},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:Defense Department},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:7,value:<LOCATION>Delaware<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:8,value:United States}]",<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,"Former Air Force Staff Sergeant <PERSON>Daniel Mould</PERSON>, wounded chemical weapon accident <DATE>2004</DATE>, helped military study burns 18 months expanded doctors' knowledge, tracked retiring <DATE>2006</DATE>; <ORGANIZATION>Army</ORGANIZATION> announced begin monitoring longterm health veterans exposed chemical agents American occupation <LOCATION>Iraq</LOCATION>, <ORGANIZATION>New York Times</ORGANIZATION> inquired <PERSON>Mould</PERSON>'s case.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-31T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/24/world/MUSTARD-MOULD/MUSTARD-MOULD-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/24/world/MUSTARD-MOULD/MUSTARD-MOULD-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/24/world/MUSTARD-MOULD/MUSTARD-MOULD-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:401},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/24/world/MUSTARD-MOULD/MUSTARD-MOULD-articleLarge.jpg,height:401},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/24/world/MUSTARD-MOULD/MUSTARD-MOULD-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/24/world/MUSTARD-MOULD/MUSTARD-MOULD-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",1570,"An <ORGANIZATION>Air Force</ORGANIZATION> staff sergeant’s injuries from a chemical round led the <ORGANIZATION>Army</ORGANIZATION> to urge lifelong monitoring of such cases, but he says he was not tracked after retiring.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/us/veterans-chemical-burns-expanded-military-doctors-knowledge-but-his-care-faltered.html,54a329c07988102761d6cf2c,null,"{main:A Veteran’s <ORGANIZATION>Chemical Burns Expanded Military Doctors<\/ORGANIZATION>’ Knowledge, but His Care Faltered,print_headline:Veteran’s <ORGANIZATION>Burns Helped Science<\/ORGANIZATION>, Bared Lapses}","{contributor:<PERSON>John Ismay<\/PERSON> contributed reporting.,original:By <PERSON>C. J. CHIVERS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:C.,role:reported,organization:,middlename:J.,rank:1,lastname:CHIVERS}]}",article
Risks abound ordinary citizens piling stock markets pace <DATE>2007</DATE>.,null,"[{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Shenzhen China<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>Beijing China<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:3,value:<LOCATION>Hong Kong<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:<ORGANIZATION>China Securities Regulatory Commission<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Stocks Bonds},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:6,value:China}]",Business Day,Risks abound ordinary citizens piling stock markets pace <DATE>2007</DATE>.,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-29T18:20:35Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/30/business/30bits-chinastocks-pic/30bits-chinastocks-pic-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/business/30bits-chinastocks-pic/30bits-chinastocks-pic-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/30/business/30bits-chinastocks-pic/30bits-chinastocks-pic-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:401},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/business/30bits-chinastocks-pic/30bits-chinastocks-pic-articleLarge.jpg,height:401},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/30/business/30bits-chinastocks-pic/30bits-chinastocks-pic-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/business/30bits-chinastocks-pic/30bits-chinastocks-pic-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",1012,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/29/seeking-to-ride-on-chinas-stock-market-highs/,54a1e21d7988104803cc88c5,Dealbook,"{main:Seeking Ride <LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION>'s Stock Market Highs,print_headline:Investors China Take Risky Ride Its Stock Market Highs,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>NEIL GOUGH<\/PERSON> CAO LI,person:[{firstname:Neil,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:GOUGH},{firstname:Cao,role:reported,organization:,rank:2,lastname:LI}]}",blogpost
How tourism flourish causing harm possible??,null,"[{name:type_of_material,rank:1,value:News}]",Opinion,How tourism flourish causing harm possible??,The New York Times,[],null,2014-12-29T17:24:13Z,[],2151,,Blog,http://www.nytimes.com/roomfordebate/2014/12/29/how-tourists-can-do-less-harm-than-good,54a212567988104803cc8935,Room For Debate,"{main:Smaller Footprints World's Welcome Mats,kicker:Room For Debate}",null,blogpost
"<PERSON>Victor Woods</PERSON> shook uncontrollably, body wracked convulsions, fellow inmates held arms shouted.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-28T11:01:40Z,[],1262,"<PERSON>Victor Woods</PERSON> shook uncontrollably, body wracked convulsions, fellow inmates held arms shouted.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/28/us/ap-us-reforming-rikers-abridged-.html,54a029bd79881001534d20bd,null,"{main:Widespread Problems Rikers Island Tough Fix,print_headline:Widespread Problems Rikers Island Tough Fix}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Coverage funeral Officer Ramos, shot dead patrol partner sat car.",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:Ramos, Rafael 1974-2014},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Attacks Police}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"Coverage funeral Officer Ramos, shot dead patrol partner sat car.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-27T09:27:57Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/28WAKEBLOG2/28WAKEBLOG2-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/28WAKEBLOG2/28WAKEBLOG2-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/28WAKEBLOG2/28WAKEBLOG2-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/28WAKEBLOG2/28WAKEBLOG2-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/28WAKEBLOG2/28WAKEBLOG2-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/28WAKEBLOG2/28WAKEBLOG2-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",2436,null,Blog,http://cityroom.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/27/latest-updates-from-the-funeral-of-officer-rafael-ramos/,549ed29c7988105ced788722,null,"{main:Updates From Funeral N.Y.P.D. Officer Rafael Ramos,kicker:City Room}","{original:By THE <LOCATION>NEW YORK<\/LOCATION> TIMES,person:[],organization:The New York Times}",blogpost
"Thousands police officers nation packed church spilled streets <DATE>Saturday</DATE> honor Officer <PERSON>Rafael Ramos</PERSON> devoted family man, aspiring chaplain hero, air unrest surrounding ambush shooting...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-27T01:10:32Z,[],857,"Thousands police officers nation packed church spilled streets <DATE>Saturday</DATE> honor Officer <PERSON>Rafael Ramos</PERSON> devoted family man, aspiring chaplain hero, air unrest surrounding ambush shooting completely pushed.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/27/us/ap-us-nypd-officers-shot.html,549e4da77988105ced7886c3,null,"{main:NYC Officer Mourned Funeral Tensions Linger,print_headline:NYC Officer Mourned Funeral Tensions Linger}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
