snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
<LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s central bank <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> monetary tools maintain adequate liquidity reasonable growth credit social financing.,null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T03:22:56Z,[],103,<LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s central bank <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> monetary tools maintain adequate liquidity reasonable growth credit social financing.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-china-economy-policy.html,54a3b2de7988102761d6d665,null,"{main:China Central Bank Says Maintain Steady Credit Growth,print_headline:China Central Bank Says Maintain Steady Credit Growth}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"President <PERSON>Nicolas Maduro</PERSON> vowed <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> reform <LOCATION>Venezuela</LOCATION>'s Byzantine currency controls early <DATE>2015</DATE> part six-month plan shake <LOCATION>Venezuela</LOCATION> recession, foes accused incompetence inaction.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T17:25:50Z,[],650,"President <PERSON>Nicolas Maduro</PERSON> vowed <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> reform <LOCATION>Venezuela</LOCATION>'s Byzantine currency controls early <DATE>2015</DATE> part six-month plan shake <LOCATION>Venezuela</LOCATION> recession, foes accused incompetence inaction.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/business/30reuters-venezuela-economy.html,54a326f37988102761d6cf24,null,"{main:Recession-Hit <LOCATION>Venezuela<\/LOCATION> Vows New Year Reforms, Foes Scoff,print_headline:Recession-Hit <LOCATION>Venezuela<\/LOCATION> Vows New Year Reforms, Foes Scoff}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Crunch time <LOCATION>Argentina</LOCATION> fixing debt default <DATE>January</DATE>, investors hoped, year country's president takes office ailing economy moving.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T13:51:32Z,[],783,"Crunch time <LOCATION>Argentina</LOCATION> fixing debt default <DATE>January</DATE>, investors hoped, year country's president takes office ailing economy moving.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/business/30reuters-argentina-debt-analysis.html,54a2f50e7988102761d6ce9d,null,"{main:Analysis-Argentina's Debt Crisis Seen Rumbling Until 2015 Election,print_headline:Analysis-Argentina's Debt Crisis Seen Rumbling Until 2015 Election}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
Emails and documents filed in court provide a look at the extent to which <ORGANIZATION>Morgan Stanley</ORGANIZATION> influenced New Century’s push into riskier mortgages in the run-up to the financial crisis.,null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Subprime Mortgage Crisis},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:2,value:Justice Department},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:3,value:American Civil Liberties Union},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:4,value:New Century Financial Corp},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:5,value:Morgan Stanley}]",Business Day,Emails and documents filed in court provide a look at the extent to which <ORGANIZATION>Morgan Stanley</ORGANIZATION> influenced New Century’s push into riskier mortgages in the run-up to the financial crisis.,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-29T20:43:35Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/30/business/dbpix-mortgage/dbpix-mortgage-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/business/dbpix-mortgage/dbpix-mortgage-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/30/business/dbpix-mortgage/dbpix-mortgage-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:384},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/business/dbpix-mortgage/dbpix-mortgage-articleLarge.jpg,height:384},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/30/business/dbpix-mortgage/dbpix-mortgage-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/business/dbpix-mortgage/dbpix-mortgage-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1320,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/29/court-filing-illuminates-morgan-role-in-lending/,54a203a17988104803cc88fc,Dealbook,"{main:Court Filing Illuminates Morgan Stanley Role Lending,print_headline:Court Filing Illuminates Morgan Role Lending,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>NATHANIEL POPPER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Nathaniel,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:POPPER}]}",blogpost
"Oil prices rose <DATE>Monday</DATE>, dropping past sessions, escalating clashes <LOCATION>Libya</LOCATION> stoked worries supply <ORGANIZATION>OPEC</ORGANIZATION> member.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-28T20:04:51Z,[],290,"Oil prices rose <DATE>Monday</DATE>, dropping past sessions, escalating clashes <LOCATION>Libya</LOCATION> stoked worries supply <ORGANIZATION>OPEC</ORGANIZATION> member.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/28/business/28reuters-markets-oil.html,54a0a8fb7988101f98e3ee67,null,"{main:Oil Prices Climb Worries Over Libyan Supply,print_headline:Oil Prices Climb Worries Over Libyan Supply}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
When regime change??,null,[],Opinion,When regime change??,The New York Times,[],OpEd,2014-12-27T09:12:34Z,[],509,null,Blog,http://krugman.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/27/fiscal-policy-at-the-zero-lower-bound-again/,549ebeba7988105ced78870f,null,"{main:Fiscal Policy Zero Lower Bound, Again,kicker:<PERSON>Paul Krugman<\/PERSON>}","{original:By <PERSON>PAUL KRUGMAN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Paul,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:KRUGMAN}]}",blogpost
"Russian authorities significantly scaled up rescue funds for mid-sized lender <ORGANIZATION>Trust Bank</ORGANIZATION> on <DATE>Friday</DATE>, saying they would provide up to <MONEY>$2.4 billion</MONEY> in loans to bail out the first commercial banking victim of the country's currency crisis.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-26T06:19:06Z,[],431,"Russian authorities significantly scaled up rescue funds for mid-sized lender <ORGANIZATION>Trust Bank</ORGANIZATION> on <DATE>Friday</DATE>, saying they would provide up to <MONEY>$2.4 billion</MONEY> in loans to bail out the first commercial banking victim of the country's currency crisis.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/26/business/26reuters-russia-crisis-trust-bank.html,549d44907988103babf08b6b,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Russia<\/LOCATION> Scales Up Trust Bank Bailout Crisis Bites,print_headline:<LOCATION>Russia<\/LOCATION> Scales Up Trust Bank Bailout Crisis Bites}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Brent crude futures held above <MONEY>$60</MONEY> a barrel on <DATE>Friday</DATE> as strong <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> economic data supported the market, but oil prices were track for their fifth straight weekly decline as a building supply glut capped gains.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-25T21:52:22Z,[],298,"Brent crude futures held above <MONEY>$60</MONEY> a barrel on <DATE>Friday</DATE> as strong <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> economic data supported the market, but oil prices were track for their fifth straight weekly decline as a building supply glut capped gains.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/25/business/25reuters-markets-oil.html,549ccdbc7988103babf08acb,null,"{main:Brent Holds Above <MONEY>$60<\/MONEY>, but Heads for Fifth Weekly Drop,print_headline:Brent Holds Above <MONEY>$60<\/MONEY>, but Heads for Fifth Weekly Drop}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The electricity shut-off peninsula, annexed <LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION> months ago, <LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION> warned <LOCATION>Ukraine</LOCATION> join Western military alliance.",10,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Ukraine<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>Crimea Ukraine<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:3,value:<LOCATION>Russia<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:4,value:North Atlantic Treaty Organization},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:5,value:Power Failures Blackouts}]",World,<LOCATION>Ukraine</LOCATION> temporarily shuts electricity Russian-annexed Crimean Peninsula make point territory reliant Ukrainian energy sources; incident occurs <LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION> warns <LOCATION>Ukraine</LOCATION> joining <ORGANIZATION>NATO</ORGANIZATION>.,The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-25T00:00:00Z,[],803,"The electricity shut-off peninsula, annexed <LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION> months ago, <LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION> warned <LOCATION>Ukraine</LOCATION> join Western military alliance.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/25/world/europe/ukraine-briefly-cuts-power-to-crimea-amid-dispute-with-russia-over-nato.html,549ae5e77988102d96d56846,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:<LOCATION>Ukraine<\/LOCATION> Briefly Cuts Power Crimea Amid Feud With <LOCATION>Russia<\/LOCATION> Over <ORGANIZATION>NATO<\/ORGANIZATION>,print_headline:<LOCATION>Ukraine<\/LOCATION> Briefly Cuts Power Crimea Amid Feud With <LOCATION>Russia<\/LOCATION> Over NATO}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ANDREW ROTH<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Andrew,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:ROTH}]}",article
"The <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Commodity Futures Trading Commission <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> fined <ORGANIZATION>MF Global Holdings Ltd</ORGANIZATION> wrongdoing collapse futures brokerage, continue lawsuit firm's chief, <PERSON>Jon Corzine</PERSON>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-24T12:34:59Z,[],213,"The <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Commodity Futures Trading Commission <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> fined <ORGANIZATION>MF Global Holdings Ltd</ORGANIZATION> wrongdoing collapse futures brokerage, continue lawsuit firm's chief, <PERSON>Jon Corzine</PERSON>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/24/business/24reuters-mf-global-hldg-settlement.html,549af9727988100306690dc4,null,"{main:MF Global Holdings to Pay <MONEY>$100 Million<\/MONEY> Fine in <ORGANIZATION>CFTC<\/ORGANIZATION> Settlement,print_headline:MF <ORGANIZATION>Global Holdings<\/ORGANIZATION> to Pay <MONEY>$100 Million<\/MONEY> Fine in <ORGANIZATION>CFTC<\/ORGANIZATION> Settlement}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
