snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"<ORGANIZATION>Hyundai Motor C.</ORGANIZATION> affiliate <ORGANIZATION>Kia Motors Corp</ORGANIZATION> forecast sales year grow slowest pace <DATE>2003</DATE>, hampered capacity constraints weaker yen give Japanese rivals edge key markets.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T18:11:36Z,[],387,"<ORGANIZATION>Hyundai Motor Co</ORGANIZATION> affiliate <ORGANIZATION>Kia Motors Corp</ORGANIZATION> forecast sales year grow slowest pace <DATE>2003</DATE>, hampered capacity constraints weaker yen give Japanese rivals edge key markets.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-hyundai-motor-kia-motors-sales.html,54a5d48a7988102023c94dd6,null,"{main:Hyundai-Kia See <DATE>2015<\/DATE> Sales Growth Weakest 12 Years,print_headline:Hyundai-Kia See <DATE>2015<\/DATE> Sales Growth Weakest 12 Years}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"A Bosnian court indicted Muslim priest <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> recruiting people fight <ORGANIZATION>Islamic State</ORGANIZATION> group <LOCATION>Syria Iraq</LOCATION>, law aimed stopping people traveling fight alongside militants <LOCATION>Middle East</LOCATION>.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T09:56:05Z,[],237,"A Bosnian court indicted Muslim priest <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> recruiting people fight <ORGANIZATION>Islamic State</ORGANIZATION> group <LOCATION>Syria Iraq</LOCATION>, law aimed stopping people traveling fight alongside militants <LOCATION>Middle East</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/world/middleeast/31reuters-mideast-crisis-bosnia.html,54a40f037988102761d6e0fc,Middle East,"{main:Bosnian Indicted Over Recruiting Militants <LOCATION>Syria Iraq<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:Bosnian Indicted Over Recruiting Militants <LOCATION>Syria Iraq<\/LOCATION>}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The global fast-food chain filed public tortured trappings served technology stocks., notes <PERSON>Jeffrey Goldfarb Reuters Breakingviews</PERSON>.",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Meyer<\/PERSON>, Danny},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:<ORGANIZATION>Leonard Green & Partners<\/ORGANIZATION>},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:Shake Shack},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Fast Food Industry},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Initial Public Offerings}]",Business Day,"The global fast-food chain filed public tortured trappings served technology stocks., notes <PERSON>Jeffrey Goldfarb Reuters Breakingviews</PERSON>.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-30T14:00:40Z,[],400,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/shake-shack-i-p-o-offers-healthy-profits-and-curious-metrics/,54a2f6ac7988102761d6cea1,Dealbook,"{main:Shake Shack I.P.O. Offers Healthy Profits Curious Metrics,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>JEFFREY GOLDFARB<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Jeffrey,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:GOLDFARB}]}",blogpost
The BlackBerry's blinking red light haunt.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T03:01:15Z,[],853,The BlackBerry's blinking red light haunt.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/us/ap-us-digital-life-review-blackberry-classic.html,54a25c727988104803cc89fb,null,"{main:Review: IPhone User Tries Go Back BlackBerry,print_headline:Review: IPhone User Tries Go Back BlackBerry}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
A couple married President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON>'s vacation spot <LOCATION>Hawaii</LOCATION> learned hard big day rarely planned.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T02:31:04Z,[],601,A couple married President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON>'s vacation spot <LOCATION>Hawaii</LOCATION> learned hard big day rarely planned.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/us/ap-us-obama-wedding-snafu.html,54a2556a7988104803cc89e2,null,"{main:Obama Golf Game Forces Army Couple Move Wedding,print_headline:Obama Golf Game Forces Army Couple Move Wedding}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<ORGANIZATION>Hyundai Motor</ORGANIZATION> Co <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> build  factories <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>, manufacturing plants 2012 South Korean automaker bets growth world's biggest car market economy slows.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T01:25:42Z,[],383,"<ORGANIZATION>Hyundai Motor</ORGANIZATION> Co <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> build  factories <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>, manufacturing plants 2012 South Korean automaker bets growth world's biggest car market economy slows.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/business/30reuters-hyundai-motor-china.html,54a245ee7988104803cc89ce,null,"{main:Hyundai Motor Build Two <LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION> Plants Amid Slowing Economy,print_headline:Hyundai Motor Build Two <LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION> Plants Amid Slowing Economy}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
A couple married President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON>'s vacation spot <LOCATION>Hawaii</LOCATION> learned hard big day rarely planned.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-29T12:24:23Z,[],531,A couple married President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON>'s vacation spot <LOCATION>Hawaii</LOCATION> learned hard big day rarely planned.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/29/us/ap-us-obama-wedding-snafu.html,54a18f027988104803cc8819,null,"{main:Obama Golf Game Bumps Army Couple's Wedding Spot,print_headline:Obama Golf Game Bumps Army Couple's Wedding Spot}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Officials acknowledge barely made dent larger, longer-term campaign kill ideology animates terrorist movement.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:Islamic State Iraq <LOCATION>Syria<\/LOCATION> ISIS},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>Nagata<\/LOCATION>, <PERSON>Michael<\/PERSON> K},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:United States Defense Military Forces},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Terrorism},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Psychology Psychologists},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:6,value:United States}]",<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,Internal conference <ORGANIZATION>Maj Gen Michael K Nagata</ORGANIZATION> experts convened discuss ideology drives <ORGANIZATION>Islamic State</ORGANIZATION> group offers view struggle understand group's appeal ways combat influence; <ORGANIZATION>Nagata</ORGANIZATION> picked <PERSON>Pres Obama</PERSON> train American-backed army Syrian rebels fight Islamic State.,The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-29T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/29/world/JP-ISIS/JP-ISIS-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/world/JP-ISIS/JP-ISIS-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/29/world/JP-ISIS/JP-ISIS-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:718},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/world/JP-ISIS/JP-ISIS-articleLarge.jpg,height:718},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/29/world/JP-ISIS/JP-ISIS-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/world/JP-ISIS/JP-ISIS-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1221,"Officials acknowledge barely made dent larger, longer-term campaign kill ideology animates terrorist movement.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/29/us/politics/in-battle-to-defang-isis-us-targets-its-psychology-.html,54a0b54e7988101f98e3ee7b,Politics,"{main:In Battle Defang <ORGANIZATION>ISIS<\/ORGANIZATION>, <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Targets Its Psychology,print_headline:In Battle Defang <ORGANIZATION>ISIS<\/ORGANIZATION>, <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Targets Its Psychology}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ERIC SCHMITT<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Eric,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SCHMITT}]}",article
"Ten years after 230,000 died in the world’s first hemisphere-scale geo-catastrophe, a tsunami expert looks ahead.",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Borrero<\/PERSON>, Jose},{name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Aceh Province Indonesia<\/LOCATION>},{name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>Sumatra Indonesia<\/LOCATION>},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:<ORGANIZATION>United Nations Educational<\/ORGANIZATION>, Scientific Cultural Organization},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Boxing Day},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Disasters Emergencies},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Earthquakes},{name:subject,rank:4,value:Evacuations Evacuees},{name:subject,rank:5,value:Fukushima <ORGANIZATION>Daiichi Nuclear Power Plant Japan<\/ORGANIZATION>},{name:subject,rank:6,value:Geology},{name:subject,rank:7,value:Humanitarian Aid},{name:subject,rank:8,value:<LOCATION>Japan<\/LOCATION> Earthquake Tsunami 2011},{name:subject,rank:9,value:Oceans Seas},{name:subject,rank:10,value:Tidal Waves Tsunamis}]",false,"Ten years after 230,000 died in the world’s first hemisphere-scale geo-catastrophe, a tsunami expert looks ahead.",The New York Times,[],OpEd,2014-12-26T18:01:50Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/26/blogs/dotaceh/dotaceh-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/blogs/dotaceh/dotaceh-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/26/blogs/dotaceh/dotaceh-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:428},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/blogs/dotaceh/dotaceh-articleLarge.jpg,height:428},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/26/blogs/dotaceh/dotaceh-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/blogs/dotaceh/dotaceh-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",2067,null,Blog,http://dotearth.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/26/what-science-can-and-cant-do-to-cut-losses-from-the-next-tsunami/,549de98f7988105ced788636,false,"{main:What Science Can, Can't Do, Cut Losses Next Tsunami,kicker:Dot Earth}","{original:By <PERSON>ANDREW C. REVKIN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Andrew,role:reported,organization:,middlename:C.,rank:1,lastname:REVKIN}]}",blogpost
Here’s what you need to know to start your day.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,The New York Times,[],National,2014-12-26T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/26/business/26nytnow-anniversary5/26nytnow-anniversary5-thumbWide-v3.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/business/26nytnow-anniversary5/26nytnow-anniversary5-thumbWide-v3.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/26/business/26nytnow-anniversary5/26nytnow-anniversary5-articleLarge-v2.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:399},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/business/26nytnow-anniversary5/26nytnow-anniversary5-articleLarge-v2.jpg,height:399},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/26/business/26nytnow-anniversary5/26nytnow-anniversary5-thumbStandard-v3.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/business/26nytnow-anniversary5/26nytnow-anniversary5-thumbStandard-v3.jpg,height:75}]",970,Here’s what you need to know to start your day.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/26/us/tsunami-anniversary-police-shooting-christmas-movies.html,549d3d3c7988103babf08b65,null,"{main:Your <DATE>Friday<\/DATE> Briefing,seo:Tsunami Anniversary, Police Shooting, Christmas Movies}","{original:By ADEEL HASSAN,person:[{firstname:Adeel,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:HASSAN}]}",article
