snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"J.meis Winston evaded <LOCATION>Oregon</LOCATION> tacklers wound throw, feet slipped Rose Bowl turf. While failed stay upright, <ORGANIZATION>Florida State</ORGANIZATION>'s star quarterback lost ball backward head comical arc,...",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T21:01:27Z,[],761,"Jameis Winston evaded <LOCATION>Oregon</LOCATION> tacklers wound throw, feet slipped Rose Bowl turf. While failed stay upright, <ORGANIZATION>Florida State</ORGANIZATION>'s star quarterback lost ball backward head comical arc, <LOCATION>Tony Washington</LOCATION> hurdled scoop score.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/sports/ncaafootball/ap-fbc-t25-rose-bowl-winstons-nightmare.html,54a5fc967988102023c95163,College Football,"{main:Winston's Woes Part Noles' Streak-Ending Loss,print_headline:Winston's Woes Part Noles' Streak-Ending Loss}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Deals worth nearly <MONEY>$3.5 trillion</MONEY> were announced, a performance favored by low interest rates and high stock prices.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Mergers, Acquisitions Divestitures}]",Business Day,"Deals worth nearly <MONEY>$3.5 trillion</MONEY> were announced, a performance favored by low interest rates and high stock prices.",The New York Times,[],Business,2015-01-01T19:32:44Z,[],525,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/deal-makers-notched-nearly-3-5-trillion-worth-in-14-best-in-7-years/,54a5e7cc7988102023c94f8e,Dealbook,"{main:Deal Makers Notched Nearly <MONEY>$3.5<\/MONEY> <ORGANIZATION>Trillion Worth<\/ORGANIZATION> in &rsquo;14, Best in 7 Years,print_headline:Deal Makers Notched Nearly <MONEY>$3.5 Trillion<\/MONEY> Worth in ’14, Best in 7 Years,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>MICHAEL J. DE<\/PERSON> LA MERCED,person:[{firstname:Michael,role:reported,organization:,middlename:J.,rank:1,lastname:DE LA MERCED}]}",blogpost
Touchdown. Turnover. Touchdown. Turnover. Touchdown.,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T01:09:31Z,[],902,Touchdown. Turnover. Touchdown. Turnover. Touchdown.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/sports/ncaafootball/ap-fbc-t25-playoff-rose-bowl.html,54a4e57c79881011bed2ae3b,College Football,"{main:Rose Bowl Rout! <ORGANIZATION>Oregon Crushes Florida State<\/ORGANIZATION> 59-20,print_headline:Rose Bowl Rout! <ORGANIZATION>Oregon Crushes Florida State<\/ORGANIZATION> 59-20}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Harry finds selected underaged competitor dangerous multi-wizardary school competition.,null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2014-12-31T13:03:51Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire/video-harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire/video-harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire/video-harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire/video-harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire/video-harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire/video-harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",14,Harry finds selected underaged competitor dangerous multi-wizardary school competition.,Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003330659/harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire.html,54a43a8c79881011bed286ce,null,{"main":"<PERSON>Harry Potter<\/PERSON> And The Goblet Of Fire"},"{original:<ORGANIZATION>Warner Bros<\/ORGANIZATION>. Pictures,person:[{firstname:Warner,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Bros}]}",multimedia
"New Year's Eve: day overpay glass flat Champagne impossibly-high heels wear,,, ride home Uber.",null,[],Technology,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T08:31:34Z,[],557,"New Year's Eve: day overpay glass flat Champagne impossibly-high heels wear,,, ride home Uber.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/technology/ap-us-tec-uber-surge-1st-ld-writethru.html,54a3fb537988102761d6dec6,null,"{main:Beyond Uber Surge: How Get Around New Year's Eve,print_headline:Beyond Uber Surge: How Get Around New Year's Eve}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Mexican crude oil sailing <LOCATION>U.S. East Coast</LOCATION> highest rate decade, customs data reviewed <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION>, sign deepening discounts crack open markets domestic shale inundates <LOCATION>Texas</LOCATION>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T02:31:15Z,[],890,"Mexican crude oil sailing <LOCATION>U.S. East Coast</LOCATION> highest rate decade, customs data reviewed <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION>, sign deepening discounts crack open markets domestic shale inundates <LOCATION>Texas</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-mexico-crude-usa.html,54a3a6ea7988102761d6d501,null,"{main:Exclusive: <LOCATION>Mexico<\/LOCATION>'s Light Crude, Shunned <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Shale, Sails East,print_headline:Exclusive: <LOCATION>Mexico<\/LOCATION>'s Light Crude, Shunned <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Shale, Sails East}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"A weeks back, head coaches guided teams <ORGANIZATION>College Football Playoff</ORGANIZATION> posed pictures championship trophy.",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T17:00:56Z,[],785,"A weeks back, head coaches guided teams <ORGANIZATION>College Football Playoff</ORGANIZATION> posed pictures championship trophy.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/sports/ncaafootball/ap-fbc-t25-playoff-rose-bowl.html,54a3216d7988102761d6cf1d,College Football,"{main:Ducks' <PERSON>Helfrich<\/PERSON> Is 'Other Guy' Among Star Coaches,print_headline:Ducks' <PERSON>Helfrich<\/PERSON> Is 'Other Guy' Among Star Coaches}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Investor sell-off <PERCENT>8.5 percent</PERCENT> decline news airline's major crisis.,,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Airlines Airplanes},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Stocks Bonds},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:3,value:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION>}]",Business Day,null,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-30T11:30:00Z,[],423,Investor sell-off <PERCENT>8.5 percent</PERCENT> decline news airline's major crisis.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/business/international/airasia-shares.html,54a1285a7988101f98e3ef57,International Business,"{main:Shares Drop <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> After Plane Disappears,print_headline:Shares Drop <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> After Plane Goes Missing}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>NEIL GOUGH<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Neil,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:GOUGH}]}",article
"Manager <PERSON>Roy Hodgson</PERSON> offered upbeat New Year message <LOCATION>England</LOCATION>'s success-starved fans, explaining hopes team competitor Euro <DATE>2016</DATE> title.",null,[],Sports,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-29T12:16:46Z,[],329,"Manager <PERSON>Roy Hodgson</PERSON> offered upbeat New Year message <LOCATION>England</LOCATION>'s success-starved fans, explaining hopes team competitor Euro <DATE>2016</DATE> title.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/29/sports/soccer/29reuters-soccer-england-hodgson.html,54a18ccf7988104803cc8814,Soccer,"{main:<PERSON>Hodgson<\/PERSON> Wants England Be 'Serious Competitors' Euros,print_headline:<PERSON>Hodgson<\/PERSON> Wants England Be 'Serious Competitors' Euros}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
Many leaders complain Chinese censorship quietly accept censorship.,,"[{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:1,value:China},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Censorship},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:News News Media}]",Opinion,null,The New York Times,[],OpEd,2014-12-29T11:30:00Z,[],1072,Many leaders complain Chinese censorship quietly accept censorship.,Op-Ed,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/29/opinion/caving-in-to-chinas-power.html,54a086067988101f98e3ee2e,null,"{content_kicker:Op-Ed Contributor,main:Caving In <LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION>'s Power,print_headline:Caving In <LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION>'s Power,kicker:Op-Ed Contributor}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>MARK KITTO<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Mark,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:KITTO}]}",article
