snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"As Republicans assume control entire <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> <ORGANIZATION>Congress</ORGANIZATION> year, expected push controversial change macroeconomic projections determining impact tax budget legislation federal deficit.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T16:41:43Z,[],408,"As Republicans assume control entire <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> <ORGANIZATION>Congress</ORGANIZATION> year, expected push controversial change macroeconomic projections determining impact tax budget legislation federal deficit.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/us/politics/31reuters-usa-tax-dynamic.html,54a46dec79881011bed292e8,Politics,"{main:Republicans Push Ahead New Math <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Taxes, Budget,print_headline:Republicans Push Ahead New Math <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Taxes, Budget}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<LOCATION>Israel</LOCATION>'s economy grew estimated <PERCENT>2.6 percent</PERCENT> <DATE>2014</DATE>, slowest pace years, <DATE>summer</DATE> war dragged, expected pick pace year.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T08:58:48Z,[],365,"<LOCATION>Israel</LOCATION>'s economy grew estimated <PERCENT>2.6 percent</PERCENT> <DATE>2014</DATE>, slowest pace years, <DATE>summer</DATE> war dragged, expected pick pace year.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-israel-gdp.html,54a401a17988102761d6df7a,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Israel<\/LOCATION> Economy Grows 2.6 Percent <DATE>2014<\/DATE>, Seen Faster 2015,print_headline:<LOCATION>Israel<\/LOCATION> Economy Grows 2.6 Percent <DATE>2014<\/DATE>, Seen Faster 2015}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
<LOCATION>Venezuela</LOCATION>'s government <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> confirmed economy struggling emerge deep recession President <PERSON>Nicolas Maduro</PERSON> crisis engulfing oil-rich nation lot worse.,null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T17:55:29Z,[],365,<LOCATION>Venezuela</LOCATION>'s government <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> confirmed economy struggling emerge deep recession President <PERSON>Nicolas Maduro</PERSON> crisis engulfing oil-rich nation lot worse.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/world/americas/ap-lt-venezuela-economic-crisis.html,54a32e057988102761d6cf34,Americas,"{main:<LOCATION>Venezuela<\/LOCATION>'s President Blames Opposition Deep Recession,print_headline:<LOCATION>Venezuela<\/LOCATION>'s President Blames Opposition Deep Recession}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"President <PERSON>Nicolas Maduro</PERSON> vowed <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> reform <LOCATION>Venezuela</LOCATION>'s Byzantine currency controls early <DATE>2015</DATE> part six-month plan shake <LOCATION>Venezuela</LOCATION> recession, foes accused incompetence inaction.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T17:25:50Z,[],650,"President <PERSON>Nicolas Maduro</PERSON> vowed <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> reform <LOCATION>Venezuela</LOCATION>'s Byzantine currency controls early <DATE>2015</DATE> part six-month plan shake <LOCATION>Venezuela</LOCATION> recession, foes accused incompetence inaction.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/business/30reuters-venezuela-economy.html,54a326f37988102761d6cf24,null,"{main:Recession-Hit <LOCATION>Venezuela<\/LOCATION> Vows New Year Reforms, Foes Scoff,print_headline:Recession-Hit <LOCATION>Venezuela<\/LOCATION> Vows New Year Reforms, Foes Scoff}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The International Monetary Fund <ORGANIZATION>IMF</ORGANIZATION> partially responsible scale Ebola crisis West African countries policies hampered healthcare spending post-conflict states, study.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T08:01:16Z,[],520,"The International Monetary Fund <ORGANIZATION>IMF</ORGANIZATION> partially responsible scale Ebola crisis West African countries policies hampered healthcare spending post-conflict states, study.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/world/africa/30reuters-ebola-africa-imf.html,54a2a2bd7988104803cc8a77,<LOCATION>Africa</LOCATION>,"{main:IMF Focus Cutting Debt Over Health Spending Worsened Ebola Africa-Study,print_headline:IMF Focus Cutting Debt Over Health Spending Worsened Ebola Africa-Study}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
Professors leading British universities International Monetary Fund policies favoring international debt repayment social spending contributed Ebola crisis hampering health care worst-hit West African...,null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T03:59:43Z,[],347,Professors leading British universities International Monetary Fund policies favoring international debt repayment social spending contributed Ebola crisis hampering health care worst-hit West African countries.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/world/africa/ap-af-ebola-imf.html,54a269d57988104803cc8a0a,<LOCATION>Africa</LOCATION>,"{main:Researchers: IMF Policies Hindered Ebola Response,print_headline:Researchers: IMF Policies Hindered Ebola Response}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<LOCATION>Serbia</LOCATION>'s <DATE>2015</DATE> budget is in line with the terms of a one billion-euro <MONEY>$1.22 billion</MONEY> loan agreement with the <ORGANIZATION>International Monetary Fund</ORGANIZATION> that is due to be approved by the Fund's executive board in the <DATE>second half of February</DATE>, the <ORGANIZATION>IMF</ORGANIZATION> said on <DATE>Monday</DATE>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-29T13:09:09Z,[],247,"<LOCATION>Serbia</LOCATION>'s <DATE>2015</DATE> budget is in line with the terms of a one billion-euro <MONEY>$1.22 billion</MONEY> loan agreement with the <ORGANIZATION>International Monetary Fund</ORGANIZATION> that is due to be approved by the Fund's executive board in the <DATE>second half of February</DATE>, the <ORGANIZATION>IMF</ORGANIZATION> said on <DATE>Monday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/29/business/29reuters-serbia-imf.html,54a199707988104803cc8833,null,"{main:IMF Says <LOCATION>Serbia<\/LOCATION>'s Budget Is Line With One Billion-Euro Loan Deal,print_headline:IMF Says <LOCATION>Serbia<\/LOCATION>'s Budget Is Line With One Billion-Euro Loan Deal}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
<LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION>'s economy shrank sharply <DATE>November</DATE> rouble resumed slide <DATE>Monday</DATE> Western sanctions slump oil prices combined inflict contraction GDP global financial crisis.,null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-29T02:33:32Z,[],554,<LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION>'s economy shrank sharply <DATE>November</DATE> rouble resumed slide <DATE>Monday</DATE> Western sanctions slump oil prices combined inflict contraction GDP global financial crisis.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/29/business/29reuters-russia-gdp.html,54a104637988101f98e3ef1e,null,"{main:Russian Economy Suffers First Contraction Since Global Crisis,print_headline:Russian Economy Suffers First Contraction Since Global Crisis}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Oil prices rose <DATE>Monday</DATE>, dropping past sessions, escalating clashes <LOCATION>Libya</LOCATION> stoked worries supply <ORGANIZATION>OPEC</ORGANIZATION> member.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-28T20:04:51Z,[],290,"Oil prices rose <DATE>Monday</DATE>, dropping past sessions, escalating clashes <LOCATION>Libya</LOCATION> stoked worries supply <ORGANIZATION>OPEC</ORGANIZATION> member.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/28/business/28reuters-markets-oil.html,54a0a8fb7988101f98e3ee67,null,"{main:Oil Prices Climb Worries Over Libyan Supply,print_headline:Oil Prices Climb Worries Over Libyan Supply}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Shale boom, shale slump.",null,[],Opinion,"Shale boom, shale slump.",The New York Times,[],OpEd,2014-12-28T10:40:11Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/28/opinion/122814krugman3/122814krugman3-thumbWide.png},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/opinion/122814krugman3/122814krugman3-thumbWide.png,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/28/opinion/122814krugman3/122814krugman3-articleLarge.png,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:319},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/opinion/122814krugman3/122814krugman3-articleLarge.png,height:319},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/28/opinion/122814krugman3/122814krugman3-thumbStandard.png,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/opinion/122814krugman3/122814krugman3-thumbStandard.png,height:75}]",269,null,Blog,http://krugman.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/moscow-on-the-brazos/,54a024af79881001534d20b7,null,"{main:Moscow Brazos,kicker:<PERSON>Paul Krugman<\/PERSON>}","{original:By <PERSON>PAUL KRUGMAN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Paul,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:KRUGMAN}]}",blogpost
