snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
<PERSON>Matt Wolf</PERSON> high-concept Shakespeare play explicitly offer hope <LOCATION>London</LOCATION> stage.,,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Reviews},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Theater}]",Arts,null,The New York Times,[],Culture,2014-12-19T13:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/19/arts/international/19iht-lon19a/19iht-lon19a-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/19/arts/international/19iht-lon19a/19iht-lon19a-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/19/arts/international/19iht-lon19a/19iht-lon19a-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:394},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/19/arts/international/19iht-lon19a/19iht-lon19a-articleLarge.jpg,height:394},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/19/arts/international/<ORGANIZATION>19iht-lon19a/19iht-lon19a-thumbStandard<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/19/arts/international/<ORGANIZATION>19iht-lon19a/19iht-lon19a-thumbStandard<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg,height:75}]",1219,<PERSON>Matt Wolf</PERSON> high-concept Shakespeare play explicitly offer hope <LOCATION>London</LOCATION> stage.,Review,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/19/arts/high-concept-shakespeare-and-a-dash-of-hope.html,5492ea8c79881005eed9d565,null,"{content_kicker:Theater Review,main:High-Concept Shakespeare Dash Hope,print_headline:High-Concept Shakespeare Dash Hope}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>MATT WOLF<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Matt,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:WOLF}]}",article
"With a Broadway theater suddenly available, producers of the new musical comedy “Something Rotten!” dropped plans for a run in <LOCATION>Seattle</LOCATION>.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Theater},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:St James Theater}]",Arts,"With a Broadway theater suddenly available, producers of the new musical comedy “Something Rotten!” dropped plans for a run in <LOCATION>Seattle</LOCATION>.",The New York Times,[],Culture,2014-12-16T16:00:19Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/17/arts/arts2/arts2-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/17/arts/arts2/arts2-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/17/arts/arts2/arts2-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:795},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/17/arts/arts2/arts2-articleLarge.jpg,height:795},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/17/arts/arts2/arts2-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/17/arts/arts2/arts2-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",590,null,Blog,http://artsbeat.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/16/something-rotten-to-skip-seattle-premiere-and-debut-on-broadway-in-march/,54909de279881035eeb2e35b,null,"{main:'Something Rotten!' Skip <LOCATION>Seattle<\/LOCATION> Premiere Debut Broadway March,print_headline:‘Something Rotten!’ Is Set for Broadway in <DATE>March<\/DATE>,kicker:ArtsBeat}","{original:By <PERSON>PATRICK HEALY<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Patrick,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:HEALY}]}",blogpost
"Under leadership <PERSON>Waldemar Dabrowski</PERSON>, <LOCATION>Poland</LOCATION>'s Wielki Theater, raising international profile collaborations avant-garde productions.",,"[{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Warsaw Poland<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Opera},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:3,value:Tchaikovsky, <PERSON>Peter Ilyich<\/PERSON>}]",Arts,null,The New York Times,[],Culture,2014-11-18T13:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/11/18/arts/international/18iht-poltheater/18iht-poltheater-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/11/18/arts/international/18iht-poltheater/18iht-poltheater-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/11/18/arts/international/18iht-poltheater/18iht-poltheater-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/11/18/arts/international/18iht-poltheater/18iht-poltheater-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/11/18/arts/international/18iht-poltheater/18iht-poltheater-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/11/18/arts/international/18iht-poltheater/18iht-poltheater-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1069,"Under leadership <PERSON>Waldemar Dabrowski</PERSON>, <LOCATION>Poland</LOCATION>'s Wielki Theater, raising international profile collaborations avant-garde productions.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/11/18/arts/international/home-of-polish-national-opera-shines-again.html,5469f46b7988101de50ed7b3,International Arts,"{main:Home Polish National Opera Shines Again,print_headline:Home Polish National Opera Shines Again}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>REBECCA SCHMID<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Rebecca,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SCHMID}]}",article
"With popularity slipping, <PERSON>Vladimir Putin</PERSON> casting enemies.",,"[{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Russia<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Putin<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Vladimir<\/PERSON> V},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Social Conditions Trends},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Discrimination},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Minorities},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Race Ethnicity}]",Opinion,null,The New York Times,[],Editorial,2014-11-05T11:30:00Z,[],988,"With popularity slipping, <PERSON>Vladimir Putin</PERSON> casting enemies.",Op-Ed,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/11/05/opinion/masha-gessen-moscows-war-on-ethnic-minorities.html,5458ae48798810533a8dea28,null,"{content_kicker:Contributing Op-Ed | <PERSON>Masha GessenWriter<\/PERSON>,main:<LOCATION>Moscow<\/LOCATION>’s War on Ethnic Minorities,print_headline:<LOCATION>Moscow<\/LOCATION>'s War Ethnic Minorities,kicker:Op-Ed | <PERSON>Masha Gessen<\/PERSON>}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>MASHA GESSEN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Masha,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:GESSEN}]}",article
The vice president’s problems began <DATE>Thursday</DATE> when he declared that the biggest problem in dealing with <LOCATION>Syria</LOCATION> and the rise of the <ORGANIZATION>Islamic State</ORGANIZATION> was <LOCATION>America</LOCATION>’s allies in the region.,10,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:Saudi Arabia},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Biden<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Joseph<\/PERSON> R Jr},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Al Qaeda},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:4,value:<LOCATION>Syria<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:5,value:Turkey},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:United States International Relations},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:7,value:<PERSON>Erdogan<\/PERSON>, Recep Tayyip}]",World,Vice Pres <PERSON>Joseph R Biden</PERSON> Jr ocnnect Saudi leaders apologize clarify comment made suggesting <LOCATION>Saudi Arabia</LOCATION> backed Al Qaeda extremist groups <LOCATION>Syria</LOCATION>; <PERSON>Biden</PERSON> apologized officials <LOCATION>Turkey</LOCATION> United Arab Emirates.,The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-10-07T00:00:00Z,[],906,The vice president’s problems began <DATE>Thursday</DATE> when he declared that the biggest problem in dealing with <LOCATION>Syria</LOCATION> and the rise of the <ORGANIZATION>Islamic State</ORGANIZATION> was <LOCATION>America</LOCATION>’s allies in the region.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/10/07/world/middleeast/saudis-are-next-on-bidens-mideast-apology-list-after-harvard-remarks.html,543339937988104832204835,Middle East,"{main:Saudis Are Next <PERSON>Biden<\/PERSON>&#8217;s Mideast Apology List After Harvard Remarks,print_headline:Saudis Are Next on <PERSON>Biden<\/PERSON>’s Mideast Apology List After Harvard Remarks}","{contributor:,original:By MARK LANDLER,person:[{firstname:Mark,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:LANDLER}]}",article
"Vice President <PERSON>Joe Biden</PERSON> <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> poor choice words referred unscrupulous moneylenders Shylocks, prominent group fights anti-Semitism called teachable moment harmful effects stereotypes.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],null,2014-09-17T13:25:23Z,[],267,"Vice President <PERSON>Joe Biden</PERSON> <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> poor choice words referred unscrupulous moneylenders Shylocks, prominent group fights anti-Semitism called teachable moment harmful effects stereotypes.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/09/17/us/politics/ap-us-biden-jews.html,5419c4a779881037000b85de,Politics,"{main:<PERSON>Biden<\/PERSON> Says 'Shylocks' Was Poor Choice Words,print_headline:<PERSON>Biden<\/PERSON> Says 'Shylocks' Was Poor Choice Words}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Vice President <PERSON>Joe Biden</PERSON> apologized <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> referring people squeeze <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> military personnel serving overseas loans financial issues Shylocks, reference stereotypical Jewish character Shakespeare.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,Reuters,[],null,2014-09-17T00:11:01Z,[],507,"Vice President <PERSON>Joe Biden</PERSON> apologized <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> referring people squeeze <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> military personnel serving overseas loans financial issues Shylocks, reference stereotypical Jewish character Shakespeare.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/09/17/us/politics/17reuters-usa-politics-biden.html,54190a307988106440c996da,Politics,"{main:<PERSON>Biden<\/PERSON> Apologizes 'Shylocks' Gaffe, Visits <LOCATION>Iowa<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:<PERSON>Biden<\/PERSON> Apologizes 'Shylocks' Gaffe, Visits <LOCATION>Iowa<\/LOCATION>}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
A surprising theme emerged <LOCATION>New Zealand</LOCATION>'s election campaign: racism.,null,[],World,null,AP,[],null,2014-08-14T02:41:12Z,[],667,A surprising theme emerged <LOCATION>New Zealand</LOCATION>'s election campaign: racism.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/08/14/world/asia/ap-as-new-zealand-election-racism.html,53ec5a557988102d58c25e38,Asia Pacific,"{main:Racism Mars <LOCATION>New Zealand<\/LOCATION> Election Campaign,print_headline:Racism Mars New Zealand Election Campaign}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"A search bygone genre, <PERSON>Dashiell Hammett</PERSON> guide, yields set mysteries.",1,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Writing Writers},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:3,value:<LOCATION>San Francisco Calif<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Travel Vacations},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:Hammett, Dashiell}]",Travel,"<PERSON>Dan Saltzstein</PERSON> travel article shares search noir <LOCATION>San Francisco</LOCATION>, mystery writer <PERSON>Dashiell Hammett</PERSON> guide; reports trip urban landscape, lens bygone genre, yielded set mysteries.",The New York Times,[],Travel,2014-06-29T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/06/29/travel/29NOIR3/29NOIR3-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/06/29/travel/29NOIR3/29NOIR3-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/06/29/travel/29NOIR3/29NOIR3-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/06/29/travel/29NOIR3/29NOIR3-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/06/29/travel/29NOIR2/29NOIR2-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/06/29/travel/29NOIR2/29NOIR2-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",3243,"A search bygone genre, <PERSON>Dashiell Hammett</PERSON> guide, yields set mysteries.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/06/29/travel/san-francisco-noir.html,53adb07679881043482ea987,null,"{main:<LOCATION>San Francisco<\/LOCATION> Noir,print_headline:San Francisco Noir}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>DAN SALTZSTEIN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Dan,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SALTZSTEIN}]}",article
<PERSON>Emily Cox Henry Rathvon</PERSON> show mistakes.,null,"[{name:subject,rank:2,value:Crossword Puzzles},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Acrostic Puzzles}]",Crosswords/Games,<PERSON>Emily Cox Henry Rathvon</PERSON> show mistakes.,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-05-17T12:00:23Z,[],357,null,Blog,http://wordplay.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/05/17/variety-a-mistaken-acrostic/,537787d07988105a384313c6,null,"{main:Variety: A Mistaken Acrostic,kicker:Wordplay}","{original:By <PERSON>DEB AMLEN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Deb,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:AMLEN}]}",blogpost
