snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"After major shipment drugs missing US-Canadian border, forest ranger <ORGANIZATION>Navy SEAL Henry</ORGANIZATION> plunged survival mode drug cartel forces retrieve downed package. Trapped wilderness",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T01:14:58Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/04/10/movies/video-enemies-closer/video-enemies-closer-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/04/10/movies/video-enemies-closer/video-enemies-closer-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/04/10/movies/video-enemies-closer/video-enemies-closer-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/04/10/movies/video-enemies-closer/video-enemies-closer-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/04/10/movies/video-enemies-closer/video-enemies-closer-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/04/10/movies/video-enemies-closer/video-enemies-closer-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",43,"After major shipment drugs missing US-Canadian border, forest ranger <ORGANIZATION>Navy SEAL Henry</ORGANIZATION> plunged survival mode drug cartel forces retrieve downed package. Trapped wilderness",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003320959/enemies-closer.html,54a4e5e579881011bed2ae55,null,{"main":"Enemies Closer"},"{original:LionsGate Entertainment,person:[{firstname:Lionsgate,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Entertainment}]}",multimedia
<LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>'s securities-market regulator <ORGANIZATION>CVM</ORGANIZATION> <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> investigating <ORGANIZATION>Petrobras</ORGANIZATION> executives failed legal duties protect state-run oil company investors losses related giant corruption scandal.,null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T22:48:34Z,[],418,<LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>'s securities-market regulator <ORGANIZATION>CVM</ORGANIZATION> <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> investigating <ORGANIZATION>Petrobras</ORGANIZATION> executives failed legal duties protect state-run oil company investors losses related giant corruption scandal.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/business/30reuters-brazil-petrobras-regulator.html,54a372327988102761d6cfb8,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Brazil<\/LOCATION>'s Market Regulator Widens Petrobras Probe,print_headline:<LOCATION>Brazil<\/LOCATION>'s Market Regulator Widens Petrobras Probe}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
A chief suspect gunfight western <LOCATION>Mexico</LOCATION> killed 11 people turned questioning <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> government struggles impose order violent state claims pacified.,null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T20:15:57Z,[],402,A chief suspect gunfight western <LOCATION>Mexico</LOCATION> killed 11 people turned questioning <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> government struggles impose order violent state claims pacified.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/world/americas/30reuters-mexico-violence.html,54a34f047988102761d6cf6c,Americas,"{main:<LOCATION>Mexico<\/LOCATION> Questions 37 Over Shootout Troubled Western State,print_headline:<LOCATION>Mexico<\/LOCATION> Questions 37 Over Shootout Troubled Western State}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The leaders rural vigilante groups 35 members surrendered authorities clash left 11 dead western state <LOCATION>Michoacan</LOCATION>, federal official <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T16:21:16Z,[],271,"The leaders rural vigilante groups 35 members surrendered authorities clash left 11 dead western state <LOCATION>Michoacan</LOCATION>, federal official <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/world/americas/ap-lt-mexico-vigilantes.html,54a3184c7988102761d6cefe,Americas,"{main:Mexican Self-Defense Members Turn Themselves In,print_headline:Mexican Self-Defense Members Turn Themselves In}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<LOCATION>Algeria</LOCATION> <DATE>Sunday</DATE> OPEC cut production push oil prices, adding share views big producers inside cartel prefer market regulate prices, energy minister <PERSON>Youcef Yousfi</PERSON> quoted...",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-28T09:26:14Z,[],105,"<LOCATION>Algeria</LOCATION> <DATE>Sunday</DATE> OPEC cut production push oil prices, adding share views big producers inside cartel prefer market regulate prices, energy minister <PERSON>Youcef Yousfi</PERSON> quoted official <ORGANIZATION>APS</ORGANIZATION> news agency.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/28/business/28reuters-oil-opec-algeria.html,54a0133779881001534d20a6,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Algeria<\/LOCATION> Energy Minister Says <ORGANIZATION>OPEC<\/ORGANIZATION> Should Cut Oil Output-APS,print_headline:<LOCATION>Algeria<\/LOCATION> Energy Minister Says <ORGANIZATION>OPEC<\/ORGANIZATION> Should Cut Oil Output-APS}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The <ORGANIZATION>U.S. Federal Bureau Investigation</ORGANIZATION> claim made call <LOCATION>Texas</LOCATION> border town police department Mexican organized crime cartel kidnapped <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Border Patrol agent, officials <DATE>Friday</DATE>.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-26T18:10:59Z,[],301,"The <ORGANIZATION>U.S. Federal Bureau Investigation</ORGANIZATION> claim made call <LOCATION>Texas</LOCATION> border town police department Mexican organized crime cartel kidnapped <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Border Patrol agent, officials <DATE>Friday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/26/world/americas/26reuters-usa-texas-agent.html,549deb337988105ced78863b,Americas,"{main:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Looking Into Report Kidnapped Border Patrol Agent Texas,print_headline:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Looking Into Report Kidnapped Border Patrol Agent Texas}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"President <PERSON>Nicolas Maduro</PERSON> named powerful Foreign Minister <PERSON>Rafael Ramirez</PERSON> post envoy <ORGANIZATION>United Nations</ORGANIZATION> <DATE>Friday</DATE>, appointment strengthen <LOCATION>Venezuela</LOCATION>'s voice world body's Security Council <DATE>Jan. 1</DATE>.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-26T15:17:57Z,[],438,"President <PERSON>Nicolas Maduro</PERSON> named powerful Foreign Minister <PERSON>Rafael Ramirez</PERSON> post envoy <ORGANIZATION>United Nations</ORGANIZATION> <DATE>Friday</DATE>, appointment strengthen <LOCATION>Venezuela</LOCATION>'s voice world body's Security Council <DATE>Jan. 1</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/26/world/americas/26reuters-venezuela-cabinet.html,549dc31d7988105ced7885e1,Americas,"{main:<LOCATION>Venezuela<\/LOCATION>'s Maduro Moves Foreign Minister <PERSON>Ramirez<\/PERSON> U.N.,print_headline:<LOCATION>Venezuela<\/LOCATION>'s Maduro Moves Foreign Minister <PERSON>Ramirez<\/PERSON> U.N.}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"A priest found dead gunshot wound head, diocese <DATE>Friday</DATE>, marking latest series abductions, attacks highway robberies Roman Catholic clerics area southern <PERSON>Guerrero</PERSON> state dominated drug cartels.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-26T11:34:00Z,[],816,"A priest found dead gunshot wound head, diocese <DATE>Friday</DATE>, marking latest series abductions, attacks highway robberies Roman Catholic clerics area southern <PERSON>Guerrero</PERSON> state dominated drug cartels.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/26/world/americas/ap-lt-mexico-priests-killed.html,549d8e697988103babf08bdb,Americas,"{main:Third Priest Killed Dangerous Southern <LOCATION>Mexico<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:Third Priest Killed Dangerous Southern <LOCATION>Mexico<\/LOCATION>}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Roman Catholic clergy members parishioners marched <ORGANIZATION>Ciudad Altamirano</ORGANIZATION> southern <LOCATION>Mexico</LOCATION> protest series kidnappings, killings robberies priests.",8,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Mexico<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:2,value:Roman Catholic Church},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Priests},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Kidnapping Hostages},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Demonstrations, Protests Riots},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Murders, Attempted Murders Homicides},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:7,value:<PERSON>Martinez<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Maximino<\/PERSON>}]",World,"Roman Catholic clergy members hundreds parishioners rally <PERSON>Ciudad Altamirano</PERSON>, <LOCATION>Mexico</LOCATION>, demand release Rev <PERSON>Gregorio Lopez Gorostieta</PERSON>, priest kidnapped local seminary, protest ongoing kidnappings, killings robberies priests <ORGANIZATION>Guerrero State</ORGANIZATION>.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-25T00:00:00Z,[],300,"Roman Catholic clergy members parishioners marched <ORGANIZATION>Ciudad Altamirano</ORGANIZATION> southern <LOCATION>Mexico</LOCATION> protest series kidnappings, killings robberies priests.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/25/world/americas/mexicans-rally-after-a-priest-is-kidnapped-.html,549b64fd79881003066910a6,Americas,"{main:Mexicans Rally After Priest Is Kidnapped,print_headline:Mexicans Rally After Priest Is Kidnapped}","{contributor:,original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
The disappearance key wiretap document <LOCATION>Arizona</LOCATION> corruption case led prosecutors seek dismissal charges sheriff's officers accused helping cartel-connected heroin smuggling ring.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-24T15:31:29Z,[],497,The disappearance key wiretap document <LOCATION>Arizona</LOCATION> corruption case led prosecutors seek dismissal charges sheriff's officers accused helping cartel-connected heroin smuggling ring.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/24/us/ap-us-sheriffs-office-assisting-smugglers.html,549b22fc7988100306690ea7,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Arizona<\/LOCATION> Prosecutors Want Ex-Officers' Case Dismissed,print_headline:<LOCATION>Arizona<\/LOCATION> Prosecutors Want Ex-Officers' Case Dismissed}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
