snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"This year showed sheltered <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> economy geopolitical health crises world. The global economy sputtered, <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> powered ahead. Employers finally hiring lower unemployment. A plunge gas prices...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T15:35:08Z,[],1299,"This year showed sheltered <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> economy geopolitical health crises world. The global economy sputtered, <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> powered ahead. Employers finally hiring lower unemployment. A plunge gas prices rising stock market Americans feeling richer spending bit.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/ap-us-ye-top-10-business-stories.html,54a45e8079881011bed28f5d,null,"{main:Top Business Stories 2014: US Grows, World Slows,print_headline:Top Business Stories 2014: US Grows, World Slows}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
A Q. and A. on the effect of President <PERSON>Obama</PERSON>’s order to restore diplomatic relations with <LOCATION>Cuba</LOCATION>.,2,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Travel Vacations},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>Cuba<\/LOCATION>}]",Travel,Travel Q&A restrictions remain travel <LOCATION>Cuba Pres Obama</LOCATION>'s order restore diplomatic relations.,The New York Times,[],Travel,2014-12-28T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/19/travel/19Cuba-Travel/19Cuba-Travel-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/19/travel/19Cuba-Travel/19Cuba-Travel-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/19/travel/19Cuba-Travel/19Cuba-Travel-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:391},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/19/travel/19Cuba-Travel/19Cuba-Travel-articleLarge.jpg,height:391},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/19/travel/19Cuba-Travel/19Cuba-Travel-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/19/travel/19Cuba-Travel/19Cuba-Travel-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1161,A Q. and A. on the effect of President <PERSON>Obama</PERSON>’s order to restore diplomatic relations with <LOCATION>Cuba</LOCATION>.,Question,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/19/travel/how-travel-to-cuba-may-change.html,549335af79881048d26b2fd9,null,"{main:How Travel Cuba May Change,print_headline:How Travel Cuba May Change}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>MATT BEARDMORE<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Matt,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BEARDMORE}]}",article
"This year showed sheltered <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> economy geopolitical health crises world. The global economy sputtered, <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> powered ahead. Employers finally hiring lower unemployment. A plunge gas prices...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-26T11:40:58Z,[],1311,"This year showed sheltered <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> economy geopolitical health crises world. The global economy sputtered, <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> powered ahead. Employers finally hiring lower unemployment. A plunge gas prices rising stock market Americans feeling richer spending bit.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/26/us/ap-us-ye-top-10-business-stories.html,549d90857988103babf08be3,null,"{main:Top Business Stories 2014: US Grows, World Slows,print_headline:Top Business Stories 2014: US Grows, World Slows}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"International credit debit card company <ORGANIZATION>Mastercard</ORGANIZATION> stopped serving bank cards <LOCATION>Crimea</LOCATION>, <ORGANIZATION>RIA</ORGANIZATION> news agency quoted company <DATE>Friday</DATE>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-26T11:40:36Z,[],62,"International credit debit card company <ORGANIZATION>Mastercard</ORGANIZATION> stopped serving bank cards <LOCATION>Crimea</LOCATION>, <ORGANIZATION>RIA</ORGANIZATION> news agency quoted company <DATE>Friday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/26/business/26reuters-russia-crisis-crimea-mastercard.html,549d8fcb7988103babf08be0,null,"{main:<ORGANIZATION>Mastercard Stops Serving Bank Cards<\/ORGANIZATION> Crimea-RIA,print_headline:<ORGANIZATION>Mastercard Stops Serving Bank Cards<\/ORGANIZATION> Crimea-RIA}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The world's largest credit debit card companies, <ORGANIZATION>Visa Inc MasterCard Inc</ORGANIZATION>, <DATE>Friday</DATE> longer support bank cards <LOCATION>Crimea</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> sanctions imposed earlier month.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-26T10:37:09Z,[],136,"The world's largest credit debit card companies, <ORGANIZATION>Visa Inc MasterCard Inc</ORGANIZATION>, <DATE>Friday</DATE> longer support bank cards <LOCATION>Crimea</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> sanctions imposed earlier month.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/26/business/26reuters-russia-crisis-visa-crimea.html,549d81087988103babf08bbb,null,"{main:Visa, <ORGANIZATION>MasterCard<\/ORGANIZATION> Stop Supporting Bank Cards Crimea,print_headline:Visa, <ORGANIZATION>MasterCard<\/ORGANIZATION> Stop Supporting Bank Cards Crimea}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<LOCATION>Ukraine</LOCATION>'s government pro-Russian separatists <DATE>Friday</DATE> exchanged hundreds prisoners war <LOCATION>Kiev</LOCATION> suspend train bus service <LOCATION>Crimea</LOCATION>, effectively creating transportation blockade region.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-26T06:02:26Z,[],550,"<LOCATION>Ukraine</LOCATION>'s government pro-Russian separatists <DATE>Friday</DATE> exchanged hundreds prisoners war <LOCATION>Kiev</LOCATION> suspend train bus service <LOCATION>Crimea</LOCATION>, effectively creating transportation blockade region.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/26/world/europe/26reuters-ukraine-crisis-prisoners.html,549d410a7988103babf08b69,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:<LOCATION>Kiev<\/LOCATION>, Rebels Exchange POWs; Trains, Buses Crimea Suspended,print_headline:<LOCATION>Kiev<\/LOCATION>, Rebels Exchange POWs; Trains, Buses Crimea Suspended}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"As received drugstore cologne gift set, <LOCATION>Santa Claus</LOCATION> wrong.",null,[],Business Day,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-24T11:10:46Z,[],802,"As received drugstore cologne gift set, <LOCATION>Santa Claus</LOCATION> wrong.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/24/business/ap-us-on-the-money-holiday-returns-tips.html,549ae5d67988102d96d56845,null,"{main:Bad <LOCATION>Santa<\/LOCATION>? 5 Tips to Tackle Your Holiday Gift Returns,print_headline:Bad <LOCATION>Santa<\/LOCATION>? 5 Tips to Tackle Your Holiday Gift Returns}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Financial start-ups reach younger middle-class Americans upending customary fee structure.,null,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Prices Fares, Fees Rates},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Banking Financial Institutions},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Aspiration Partners LLC},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:5,value:Cherny, Andrei},{name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Berkeley Calif<\/LOCATION>},{name:glocations,rank:2,value:Palo Alto Calif}]",Business Day,Financial start-ups reach younger middle-class Americans upending customary fee structure.,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-22T20:41:24Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/23/business/dbpix-alternative/dbpix-alternative-thumbWide-v2.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/23/business/dbpix-alternative/dbpix-alternative-thumbWide-v2.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/23/business/dbpix-alternative/dbpix-alternative-articleLarge-v2.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:403},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/23/business/dbpix-alternative/dbpix-alternative-articleLarge-v2.jpg,height:403},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/23/business/dbpix-alternative/dbpix-alternative-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/23/business/dbpix-alternative/dbpix-alternative-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1348,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/22/financial-start-ups-aim-to-court-the-anti-finance-crowd/,5498c8a0798810035238e6e8,Dealbook,"{main:Financial Start-Ups Aim Court Anti-Finance Crowd,print_headline:Financial Start-Ups Aim Court Anti-Finance Crowd,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>WILLIAM ALDEN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:William,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:ALDEN}]}",blogpost
"This year showed sheltered <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> economy geopolitical health crises world. The global economy sputtered, <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> powered ahead. Employers finally hiring lower unemployment. A plunge gas prices...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-22T13:49:52Z,[],1310,"This year showed sheltered <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> economy geopolitical health crises world. The global economy sputtered, <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> powered ahead. Employers finally hiring lower unemployment. A plunge gas prices rising stock market Americans feeling richer spending bit.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/22/us/ap-us-ye-top-10-business-stories.html,54986884798810035238e589,null,"{main:Top Business Stories 2014: US Grows, World Slows,print_headline:Top Business Stories 2014: US Grows, World Slows}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
The retailer 1.2 million customer payment cards exposed security breach earlier year.,null,[],Business Day,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-19T16:45:30Z,[],310,The retailer 1.2 million customer payment cards exposed security breach earlier year.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/19/business/ap-us-staples-data-breach.html,54949cce7988107c468005a9,null,"{main:Staples: Customer Data Exposed Security Breach,print_headline:Staples: Customer Data Exposed Security Breach}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
