snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"A Pakistani court granted bail <DATE>Thursday</DATE> man accused masterminding deadly <DATE>2008</DATE> rampage Indian city <LOCATION>Mumbai</LOCATION>, lawyers.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-18T06:43:05Z,[],435,"A Pakistani court granted bail <DATE>Thursday</DATE> man accused masterminding deadly <DATE>2008</DATE> rampage Indian city <LOCATION>Mumbai</LOCATION>, lawyers.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/18/world/asia/18reuters-pakistan-india-attacks.html,5492be4579881005eed9d4cd,Asia Pacific,"{main:<LOCATION>Pakistan<\/LOCATION> Court Bails Man Accused Masterminding Mumbai Attack,print_headline:<LOCATION>Pakistan<\/LOCATION> Court Bails Man Accused Masterminding Mumbai Attack}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"A Pakistani court granted bail <DATE>Thursday</DATE> man accused masterminding deadly <DATE>2008</DATE> rampage Indian city <LOCATION>Mumbai</LOCATION>, lawyers.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-18T06:23:48Z,[],415,"A Pakistani court granted bail <DATE>Thursday</DATE> man accused masterminding deadly <DATE>2008</DATE> rampage Indian city <LOCATION>Mumbai</LOCATION>, lawyers.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/18/world/asia/18reuters-paksitan-india-attacks.html,5492ba0a79881005eed9d4c1,Asia Pacific,"{main:<LOCATION>Pakistan<\/LOCATION> Court Bails Man Accused Masterminding Mumbai Attack,print_headline:<LOCATION>Pakistan<\/LOCATION> Court Bails Man Accused Masterminding Mumbai Attack}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"In courtrooms country day, price tag put freedom accused expensive.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-06T10:36:19Z,[],900,"In courtrooms country day, price tag put freedom accused expensive.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/06/us/ap-us-bail-reform-.html,548323477988101355141bb5,null,"{main:Jail Release Could Depend Prediction Risk,print_headline:Jail Release Could Depend Prediction Risk}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"A man handgun randomly targeted people driving <LOCATION>Des Moines</LOCATION> suburb early <DATE>Monday</DATE>, shooting injuring men separate locations prompting schools students stay home, authorities.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-11-17T14:47:20Z,[],345,"A man handgun randomly targeted people driving <LOCATION>Des Moines</LOCATION> suburb early <DATE>Monday</DATE>, shooting injuring men separate locations prompting schools students stay home, authorities.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/11/17/us/ap-us-random-shooting-iowa.html,546a50f77988106d5f62653c,null,"{main:Police: <LOCATION>Iowa<\/LOCATION> Man Charged Random Shootings,print_headline:Police: <LOCATION>Iowa<\/LOCATION> Man Charged Random Shootings}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Allies <LOCATION>Chicago</LOCATION> activist convicted illegally <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> citizenship put homes collateral jail awaits sentence.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-11-17T10:56:59Z,[],267,Allies <LOCATION>Chicago</LOCATION> activist convicted illegally <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> citizenship put homes collateral jail awaits sentence.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/11/17/us/ap-us-immigration-israel-bombing.html,546a212c7988101de50edbd1,null,"{main:Chicago Activist Asks Bond, Release From Jail,print_headline:Chicago Activist Asks Bond, Release From Jail}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<PERSON>Noel Cryan</PERSON>, employee British brokerage firm <ORGANIZATION>Tullett Prebon Group</ORGANIZATION>, ordered court surrender passport released bail.",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Cryan<\/PERSON>, Noel},{name:glocations,rank:1,value:Great <LOCATION>Britain<\/LOCATION>},{name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>London England<\/LOCATION>},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:Financial Conduct Authority Great <LOCATION>Britain<\/LOCATION>},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:Serious Fraud Office United Kingdom},{name:organizations,rank:3,value:Tullett Prebon Group},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Bail},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Banking Financial Institutions},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Libor London Interbank Offered Rate}]",Business Day,"<PERSON>Noel Cryan</PERSON>, employee British brokerage firm <ORGANIZATION>Tullett Prebon Group</ORGANIZATION>, ordered court surrender passport released bail.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-11-11T06:44:45Z,[],458,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/11/11/suspect-in-libor-rigging-case-released-on-bail-in-london/,5461f72179881034af6c5c27,Dealbook,"{main:Suspect Libor-Rigging Case Is Released Bail <LOCATION>London<\/LOCATION>,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>CHAD BRAY<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Chad,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BRAY}]}",blogpost
"A French appeals court rule <DATE>Sept. 22</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>Swissbank UBS</ORGANIZATION> post bail <MONEY>1.1 billion euros 882.37 million pounds</MONEY> investigation charges helped wealthy French customers avoid tax, bank's lawyer <DATE>Monday</DATE>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],null,2014-09-08T13:15:31Z,[],217,"A French appeals court rule <DATE>Sept. 22</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>Swissbank UBS</ORGANIZATION> post bail <MONEY>1.1 billion euros 882.37 million pounds</MONEY> investigation charges helped wealthy French customers avoid tax, bank's lawyer <DATE>Monday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/09/08/business/08reuters-ubs-ag-france.html,540de4eb79881045f3790844,null,"{main:UBS Bail Decision Tax Investigation Set <DATE>Sept. 22<\/DATE>,print_headline:UBS Bail Decision Tax Investigation Set <DATE>Sept. 22<\/DATE>}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Legal, business selling weed <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> wacky.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],null,2014-09-04T11:07:37Z,[],<DATE>1985</DATE>,"Legal, business selling weed <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> wacky.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/09/04/us/ap-us-rethinking-pot-the-business-plan.html,540880cb7988102ba0beffd1,null,"{main:Legal Not, Pot Business Is Still Wacky,print_headline:Legal Not, Pot Business Is Still Wacky}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"An accused man represented clients in at least 12 federal lawsuits, but not even his fiancée is sure who he really is, officials said.",18,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Legal Profession},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Imposters Criminal},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Dickerman<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Stephen<\/PERSON> G},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:4,value:<LOCATION>Brighton Beach Brooklyn<\/LOCATION>, NY},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:5,value:Federal Bureau Investigation},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:6,value:Reyes, Ramon E Jr},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:Identity Theft}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"Man posing lawyer <PERSON>Stephen G Dickerman</PERSON> arraigned federal court <LOCATION>Brooklyn</LOCATION> charges identity theft making fraudulent statements; man represented clients 12 federal lawsuits,, fiancee,.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-08-08T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/08/08/nyregion/08LAWYER/08LAWYER-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/08/08/nyregion/08LAWYER/08LAWYER-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/08/08/nyregion/08LAWYER/08LAWYER-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/08/08/nyregion/08LAWYER/08LAWYER-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/08/08/nyregion/08LAWYER/08LAWYER-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/08/08/nyregion/08LAWYER/08LAWYER-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",852,"An accused man represented clients in at least 12 federal lawsuits, but not even his fiancée is sure who he really is, officials said.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/08/08/nyregion/us-charges-brooklyn-man-name-unknown-with-impersonating-lawyer.html,53e41ca679881071316c3ba9,null,"{main:Legal Clients Called Him <PERSON>Shlomo<\/PERSON>; <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Calls Him Fraud,print_headline:Legal Clients Called Him <PERSON>Shlomo<\/PERSON>; <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Calls Him Fraud}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>STEPHANIE CLIFFORD<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Stephanie,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:CLIFFORD}]}",article
An <LOCATION>Albuquerque</LOCATION> man facing robbery larceny charges scratched stomach pull gun grocery store clerk handed cash.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],null,2014-08-05T10:57:44Z,[],137,An <LOCATION>Albuquerque</LOCATION> man facing robbery larceny charges scratched stomach pull gun grocery store clerk handed cash.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/08/05/us/ap-us-robbery-stomach-scratch.html,53e0f1a37988101c965a5c14,null,"{main:New Mexico Man Blames Robbery Stomach Scratch,print_headline:New Mexico Man Blames Robbery Stomach Scratch}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
