snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"General Motors C. began year announcing vehicle recalls <DATE>Thursday</DATE>, ignition switch crisis continued dog automaker millions vehicles recalled <DATE>2014</DATE>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T13:50:26Z,[],400,"General Motors Co began year announcing vehicle recalls <DATE>Thursday</DATE>, ignition switch crisis continued dog automaker millions vehicles recalled <DATE>2014</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-gm-recalls-reports.html,54a597467988102023c944cc,null,"{main:General Motors Issues Three New Recalls, Cites Ignition Systems,print_headline:General Motors Issues Three New Recalls, Cites Ignition Systems}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"College football fans wanted playoff system,. But exacerbate problems sport.",11,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Football College},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Playoff Games},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Fisher<\/PERSON>, Jimbo},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:4,value:<PERSON>Harbaugh<\/PERSON>, Jim},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:5,value:<PERSON>Saban<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Nick<\/PERSON>},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:<ORGANIZATION>Florida State University<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:7,value:University Oregon},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:8,value:<ORGANIZATION>Ohio State University<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:9,value:University <LOCATION>Alabama<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:10,value:College Football Playoff National Championship}]",Sports,"<PERSON>William C Rhoden</PERSON> Sports The Times column maintains <ORGANIZATION>College Football National Championship</ORGANIZATION> serve intensify savory elements sport commercialism, ruthless recruiting battles, exorbitant coaches' salaries outsized importance athletes.",The New York Times,[],Sports,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/sports/01rhoden1/01rhoden1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/sports/01rhoden1/01rhoden1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/sports/01rhoden1/01rhoden1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:378},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/sports/01rhoden1/01rhoden1-articleLarge.jpg,height:378},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/sports/01rhoden1/01rhoden1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/sports/01rhoden1/01rhoden1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1062,"College football fans wanted playoff system,. But exacerbate problems sport.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/sports/ncaafootball/college-football-playoff-may-be-a-boon-or-just-a-pandoras-box.html,54a4c34d79881011bed2a672,College Football,"{content_kicker:Sports The Times,main:College Football Playoff May Be a Boon, or Just a Pandora’s Box,print_headline:Playoff May Be a Boon, or Just a Pandora’s Box,kicker:Sports The Times}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>WILLIAM C. RHODEN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:William,role:reported,organization:,middlename:C.,rank:1,lastname:RHODEN}]}",article
<PERSON>Jim Harbaugh</PERSON> solved significant problems <LOCATION>Michigan</LOCATION>.,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T09:53:23Z,[],998,<PERSON>Jim Harbaugh</PERSON> solved significant problems <LOCATION>Michigan</LOCATION>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/sports/ncaafootball/ap-fbc-michigan-harbaugh-arrives.html,54a40e487988102761d6e0e5,College Football,"{main:<PERSON>Harbaugh<\/PERSON>'s Hit, Now Work Begins,print_headline:<PERSON>Harbaugh<\/PERSON>'s Hit, Now Work Begins}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<PERSON>Harbaugh</PERSON>, left <LOCATION>San Francisco</LOCATION> 49ers return college coaching, expected provide jolt energy Wolverines&#8217; beleaguered football program.",,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Football College},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Coaches Managers},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:3,value:<LOCATION>San Francisco<\/LOCATION> 49ers},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:University <LOCATION>Michigan<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:5,value:<PERSON>Harbaugh<\/PERSON>, Jim}]",Sports,null,The New York Times,[],Sports,2014-12-31T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/sports/31michigan2/31michigan2-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/sports/31michigan2/31michigan2-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/sports/31michigan2/31michigan3-1419961255962-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:386},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/sports/31michigan2/31michigan3-1419961255962-articleLarge.jpg,height:386},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/sports/31michigan2/31michigan2-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/sports/31michigan2/31michigan2-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1177,"<PERSON>Harbaugh</PERSON>, left <LOCATION>San Francisco</LOCATION> 49ers return college coaching, expected provide jolt energy Wolverines&#8217; beleaguered football program.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/sports/ncaafootball/jim-harbaugh-is-michigans-next-football-coach.html,54a2f7e07988102761d6cea8,College Football,"{main:<LOCATION>Michigan<\/LOCATION> Makes It Official: <PERSON>Jim Harbaugh<\/PERSON> Is Football Coach,print_headline:<LOCATION>Michigan<\/LOCATION> Makes It Official: <PERSON>Jim Harbaugh<\/PERSON> Is Football Coach}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>JOANNE C. GERSTNER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Joanne,role:reported,organization:,middlename:C.,rank:1,lastname:GERSTNER}]}",article
"The parents of a Chinese teenager executed 18 years ago for the rape and murder of a woman he did not commit will get <MONEY>2.05 million yuan $330,491</MONEY> in compensation, a court and his father said on <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T23:29:04Z,[],390,"The parents of a Chinese teenager executed 18 years ago for the rape and murder of a woman he did not commit will get <MONEY>2.05 million yuan $330,491</MONEY> in compensation, a court and his father said on <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/world/asia/30reuters-china-crime-compensation.html,54a37c047988102761d6cfec,Asia Pacific,"{main:Parents of Wrongfully Executed Teen in <LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION> to Get <MONEY>$330,000<\/MONEY>,print_headline:Parents of Wrongfully Executed Teen in <LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION> to Get <MONEY>$330,000<\/MONEY>}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Compensation whistle-blowers, create perverse incentives reward wrongdoing.",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:Birkenfeld, <PERSON>Bradley<\/PERSON> C},{name:persons,rank:2,value:Holder, <PERSON>Eric<\/PERSON> H Jr},{name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Madsen<\/PERSON>, Robert},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:Federal Bureau Investigation},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:Internal Revenue Service},{name:organizations,rank:3,value:Justice Department},{name:organizations,rank:4,value:Securities Exchange Commission},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Classified Information State Secrets},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Ethics Official Misconduct},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Whistle-Blowers}]",Business Day,"Compensation whistle-blowers, create perverse incentives reward wrongdoing.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-30T14:18:26Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/business/Dealprof/Dealprof-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/Dealprof/Dealprof-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/business/Dealprof/Dealprof-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:600},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/Dealprof/Dealprof-articleLarge.jpg,height:600},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/business/Dealprof/<ORGANIZATION>Dealprof-thumbStandard<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/Dealprof/<ORGANIZATION>Dealprof-thumbStandard<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg,height:75}]",1251,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/whistle-blower-awards-lure-wrongdoers-looking-to-score/,54a2fae57988102761d6ceb0,Dealbook,"{main:Whistle-Blower Awards Lure Wrongdoers Looking Score,print_headline:Whistle-Blower Awards Get Results, Also May Lure Wrongdoers,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>STEVEN DAVIDOFF SOLOMON<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Steven,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Davidoff,rank:1,lastname:SOLOMON}]}",blogpost
International arbitration neutral referee depoliticize disputes.,,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Foreign Investments},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Arbitration, Conciliation Mediation},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Law Legislation}]",Opinion,null,The New York Times,[],Editorial,2014-12-30T11:30:00Z,[],918,International arbitration neutral referee depoliticize disputes.,Letter,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/opinion/settling-investor-state-disputes.html,54a12da17988101f98e3ef68,null,"{content_kicker:Letters,main:Settling Investor-State Disputes,print_headline:Settling Investor-State Disputes,kicker:Letters}",[],article
"By time <PERSON>Jim Harbaugh</PERSON> walked court halftime <LOCATION>Michigan</LOCATION> basketball game, homecoming turned full-fledged pep rally.",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T08:58:05Z,[],1106,"By time <PERSON>Jim Harbaugh</PERSON> walked court halftime <LOCATION>Michigan</LOCATION> basketball game, homecoming turned full-fledged pep rally.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/sports/ncaafootball/ap-fbc-michigan-harbaugh.html,54a2b12e7988104803cc8a93,College Football,"{main:Rousing Reception Harbaugh Michigan Return,print_headline:Rousing Reception Harbaugh Michigan Return}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<PERSON>Glenda Gomez</PERSON> adopted young children daughter <PERSON>Suhany Vasquez</PERSON>, died breast cancer <DATE>2012</DATE>. Providing family, totals members, challenge.",17,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:New York Times Neediest Cases Fund},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:2,value:Federation Protestant Welfare Agencies},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Philanthropy}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"Federation Protestant Welfare Agencies, agencies supported The New York Times Neediest Cases Fund, helps <PERSON>Glenda Gomez</PERSON> buy furniture apartment.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-30T00:00:00Z,[],733,"<PERSON>Glenda Gomez</PERSON> adopted young children daughter <PERSON>Suhany Vasquez</PERSON>, died breast cancer <DATE>2012</DATE>. Providing family, totals members, challenge.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/nyregion/after-daughters-death-welcoming-grandchildren-into-a-bustling-home.html,54a210737988104803cc892d,null,"{content_kicker:The Neediest Cases,main:Raising Grandchildren to Honor Her Daughter’s Dying Wish,print_headline:Raising Grandchildren Honor Dying Wish,kicker:The Neediest Cases}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>JOHN OTIS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:John,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:OTIS}]}",article
"The university expected announce hiring <PERSON>Harbaugh</PERSON>, finished fourth season coach <LOCATION>San Francisco</LOCATION> 49ers <DATE>Sunday</DATE>, noon <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>.",8,"[{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Harbaugh<\/PERSON>, Jim},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Football College},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Football},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Coaches Managers},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:5,value:University <LOCATION>Michigan<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:6,value:<LOCATION>San Francisco<\/LOCATION> 49ers}]",Sports,"University <LOCATION>Michigan</LOCATION> introduce <PERSON>Jim Harbaugh</PERSON> football coach press conference; <PERSON>Harbaugh</PERSON>, finished fourth season coach <LOCATION>San Francisco</LOCATION> 49ers, considered coach collegiate professional level.",The New York Times,[],Sports,2014-12-30T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/30/sports/harbaugh-001/harbaugh-1419895383714-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/sports/harbaugh-001/harbaugh-1419895383714-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/30/sports/harbaugh-001/harbaugh-1419895383714-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:366},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/sports/harbaugh-001/harbaugh-1419895383714-articleLarge.jpg,height:366},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/30/sports/harbaugh-001/harbaugh-1419895383714-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/sports/harbaugh-001/harbaugh-1419895383714-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",795,"The university expected announce hiring <PERSON>Harbaugh</PERSON>, finished fourth season coach <LOCATION>San Francisco</LOCATION> 49ers <DATE>Sunday</DATE>, noon <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/sports/football/jim-harbaugh-said-to-be-michigans-next-football-coach.html,54a1931e7988104803cc8825,College Football,"{main:<PERSON>Jim Harbaugh<\/PERSON> Is Said Be Next Coach <LOCATION>Michigan<\/LOCATION>, His Alma Mater,print_headline:Harbaugh Is Said Be Next Coach <LOCATION>Michigan<\/LOCATION>, His Alma Mater}","{contributor:<PERSON>Joanne Gerstner<\/PERSON> contributed reporting.,original:By <PERSON>TIM ROHAN JOANNE C. GERSTNER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Tim,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:ROHAN},{firstname:Joanne,role:reported,organization:,middlename:C.,rank:2,lastname:GERSTNER}]}",article
