snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Even country corruption part daily life, revelations criminal ring smack heart capital stunned citizens.",16,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Italy<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Organized Crime},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:3,value:<LOCATION>Rome Italy<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:4,value:Carminati, <PERSON>Massimo 1958<\/PERSON>-},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Corruption Institutional},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Ethics Official Misconduct}]",World,Italian public stunned inquiry uncovering criminal ring heart <LOCATION>Rome</LOCATION> bloomed national scandal; two-year investigation lead arrests <PERSON>Massimo Carminati</PERSON> 36 accused infiltrating contracts wide assortment tasks including garbage collection park maintenance.,The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-12T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/12/world/12mafia/12mafia-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/12/world/12mafia/12mafia-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/12/world/12mafia/12mafia-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:398},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/12/world/12mafia/12mafia-articleLarge.jpg,height:398},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/12/world/12mafia/12mafia-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/12/world/12mafia/12mafia-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1354,"Even country corruption part daily life, revelations criminal ring smack heart capital stunned citizens.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/12/world/italy-gasps-as-inquiry-reveals-mobs-long-reach.html,548a5d1e7988102fcc1306ad,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:<LOCATION>Italy<\/LOCATION> Gasps Inquiry Reveals Mob&#8217;s Long Reach,print_headline:<LOCATION>Italy<\/LOCATION> Gasps as Inquiry Reveals Mob’s Long Reach}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ELISABETTA<\/PERSON> POVOLEDO,person:[{firstname:Elisabetta,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:POVOLEDO}]}",article
"The leaders Islamic State created currency, part grandiose plan restore caliphate era dominated <LOCATION>Middle East</LOCATION> 1,300 years ago.",8,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:Islamic State Iraq <LOCATION>Syria<\/LOCATION> ISIS},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Currency},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:3,value:Iraq},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:4,value:<LOCATION>Syria<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Muslims Islam},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:International Relations}]",World,"Islamic State created currency, part plan restore caliphate era dominated <LOCATION>Middle East</LOCATION> 1,300 years ago; begin minting gold, silver copper coins legal tender lands controlled group <ORGANIZATION>ISIS</ORGANIZATION> ISIL.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-11-15T00:00:00Z,[],666,"The leaders Islamic State created currency, part grandiose plan restore caliphate era dominated <LOCATION>Middle East</LOCATION> 1,300 years ago.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/11/15/world/middleeast/islamic-state-says-it-plans-to-issue-its-own-currency-.html,54669df079881049c1903df1,Middle East,"{main:Islamic State Says It Plans Issue Its Own Currency,print_headline:Islamic State Says It Plans Issue Its Own Currency}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>RICK GLADSTONE<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Rick,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:GLADSTONE}]}",article
President <PERSON>Obama</PERSON>&#8217;s top military adviser deploying limited number American forces fight alongside Iraqi troops moving retake areas held militants.,10,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:United States Defense Military Forces},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Dempsey<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Martin<\/PERSON> E},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Islamic State Iraq <LOCATION>Syria<\/LOCATION> ISIS},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:4,value:Iraq},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:5,value:<LOCATION>Mosul Iraq<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:6,value:<PERSON>Baghdadi<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Abu Bakr<\/PERSON> al-}]",<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,"<PERSON>Gen Martin E Dempsey</PERSON>, chairman <ORGANIZATION>Joint Chiefs Staff</ORGANIZATION>, tells <ORGANIZATION>House</ORGANIZATION> committee deploying limited number American forces accompany Iraqi troops complex offensive operations retake <LOCATION>Mosul</LOCATION> areas control <ORGANIZATION>Islamic State</ORGANIZATION> militants.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-11-14T00:00:00Z,[],849,President <PERSON>Obama</PERSON>&#8217;s top military adviser deploying limited number American forces fight alongside Iraqi troops moving retake areas held militants.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/11/14/us/top-us-general-says-hes-open-to-using-ground-troops-in-iraq.html,5464edcf7988101671e420fb,null,"{main:Top <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> General Says He&#8217;s Open Using Ground Troops Retake Mosul,print_headline:Top <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> General Says He’s Open to Using Ground Troops to Retake Mosul}","{contributor:<PERSON>Helene Cooper<\/PERSON> reported <LOCATION>Washington<\/LOCATION>, <PERSON>David D. Kirkpatrick<\/PERSON> <LOCATION>Baghdad<\/LOCATION>, <PERSON>Rick Gladstone<\/PERSON> <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION>.,original:By <PERSON>HELENE COOPER<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>DAVID D. KIRKPATRICK RICK GLADSTONE<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Helene,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:COOPER},{firstname:David,role:reported,organization:,rank:2}]}",article
"Countering rumors dead, <PERSON>Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi</PERSON>, <ORGANIZATION>Islamic State</ORGANIZATION> leader, issued call arms audio clip posted online.",,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Muslims Islam},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:2,value:Iraq},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Baghdadi<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Abu Bakr<\/PERSON> al-},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Islamic State Iraq <LOCATION>Syria<\/LOCATION> ISIS}]",World,null,The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-11-14T00:00:00Z,[],771,"Countering rumors dead, <PERSON>Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi</PERSON>, <ORGANIZATION>Islamic State</ORGANIZATION> leader, issued call arms audio clip posted online.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/11/14/world/middleeast/abu-bakr-baghdadi-islamic-state-leader-calls-for-new-fight-against-west.html,5464d99f7988104000b1aa8d,Middle East,"{main:ISIS Chief Emerges, Urging ‘Volcanoes of Jihad’,print_headline:ISIS Chief Is Said to Emerge, Urging ‘Volcanoes of Jihad’}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>DAVID D. KIRKPATRICK RICK GLADSTONE<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:David,role:reported,organization:,rank:1}]}",article
"A <ORGANIZATION>White House</ORGANIZATION> proposal protect service members predatory loans, national lending standard needed country.",10,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Credit Debt},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:United States Defense Military Forces},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Editorials},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Consumer Protection},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Payday Loans},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:Regulation Deregulation Industry},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:8,value:Consumer Financial Protection Bureau},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:9,value:House Representatives},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:10,value:Senate}]",Opinion,Editorial welcomes <PERSON>Obama</PERSON> administration's proposed improvement federal rules meant protect service members predatory loans; notes predatory loans afflict service members affect poor working-class Americans; calls national standard consumer lending.,The New York Times,[],Editorial,2014-10-19T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/10/19/opinion/19editorial-pic/19editorial-pic-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/10/19/opinion/19editorial-pic/19editorial-pic-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/10/19/opinion/19editorial-pic/19editorial-pic-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/10/19/opinion/19editorial-pic/19editorial-pic-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/10/19/opinion/19editorial-pic/19editorial-pic-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/10/19/opinion/19editorial-pic/19editorial-pic-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",535,"A <ORGANIZATION>White House</ORGANIZATION> proposal protect service members predatory loans, national lending standard needed country.",Editorial,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/10/19/opinion/sunday/a-rate-cap-for-all-consumer-loans.html,5442bf587988103ffb144846,<DATE>Sunday</DATE> Review,"{content_kicker:Editorial,main:A Rate Cap All Consumer Loans,print_headline:A Rate Cap All Consumer Loans,kicker:Editorial}","{contributor:,original:By THE EDITORIAL BOARD,person:[],organization:THE EDITORIAL BOARD}",article
A federal appeals court rejected arguments that <LOCATION>New York State</LOCATION>’s top financial regulator lacked jurisdiction.,null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:Lawsky, Benjamin M},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:Department Financial Services NYS},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Consumer Protection},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Credit Debt},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Law Legislation},{name:subject,rank:4,value:Native Americans},{name:subject,rank:5,value:Payday Loans}]",Business Day,A federal appeals court rejected arguments that <LOCATION>New York State</LOCATION>’s top financial regulator lacked jurisdiction.,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-10-01T19:28:36Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/07/17/business/dealbook/dbpix-lawsky/dbpix-lawsky-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/07/17/business/dealbook/dbpix-lawsky/dbpix-lawsky-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/07/17/business/dealbook/dbpix-lawsky/dbpix-lawsky-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:377},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/07/17/business/dealbook/dbpix-lawsky/dbpix-lawsky-articleLarge.jpg,height:377},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/07/17/business/dealbook/dbpix-lawsky/dbpix-lawsky-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/07/17/business/dealbook/dbpix-lawsky/dbpix-lawsky-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",637,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/10/01/appeals-court-rejects-claims-by-american-indian-payday-lenders/,542c8e937988105a9b09f7a8,Dealbook,"{main:Appeals Court Rejects Claims American Indian Payday Lenders,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>JESSICA SILVER-GREENBERG<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Jessica,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SILVER-GREENBERG}]}",blogpost
A lack statewide regulation so-called payday auto-title loans acutely felt low-income borrowers.,23A,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Automobile Financing},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Credit Debt},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Consumer Protection},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Texas Tribune},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:5,value:<LOCATION>Texas<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Automobiles}]",<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,The New York Times,[],National,2014-08-24T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/08/24/travel/24TTPAYDAY/24TTPAYDAY-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/08/24/travel/24TTPAYDAY/24TTPAYDAY-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/08/24/travel/24TTPAYDAY/24TTPAYDAY-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:411},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/08/24/travel/24TTPAYDAY/24TTPAYDAY-articleLarge.jpg,height:411},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/08/24/travel/24TTPAYDAY/24TTPAYDAY-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/08/24/travel/24TTPAYDAY/24TTPAYDAY-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1027,A lack statewide regulation so-called payday auto-title loans acutely felt low-income borrowers.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/08/24/us/thousands-in-texas-lose-cars-amid-calls-for-loan-restrictions.html,53f9180b79881001aab76b54,null,"{content_kicker:The Texas Tribune,main:Thousands Texas Lose Cars Amid Calls Loan Restrictions,print_headline:Thousands Lose Cars Amid Calls Loan Restrictions}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>CORRIE MACLAGGAN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Corrie,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:MACLAGGAN}]}",article
"A spotlight on derivatives, risky mortgages and repo markets — practices all linked to the <DATE>2008</DATE> financial crisis — gave DealBook a certain “Groundhog Day” quality this week.",null,[],Business Day,"A spotlight on derivatives, risky mortgages and repo markets — practices all linked to the <DATE>2008</DATE> financial crisis — gave DealBook a certain “Groundhog Day” quality this week.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-08-15T15:43:43Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/08/15/business/dbpix-verse/dbpix-verse-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/08/15/business/dbpix-verse/dbpix-verse-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/08/15/business/dbpix-verse/dbpix-verse-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:405},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/08/15/business/dbpix-verse/dbpix-verse-articleLarge.jpg,height:405},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/08/15/business/dbpix-verse/dbpix-verse-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/08/15/business/dbpix-verse/dbpix-verse-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",447,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/08/15/weekend-reading-derivatives-mortgages-and-repo-markets-in-2014-or-2008/,53ee6316798810749b8429de,Dealbook,"{main:Weekend Reading: Derivatives, Mortgages Repo Markets 2014 2008??,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By DEALBOOK,person:[{firstname:Dealbook,role:reported,organization:,rank:1}]}",blogpost
<PERSON>Kinder Morgan</PERSON>’s reorganization puts master limited partnerships in question. |Kinder Morganu2019s reorganization puts master limited partnerships question. | An arbitration panel eased blame <ORGANIZATION>Ernst & Young</ORGANIZATION> audits <ORGANIZATION>Lehman Brothers</ORGANIZATION>. | <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> prosecutors accused payday lenders usury. | <ORGANIZATION>Chiquita Brands</ORGANIZATION>...|Kinder Morganu2019s reorganization puts master limited partnerships question. | An arbitration panel eased blame <ORGANIZATION>Ernst & Young</ORGANIZATION> audits <ORGANIZATION>Lehman Brothers</ORGANIZATION>. | <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> prosecutors accused payday lenders usury. | <ORGANIZATION>Chiquita Brands</ORGANIZATION> received counter inversion plan.| <ORGANIZATION>Chiquita</ORGANIZATION> Brands...,null,[],Business Day,<PERSON>Kinder Morgan</PERSON>’s reorganization puts master limited partnerships in question. | An arbitration panel has eased the blame on <ORGANIZATION>Ernst & Young</ORGANIZATION> for audits of <ORGANIZATION>Lehman Brothers</ORGANIZATION>. | <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> prosecutors have accused payday lenders with usury. | <ORGANIZATION>Chiquita Brands</ORGANIZATION> has received a counter to its inversion plan.,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-08-12T07:35:47Z,[],1756,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/08/12/morning-agenda-uncertainty-over-master-limited-partnerships/,53e9fc5179881068933b21f4,Dealbook,"{main:Morning Agenda: Uncertainty Over Master Limited Partnerships,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By SYDNEY EMBER,person:[{firstname:<LOCATION>Sydney<\/LOCATION>,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:EMBER}]}",blogpost
"What you need to know for <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>: rain later and lots of it, the city’s public housing stock in crisis, and non-scooping dog owners caught on camera.",null,[],<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"What you need to know for <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>: rain later and lots of it, the city’s public housing stock in crisis, and non-scooping dog owners caught on camera.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-08-12T05:45:42Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/08/12/nyregion/12NYTODAY/12NYTODAY-thumbWide-v2.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/08/12/nyregion/12NYTODAY/12NYTODAY-thumbWide-v2.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/08/12/nyregion/12NYTODAY/12NYTODAY-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:396},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/08/12/nyregion/12NYTODAY/12NYTODAY-articleLarge.jpg,height:396},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/08/12/nyregion/12NYTODAY/12NYTODAY-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/08/12/nyregion/12NYTODAY/12NYTODAY-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",854,null,Blog,http://cityroom.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/08/12/new-york-today-strong-moisture-transport/,53e9e27d79881068933b21c5,null,"{main:<LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION> Today: 'Strong Moisture Transport',kicker:City Room}","{original:By <PERSON>ANDY NEWMAN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Andy,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:NEWMAN}]}",blogpost
