snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
Sponsors <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> New J.rsey legislation improve transparency authority plan votes override vetoes governors.,17,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:Port Authority <LOCATION>New York New Jersey<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:Christie, Christopher J},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Cuomo<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Andrew<\/PERSON> M},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:4,value:New Jersey},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:5,value:New York State},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:6,value:George Washington Bridge},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:State Legislatures}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"Backers bipartisan legislation reform corrupt Port Authority <LOCATION>New York New Jersey</LOCATION>, rejected <ORGANIZATION>New York Gov Andrew M Cuomo New Jersey Gov Chris Christie</ORGANIZATION>, override governors' vetoes; states' leaders vote overturn vetoes ceremonial, end legislative term approaching vote pass <DATE>2015</DATE>.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-31T00:00:00Z,[],494,Sponsors <LOCATION>New York New Jersey</LOCATION> legislation improve transparency authority plan votes override vetoes governors.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/nyregion/lawmakers-look-to-override-christie-and-cuomo-on-port-authority-overhaul.html,54a367b27988102761d6cfa5,null,"{main:Lawmakers Look Override Christie Cuomo Port Authority Overhaul,print_headline:Lawmakers 2 Capitals Look Revive Reform Bill}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>KATE ZERNIKE JESSE McKINLEY<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Kate,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:ZERNIKE},{firstname:Jesse,role:reported,organization:,rank:2,lastname:McKINLEY}]}",article
<LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>'s securities-market regulator <ORGANIZATION>CVM</ORGANIZATION> <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> investigating <ORGANIZATION>Petrobras</ORGANIZATION> executives failed legal duties protect state-run oil company investors losses related giant corruption scandal.,null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T22:48:34Z,[],418,<LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>'s securities-market regulator <ORGANIZATION>CVM</ORGANIZATION> <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> investigating <ORGANIZATION>Petrobras</ORGANIZATION> executives failed legal duties protect state-run oil company investors losses related giant corruption scandal.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/business/30reuters-brazil-petrobras-regulator.html,54a372327988102761d6cfb8,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Brazil<\/LOCATION>'s Market Regulator Widens Petrobras Probe,print_headline:<LOCATION>Brazil<\/LOCATION>'s Market Regulator Widens Petrobras Probe}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The bill, passed houses <LOCATION>New York New Jersey Legislatures</LOCATION> year, provided raft financial, ethical administrative rules bistate agency.",1,"[{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:1,value:New York State},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:2,value:New Jersey},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Port Authority <LOCATION>New York New Jersey<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:4,value:Christie, Christopher J},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:5,value:<PERSON>Cuomo<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Andrew<\/PERSON> M},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Governors US},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:Law Legislation},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:8,value:Democratic Party},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:9,value:Republican Party}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,<LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> Gov Andrew M <ORGANIZATION>Cuomo New Jersey Gov Chris Christie</ORGANIZATION> defy unanimous votes Legislatures veto bill aimed overhauling Port Authority <LOCATION>New York New Jersey</LOCATION>; outline variety proposals add value improve authority's operations; decision veto <PERSON>Cuomo Christie</PERSON> face lingering federal inquiries.,The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-28T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/port/port-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/port/port-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/port/port-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:403},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/port/port-articleLarge.jpg,height:403},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/port/port-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/port/port-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",889,"The bill, passed houses <LOCATION>New York New Jersey Legislatures</LOCATION> year, provided raft financial, ethical administrative rules bistate agency.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/nyregion/cuomo-and-christie-announce-they-will-veto-bill-to-overhaul-port-authority.html,549f45c779881001534d1fb6,null,"{main:<PERSON>Cuomo Christie<\/PERSON>, Defying Legislatures, Reject Bill Overhaul Port Authority,print_headline:Governors Veto Bill Overhaul Port Authority}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>JESSE McKINLEY<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Jesse,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:McKINLEY}]}",article
It’s a rare shift in a long-opaque industry: A firm is letting investors hire an outside monitor to review a fund’s books and practices.,1,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Private Equity},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Freeman Spogli<\/PERSON> & Co},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Regulation Deregulation Industry},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Securities Exchange Commission},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Dodd-Frank Wall Street Reform Consumer Protection Act 2010},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Prices Fares, Fees Rates},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:7,value:<PERSON>Appelbaum<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Eileen<\/PERSON>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Prices Fares, Fees Rates},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Pensions Retirement Plans},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Securities Exchange Commission},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Dodd-Frank Wall Street Reform Consumer Protection Act 2010},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Private Equity},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:Regulation Deregulation Industry}]",Business Day,null,The New York Times,[],SundayBusiness,2014-12-28T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/28/business/28-PRIVATE-1/28-PRIVATE-1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/business/28-PRIVATE-1/28-PRIVATE-1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/28/business/28-PRIVATE-1/28-PRIVATE-1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:343},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/business/28-PRIVATE-1/28-PRIVATE-1-articleLarge.jpg,height:343},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/28/business/28-PRIVATE-JP/28-PRIVATE-JP-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/business/28-PRIVATE-JP/28-PRIVATE-JP-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1944,It’s a rare shift in a long-opaque industry: A firm is letting investors hire an outside monitor to review a fund’s books and practices.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/business/entering-the-secret-garden-of-private-equity.html,549ed0ec7988105ced78871d,null,"{main:Entering Secret Garden Private Equity,print_headline:Entering Secret Garden Private Equity}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>GRETCHEN MORGENSON<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Gretchen,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:MORGENSON}]}",article
"The legislation would open all of the agency’s meetings, and require its officials to acknowledge that their duty is to the <LOCATION>Port Authority New York New Jersey</LOCATION>, not to the governor who appointed them.",23,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:Port Authority of <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION> and <LOCATION>New Jersey<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:Christie, Christopher J},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Cuomo<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Andrew<\/PERSON> M},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Ethics Official Misconduct},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:5,value:New York State},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:6,value:New Jersey},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:Law Legislation}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"Neither <ORGANIZATION>New York Gov Andrew M Cuomo New Jersey Gov Chris Christie</ORGANIZATION> sign <ORGANIZATION>Port Authority New York New Jersey Transparency</ORGANIZATION> Accountability Act <DATE>2014</DATE>, unanimously passed state's legislatures; bill, impose administrative, financial ethical requirements agency controlled states, approved governors order pass.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-25T00:00:00Z,[],911,"The legislation would open all of the agency’s meetings, and require its officials to acknowledge that their duty is to the <ORGANIZATION>Port Authority</ORGANIZATION> of <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>New Jersey</LOCATION>, not to the governor who appointed them.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/25/nyregion/cuomo-and-christie-silent-as-deadline-for-port-authority-bill-approaches.html,549b780979881003066910b9,null,"{main:Cuomo Christie Silent Deadline Port Authority Bill Approaches,print_headline:Cuomo Christie Silent Deadline Port Authority Bill Approaches}","{contributor:<PERSON>Kate Zernike<\/PERSON> contributed reporting New Jersey.,original:By <PERSON>JESSE McKINLEY<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Jesse,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:McKINLEY}]}",article
Insider trading is a crime entirely defined by common law — an accumulation of cases and judicial precedents that date from the <DATE>1960s</DATE> — and fitting a case into that thicket can be problematic.,1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Insider Trading},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Chiasson<\/PERSON>, Anthony},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Newman<\/PERSON>, Todd <DATE>1965<\/DATE>-},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Securities Commodities Violations},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Law Legislation},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:6,value:Bharara, Preet}]",Business Day,"<PERSON>James B Stewart</PERSON> Common Sense column contends dismissal insider trading convictions <PERSON>Anthony Chiasson Todd Newman</PERSON> underscores clear-cut law insider trading; notes due lack law, insider trading cases pursued anti-fraud statutes, complicates proceedings.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-20T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/20/business/20stewart-web1/20stewart-web1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/20/business/20stewart-web1/20stewart-web1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/20/business/20stewart-web1/20stewart-web1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:387},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/20/business/20stewart-web1/20stewart-web1-articleLarge.jpg,height:387},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/20/business/20stewart-web1/20stewart-web1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/20/business/20stewart-web1/20stewart-web1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1563,Insider trading is a crime entirely defined by common law — an accumulation of cases and judicial precedents that date from the <DATE>1960s</DATE> — and fitting a case into that thicket can be problematic.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/20/business/the-insider-trading-morass.html,549464dc7988107c46800482,null,"{content_kicker:Common Sense,main:Delving Into Morass Insider Trading,print_headline:Delving Into Morass Insider Trading,kicker:Common Sense}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>JAMES B. STEWART<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:James,role:reported,organization:,rank:1}]}",article
"To achieve its independence from the the <ORGANIZATION>Frank Lloyd Wright Foundation</ORGANIZATION>, an architecture school says it needs to raise <MONEY>$2 million</MONEY> by the end of <DATE>2015</DATE>.",null,"[{name:glocations,rank:1,value:Chicago Ill},{name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>Scottsdale Ariz<\/LOCATION>},{name:glocations,rank:3,value:<LOCATION>Wisconsin<\/LOCATION>},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:Higher Learning Commission},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:Taliesin West},{name:organizations,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Wright<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Frank Lloyd<\/PERSON>, Foundation},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Accreditation},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Architecture},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Colleges Universities}]",Arts,"To achieve its independence from the the <ORGANIZATION>Frank Lloyd Wright Foundation</ORGANIZATION>, an architecture school says it needs to raise <MONEY>$2 million</MONEY> by the end of <DATE>2015</DATE>.",The New York Times,[],Culture,2014-12-15T11:43:04Z,[],202,null,Blog,http://artsbeat.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/15/wright-architecture-school-sets-fund-raising-goal-for-independence/,548f107f79881018ac4bb303,null,"{main:Wright Architecture School Sets Fund-raising Goal Independence,print_headline:Architecture School Sets <MONEY>$2 Million<\/MONEY> Goal,kicker:ArtsBeat}","{original:By <PERSON>ROBIN POGREBIN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Robin,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:POGREBIN}]}",blogpost
"Nearly years <PERSON>James Brown</PERSON> died, disputed remains mired lawsuits, trust set needy children aid intended recipients.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Music},{is_major:Y,name:creative_works,rank:11,value:Get On Up Movie},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Wills Estates},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Television},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Movies},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:5,value:<PERSON>Brown<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>James<\/PERSON> 1933-2006},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Royalties},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:7,value:<LOCATION>South Carolina<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:8,value:Suits Litigation Civil},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:9,value:Philanthropy},{is_major:N,name:creative_works,rank:10,value:Mr. Dynamite: The Rise <PERSON>James Brown<\/PERSON> TV Program}]",<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,Estate legendary singer <PERSON>James Brown</PERSON> remains mired lawsuits years death; battle <PERSON>Brown</PERSON>'s continues documentary Mr Dynamite: The Rise <PERSON>James Brown</PERSON> film Get On Up focused attention life.,The New York Times,[],National,2014-12-14T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/14/us/SOUL/SOUL-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/14/us/SOUL/SOUL-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/14/us/SOUL/SOUL-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:395},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/14/us/SOUL/SOUL-articleLarge.jpg,height:395},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/14/us/SOUL/SOUL-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/14/us/SOUL/SOUL-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1944,"Nearly years <PERSON>James Brown</PERSON> died, disputed remains mired lawsuits, trust set needy children aid intended recipients.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/14/us/downbeat-legacy-for-james-brown-godfather-of-soul-a-will-in-deep-dispute.html,548cd0b8798810543aba4aa9,null,"{main:Downbeat Legacy <PERSON>James Brown<\/PERSON>, Godfather Soul: A Will Dispute,print_headline:Downbeat Legacy Godfather Soul: A Will Deep Dispute}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>LARRY ROHTER STEVE KNOPPER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Larry,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:ROHTER},{firstname:Steve,role:reported,organization:,rank:2,lastname:KNOPPER}]}",article
"The appeals court ruling overturning convictions hedge fund managers narrowing parameters insider trading, contends <PERSON>Michael Perino</PERSON>.",null,"[{name:type_of_material,rank:1,value:News},{name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Chiasson<\/PERSON>, Anthony},{name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Newman<\/PERSON>, Todd <DATE>1965<\/DATE>-},{name:subject,rank:4,value:Insider Trading},{name:organizations,rank:5,value:Securities Exchange Commission},{name:organizations,rank:6,value:Supreme Court US}]",Business Day,"The appeals court ruling overturning convictions hedge fund managers narrowing parameters insider trading, contends <PERSON>Michael Perino</PERSON>.",The New York Times,[],null,2014-12-12T14:56:24Z,[],2039,<PERSON>Michael Perino</PERSON> is a professor at <ORGANIZATION>St. John’s University School of Law</ORGANIZATION> and the author of “The Hellhound of Wall Street: How <PERSON>Ferdinand Pecora</PERSON>’s Investigation of the <ORGANIZATION>Great Crash Forever Changed American Finance</ORGANIZATION>.”,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/12/the-gift-of-inside-information/,548b48d779881004157bb3b6,Dealbook,"{main:The Gift Inside Information,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>MICHAEL PERINO<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Michael,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:PERINO}]}",blogpost
"The latest appeals court decision make insider-trading cases harder, give free pass hedge funds trade confidential information, <PERSON>Peter J. Henning</PERSON> writes White Collar Watch.",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:Bharara, Preet},{name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Chiasson<\/PERSON>, Anthony},{name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Newman<\/PERSON>, Todd <DATE>1965<\/DATE>-},{name:persons,rank:4,value:<PERSON>Steinberg<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Michael Saren<\/PERSON>},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:Justice Department},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:Securities Exchange Commission},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Decisions Verdicts},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Insider Trading},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Suits Litigation Civil}]",Business Day,"The latest appeals court decision make insider-trading cases harder, give free pass hedge funds trade confidential information, <PERSON>Peter J. Henning</PERSON> writes White Collar Watch.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-10T19:07:39Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/11/business/dbpix-bharara-1/dbpix-bharara-1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/11/business/dbpix-bharara-1/dbpix-bharara-1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/11/business/dbpix-bharara-1/dbpix-bharara-1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/11/business/dbpix-bharara-1/dbpix-bharara-1-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/11/business/dbpix-bharara-1/dbpix-bharara-1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/11/business/dbpix-bharara-1/dbpix-bharara-1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1323,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/10/what-an-appeals-court-insider-trading-decision-does-and-doesnt-do/,5488e1b07988104c17459f6b,Dealbook,"{main:What Appeals Court Insider Trading Decision Does, Doesn't, Do,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>PETER J. HENNING<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Peter,role:reported,organization:,middlename:J.,rank:1,lastname:HENNING}]}",blogpost
