snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
The recent volatility stocks unpredictability interest rates potent reminder investors diversified.,1,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Stocks Bonds},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:2,value:United States},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Government Bonds},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Interest Rates},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Credit Debt},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Quantitative Easing}]",Business Day,<PERSON>James B Stewart</PERSON> Common Sense column reflects surprising drop yield 10-year <ORGANIZATION>United States Treasury</ORGANIZATION> note wild gyrations stock market; notes volatility stocks unpredictability interest rates important reminder investors diversified mix stocks bonds.,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-10-18T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/10/18/business/Stewart/Stewart-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/10/18/business/Stewart/Stewart-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/10/18/business/Stewart/Stewart-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:332},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/10/18/business/Stewart/Stewart-articleL.rge.jpg,height:332},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/10/18/business/Stewart/<ORGANIZATION>Stewart-thumbStandard<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/10/18/business/Stewart/<ORGANIZATION>Stewart-thumbStandard<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg,height:75}]",997,The recent volatility stocks unpredictability interest rates potent reminder investors diversified.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/10/18/business/amid-tumult-in-stocks-bonds-prove-steady.html,54412bbe79881042fc4f43db,null,"{content_kicker:Common Sense,main: Amid Tumult, Bonds Prove Steady,print_headline:Amid Tumult, Bonds Prove Steady,kicker:Common Sense}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>JAMES B. STEWART<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:James,role:reported,organization:,rank:1}]}",article
"The <ORGANIZATION>Pimco</ORGANIZATION> Total Return Fund, world's largest bond fund, cut holdings <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> government-related securities mortgages straight month <DATE>March</DATE> continued bets <ORGANIZATION>Federal Reserve</ORGANIZATION> conclude bond purchases year,...",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],null,2014-04-09T18:24:17Z,[],772,"The <ORGANIZATION>Pimco</ORGANIZATION> Total Return Fund, world's largest bond fund, cut holdings <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> government-related securities mortgages straight month <DATE>March</DATE> continued bets <ORGANIZATION>Federal Reserve</ORGANIZATION> conclude bond purchases year, data firm's website showed <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/04/09/business/09reuters-funds-investing-pimco.html,5345c96f79881065d6e27d20,null,"{main:Pimco Total Return Cuts Mortgage, <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Government Holdings March: Website,print_headline:Pimco Total Return Cuts Mortgage, <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Government Holdings March: Website}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"At one point, <MONEY>$50 billion</MONEY> in federal loan guarantees were meant to cover nuclear projects, but a plant in <LOCATION>Georgia</LOCATION> may receive the only guarantees made.",3,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:4,value:<LOCATION>Georgia<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Nuclear Energy},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:5,value:<PERSON>Moniz<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Ernest<\/PERSON> J},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Federal Aid US},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Energy Department}]",Business Day,"Energy <PERSON>Sec Ernest Moniz</PERSON> is set to announce that he will finish a <MONEY>$6.5 billion</MONEY> loan guarantee and another soon for <MONEY>$1.8 billion</MONEY> to help three <LOCATION>Georgia</LOCATION> electric companies build first new nuclear reactors in <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> in three decades; announcement comes far later than anticipated and may effectively end loan program established in <DATE>2005</DATE> by <ORGANIZATION>Congress</ORGANIZATION>, which at one point had promised to support <MONEY>$50 billion</MONEY> in loans for nuclear projects.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-02-19T00:00:00Z,[],598,"At one point, <MONEY>$50 billion</MONEY> in federal loan guarantees were meant to cover nuclear projects, but a plant in <LOCATION>Georgia</LOCATION> may receive the only guarantees made.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/02/19/business/energy-environment/loan-program-for-reactors-is-fizzling.html,53040bbf79881027badd9871,Energy & Environment,"{main:Loan Program Reactors Is Fizzling,print_headline:Loan Program Reactors Is Fizzling}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>MATTHEW L. WALD<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Matthew,role:reported,organization:,middlename:L.,rank:1,lastname:WALD}]}",article
"The tax-free status municipal bonds appealing year, tax rules effect.",7,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Personal Finances},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Asset Allocation Personal Finances},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Municipal Bonds},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:High Net Worth Individuals}]",Your Money,"Municipal bonds have been depressed, but their tax-free status is likely to become even more appealing in <DATE>2014</DATE>, as new tax rules go into effect; munis are seen as especially good for well-off people past 70 1/2, who are required to take minimum distributions from their retirement plans.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-02-11T00:00:00Z,[],1071,"The tax-free status municipal bonds appealing year, tax rules effect.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/02/11/your-money/after-setbacks-municipal-bond-sector-is-looking-up.html,52f95e9b7988100d7fbb6b59,null,"{main:After Setbacks, Municipal Bond Sector Is Looking Up,print_headline:After Setbacks, Municipal Bond Sector Is Looking Up}","{contributor:,original:By CONRAD DE AENLLE,person:[{firstname:Conrad,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:DE AENLLE}]}",article
