snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Uber, Facebook, Instagram &#8212;, rage, <DATE>2014</DATE> winds ready fresh. From ride-hailing photo sharing, up-and coming apps startups watch <DATE>2015</DATE>. W.ich...",null,[],Technology,null,A.,[],None,2015-01-01T13:09:18Z,[],840,"Uber, Facebook, Instagram &#8212;, rage, <DATE>2014</DATE> winds ready fresh. From ride-hailing photo sharing, up-and coming apps startups watch <DATE>2015</DATE>. Which breakout hit year??",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/technology/ap-us-tec-startups-to-watch-in-2015.html,54a58e407988102023c941fb,null,"{main:In With New: Snappy Apps 2015,print_headline:In With New: Snappy Apps 2015}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Beset critics buffeted economic woes, <ORGANIZATION>European Union</ORGANIZATION> chiefs forgiven thinking Pope <PERSON>Francis</PERSON> apply balm New Year address <ORGANIZATION>EU</ORGANIZATION> parliament.",null,[],Business Day,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T11:26:15Z,[],694,"Beset critics buffeted economic woes, <ORGANIZATION>European Union</ORGANIZATION> chiefs forgiven thinking Pope <PERSON>Francis</PERSON> apply balm New Year address <ORGANIZATION>EU</ORGANIZATION> parliament.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/business/ap-eu-europes-new-year.html,54a575c579881011bed2ceaa,null,"{main:Troubled <ORGANIZATION>EU<\/ORGANIZATION> Hoping Only Way Is Up 2015,print_headline:Troubled <ORGANIZATION>EU<\/ORGANIZATION> Hoping Only Way Is Up 2015}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<LOCATION>India</LOCATION> scrapped 65-year-old <ORGANIZATION>Planning Commission</ORGANIZATION>, Prime Minister <PERSON>Narendra Modi</PERSON> accused stifling growth Soviet-style bureaucracy, replacing <DATE>Thursday</DATE> body involve regions.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T10:36:52Z,[],362,"<LOCATION>India</LOCATION> scrapped 65-year-old <ORGANIZATION>Planning Commission</ORGANIZATION>, Prime Minister <PERSON>Narendra Modi</PERSON> accused stifling growth Soviet-style bureaucracy, replacing <DATE>Thursday</DATE> body involve regions.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/world/asia/01reuters-india-politics.html,54a56a4979881011bed2cc20,Asia Pacific,"{main:<LOCATION>India<\/LOCATION> PM Replaces Soviet-Style Planning Body, Aiming Boost Growth,print_headline:<LOCATION>India<\/LOCATION> PM Replaces Soviet-Style Planning Body, Aiming Boost Growth}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<LOCATION>Latvia</LOCATION> took over the six-month rotating presidency of the <LOCATION>European Union</LOCATION> on <DATE>Thursday</DATE>, pledging to launch a <MONEY>315 billion</MONEY> euro <MONEY>$381 billion</MONEY> investment plan for the bloc and hoping to start a review of <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>'s border defense.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T09:21:27Z,[],286,"<LOCATION>Latvia</LOCATION> took over the six-month rotating presidency of the <LOCATION>European Union</LOCATION> on <DATE>Thursday</DATE>, pledging to launch a <MONEY>315 billion</MONEY> euro <MONEY>$381 billion</MONEY> investment plan for the bloc and hoping to start a review of <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>'s border defense.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/world/europe/01reuters-eu-latvia.html,54a558b879881011bed2c834,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:<LOCATION>Latvia<\/LOCATION> Takes <ORGANIZATION>EU<\/ORGANIZATION> Reins Focused Growth Plan, <ORGANIZATION>Border Defense<\/ORGANIZATION>,print_headline:<LOCATION>Latvia<\/LOCATION> Takes <ORGANIZATION>EU<\/ORGANIZATION> Reins Focused Growth Plan, <ORGANIZATION>Border Defense<\/ORGANIZATION>}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Beset critics buffeted economic woes, <ORGANIZATION>European Union</ORGANIZATION> chiefs forgiven thinking Pope <PERSON>Francis</PERSON> apply balm New Year address <ORGANIZATION>EU</ORGANIZATION> parliament.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T07:44:52Z,[],694,"Beset critics buffeted economic woes, <ORGANIZATION>European Union</ORGANIZATION> chiefs forgiven thinking Pope <PERSON>Francis</PERSON> apply balm New Year address <ORGANIZATION>EU</ORGANIZATION> parliament.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/world/europe/ap-eu-europes-new-year-.html,54a5424279881011bed2c33b,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:Troubled <ORGANIZATION>EU<\/ORGANIZATION> Hoping Only Way Is Up 2015,print_headline:Troubled <ORGANIZATION>EU<\/ORGANIZATION> Hoping Only Way Is Up 2015}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Cuban police detained dozen dissidents <LOCATION>Havana</LOCATION> prison demand fellow opponents government released, dissidents <DATE>Thursday</DATE>.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T04:57:09Z,[],358,"Cuban police detained dozen dissidents <LOCATION>Havana</LOCATION> prison demand fellow opponents government released, dissidents <DATE>Thursday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/world/americas/01reuters-cuba-usa-dissidents.html,54a51a2179881011bed2ba2d,Americas,"{main:Cuban Police Detain Protesters Outside Prison, Dissidents Say,print_headline:Cuban Police Detain Protesters Outside Prison, Dissidents Say}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Readers, including <PERSON>Marc Rotenberg</PERSON> Electronic Privacy Information Center, fault <ORGANIZATION>Federal Trade Commission</ORGANIZATION> strategy.",18,"[{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:1,value:Federal Trade Commission},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Privacy},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Law Legislation},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Computers Internet}]",Opinion,null,The New York Times,[],Letters,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,[],330,"Readers, including <PERSON>Marc Rotenberg</PERSON> Electronic Privacy Information Center, fault <ORGANIZATION>Federal Trade Commission</ORGANIZATION> strategy.",Letter,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/opinion/online-privacy-who-writes-the-rules.html,54a49c8e79881011bed29d95,null,"{content_kicker:Letters,main:Online Privacy: Who Writes Rules??,print_headline:Online Privacy: Who Writes Rules??,kicker:Letters}",[],article
"After more than 30 years of serving up inexpensive food and drinks on West 72nd Street, the chain’s original restaurant will close for good on <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.",15,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Restaurants},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Barbecue},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Landmarks Preservation Commission},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:4,value:Upper West Side <LOCATION>Manhattan<\/LOCATION>, NY}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"<LOCATION>Dallas</LOCATION> BBQ restaurant West 72nd Street, restaurant small chain, closes due rent increase.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/nyregion/BBQ1/BBQ1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/nyregion/BBQ1/BBQ1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/nyregion/BBQ1/BBQ1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:396},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/nyregion/BBQ1/BBQ1-articleLarge.jpg,height:396},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/nyregion/BBQ1/BBQ1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/nyregion/BBQ1/BBQ1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",733,"After more than 30 years of serving up inexpensive food and drinks on West 72nd Street, the chain’s original restaurant will close for good on <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/nyregion/long-out-of-place-on-an-exclusive-manhattan-block-a-restaurant-moves-out.html,54a494bb79881011bed29bce,null,"{main:Barbecue Chain’s Original Link, in Unlikely Spot, Is No More,print_headline:Chain’s Original Link, in Unlikely Spot, Is No More}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ELIZABETH A. HARRIS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Elizabeth,role:reported,organization:,middlename:A.,rank:1,lastname:HARRIS}]}",article
"The grand arcade century-old <LOCATION>Manhattan</LOCATION> skyscraper open 30-, 60- 90-minute tours day, visitors photographs.",16,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Woolworth Building NYC},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Historic Buildings Sites},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Witkoff Group},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Alchemy Properties Inc},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:5,value:Manhattan NYC},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:6,value:<PERSON>Curry<\/PERSON>, Helen Post <DATE>1948<\/DATE>-},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:7,value:Gilbert, <PERSON>Cass<\/PERSON> 1859-1934}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"<PERSON>David W Dunlap</PERSON> Building Blocks column observes tours offered <ORGANIZATION>Woolworth Building</ORGANIZATION>'s grand arcade, arguably dazzling lobby <LOCATION>New York City</LOCATION>; notes tours part agreement building owner <ORGANIZATION>Witkoff Group Helen Post Curry</ORGANIZATION>, great-granddaughter arcade designer <PERSON>Cass Gilbert</PERSON>; lobby largely off-limits public years.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/nyregion/01BLOCKS-web1/01BLOCKS-web1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/nyregion/01BLOCKS-web1/01BLOCKS-web1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/nyregion/01BLOCKS-web1/01BLOCKS-web1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:398},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/nyregion/01BLOCKS-web1/01BLOCKS-web1-articleLarge.jpg,height:398},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/nyregion/01BLOCKS-web1/01BLOCKS-web1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/nyregion/01BLOCKS-web1/01BLOCKS-web1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",842,"The grand arcade century-old <LOCATION>Manhattan</LOCATION> skyscraper open 30-, 60- 90-minute tours day, visitors photographs.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/nyregion/off-limits-for-over-a-decade-lobby-of-woolworth-building-is-open-for-tours.html,54a417d57988102761d6e201,null,"{content_kicker:Building Blocks,main:Woolworth Building’s Grand Arcade Is Once Again a Sight All Can See,print_headline:Grand Arcade Is Once Again Sight All Can See,kicker:Building Blocks}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>DAVID W. DUNLAP<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:David,role:reported,organization:,middlename:W.,rank:1,lastname:DUNLAP}]}",article
"The vote, due held <DATE>Jan. 25</DATE>, pit prime minister&#8217;s party left-wing group opposed recent austerity measures.",9,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Greece<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:Tsipras, <PERSON>Alexis<\/PERSON>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Elections},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Legislatures Parliaments},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Politics Government},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:Coalition Radical Left <LOCATION>Greece<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:7,value:New Democracy Greece},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:8,value:Papoulias, Karolos},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:9,value:<PERSON>Samaras<\/PERSON>, Antonis}]",World,"Greek Parliament dissolved failing choose president; early general elections widely referendum austerity programs left-wing opposition candidate <PERSON>Alexis Tsipras</PERSON>, vowed demand cancellation country's debts, emerges front-runner.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/world/europe/01GREECE/01GREECE-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/world/europe/01GREECE/01GREECE-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/world/europe/01GREECE/01GREECE-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/world/europe/01GREECE/01GREECE-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/world/europe/01GREECE/01GREECE-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/world/europe/01GREECE/01GREECE-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",460,"The vote, due held <DATE>Jan. 25</DATE>, pit prime minister&#8217;s party left-wing group opposed recent austerity measures.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/world/europe/greece-dissolves-parliament-to-prepare-for-early-elections.html,54a3e8b87988102761d6dc8e,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:As Early Elections Near, Greek Legislators Disband,print_headline:As Early Elections Near, Greek Legislators Disband}","{contributor:,original:By ALAN COWELL,person:[{firstname:Alan,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:COWELL}]}",article
