snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
More dozen giant turbines erected remote mesa western <LOCATION>New Mexico</LOCATION> began churning power state's largest electric provider New Year's Day.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T11:15:33Z,[],569,More dozen giant turbines erected remote mesa western <LOCATION>New Mexico</LOCATION> began churning power state's largest electric provider New Year's Day.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/us/ap-us-renewable-energy-standards.html,54a573e079881011bed2ce31,null,"{main:States Work Meet New Renewable Energy Standards,print_headline:States Work Meet New Renewable Energy Standards}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
The <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> stock market solid year.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T16:12:00Z,[],132,The <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> stock market solid year.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/ap-financial-markets-us-close.html,54a467a879881011bed29173,null,"{main:S&P 500 Index Ends 2014 With Gain 11 Percent,print_headline:S&P 500 Index Ends 2014 With Gain 11 Percent}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"It great year stock market <DATE>2014</DATE>, case gains evenly distributed industries.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T12:36:30Z,[],576,"It great year stock market <DATE>2014</DATE>, case gains evenly distributed industries.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/ap-ye-financial-markets-inside-the-market.html,54a4355779881011bed284fb,null,"{main:Sector-By-Sector Breakdown 2014's Market Moves,print_headline:Sector-By-Sector Breakdown 2014's Market Moves}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Stocks delivered <DATE>2014</DATE>.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T11:48:36Z,[],1201,Stocks delivered <DATE>2014</DATE>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/ap-ye-financial-markets-resilient-bull-.html,54a429b67988102761d6e7f7,null,"{main:Bull Market Stocks Keeps Going 2014,print_headline:Bull Market Stocks Keeps Going 2014}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"When Xi Jinping wanted deliver political message <LOCATION>Hong Kong</LOCATION> protesters demanding free elections threatening streets, summoned tycoons dominate city&#8217;s economy. The words Chinese leader...",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T00:30:59Z,[],2444,"When Xi Jinping wanted deliver political message <LOCATION>Hong Kong</LOCATION> protesters demanding free elections threatening streets, summoned tycoons dominate city&#8217;s economy. The words Chinese leader <DATE>September 22</DATE> meeting <LOCATION>Beijing</LOCATION> uncompromising surprising. He entertain demand full universal suffrage <LOCATION>Hong Kong</LOCATION>, people attended.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-hongkong-china-economy-specialreport.html,54a38aca7988102761d6d1c4,null,"{main:Special Report: The <ORGANIZATION>Mainland<\/ORGANIZATION>'s Colonization <LOCATION>Hong Kong<\/LOCATION> Economy,print_headline:Special Report: The <ORGANIZATION>Mainland<\/ORGANIZATION>'s Colonization Hong Kong Economy}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"When Xi Jinping wanted deliver political message <LOCATION>Hong Kong</LOCATION> protesters demanding free elections threatening streets, summoned tycoons dominate city&#8217;s economy. The words Chinese leader...",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T20:01:53Z,[],2385,"When Xi Jinping wanted deliver political message <LOCATION>Hong Kong</LOCATION> protesters demanding free elections threatening streets, summoned tycoons dominate city&#8217;s economy. The words Chinese leader <DATE>September 22</DATE> meeting <LOCATION>Beijing</LOCATION> uncompromising surprising. He entertain demand full universal suffrage <LOCATION>Hong Kong</LOCATION>, people attended.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/business/30reuters-hongkong-china-economy-specialreport.html,54a34b827988102761d6cf69,null,"{main:Special Report: The <ORGANIZATION>Mainland<\/ORGANIZATION>'s Colonization <LOCATION>Hong Kong<\/LOCATION> Economy,print_headline:Special Report: The <ORGANIZATION>Mainland<\/ORGANIZATION>'s Colonization Hong Kong Economy}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> stocks fell <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> investors engaged profit-taking pull major indexes record levels, trend modest moves low volume continued heading final trading day year.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T06:57:06Z,[],477,"<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> stocks fell <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> investors engaged profit-taking pull major indexes record levels, trend modest moves low volume continued heading final trading day year.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/business/30reuters-markets-stocks-usa.html,54a293477988104803cc8a62,null,"{main:Wall St. Pulls Back From Record; Utilities Slump,print_headline:Wall St. Pulls Back From Record; Utilities Slump}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Ignoring gloomy global economic news, <ORGANIZATION>S.&P.</ORGANIZATION> 500 <ORGANIZATION>Nasdaq</ORGANIZATION> index rose slightly Dow fell <PERCENT>0.1 percent</PERCENT>.",2,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Stocks Bonds},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Standard & Poor's 500-Stock Index},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Nasdaq Composite Index},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Dow Jones Stock Average}]",Business Day,"Investors disregard downbeat global economic news falling energy prices, declining ruble concerns <LOCATION>Greece</LOCATION> reneging bailout inch stocks higher.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-30T00:00:00Z,[],399,"Ignoring gloomy global economic news, <ORGANIZATION>S.&P.</ORGANIZATION> 500 <ORGANIZATION>Nasdaq</ORGANIZATION> index rose slightly Dow fell <PERCENT>0.1 percent</PERCENT>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/business/daily-stock-market-activity.html,54a16dac7988101f98e3efc4,null,"{main:Wavering, Markets Mostly Rise,print_headline:Wavering, Markets Mostly Rise}","{contributor:,original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Retirees flocking join fellow artists, letter carriers, <LOCATION>R.V.</LOCATION> enthusiasts places stay active needed care.",1,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Retirement},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Retirement Communities Assisted Living},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Elder Care},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Nursing Homes}]",Your Money,"Retiring column; retirement communities cater people interests, passions, ways life, artists, homosexuals car enthusiasts, popular.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-27T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27retiring-pic/27retiring-pic-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27retiring-pic/27retiring-pic-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27retiring-pic/27retiring-pic-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27retiring-pic/27retiring-pic-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27retiring-pic/27retiring-pic-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27retiring-pic/27retiring-pic-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1328,"Retirees flocking join fellow artists, letter carriers, <LOCATION>R.V.</LOCATION> enthusiasts places stay active needed care.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/27/your-money/finding-communities-that-connect-and-nurture-the-like-minded.html,549dbcba7988105ced7885d5,null,"{content_kicker:Retiring,main:Finding Communities That Connect Nurture Like-Minded,print_headline:Choosing Home Stay Connected,kicker:Retiring}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ABBY ELLIN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Abby,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:ELLIN}]}",article
The prisoner exchange peace talks <ORGANIZATION>Russia Organization Security Cooperation Europe</ORGANIZATION> halt <LOCATION>Belarus</LOCATION>.,4,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Ukraine<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Prisoners War},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:3,value:<LOCATION>Russia<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:4,value:<LOCATION>Crimea Ukraine<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:5,value:Organization Security Cooperation Europe}]",World,"Ukrainian government pro-Russian separatists begin swapping prisoners war, peace talks break down; <LOCATION>Ukraine</LOCATION> states intends cut passenger cargo rail services <ORGANIZATION>Crimean Peninsula</ORGANIZATION>, annexed <LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION> March.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-27T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/27/world/UKRAINE-1/UKRAINE-1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/world/UKRAINE-1/UKRAINE-1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/27/world/UKRAINE-1/UKRAINE-1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:381},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/world/UKRAINE-1/UKRAINE-1-articleLarge.jpg,height:381},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/27/world/UKRAINE-1/UKRAINE-1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/world/UKRAINE-1/UKRAINE-1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",477,The prisoner exchange peace talks <ORGANIZATION>Russia Organization Security Cooperation Europe</ORGANIZATION> halt <LOCATION>Belarus</LOCATION>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/27/world/europe/ukraine-prisoner-swap-as-peace-talks-break-down.html,549da5a07988105ced7885af,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:<LOCATION>Ukraine<\/LOCATION> Separatists Swap Prisoners Peace Talks Falter,print_headline:<LOCATION>Ukraine<\/LOCATION> Separatists Swap Prisoners Peace Talks Falter}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ANDREW ROTH<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Andrew,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:ROTH}]}",article
