snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"The blood militants killed <ORGANIZATION>Islamic State</ORGANIZATION>'s rout Iraqi town <LOCATION>Jalawla</LOCATION> washed, turf war brewing Kurdish Shi'ite forces jointly drove insurgents.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-08T06:28:29Z,[],905,"The blood militants killed <ORGANIZATION>Islamic State</ORGANIZATION>'s rout Iraqi town <LOCATION>Jalawla</LOCATION> washed, turf war brewing Kurdish Shi'ite forces jointly drove insurgents.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/08/world/middleeast/08reuters-mideast-crisis-jalawla.html,54858be679881040e1d4c256,Middle East,"{main:Rivalries Resurface Iraqi Town Recaptured From Islamic State,print_headline:Rivalries Resurface Iraqi Town Recaptured From Islamic State}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
The weekend offered <LOCATION>Buffalo</LOCATION> region chance dig record levels deep snow flood warning effect rising temperatures rain.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-11-22T00:40:06Z,[],643,The weekend offered <LOCATION>Buffalo</LOCATION> region chance dig record levels deep snow flood warning effect rising temperatures rain.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/11/22/us/ap-us-wintry-weather.html,5470226379881031a977ef09,null,"{main:Cleanup, Flood Threat Looms After Huge NY Snow,print_headline:Cleanup, Flood Threat Looms After Huge NY Snow}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"In story <DATE>Nov. 21</DATE> Buffalo snowstorms, <ORGANIZATION>The Associated Press</ORGANIZATION> reported erroneously warmer temperatures make snow heavier. Warmer temperatures increase snow's weight.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-11-21T01:10:58Z,[],774,"In story <DATE>Nov. 21</DATE> Buffalo snowstorms, <ORGANIZATION>The Associated Press</ORGANIZATION> reported erroneously warmer temperatures make snow heavier. Warmer temperatures increase snow's weight.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/11/21/us/ap-us-wintry-weather.html,546ed7b37988106ad45c68ff,null,"{main:Correction: Wintry Weather Story,print_headline:Correction: Wintry Weather Story}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Judge <ORGANIZATION>Colleen McMahon United States District Court Manhattan 1960s</ORGANIZATION> band Turtles rights recordings <ORGANIZATION>New York State</ORGANIZATION> law.,5,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Music},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Royalties},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Sirius <ORGANIZATION>XM Radio Inc<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Copyrights Copyright Violations},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Audio Recordings, Downloads Streaming},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:Turtles, The Music Group},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:7,value:<ORGANIZATION>Pandora Media Inc<\/ORGANIZATION>}]",Business Day,"Judge <ORGANIZATION>Colleen McMahon United States District Court Manhattan</ORGANIZATION> rules <ORGANIZATION>Sirius XM</ORGANIZATION> copyright case, <DATE>1960s</DATE> band Turtles royalty rights recordings <ORGANIZATION>New York State</ORGANIZATION> law; decision bolsters music industry's position recordings covered state laws.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-11-17T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/11/17/business/turtles/turtles-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/11/17/business/turtles/turtles-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/11/17/business/turtles/turtles-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:323},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/11/17/business/turtles/turtles-articleLarge.jpg,height:323},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/11/17/business/turtles/turtles-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/11/17/business/turtles/turtles-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",427,Judge <ORGANIZATION>Colleen McMahon United States District Court Manhattan 1960s</ORGANIZATION> band Turtles rights recordings <ORGANIZATION>New York State</ORGANIZATION> law.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/11/17/business/media/judge-rules-against-sirius-xm-on-royalties-in-suit-by-the-turtles.html,54692e8d7988101de50ec5ce,Media,"{main:Sirius XM Has Setback Lawsuit,print_headline:Sirius XM Has Setback Lawsuit}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>BEN SISARIO<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Ben,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SISARIO}]}",article
"<LOCATION>California</LOCATION>'s deepening drought shrinking rice harvest, bad news farmers, migratory birds sushi lovers.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-10-29T02:48:41Z,[],620,"<LOCATION>California</LOCATION>'s deepening drought shrinking rice harvest, bad news farmers, migratory birds sushi lovers.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/10/29/us/ap-us-california-drought-rice-harvest.html,54508e977988107738c7d65c,null,"{main:<LOCATION>California<\/LOCATION> Drought Takes Bite Out Rice Harvest,print_headline:<LOCATION>California<\/LOCATION> Drought Takes Bite Out Rice Harvest}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Paperback books interest.,32,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Books Literature}]",Books,null,The New York Times,[],BookReview,2014-10-26T00:00:00Z,[],490,Paperback books interest.,List,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/10/26/books/review/paperback-row.html,544a68ce79881005a1ef44f1,<DATE>Sunday</DATE> Book Review,"{main:Paperback Row,print_headline:Paperback Row}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>IHSAN TAYLOR<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Ihsan,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:TAYLOR}]}",article
"<LOCATION>Missouri</LOCATION> authorities drawing contingency plans seeking intelligence <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> police departments out-of-state agitators, fearing fresh riots erupt grand jury indict white officer killing black teen.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-10-07T14:09:52Z,[],1116,"<LOCATION>Missouri</LOCATION> authorities drawing contingency plans seeking intelligence <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> police departments out-of-state agitators, fearing fresh riots erupt grand jury indict white officer killing black teen.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/10/07/us/07reuters-usa-missouri-shooting-plans.html,54342d3f79881017f2d282fa,null,"{main:Exclusive: <LOCATION>Missouri<\/LOCATION> Police Plan Possible Riots Brown Cop Not Charged,print_headline:Exclusive: <LOCATION>Missouri<\/LOCATION> Police Plan Possible Riots Brown Cop Not Charged}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<PERSON>Maureen Stefanides</PERSON> wanted to fulfill her father’s request after long nursing home stays left him weak and unhappy, but the forces of the health care system seemed stacked against her.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Death Dying},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Elder Care},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Hospice Care},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Health Insurance Managed Care},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:5,value:Nursing Homes},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:6,value:Home Health Care},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:Medicaid},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:8,value:Medicare},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:9,value:Elderly}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,Institute Medicine report calls fundamental overhaul country's end-of-life care; highlights plight <PERSON>Maureen Stefanides</PERSON> unsuccessful struggle health care system fulfill father <PERSON>Joseph Andrey</PERSON>'s dearest die home.,The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-09-26T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/09/26/nyregion/SUBjpDYING2/SUBjpDYING2-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/09/26/nyregion/SUBjpDYING2/SUBjpDYING2-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/09/26/nyregion/SUBjpDYING2/SUBjpDYING2-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:337},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/09/26/nyregion/SUBjpDYING2/SUBjpDYING2-articleLarge.jpg,height:337},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/09/26/nyregion/SUBjpDYING2/SUBjpDYING2-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/09/26/nyregion/SUBjpDYING2/SUBjpDYING2-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",4912,"<PERSON>Maureen Stefanides</PERSON> wanted to fulfill her father’s request after long nursing home stays left him weak and unhappy, but the forces of the health care system seemed stacked against her.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/09/26/nyregion/family-fights-health-care-system-for-simple-request-to-die-at-home.html,5424c86f79881017ba4e8b51,null,"{main:Fighting to Honor a Father’s Last Wish: To Die at Home,print_headline:A Father’s Last Wish, and a Daughter’s Anguish}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>NINA BERNSTEIN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Nina,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BERNSTEIN}]}",article
"The ruling federal judge <LOCATION>California</LOCATION>, based state&#8217;s copyright laws, favor Turtles, &#8217;60s group sued copyright infringement.",3,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:Sirius <ORGANIZATION>XM Radio Inc<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Royalties},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Copyrights Copyright Violations},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Music},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:5,value:Audio Recordings, Downloads Streaming},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:Turtles, The Music Group}]",Business Day,"<ORGANIZATION>United States District Court Judge Philip S Gutierrez Los Angeles</ORGANIZATION> rules <ORGANIZATION>Sirius XM</ORGANIZATION> liable copyright infringement failing pay royalties recordings made <DATE>1972</DATE>; case, wide implications digital music business, filed <DATE>2013</DATE> members <DATE>1960s</DATE> band Turtles.",,[],Business,2014-09-24T00:00:00Z,[],603,"The ruling federal judge <LOCATION>California</LOCATION>, based state&#8217;s copyright laws, favor Turtles, &#8217;60s group sued copyright infringement.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/09/24/business/media/sirius-xm-loses-suit-on-royalties-for-oldies.html,542207f17988101d51328592,Media,"{main:Sirius <ORGANIZATION>XM<\/ORGANIZATION> Loses Lawsuit Royalties Oldies,print_headline:Sirius <ORGANIZATION>XM<\/ORGANIZATION> Loses Suit Royalties Oldies}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>BEN SISARIO<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Ben,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SISARIO}]}",article
"Nearly 60 years death, heard <PERSON>H.L. Mencken</PERSON>.",null,[],Arts,null,AP,[],null,2014-09-17T09:44:44Z,[],639,"Nearly 60 years death, heard <PERSON>H.L. Mencken</PERSON>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/09/17/arts/ap-us-books-menckens-days.html,541990927988106440c9a2d2,null,"{main:New Mencken Book Features Unpublished Material,print_headline:New Mencken Book Features Unpublished Material}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
