snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
We seasonal charitable giving put fig leaf ways passion cheap clothes toys contributes problems solve donations.,null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:Leonard, Annie},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:GoodGuide},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:Greenpeace},{name:organizations,rank:3,value:Heifer International},{name:organizations,rank:4,value:Oxfam},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Gifts},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Parenting},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Philanthropy}]",<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,We seasonal charitable giving put fig leaf ways passion cheap clothes toys contributes problems solve donations.,The New York Times,[],Styles,2014-12-22T09:40:37Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/19/us/motherlode-goat/motherlode-goat-thumbWide.png},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/19/us/motherlode-goat/motherlode-goat-thumbWide.png,height:126},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/19/us/motherlode-goat/motherlode-goat-thumbStandard.png,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/19/us/motherlode-goat/motherlode-goat-thumbStandard.png,height:75}]",910,null,Blog,http://parenting.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/22/read-this-before-you-buy-another-holiday-gift-or-goat/,54982dcc7988104a1e0df565,null,"{main:Read This Before You Buy Another Holiday Gift Goat,kicker:Motherlode}","{original:By <PERSON>CHRISTINE BADER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Christine,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BADER}]}",blogpost
"The site is a huge cultural force, but an unfulfilled economic one. <PERSON>Susan Wojcicki</PERSON>’s mission is to change that.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:YouTube.com},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Wojcicki<\/PERSON>, Susan},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Video Recordings, Downloads Streaming},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Web-Original Programming},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Online Advertising},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Computers Internet}]",Business Day,"Youtube achieved enormous success developing user base, billion people watching 300 million hours footage daily, largely failed monetize success; chief executive <PERSON>Susan Wojcicki</PERSON> undertaken mission confront problems deter heavy advertising investment site, avoid danger replaced newcomer.",The New York Times,[],SundayBusiness,2014-12-21T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/21/business/21-YOUTUBE/21-YOUTUBE-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/21/business/21-YOUTUBE/21-YOUTUBE-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/21/business/21-YOUTUBE/21-YOUTUBE-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:686},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/21/business/21-YOUTUBE/21-YOUTUBE-articleLarge.jpg,height:686},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/21/business/21-YOUTUBE/21-YOUTUBE-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/21/business/21-YOUTUBE/21-YOUTUBE-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",3480,"The site is a huge cultural force, but an unfulfilled economic one. <PERSON>Susan Wojcicki</PERSON>’s mission is to change that.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/21/business/youtubes-chief-hitting-a-new-play-button.html,5495b23b79881029b367dd95,null,"{main:YouTube’s Chief, Hitting a New ‘Play’ Button,print_headline:Hitting a New ‘Play’ Button}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>JONATHAN MAHLER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Jonathan,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:MAHLER}]}",article
The <LOCATION>Singapore</LOCATION> investor <ORGANIZATION>Temasek</ORGANIZATION> Chinese social network operator <ORGANIZATION>Tencent</ORGANIZATION> leaders fund-raising round company 10 times ridership Uber.,null,"[{name:organizations,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Didi Dache<\/PERSON>},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:DST Global Solutions},{name:organizations,rank:3,value:<ORGANIZATION>Temasek Holdings<\/ORGANIZATION>},{name:organizations,rank:4,value:<ORGANIZATION>Tencent Holdings Ltd<\/ORGANIZATION>},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Mobile Applications},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Taxicabs Taxicab Drivers},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Venture Capital}]",Business Day,The <LOCATION>Singapore</LOCATION> investor <ORGANIZATION>Temasek</ORGANIZATION> Chinese social network operator <ORGANIZATION>Tencent</ORGANIZATION> leaders fund-raising round company 10 times ridership Uber.,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-10T12:06:32Z,[],724,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/10/didi-dache-a-chinese-ride-hailing-app-raises-700-million/,54887dba7988104c174598c0,Dealbook,"{main:<PERSON>Didi Dache<\/PERSON>, a Chinese Ride-Hailing App, Raises <MONEY>$700 Million<\/MONEY>,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>ZHENG WU VANESSA PIAO<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Zheng,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:WU},{firstname:Vanessa,role:reported,organization:,rank:2,lastname:PIAO}]}",blogpost
"Microsoft shareholders gave a lukewarm vote of approval <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> for CEO <PERSON>Satya Nadella</PERSON>'s <MONEY>$84 million</MONEY> pay package, after an investor advisory group said the company was paying him too much.",null,[],Technology,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-03T13:50:22Z,[],681,"Microsoft shareholders gave a lukewarm vote of approval <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> for CEO <PERSON>Satya Nadella</PERSON>'s <MONEY>$84 million</MONEY> pay package, after an investor advisory group said the company was paying him too much.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/03/technology/ap-us-tec-microsoft-ceo-pay.html,547f5c217988105a33db535d,null,"{main:Microsoft Shareholders Approve <MONEY>$84 Million<\/MONEY> CEO Pay,print_headline:Microsoft Shareholders Approve <MONEY>$84 Million<\/MONEY> CEO Pay}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<LOCATION>China</LOCATION> banned private clubs historical buildings, parks public facilities hindering fight corruption, state media <DATE>Monday</DATE>, government broadens anti-graft frugality campaigns.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-10-27T05:32:20Z,[],251,"<LOCATION>China</LOCATION> banned private clubs historical buildings, parks public facilities hindering fight corruption, state media <DATE>Monday</DATE>, government broadens anti-graft frugality campaigns.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/10/27/world/asia/27reuters-china-corruption.html,544e118379881024bc777437,Asia Pacific,"{main:<LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION> Bans Private Clubs Parks, Historical Buildings Graft Crackdown,print_headline:<LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION> Bans Private Clubs Parks, Historical Buildings Graft Crackdown}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The <LOCATION>European Union</LOCATION> afford fiscal belt-tightening halt investment needed spur slowing economies, <LOCATION>Austria</LOCATION>'s leader <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>, setting clash <LOCATION>Brussels Austria</LOCATION>'s <DATE>2015</DATE> budget deficit target.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-10-21T06:47:24Z,[],401,"The <LOCATION>European Union</LOCATION> afford fiscal belt-tightening halt investment needed spur slowing economies, <LOCATION>Austria</LOCATION>'s leader <DATE>Tuesday</DATE>, setting clash <LOCATION>Brussels Austria</LOCATION>'s <DATE>2015</DATE> budget deficit target.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/10/21/business/21reuters-eurozone-economy-austria.html,54463a5a798810347c1a9539,null,"{main:<ORGANIZATION>EU<\/ORGANIZATION> Can't Let Austerity Override Investment-Austria's Faymann,print_headline:<ORGANIZATION>EU<\/ORGANIZATION> Can't Let Austerity Override Investment-Austria's Faymann}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
Republicans waging take-no-prisoners battle boot Democrats GOP property: seats <ORGANIZATION>House</ORGANIZATION> districts presidential nominee Mitt Romney carried <DATE>2012</DATE>.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-10-18T03:52:24Z,[],868,Republicans waging take-no-prisoners battle boot Democrats GOP property: seats <ORGANIZATION>House</ORGANIZATION> districts presidential nominee Mitt Romney carried <DATE>2012</DATE>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/10/18/us/politics/ap-us-house-democrats-romney-districts.html,54421c5c7988107a7b7f610d,Politics,"{main:GOP Targets Dem House Districts That Backed Romney,print_headline:GOP Targets Dem House Districts That Backed Romney}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<LOCATION>Amazon</LOCATION>’s accomplishments are dwarfed only by its ambitions. A former executive talks about the potential and the perils as the retailer enters its third decade, as well as why the dispute with <ORGANIZATION>Hachette</ORGANIZATION> is so important.",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Bezos<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Jeffrey<\/PERSON> P},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:Alvarez & Marsal},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:Amazon.com Inc},{name:organizations,rank:3,value:Hachette Book Group},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Book Trade Publishing},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Books Literature},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Shopping Retail},{name:subject,rank:4,value:Work-Life Balance}]",Technology,"<LOCATION>Amazon</LOCATION>’s accomplishments are dwarfed only by its ambitions. A former executive talks about the potential and the perils as the retailer enters its third decade, as well as why the dispute with <ORGANIZATION>Hachette</ORGANIZATION> is so important.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-09-26T07:27:11Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/09/26/technology/26bits-amazonqanda-pic2/26bits-amazonqanda-pic2-thumbWide-v2.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/09/26/technology/26bits-amazonqanda-pic2/26bits-amazonqanda-pic2-thumbWide-v2.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/09/26/technology/26bits-amazonqanda-pic2/26bits-amazonqanda-pic2-articleLarge-v2.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:393},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/09/26/technology/26bits-amazonqanda-pic2/26bits-amazonqanda-pic2-articleLarge-v2.jpg,height:393},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/09/26/technology/26bits-amazonqanda-pic2/26bits-amazonqanda-pic2-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/09/26/technology/26bits-amazonqanda-pic2/26bits-amazonqanda-pic2-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1009,null,Blog,http://bits.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/09/26/examining-the-amazon-way/,54254e1c79881017ba4e8ceb,null,"{main:Examining Amazon Way,print_headline:A Closer Look Ways <LOCATION>Amazon<\/LOCATION>,kicker:Bits}","{original:By <PERSON>DAVID STREITFELD<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:David,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:STREITFELD}]}",blogpost
"The Democrat running <LOCATION>Wisconsin</LOCATION> governor acknowledges campaign lifted policy platforms, including exact language, like-minded candidates.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,,[],null,2014-09-22T14:17:07Z,[],801,"The Democrat running <LOCATION>Wisconsin</LOCATION> governor acknowledges campaign lifted policy platforms, including exact language, like-minded candidates.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/09/22/us/politics/ap-us-governor-wisconsin.html,542068867988104c4a5010ab,Politics,"{main:Campaigns Commonly Share Policy Platforms, Slogans,print_headline:Campaigns Commonly Share Policy Platforms, Slogans}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Visitors at <PERSON>Jane Austen</PERSON>’s <ORGANIZATION>House Museum</ORGANIZATION> in <LOCATION>Chawton</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Hampshire</LOCATION>, can see the 11 booklets that formed “The Watsons,” a novel <PERSON>Austen</PERSON> abandoned, as well as a needle case and other domestic tools belonging to the writer.",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Austen<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Jane<\/PERSON>},{name:glocations,rank:1,value:Hampshire England},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Austen<\/PERSON>'s, <PERSON>Jane<\/PERSON>, <ORGANIZATION>House<\/ORGANIZATION> Museum <LOCATION>Chawton<\/LOCATION>, <LOCATION>England<\/LOCATION>},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:Bodleian Libraries},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Books Literature},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Manuscripts},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Writing Writers}]",Arts,"Visitors at <PERSON>Jane Austen</PERSON>’s <ORGANIZATION>House Museum</ORGANIZATION> in <LOCATION>Chawton</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Hampshire</LOCATION>, can see the 11 booklets that formed “The Watsons,” a novel <PERSON>Austen</PERSON> abandoned, as well as a needle case and other domestic tools belonging to the writer.",The New York Times,[],Culture,2014-09-19T13:00:41Z,[],302,null,Blog,http://artsbeat.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/09/19/rare-jane-austen-manuscript-goes-on-exhibit/,541c617679881060032a2176,null,"{main:Rare <PERSON>Jane Austen<\/PERSON> Manuscript Goes Exhibit,print_headline:Rare Austen Manuscript Goes Display,kicker:ArtsBeat}","{original:By <PERSON>JENNIFER SCHUESSLER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Jennifer,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SCHUESSLER}]}",blogpost
