snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"A.ready, series unrelated policy decisions reduced ability track family change <LOCATION>America</LOCATION>.",null,"[{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:1,value:Census Bureau},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Marriages},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Divorce, Separations Annulments},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Statistics},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Social Conditions Trends},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Families Family Life},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:7,value:United States}]",The Upshot,null,The New York Times,[],Upshot,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/07/upshot/01UP-Divorce/01UP-Divorce-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/07/upshot/01UP-Divorce/01UP-Divorce-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/07/upshot/01UP-Divorce/01UP-Divorce-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:399},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/07/upshot/01UP-Divorce/01UP-Divorce-articleLarge.jpg,height:399},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/07/upshot/01UP-Divorce/01UP-Divorce-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/07/upshot/01UP-Divorce/01UP-Divorce-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1418,"Already, series unrelated policy decisions reduced ability track family change <LOCATION>America</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/upshot/census-bureaus-plan-to-cut-marriage-and-divorce-questions-has-academics-up-in-arms.html,54a420057988102761d6e4bc,null,"{content_kicker:Vanishing Data,main:Census Bureau’s Plan to Cut Marriage and Divorce Questions Has Academics Up in Arms,kicker:The Upshot}","{original:By <PERSON>JUSTIN WOLFERS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Justin,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:WO.FERS}]}",article
Two Albanian seamen killed <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> salvage operation car ferry caught fire <LOCATION>Greece</LOCATION>'s <LOCATION>Adriatic Coast</LOCATION> days ago voyage <LOCATION>Italy</LOCATION>.,null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T11:03:13Z,[],509,Two Albanian seamen killed <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> salvage operation car ferry caught fire <LOCATION>Greece</LOCATION>'s <LOCATION>Adriatic Coast</LOCATION> days ago voyage <LOCATION>Italy</LOCATION>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/world/europe/30reuters-greece-ship.html,54a2ccf87988104803cc8ada,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:<LOCATION>Italy<\/LOCATION> Warns Ferry Fire Death Toll Could Rise, Two Killed Salvage,print_headline:<LOCATION>Italy<\/LOCATION> Warns Ferry Fire Death Toll Could Rise, Two Killed Salvage}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<PERSON>Tex G. Hall</PERSON>, tribal chief connected oil industry, pushed profits <ORGANIZATION>Fort Berthold Reservation</ORGANIZATION>. But accusations corruption murder hire upended business usual.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Oil Petroleum Gasoline},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:11,value:<LOCATION>North Dakota<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:12,value:Creveling, <PERSON>Sarah<\/PERSON> M <DATE>1986<\/DATE>-},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:13,value:<PERSON>Clarke<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Kristopher David<\/PERSON> <DATE>1983<\/DATE>-},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:14,value:<PERSON>Carlile<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Douglas<\/PERSON> 1950-2013},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:15,value:<LOCATION>Mandan<\/LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Hidatsa<\/LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Arikara<\/LOCATION> Nation},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:16,value:Corruption Institutional},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:2,value:Fort Berthold Indian Reservation ND},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:Hall, Tex G},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Murders, Attempted Murders Homicides},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:5,value:<PERSON>Henrikson<\/PERSON>, James <DATE>1979<\/DATE>-},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:6,value:Hydraulic Fracturing},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:7,value:Series},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:8,value:Native Americans},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:9,value:Bakken Shale Field ND},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:10,value:Spokane Wash}]",<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,"Tenure <PERSON>Tex G Hall</PERSON>, tribal chief <ORGANIZATION>Fort Berthold Indian Reservation North Dakota</ORGANIZATION> pushed rapid development oil terms chief, upended allegations corruption murder; <PERSON>Hall</PERSON> close relationship <PERSON>James Henrikson</PERSON>, man charged murdering <PERSON>Douglas Carlile Kristopher Clarke</PERSON> due events related reservation's oil industry, investigation laid bare concerns hydraulic fracturing boom effects environment Series: Black-Gold Rush.",The New York Times,[],National,2014-12-29T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/28/us/ndakota3-slide-show-slide-L8U0/ndakota3-slide-show-slide-L8U0-thumbWide-v3.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/us/ndakota3-slide-show-slide-L8U0/ndakota3-slide-show-slide-L8U0-thumbWide-v3.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/28/us/ndakota3-slide-show-slide-L8U0/ndakota3-slide-show-slide-L8U0-articleLarge-v2.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:367},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/us/ndakota3-slide-show-slide-L8U0/ndakota3-slide-show-slide-L8U0-articleLarge-v2.jpg,height:367},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/28/us/ndakota3-slide-show-slide-L8U0/ndakota3-slide-show-slide-L8U0-thumbStandard-v3.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/us/ndakota3-slide-show-slide-L8U0/ndakota3-slide-show-slide-L8U0-thumbStandard-v3.jpg,height:75}]",4615,"<PERSON>Tex G. Hall</PERSON>, tribal chief connected oil industry, pushed profits <ORGANIZATION>Fort Berthold Reservation</ORGANIZATION>. But accusations corruption murder hire upended business usual.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/29/us/in-north-dakota-where-oil-corruption-and-bodies-surface.html,54a0d4d97988101f98e3eee0,null,"{main:In <LOCATION>North Dakota<\/LOCATION>, Tale Oil, Corruption Death,print_headline:Where Oil, Corruption Bodies Surface}","{contributor:<PERSON>Robert Gebeloff<\/PERSON> contributed reporting <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION>.,original:By <PERSON>DEBORAH SONTAG<\/PERSON> BRENT McDONALD,person:[{firstname:Deborah,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SONTAG},{firstname:Brent,role:reported,organization:,rank:2,lastname:McDONALD}]}",article
"<LOCATION>Saudi Arabia</LOCATION>'s <DATE>2015</DATE> state budget assumes an oil price close to current levels of around <MONEY>$60</MONEY> &#163;38.56 a barrel for Brent crude &lt;LCOC1&gt;, a shift from past budgets which were based on prices well below market levels, analysts say.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-28T05:34:06Z,[],651,"<LOCATION>Saudi Arabia</LOCATION>'s <DATE>2015</DATE> state budget assumes an oil price close to current levels of around <MONEY>$60</MONEY> &#163;38.56 a barrel for Brent crude &lt;LCOC1&gt;, a shift from past budgets which were based on prices well below market levels, analysts say.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/28/business/28reuters-saudi-budget.html,549fdd1679881001534d2081,null,"{main:Saudi <DATE>2015<\/DATE> Budget Based on Oil Price Around <MONEY>$60-Analysts<\/MONEY>,print_headline:Saudi <DATE>2015<\/DATE> Budget Based on Oil Price Around <MONEY>$60-Analysts<\/MONEY>}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"In <LOCATION>Vancouver</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Wash.</LOCATION>, proposed terminal oil shipments led city environmental groups push builder quickly finish competing waterfront real estate project.",20,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Real Estate Housing Residential},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Real Estate Commercial},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Oil Petroleum Gasoline},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:4,value:<LOCATION>Columbia River Pacific Northwest<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:5,value:<LOCATION>Washington<\/LOCATION> State},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Oil Spills},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:Area Planning Renewal},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:8,value:Vancouver Wash}]",<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,"City officials and environmental groups in <LOCATION>Vancouver</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Wash</LOCATION>, are pushing for builders to complete <MONEY>$1.3 billion</MONEY> real estate project called the Waterfront in effort to block proposed oil terminal planned nearby along <LOCATION>Columbia River</LOCATION>; are hoping that presence of residences and businesses so close to terminal, where trains would take 360,000 barrels a day, is likely to threaten its approval as it undergoes environmental review.",The New York Times,[],National,2014-12-28T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/28/us/RAIL/RAIL-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/us/RAIL/RAIL-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/28/us/RAIL/RAIL-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:449},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/us/RAIL/RAIL-articleLarge.jpg,height:449},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/28/us/RAIL/RAIL-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/us/RAIL/RAIL-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1263,"In <LOCATION>Vancouver</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Wash.</LOCATION>, proposed terminal oil shipments led city environmental groups push builder quickly finish competing waterfront real estate project.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/us/race-to-build-on-river-could-block-pacific-oil-route.html,549f353579881001534d1fae,null,"{main:Race Build River Could Block Pacific Oil Route,print_headline:Race Build River Could Block Pacific Oil Route}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>KIRK JOHNSON<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Kirk,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:JOHNSON}]}",article
"Questions answers file return year, time taxpayers report health care status I.R.S.",2,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Tax Preparers Preparation},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Tax Credits, Deductions Exemptions},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Health Insurance Managed Care},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Patient Protection Affordable Care Act 2010},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Income Tax},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:Internal Revenue Service}]",Your Money,Questions answers taxpayers bought health care health insurance exchange report health care status tax returns.,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-26T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/26/business/PenaltyQA/PenaltyQA-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/business/PenaltyQA/PenaltyQA-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/26/business/PenaltyQA/PenaltyQA-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/business/PenaltyQA/PenaltyQA-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/<ORGANIZATION>26/business/PenaltyQA/PenaltyQA-thumbStandard<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/<ORGANIZATION>26/business/PenaltyQA/PenaltyQA-thumbStandard<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg,height:75}]",1296,"Questions answers file return year, time taxpayers report health care status I.R.S.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/26/your-money/how-affordable-care-act-rules-affect-your-taxes.html,549cb9cb7988103babf08ab0,null,"{content_kicker:Q. A.,main:How Affordable Care Act Rules Affect Your Taxes,print_headline:The New Health Care Rules Taxes,kicker:Q. A.}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>TARA SIEGEL BERNARD<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Tara,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Siegel,rank:1,lastname:BERNARD}]}",article
Readers respond column Mark Bittman problems face.,26,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Income Inequality},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Demonstrations, Protests Riots},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Police Brutality, Misconduct Shootings},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Federal Budget US}]",Opinion,null,The New York Times,[],Letters,2014-12-26T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/26/opinion/26LETTERSbittman2/26LETTERSbittman2-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/opinion/26LETTERSbittman2/26LETTERSbittman2-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/26/opinion/26LETTERSbittman2/26LETTERSbittman2-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:762},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/opinion/26LETTERSbittman2/26LETTERSbittman2-articleLarge.jpg,height:762},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/26/opinion/26LETTERSbittman2/26LETTERSbittman2-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/opinion/26LETTERSbittman2/26LETTERSbittman2-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",689,Readers respond column Mark Bittman problems face.,Letter,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/26/opinion/fixing-whats-wrong-with-america.html,549c94bd7988103babf08a6c,null,"{content_kicker:Letters,main:Fixing What&#8217;s Wrong With <LOCATION>America<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:Fixing What’s Wrong With <LOCATION>America<\/LOCATION>,kicker:Letters}",[],article
"<PERSON>Ava DuVernay</PERSON>&#8217;s film &#8220;<LOCATION>Selma</LOCATION>&#8221; civil rights demonstrators <DATE>March 1965</DATE> Alabama bridge era black Americans, progress made promises unkept.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Movies},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:DuVernay, Ava},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Oyelowo<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>David<\/PERSON>},{is_major:Y,name:creative_works,rank:4,value:Selma Movie}]",Movies,"A O Scott reviews movie <LOCATION>Selma</LOCATION>, directed <PERSON>Ava DuVernay</PERSON> starring <PERSON>David Oyelowo</PERSON>.",The New York Times,[],Culture,2014-12-25T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/25/arts/SELMA/SELMA-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/arts/SELMA/SELMA-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/25/arts/SELMA/SELMA-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:382},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/arts/SELMA/SELMA-articleLarge.jpg,height:382},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/25/arts/SELMA/SELMA-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/arts/SELMA/SELMA-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1370,"<PERSON>Ava DuVernay</PERSON>&#8217;s film &#8220;<LOCATION>Selma</LOCATION>&#8221; civil rights demonstrators <DATE>March 1965</DATE> Alabama bridge era black Americans, progress made promises unkept.",Review,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/25/arts/in-selma-king-is-just-one-of-the-heroes.html,549a95b17988102d96d567c8,null,"{content_kicker:Movie Review,main:A 50-Mile <DATE>March<\/DATE>, Nearly 50 Years Later,seo:In &#8216;<LOCATION>Selma<\/LOCATION>,&#8217; King Is Just One Many Heroes,print_headline:A 50-Mile <DATE>March<\/DATE>, Nearly 50 Years Later,kicker:Movie Review | '<LOCATION>Selma<\/LOCATION>'| 'Selma'}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>A. O. SCOTT<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:A.,role:reported,organization:,middlename:O.,rank:1,lastname:SCOTT}]}",article
<LOCATION>Indianapolis</LOCATION> quarterback Andrew Luck sensational fantasy leagues year &#8212; top scorer standard formats consistent passer. Just point fantasy players title game week...,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-24T18:12:19Z,[],742,<LOCATION>Indianapolis</LOCATION> quarterback Andrew Luck sensational fantasy leagues year &#8212; top scorer standard formats consistent passer. Just point fantasy players title game week watched put points.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/24/sports/football/ap-fbn-fantasy-football.html,549b48ee7988100306690f19,Pro Football,"{main:FANTASY PLAYS: Lessons From 2014 Fantasy Season,print_headline:FANTASY PLAYS: Lessons From 2014 Fantasy Season}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"New players <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s shadow banking sector growing rapidly attempts clamp opaque lending, taking advantage regulatory anomaly prosper raising risks build-up debt slowing economy.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-22T16:11:47Z,[],822,"New players <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s shadow banking sector growing rapidly attempts clamp opaque lending, taking advantage regulatory anomaly prosper raising risks build-up debt slowing economy.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/22/business/22reuters-china-economy-shadowbanking.html,54988985798810035238e5fb,null,"{main:<LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION>'s Shadow Banking Adapts Grows Rules Tighten,print_headline:<LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION>'s Shadow Banking Adapts Grows Rules Tighten}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
