snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"The owner <PERSON>McNally Jackson</PERSON> Books <LOCATION>Manhattan</LOCATION> steady income, began seven-day delivery The Times.",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:McNally, <PERSON>Sarah<\/PERSON>}]",null,"The owner <PERSON>McNally Jackson</PERSON> Books <LOCATION>Manhattan</LOCATION> steady income, began seven-day delivery The Times.",The New York Times,[],null,2014-11-19T17:09:02Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/11/19/blogs/sarah/sarah-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/11/19/blogs/sarah/sarah-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/11/19/blogs/sarah/sarah-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/11/19/blogs/sarah/sarah-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",689,null,Blog,http://www.nytimes.com/times-insider/2014/11/19/reading-the-times-with-sarah-mcnally/,546d151979881016298c7794,null,"{main:Reading The Times With <PERSON>Sarah McNally<\/PERSON>,kicker:Times Insider}","{original:By <PERSON>SUSAN LEHMAN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Susan,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:LEHMAN}]}",blogpost
Lamenting the loss of a favorite spot you haven’t visited in a decade.,1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Small Business},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>New York City<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Gentrification},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Music},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:5,value:Swift, Taylor}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"<LOCATION>Ginia Bellafante Big City</LOCATION> column holds residents <LOCATION>New York City</LOCATION> blame demise cherished city institutions spread sameness, financially supported local small businesses.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-11-02T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/11/02/nyregion/02BIG/02BIG-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/11/02/nyregion/02BIG/02BIG-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/11/02/nyregion/02BIG/02BIG-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:396},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/11/02/nyregion/02BIG/02BIG-articleLarge.jpg,height:396},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/11/02/nyregion/02BIG/02BIG-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/11/02/nyregion/02BIG/02BIG-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",946,Lamenting the loss of a favorite spot you haven’t visited in a decade.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/11/02/nyregion/its-taylor-swifts-city-now.html,5453ec1c7988106136a8acf7,null,"{content_kicker:Big City,main: It&#8217;s Taylor Swift&#8217;s City Now,print_headline:It’s Taylor Swift’s City Now,kicker:Big City}","{contributor:,original:By GINIA BELLAFANTE,person:[{firstname:Ginia,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BELLAFANTE}]}",article
"<ORGANIZATION>American Express Co</ORGANIZATION>, world's largest credit card issuer, reported <PERCENT>8.1 percent</PERCENT> rise quarterly profit due higher spending <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> customers credit cards rise net interest income.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-10-15T16:18:19Z,[],287,"<ORGANIZATION>American Express Co</ORGANIZATION>, world's largest credit card issuer, reported <PERCENT>8.1 percent</PERCENT> rise quarterly profit due higher spending <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> customers credit cards rise net interest income.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/10/15/business/15reuters-americanexpress-results.html,543ed88d79881001751bf64b,null,"{main:AmEx Quarterly Profit Rises <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Card Holders Spend More,print_headline:AmEx Quarterly Profit Rises <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Card Holders Spend More}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"After asking <ORGANIZATION>Comcast</ORGANIZATION> about a customer’s billing issue, the Haggler got a quick answer — and a rare look at a corporate attempt, called <PERSON>Einstein</PERSON>, to fix a systemic problem.",5,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:<ORGANIZATION>Comcast<\/ORGANIZATION> Corporation},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Cable Television},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Customer Relations},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Prices Fares, Fees Rates}]",Your Money,"<PERSON>David Segal</PERSON> The Haggler column relates outcome billing dispute <ORGANIZATION>Comcast</ORGANIZATION>, noting rare instance company made concerted effort address systemic problem; observes company installing customer service system, called <PERSON>Einstein</PERSON>, aimed reducing replication errors.",The New York Times,[],SundayBusiness,2014-10-12T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/10/12/business/12-HAGGLER/12-HAGGLER-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/10/12/business/12-HAGGLER/12-HAGGLER-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/10/12/business/12-HAGGLER/12-HAGGLER-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:550},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/10/12/business/12-HAGGLER/12-HAGGLER-articleLarge.jpg,height:550},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/10/12/business/12-HAGGLER/12-HAGGLER-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/10/12/business/12-HAGGLER/12-HAGGLER-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",952,"After asking <ORGANIZATION>Comcast</ORGANIZATION> about a customer’s billing issue, the Haggler got a quick answer — and a rare look at a corporate attempt, called <PERSON>Einstein</PERSON>, to fix a systemic problem.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/10/12/your-money/when-a-company-doesnt-sound-like-a-broken-record.html,54393a7c7988104fa3cb20e3,null,"{content_kicker:The Haggler,main:When a Company Doesn’t Sound Like a Broken Record,print_headline:When a Company Doesn’t Sound Like a Broken Record,kicker:The Haggler}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>DAVID SEGAL<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:David,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SEGAL}]}",article
Even researchers psychology credit card admit don&#8217;t cash debit cards.,1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Credit Cards},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Personal Finances}]",Your Money,<PERSON>Ron Lieber</PERSON> Your Money column contends biggest threat people's financial lives thieves fact people credit cards often; notes researchers psychology credit card admit overuse credit cards.,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-10-11T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/10/11/your-money/11money-illo1/11money-illo1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/10/11/your-money/11money-illo1/11money-illo1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/10/11/your-money/11money-illo1/11money-illo1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:813},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/10/11/your-money/11money-illo1/11money-illo1-articleLarge.jpg,height:813},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/10/11/your-money/11money-illo1/11money-illo1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/10/11/your-money/11money-illo1/11money-illo1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1442,Even researchers psychology credit card admit don&#8217;t cash debit cards.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/10/11/your-money/the-slippery-plastic-slope-to-overspending.html,5438241f7988104fa3cb1b15,null,"{content_kicker:Your Money,main:The Most Serious Threat When Using Credit: You,print_headline:The Most Serious Threat When Using Credit: You,kicker:Your Money}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>RON LIEBER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Ron,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:LIEBER}]}",article
"<ORGANIZATION>PayPal</ORGANIZATION>, <ORGANIZATION>Apple</ORGANIZATION> betting billions mobile payments.",null,[],Technology,null,AP,[],null,2014-10-01T15:51:35Z,[],960,"<ORGANIZATION>PayPal</ORGANIZATION>, <ORGANIZATION>Apple</ORGANIZATION> betting billions mobile payments.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/10/01/technology/ap-us-tec-digital-life-review-mobile-payments.html,542c5b857988105a9b09f6cd,null,"{main:Review: Pay Phone Just Keep Using Plastic??,print_headline:Review: Pay Phone Just Keep Using Plastic??}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"All takes blood, sweat selfies.",44,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Video Recordings, Downloads Streaming},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Music},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Social Media},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Advertising Marketing},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:5,value:theAudience},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:Instagram Inc},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:7,value:Vine Labs Inc},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:8,value:YouTube.com},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:9,value:Chainsmokers Music Group},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:10,value:<PERSON>Luckett<\/PERSON>, Oliver}]",Magazine,"Taffy Brodesser-Akner article examines social-media publishing company theAudience turned social media celebrities clear A-list Hollywood celebrities reluctant sign on; notes bulk company's revenue so-called Influencers, people popular social media platforms.",The New York Times,[],Magazine,2014-09-21T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/09/21/magazine/21audience_ss-slide-ZEDM/21audience_ss-slide-ZEDM-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/09/21/magazine/21audience_ss-slide-ZEDM/21audience_ss-slide-ZEDM-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/09/21/magazine/21audience_ss-slide-ZEDM/21audience_ss-slide-ZEDM-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/09/21/magazine/21audience_ss-slide-ZEDM/21audience_ss-slide-ZEDM-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/09/21/magazine/21audience_ss-slide-ZEDM/21audience_ss-slide-ZEDM-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/09/21/magazine/21audience_ss-slide-ZEDM/21audience_ss-slide-ZEDM-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",3407,"All takes blood, sweat selfies.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/09/21/magazine/turning-microcelebrity-into-a-big-business.html,541c39f97988100a1c660ef2,null,"{main:Turning Microcelebrity Into Big Business,print_headline:The Influencers}","{contributor:,original:By TAFFY BRODESSER-AKNER,person:[{firstname:Taffy,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BRODESSER-AKNER}]}",article
<ORGANIZATION>American Express Co</ORGANIZATION> reported <PERCENT>9 percent</PERCENT> rise <DATE>second-quarter</DATE> profit customers credit cards recovering <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> economy.,null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],null,2014-07-29T16:33:50Z,[],388,<ORGANIZATION>American Express Co</ORGANIZATION> reported <PERCENT>9 percent</PERCENT> rise <DATE>second-quarter</DATE> profit customers credit cards recovering <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> economy.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/07/29/business/29reuters-americanexpress-results.html,53d805eb7988102d7f3ebd4e,null,"{main:AmEx Profit Rises 9 Percent Card Holders Spend More,print_headline:AmEx Profit Rises 9 Percent Card Holders Spend More}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Twitter Facebook, fighting attention social media users advertisers, announced baby steps world e-commerce <DATE>Thursday</DATE>.",null,"[{name:organizations,rank:2,value:Facebook Inc},{name:organizations,rank:3,value:Twitter},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:CardSpring Inc},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Social Media},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Mergers, Acquisitions Divestitures},{name:subject,rank:1,value:E-Commerce}]",Technology,"Twitter Facebook, fighting attention social media users advertisers, announced baby steps world e-commerce <DATE>Thursday</DATE>.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-07-17T18:19:20Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/07/17/technology/17bits-fb/17bits-fb-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/07/17/technology/17bits-fb/17bits-fb-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/07/17/technology/17bits-fb/17bits-fb-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/07/17/technology/17bits-fb/17bits-fb-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",506,null,Blog,http://bits.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/07/17/coming-soon-to-social-media-click-to-buy-now/,53c84c407988102406602966,null,"{main:Coming Soon Social Media: Click Buy Now,print_headline:,kicker:Bits}","{original:By <PERSON>VINDU GOEL<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Vindu,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:GOEL}]}",blogpost
"<ORGANIZATION>American Express Co</ORGANIZATION> hindered price competition <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> credit card market prevented merchants consumers reaping cost savings, lawyer <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> government <DATE>Monday</DATE> day trial <LOCATION>Brooklyn</LOCATION> federal...",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],null,2014-07-07T15:00:45Z,[],467,"<ORGANIZATION>American Express Co</ORGANIZATION> hindered price competition <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> credit card market prevented merchants consumers reaping cost savings, lawyer <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> government <DATE>Monday</DATE> day trial <LOCATION>Brooklyn</LOCATION> federal court.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/07/07/business/07reuters-usa-antirust-amex.html,53baeeb77988107605eefb1e,null,"{main:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION>, Amex Duel Antitrust Trial Over Credit Card Fees,print_headline:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION>, Amex Duel Antitrust Trial Over Credit Card Fees}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
