snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Smugglers bring migrants <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION> sea adopted, dangerous tactic: cramming hundreds large cargo ship, setting automated crash coast, abandoning helm.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T18:17:23Z,[],782,"Smugglers bring migrants <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION> sea adopted, dangerous tactic: cramming hundreds large cargo ship, setting automated crash coast, abandoning helm.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/world/europe/ap-eu-italy-migrants-stranded-at-sea.html,54a5d6057988102023c94df5,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:New Tactic: Smugglers Put Ships Autopilot,print_headline:New Tactic: Smugglers Put Ships Autopilot}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"The destroyer <PERSON>Sampson</PERSON> dispatched Flight 8501 search area expanded 60,000 square miles.",6,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Aviation Accidents, Safety Disasters},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:3,value:<LOCATION>Indonesia<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Airlines Airplanes}]",World,"<LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> destroyer <PERSON>Sampson</PERSON> join search missing <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501, <LOCATION>Indonesia</LOCATION> expands search area <LOCATION>Java</LOCATION> Sea 60,000 miles.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-30T00:00:00Z,[],1115,"The destroyer <PERSON>Sampson</PERSON> dispatched Flight 8501 search area expanded 60,000 square miles.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/world/asia/airasia-8501-jet-missing-indonesia.html,54a145547988101f98e3ef86,Asia Pacific,"{main:Search <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Jet Widens Receives Assistance From <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Warship,print_headline:Search <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Jet Widens Receives Assistance From <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Warship}","{contributor:Reporting contributed <PERSON>Jeffrey Hutton Surabaya<\/PERSON>, <LOCATION>Indonesia<\/LOCATION>; <LOCATION>Austin Ramzy Hong Kong<\/LOCATION>; <PERSON>Nicola Clark<\/PERSON> <LOCATION>Paris<\/LOCATION>; <PERSON>Christopher Drew<\/PERSON> <LOCATION>Washington<\/LOCATION>; <PERSON>Poypiti Amatatham Muktita Suhartono Bangkok<\/PERSON>.,original:By <PERSON>THOMAS FULLER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Thomas,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:FULLER}]}",article
"The Australian Malaysian governments ships scouring <ORGANIZATION>Indian Ocean Malaysia Airlines</ORGANIZATION> Flight 370, disappeared <DATE>March 8</DATE>.",8,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:<ORGANIZATION>Malaysia Airlines<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight 370},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Aviation Accidents, Safety Disasters},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:5,value:<LOCATION>Malaysia<\/LOCATION> Airlines}]",World,"Australian Malaysian governments ships searching <ORGANIZATION>Malaysia Airlines</ORGANIZATION> Flight 370, vanished Indian Ocean <DATE>March 8</DATE> 239 passengers crew aboard.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-29T00:00:00Z,[],554,"The Australian Malaysian governments ships scouring <ORGANIZATION>Indian Ocean Malaysia Airlines</ORGANIZATION> Flight 370, disappeared <DATE>March 8</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/29/world/asia/aviation-mystery-of-malaysia-airlines-flight-370-remains-unsolved.html,54a0b88b7988101f98e3ee84,Asia Pacific,"{main:In Shadow New Search, Long Aviation Mystery Remains Unsolved,print_headline:In Shadow New Search, Long Aviation Mystery Remains Unsolved}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>KEITH BRADSHER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Keith,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BRADSHER}]}",article
<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501 disappeared part world <ORGANIZATION>Malaysia Airlines</ORGANIZATION> Flight 370 differs important ways.,null,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Aviation Accidents, Safety Disasters},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:<ORGANIZATION>Malaysia Airlines<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight 370},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501}]",World,null,The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-29T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/29/world/29plane/29plane-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/world/29plane/29plane-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/29/world/29plane/29plane-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/world/29plane/29plane-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/29/world/29plane/29plane-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/world/29plane/29plane-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",961,<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501 disappeared part world <ORGANIZATION>Malaysia Airlines</ORGANIZATION> Flight 370 differs important ways.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/29/world/asia/questions-about-flight-8501.html,54a067057988101f98e3edfd,Asia Pacific,"{main:Two Flights Go Missing, Their Stories Are Not Same,seo:The Facts <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>NICOLA CLARK<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Nicola,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:CLARK}]}",article
Hundreds New Englanders sounding alarm <ORGANIZATION>Coast Guard</ORGANIZATION> plan convert old-style foghorns technology.,null,[],Business Day,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-28T10:02:48Z,[],129,Hundreds New Englanders sounding alarm <ORGANIZATION>Coast Guard</ORGANIZATION> plan convert old-style foghorns technology.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/28/business/ap-us-fading-foghorns.html,54a01c6279881001534d20ac,null,"{main:Residents Alarmed Coast Guard Changes Foghorns,print_headline:Residents Alarmed Coast Guard Changes Foghorns}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"New books technology experts examine consumer-ranking techniques widespread, offer advice people protect.",3,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Credit Scores},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Books Literature},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Privacy},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Data-Mining Database Marketing},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:5,value:<PERSON>Fertik<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Michael<\/PERSON>},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:6,value:Pasquale, Frank},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:7,value:<PERSON>Thompson<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>David<\/PERSON> C <DATE>1979<\/DATE>-},{is_major:N,name:creative_works,rank:8,value:The Black Box Society: The Secret Algorithms That Control Money Information Book},{is_major:N,name:creative_works,rank:9,value:The Reputation Economy: How Optimize Your Digital Footprint A World Where Your Reputation Is Your Most Valuable Asset Book}]",Technology,Natasha Singer Technophobia column cites nonfiction books reveal companies secretly rank score consumers; notes The Reputation Economy: How Optimize Your Digital Footprint A World Where Your Reputation Is Your Most Valuable Asset <PERSON>Michael Fertik David Thompson</PERSON> The Black Box Society: The <ORGANIZATION>Secret Algorithms That Control Money Information Frank Pasquale</ORGANIZATION> differ substantially advising people protect.,The New York Times,[],SundayBusiness,2014-12-28T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/28/business/28-TECHNO/28-TECHNO-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/business/28-TECHNO/28-TECHNO-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/28/business/28-TECHNO/28-TECHNO-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:412},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/business/28-TECHNO/28-TECHNO-articleLarge.jpg,height:412},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/28/business/28-TECHNO/28-TECHNO-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/business/28-TECHNO/28-TECHNO-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1033,"New books technology experts examine consumer-ranking techniques widespread, offer advice people protect.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/technology/the-scoreboards-where-you-cant-see-your-score.html,549ecfcf7988105ced788713,null,"{content_kicker:Technophoria,main:The Scoreboards Where You Can’t See Your Score,print_headline:The Scoreboards Where You Can’t See Your Score,kicker:Technophoria}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>NATASHA<\/PERSON> SINGER,person:[{firstname:Natasha,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SINGER}]}",article
"Unwanted calls, estate planning, career toilet parts replacement subjects tackled Shortcuts columns year.",5,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Telemarketing},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Wills Estates},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Careers Professions},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Bathrooms Toilets},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:5,value:<ORGANIZATION>NoMoRobo Telephone Science Corp<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:Federal Communications Commission},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:7,value:Federal Trade Commission}]",Your Money,"<PERSON>Alina Tugend</PERSON> Shortcuts column, reviewing columns <DATE>2014</DATE>, finds themes consumer concerns changing workplace environments dominant; offers followups columns automated telemarketing calls, estate planning, switching careers finding replacement bathroom parts.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-27T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27shortcuts-pic2/27shortcuts-pic2-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27shortcuts-pic2/27shortcuts-pic2-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27shortcuts-pic2/27shortcuts-pic2-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27shortcuts-pic2/27shortcuts-pic2-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27shortcuts-pic2/27shortcuts-pic2-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27shortcuts-pic2/27shortcuts-pic2-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1277,"Unwanted calls, estate planning, career toilet parts replacement subjects tackled Shortcuts columns year.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/27/your-money/a-year-of-shortcuts-the-fight-against-robocalls-gains-ground.html,549d9c677988105ced788592,null,"{content_kicker:Shortcuts,main:A Year Fighting Robocalls, Finding Right Parts,print_headline:A Year Fighting Robocalls, Finding Right Parts,kicker:Shortcuts}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ALINA TUGEND<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Alina,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:TUGEND}]}",article
"Standard Chartered Plc hired prosecutors police transactions criminal activity, spokesman <DATE>Friday</DATE>, British bank wrestles series legal compliance problems.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-26T15:12:19Z,[],376,"Standard Chartered Plc hired prosecutors police transactions criminal activity, spokesman <DATE>Friday</DATE>, British bank wrestles series legal compliance problems.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/26/business/26reuters-standardchartered-compliance.html,549dc1b67988105ced7885df,null,"{main:Standard Chartered Hires Ex <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Prosecutors Amid Sanctions Probe,print_headline:Standard Chartered Hires Ex <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Prosecutors Amid Sanctions Probe}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
Big tobacco companies deploying financial resources knowledge bid dominate potentially huge market cigarette alternatives.,1,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:E-Cigarettes},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Smoking Tobacco},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Series},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Nicotine},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:5,value:<PERSON>Philip Morris<\/PERSON> Companies Inc},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:<PERSON>Reynolds<\/PERSON>, R J, Tobacco Co},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:Research}]",Business Day,Big tobacco companies pouring money resources developing cigarette alternatives effort dominate potentially lucrative e-cigarette market; experimenting dozens high-tech instruments deliver nicotine industry critics health officials warn devices create generation addicts Series: The New Smoke.,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-25T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/25/business/Nicotinejp/Nicotinejp-thumbWide-v2.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/business/Nicotinejp/Nicotinejp-thumbWide-v2.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/25/business/Nicotinejp/Nicotinejp-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:393},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/business/Nicotinejp/Nicotinejp-articleLarge.jpg,height:393},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/25/business/Nicotinejp/Nicotinejp-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/25/business/Nicotinejp/Nicotinejp-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",1677,Big tobacco companies deploying financial resources knowledge bid dominate potentially huge market cigarette alternatives.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/25/business/race-to-deliver-nicotines-punch-with-less-risk.html,549b6ecb79881003066910ae,null,"{content_kicker:The New Smoke,main:Race Deliver Nicotine&#8217;s Punch, With Less Risk,print_headline:Race to Deliver Nicotine’s Punch, With Less Risk,kicker:The New Smoke}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>BARRY MEIER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Barry,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:MEIER}]}",article
Apple Inc pushed first-ever automated security update Macintosh computers defend newly identified bugs security researchers warned enable hackers gain remote control machines.,null,[],Technology,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-23T00:24:41Z,[],229,Apple Inc pushed first-ever automated security update Macintosh computers defend newly identified bugs security researchers warned enable hackers gain remote control machines.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/23/technology/23reuters-apple-cybersecurity.html,5498fcdb798810035238e756,null,"{main:Apple Pushes First Ever Automated Security Update Mac Users,print_headline:Apple Pushes First Ever Automated Security Update Mac Users}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
