snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Mexican crude oil sailing <LOCATION>U.S. East Coast</LOCATION> highest rate decade, customs data reviewed <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION>, sign deepening discounts crack open markets domestic shale inundates <LOCATION>Texas</LOCATION>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T02:31:15Z,[],890,"Mexican crude oil sailing <LOCATION>U.S. East Coast</LOCATION> highest rate decade, customs data reviewed <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION>, sign deepening discounts crack open markets domestic shale inundates <LOCATION>Texas</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-mexico-crude-usa.html,54a3a6ea7988102761d6d501,null,"{main:Exclusive: <LOCATION>Mexico<\/LOCATION>'s Light Crude, Shunned <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Shale, Sails East,print_headline:Exclusive: <LOCATION>Mexico<\/LOCATION>'s Light Crude, Shunned <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Shale, Sails East}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The <PERSON>Obama</PERSON> administration opened front global battle oil market share, effectively clearing shipment million barrels day ultra-light <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> crude rest world.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T01:14:15Z,[],992,"The <PERSON>Obama</PERSON> administration opened front global battle oil market share, effectively clearing shipment million barrels day ultra-light <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> crude rest world.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-usa-crude-exports-analysis.html,54a394a47988102761d6d2ed,null,"{main:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Opening Oil Export Tap Widens Battle Global Market,print_headline:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Opening Oil Export Tap Widens Battle Global Market}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
<ORGANIZATION>Excelerate Energy</ORGANIZATION>'s Texan liquefied natural gas terminal plan victim oil price slump threatening economics <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> LNG export projects.,null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T13:21:42Z,[],642,<ORGANIZATION>Excelerate Energy</ORGANIZATION>'s Texan liquefied natural gas terminal plan victim oil price slump threatening economics <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> LNG export projects.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/business/30reuters-usa-lng-excelerate.html,54a2ee007988102761d6ce8f,null,"{main:Exclusive: Oil Price Crash Claims First <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> LNG Project Casualty,print_headline:Exclusive: Oil Price Crash Claims First <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> LNG Project Casualty}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The <PERSON>Obama</PERSON> administration <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> bowed months growing pressure 40-year-old ban exports domestic crude, taking steps expected unleash wave ultra-light shale oil global markets.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T13:07:56Z,[],841,"The <PERSON>Obama</PERSON> administration <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> bowed months growing pressure 40-year-old ban exports domestic crude, taking steps expected unleash wave ultra-light shale oil global markets.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/business/30reuters-usa-crude-exports-guidance.html,54a2ea7d7988102761d6ce81,null,"{main:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Opens Door Oil Exports After Year Pressure,print_headline:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Opens Door Oil Exports After Year Pressure}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Canary Wharf owner <ORGANIZATION>Songbird Estates Plc</ORGANIZATION> has told shareholders to take no action on a Qatari-led <MONEY>$4 billion 2.57 billion pounds</MONEY> takeover bid, reiterating that the <MONEY>350 pence</MONEY> per share cash offer undervalued the company.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T11:16:01Z,[],410,"Canary Wharf owner <ORGANIZATION>Songbird Estates Plc</ORGANIZATION> has told shareholders to take no action on a Qatari-led <MONEY>$4 billion 2.57 billion pounds</MONEY> takeover bid, reiterating that the <MONEY>350 pence</MONEY> per share cash offer undervalued the company.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/business/30reuters-songbird-m-a-qatar.html,54a2d0787988104803cc8ae2,null,"{main:Songbird Tells Shareholders to Take No Action on <MONEY>$4 Billion<\/MONEY> Bid,print_headline:Songbird Tells Shareholders to Take No Action on <MONEY>$4 Billion<\/MONEY> Bid}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Interest rates short-term <ORGANIZATION>Treasury</ORGANIZATION> bills fell <DATE>Monday</DATE>'s auction, rising week.",null,[],Business Day,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-29T15:36:05Z,[],162,"Interest rates short-term <ORGANIZATION>Treasury</ORGANIZATION> bills fell <DATE>Monday</DATE>'s auction, rising week.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/29/business/ap-us-treasury-bills.html,54a1bbeb7988104803cc8878,null,"{main:Rates Fall Weekly US Treasury Bill Auction,print_headline:Rates Fall Weekly US Treasury Bill Auction}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"After taking <PERCENT>7.7 percent</PERCENT> sake, <PERSON>Carl Icahn</PERSON> activist investor year urge breakup.",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Icahn<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Carl<\/PERSON> C},{name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Whitworth<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Ralph<\/PERSON> V},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:<ORGANIZATION>Manitowoc Company Inc<\/ORGANIZATION>},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:Relational Investors LLC},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Shareholder Rights Activism}]",Business Day,"After taking <PERCENT>7.7 percent</PERCENT> sake, <PERSON>Carl Icahn</PERSON> activist investor year urge breakup.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-29T08:53:22Z,[],204,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/29/icahn-calls-for-manitowoc-to-split-into-two/,54a15d397988101f98e3efad,Dealbook,"{main:<PERSON>Icahn<\/PERSON> Calls Manitowoc Split Two,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By DEALBOOK,person:[{firstname:Dealbook,role:reported,organization:,rank:1}]}",blogpost
Cleaning lockers heading home offseason experience <ORGANIZATION>Philadelphia Eagles New York Giants</ORGANIZATION>.,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-29T03:47:33Z,[],790,Cleaning lockers heading home offseason experience <ORGANIZATION>Philadelphia Eagles New York Giants</ORGANIZATION>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/29/sports/football/ap-fbn-eagles-giants-folo.html,54a116007988101f98e3ef2d,Pro Football,"{main:Different Prospects Eagles Giants '15,print_headline:Different Prospects Eagles Giants '15}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Few issues presidential campaign close meaningful economy. The latest Associated Press-GfK poll offers public feels issue, touches aspect American life. As <DATE>2016</DATE>...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-27T08:38:11Z,[],787,"Few issues presidential campaign close meaningful economy. The latest Associated Press-GfK poll offers public feels issue, touches aspect American life. As <DATE>2016</DATE> candidates set kick campaigns, things public opinion economy.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/27/us/politics/ap-us-ap-poll-economy-5-things.html,549eb71f7988105ced788703,Politics,"{main:AP-GfK Poll: 5 Things Know About Economy,print_headline:AP-GfK Poll: 5 Things Know About Economy}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"When time pick college, <PERSON>Abby Slusher</PERSON> leaned private school southeastern <LOCATION>Michigan</LOCATION> home small campus class sizes. Her mother pushed <ORGANIZATION>Adrian College</ORGANIZATION> reason: A program guaranteeing graduate...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-26T01:28:18Z,[],774,"When it came time to pick a college, <PERSON>Abby Slusher</PERSON> leaned toward a private school near her southeastern <LOCATION>Michigan</LOCATION> home for the small campus and class sizes. Her mother pushed <ORGANIZATION>Adrian College</ORGANIZATION> for another reason: A new program guaranteeing every graduate would make more than <MONEY>$37,000</MONEY> or get some or all student loans reimbursed.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/26/us/ap-us-college-wage-guarantee.html,549d005a7988103babf08b1b,null,"{main:College Sees Small, Big Benefits With Loan Promise,print_headline:College Sees Small, Big Benefits With Loan Promise}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
