snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Though popular home respected abroad, year Chancellor <PERSON>Angela Merkel</PERSON> loses touch??",8,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Germany<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Merkel<\/PERSON>, Angela},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:3,value:<LOCATION>Europe<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Immigration Emigration},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:5,value:<LOCATION>Greece<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Speeches Statements}]",World,Memo <LOCATION>Berlin</LOCATION>; German Chancellor <PERSON>Angela Merkel</PERSON> faces significant challenges 10th year office anti-foreigner sentiment grows Greek economic crisis continues.,The New York Times,[],Foreign,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/world/MERKEL/MERKEL-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/world/MERKEL/MERKEL-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/world/MERKEL/MERKEL-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:388},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/world/MERKEL/MERKEL-articleLarge.jpg,height:388},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/world/MERKEL/MERKEL-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/world/MERKEL/MERKEL-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1059,"Though popular home respected abroad, year Chancellor <PERSON>Angela Merkel</PERSON> loses touch??",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/world/euro-and-immigration-promise-challenges-for-merkel-in-2015.html,54a4a94f79881011bed2a080,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{content_kicker:Memo From <LOCATION>Berlin<\/LOCATION>,main:Euro Immigration Promise Challenges <PERSON>Merkel<\/PERSON> 2015,print_headline:Euro Immigration Promise Challenges <PERSON>Merkel<\/PERSON> 2015,kicker:Memo From <LOCATION>Berlin<\/LOCATION>}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ALISON SMALE<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Alison,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SMALE}]}",article
A writer urges airlines compelled upgrade flight-tracking technology.,18,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Airlines Airplanes},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Aviation Accidents, Safety Disasters},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Accidents Safety}]",Opinion,null,The New York Times,[],Letters,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,[],177,A writer urges airlines compelled upgrade flight-tracking technology.,Letter,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/opinion/improving-flight-safety.html,54a49e0779881011bed29ded,null,"{content_kicker:Letter,main:Improving Flight Safety,print_headline:Improving Flight Safety,kicker:Letter}",[],article
<ORGANIZATION>Ambac Assurance Corp</ORGANIZATION> sued <ORGANIZATION>Bank of America Corp</ORGANIZATION> to recoup <MONEY>hundreds of millions of dollars</MONEY> of losses from insuring roughly <MONEY>$1.68 billion</MONEY> of securities backed at least in part by risky mortgages from the bank's <ORGANIZATION>Countrywide Home Loans</ORGANIZATION> unit.,null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T11:40:22Z,[],383,<ORGANIZATION>Ambac Assurance Corp</ORGANIZATION> sued <ORGANIZATION>Bank of America Corp</ORGANIZATION> to recoup <MONEY>hundreds of millions of dollars</MONEY> of losses from insuring roughly <MONEY>$1.68 billion</MONEY> of securities backed at least in part by risky mortgages from the bank's <ORGANIZATION>Countrywide Home Loans</ORGANIZATION> unit.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/business/31reuters-bankofamerica-ambac-lawsuit.html,54a427987988102761d6e743,null,"{main:Ambac Sues Bank America Over Countrywide Mortgage Bonds,print_headline:Ambac Sues Bank America Over Countrywide Mortgage Bonds}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
The sheer volume flights skies <LOCATION>Southeast Asia</LOCATION> putting pressure outdated air traffic control pilots risky unilateral action crises possibly faced <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> Flight QZ8501.,null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T02:38:20Z,[],748,The sheer volume flights skies <LOCATION>Southeast Asia</LOCATION> putting pressure outdated air traffic control pilots risky unilateral action crises possibly faced <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> Flight QZ8501.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/world/asia/31reuters-indonesia-airplane-trafficcontrol.html,54a3a8587988102761d6d52e,Asia Pacific,"{main:Crowded Skies Southeast Asia Put Pressure Pilots, Air Traffic Control,print_headline:Crowded Skies Southeast Asia Put Pressure Pilots, Air Traffic Control}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
The Met&#8217;s recent performances &#8220;La Traviata&#8221; &#8220;Aida&#8221; showcased potential pitfalls triumphs await young Americans singing Verdi.,null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Opera},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:2,value:Metropolitan Opera},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Costello<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Stephen<\/PERSON>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:4,value:<PERSON>Wilson<\/PERSON>, Tamara},{is_major:Y,name:creative_works,rank:5,value:La Traviata Opera}]",Arts,"<PERSON>Zachary Woolfe</PERSON> Critic's Notebook notes rising tenor <PERSON>Stephen Costello</PERSON>'s performance Metropolitan Opera production Verdi opera La Traviata, sings role <PERSON>Alfredo</PERSON>, perfect devoid passion.",The New York Times,[],Culture,2014-12-31T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/arts/verdi1/verdi1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/arts/verdi1/verdi1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/arts/verdi1/verdi1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/arts/verdi1/verdi1-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/arts/verdi1/verdi1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/arts/verdi1/verdi1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",749,The Met&#8217;s recent performances &#8220;La Traviata&#8221; &#8220;Aida&#8221; showcased potential pitfalls triumphs await young Americans singing Verdi.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/arts/music/stephen-costello-and-tamara-wilson-show-opposing-approaches.html,54a31fa17988102761d6cf15,Music,"{content_kicker:Critic&#8217;s Notebook,main:When Singing Verdi, Perfection Is No Substitute Passion,seo:<PERSON>Stephen Costello Tamara Wilson<\/PERSON> Show Opposing Approaches,print_headline:When Singing Verdi, Perfection Is No Substitute Passion,kicker:Critic&#8217;s Notebook}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ZACHARY WOOLFE<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Zachary,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:WOOLFE}]}",article
"A undeclared candidate, <PERSON>Hillary Rodham Clinton</PERSON> sits atop prospective field Democratic presidential candidates <DATE>2016</DATE>. But <PERSON>Clinton</PERSON>, runs, she'll work hard underdog.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T02:18:38Z,[],689,"A undeclared candidate, <PERSON>Hillary Rodham Clinton</PERSON> sits atop prospective field Democratic presidential candidates <DATE>2016</DATE>. But <PERSON>Clinton</PERSON>, runs, she'll work hard underdog.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/us/politics/ap-us-dem-2016-clinton-5-things.html,54a2529d7988104803cc89df,Politics,"{main:Will <PERSON>Clinton<\/PERSON> Run? She Needs to Decide in <DATE>2015<\/DATE>,print_headline:Will <PERSON>Clinton<\/PERSON> Run? She Needs to Decide in <DATE>2015<\/DATE>}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
The experience accident victims families shows opportunities raise public alarm bells defective ignition switches lost.,1,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:General Motors},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Automobile Safety Features Defects},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Suits Litigation Civil},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:King & Spalding},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Deaths Fatalities},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Liability Products}]",Business Day,"Experience families accident victims unsuccessfully hold <ORGANIZATION>General Motors</ORGANIZATION> legally accountable car accident deaths reveals lost opportunities raise public awareness defective ignition switches; lawyers cases accepted law firms unwilling risk costs challenging company court, defects linked 42 deaths uncovered sooner lives saved.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-30T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/30/business/settlements1/settlements1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/business/settlements1/settlements1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/30/business/settlements1/settlements1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:448},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/business/settlements1/settlements1-articleLarge.jpg,height:448},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/30/business/settlements1/settlements1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/business/settlements1/settlements1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1674,The experience accident victims families shows opportunities raise public alarm bells defective ignition switches lost.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/business/victims-of-gm-deadly-defect-fall-through-legal-cracks.html,54a20e357988104803cc8928,null,"{main:Victims G.M. Deadly Defect Fall Through Legal Cracks,print_headline:Falling Through Legal Cracks}","{contributor:<PERSON>Danielle Ivory Rebecca R. Ruiz<\/PERSON> contributed reporting.,original:By <PERSON>BARRY MEIER HILARY STOUT<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Barry,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:MEIER},{firstname:Hilary,role:reported,organization:,rank:2,lastname:STOUT}]}",article
The German insurance giant faces responsibility lead reinsurer <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia Malaysia Airlines</ORGANIZATION>.,5,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:Allianz SE},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Aviation Accidents, Safety Disasters},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:4,value:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:5,value:<LOCATION>Malaysia<\/LOCATION> Airlines},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:<LOCATION>Malaysia<\/LOCATION> Airlines Flight 17},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:<ORGANIZATION>Malaysia Airlines<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight 370},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:8,value:Insurance}]",Business Day,"<ORGANIZATION>Allianz</ORGANIZATION> confirms main reinsurer <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION>, means company responsible part estimated hundreds <MONEY>millions dollars</MONEY> payouts major passenger jet disasters <DATE>2014</DATE>.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-30T00:00:00Z,[],926,The German insurance giant faces responsibility lead reinsurer <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia Malaysia Airlines</ORGANIZATION>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/business/international/allianz-is-to-share-in-payouts-over-3-malaysia-linked-air-disasters.html,54a1aea87988104803cc885d,International Business,"{main:Allianz Is Share Payouts Over 3 Malaysia-Linked Air Disasters,print_headline:Allianz Liable Part Air Disaster Payouts}","{contributor:<PERSON>Neil Gough<\/PERSON> contributed reporting <LOCATION>Hong Kong<\/LOCATION> <PERSON>Nicola Clark Paris<\/PERSON>.,original:By <PERSON>DAVID JOLLY<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:David,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:JOLLY}]}",article
A group judges suing <LOCATION>California</LOCATION>'s public pension system <ORGANIZATION>Calpers</ORGANIZATION> state <LOCATION>California</LOCATION> claims pension contributions doubled unlawfully.,null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-29T18:35:52Z,[],313,A group judges suing <LOCATION>California</LOCATION>'s public pension system <ORGANIZATION>Calpers</ORGANIZATION> state <LOCATION>California</LOCATION> claims pension contributions doubled unlawfully.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/29/business/29reuters-usa-pensions-judges.html,54a1e5987988104803cc88cb,null,"{main:<LOCATION>California<\/LOCATION> Judges Sue Calpers Pension System Over Contributions,print_headline:<LOCATION>California<\/LOCATION> Judges Sue Calpers Pension System Over Contributions}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"There fire alarms, knocks door crew, thick, acrid smoke filling cabins waking passengers overnight ferry <LOCATION>Greece Italy</LOCATION>.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-29T17:02:54Z,[],1036,"There fire alarms, knocks door crew, thick, acrid smoke filling cabins waking passengers overnight ferry <LOCATION>Greece Italy</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/29/world/europe/ap-eu-greece-ferry-fire.html,54a1d0617988104803cc88a2,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:Ferry Passengers Recount Chaos: No Fire Alarm, Just Smoke,print_headline:Ferry Passengers Recount Chaos: No Fire Alarm, Just Smoke}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
