snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Consumers paid <MONEY>$15 million</MONEY> in just four days to watch The Interview from the comfort of their couches, building expectations that other hot, new films might also make their debut online.",null,[],Arts,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-29T21:27:01Z,[],688,"Consumers paid <MONEY>$15 million</MONEY> in just four days to watch The Interview from the comfort of their couches, building expectations that other hot, new films might also make their debut online.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/29/arts/29reuters-northkorea-cybersecurity-streaming.html,54a20db17988104803cc8927,null,"{main:As 'Interview' Takes Streaming Plunge, Hollywood Tests Waters,print_headline:As 'Interview' Takes Streaming Plunge, Hollywood Tests Waters}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
A surge native Californians Northeasterners travel home South highlights role place pursue American dream.,1,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:Southern States US},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Population},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:3,value:United States},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:States US},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Census},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Prices Fares, Fees Rates},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:7,value:Social Conditions Trends}]",The Upshot,"The Upshot; Americans grew <LOCATION>California</LOCATION>, <ORGANIZATION>Midwest Northeast</ORGANIZATION>, reverse past migration, live Southeast travel back childhood homes holidays; pattern holiday travel highlights Southeast region people move find American dream, drawn lower cost living; changing migration patterns larger political, economic social ramifications.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-25T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/business/25UP-Migration/25UP-Migration-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/25UP-Migration/25UP-Migration-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/business/25UP-Migration/25UP-Migration-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/25UP-Migration/25UP-Migration-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/business/25UP-Migration/25UP-Migration-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/25UP-Migration/25UP-Migration-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1250,A surge native Californians Northeasterners travel home South highlights role place pursue American dream.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/25/upshot/going-home-from-the-south-a-new-holiday-exodus.html,549afb5d7988100306690dcb,null,"{content_kicker:Nation Move,main:Going Home From South, New Holiday Exodus,print_headline:Heading Home From South New Exodus,kicker:The Upshot}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ALAN BLINDER<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>ROBERT GEBELOFF DAVID LEONHARDT<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Alan,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BLINDER},{firstname:Robert,role:reported,organization:,rank:2,lastname:GEBELOFF},{firstname:David,role:reported,organization:,rank:3,lastname:LEONHARDT}]}",article
British oil and gas explorer <ORGANIZATION>Ophir Energy Plc</ORGANIZATION> offered to buy <ORGANIZATION>Salamander Energy Plc</ORGANIZATION> for <MONEY>267 million pounds $419 million</MONEY> to expand in <LOCATION>southeast Asia</LOCATION>.,null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-11-21T08:33:12Z,[],376,British oil and gas explorer <ORGANIZATION>Ophir Energy Plc</ORGANIZATION> offered to buy <ORGANIZATION>Salamander Energy Plc</ORGANIZATION> for <MONEY>267 million pounds $419 million</MONEY> to expand in <LOCATION>southeast Asia</LOCATION>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/11/21/business/21reuters-salamander-enrgy-m-a-ophir.html,546f3fa47988106ad45c6a02,null,"{main:Ophir Energy Offers Buy Salamander SE <LOCATION>Asia<\/LOCATION> Push,print_headline:Ophir Energy Offers Buy Salamander SE <LOCATION>Asia<\/LOCATION> Push}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s exports large trade surplus <DATE>October</DATE> pointed signs manipulation inflows speculative hot money, official <ORGANIZATION>Shanghai Securities News</ORGANIZATION> <DATE>Monday</DATE>, suggesting firms continue over-invoice trade deals avoid...",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-11-09T20:21:38Z,[],473,"<LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s exports large trade surplus <DATE>October</DATE> pointed signs manipulation inflows speculative hot money, official <ORGANIZATION>Shanghai Securities News</ORGANIZATION> <DATE>Monday</DATE>, suggesting firms continue over-invoice trade deals avoid capital controls.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/11/09/business/09reuters-china-economy-trade.html,546013fa7988106af1739949,null,"{main:China <DATE>October<\/DATE> Trade Data Shows Signs Manipulation, Hot Money Inflows-State Newspaper,print_headline:China <DATE>October<\/DATE> Trade Data Shows Signs Manipulation, Hot Money Inflows-State Newspaper}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"A sudden swell <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s exports gold jewellery signal resurgence speculative currency inflows inflated trade receipts, raising prospect central bank act weaken yuan punish speculators.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-11-06T16:18:24Z,[],714,"A sudden swell <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s exports gold jewellery signal resurgence speculative currency inflows inflated trade receipts, raising prospect central bank act weaken yuan punish speculators.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/11/06/business/06reuters-china-currency-yuan.html,545be67279881039320eceb3,null,"{main:<LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION> Gold Jewels Exports Spike Points Hot Money Revival,print_headline:<LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION> Gold Jewels Exports Spike Points Hot Money Revival}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The federal government <DATE>Thursday</DATE> announced bitcoin securities fraud case, accusing <LOCATION>Texas</LOCATION> man engineering Ponzi scheme people turn bitcoins return promises high interest rates ability...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-11-06T11:54:18Z,[],319,"The federal government <DATE>Thursday</DATE> announced bitcoin securities fraud case, accusing <LOCATION>Texas</LOCATION> man engineering Ponzi scheme people turn bitcoins return promises high interest rates ability recoup investment time.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/11/06/us/ap-us-bitcoin-ponzi-scheme.html,545ba8ab7988106e4390c503,null,"{main:US Announces 1st Bitcoin Securities Fraud Case,print_headline:US Announces 1st Bitcoin Securities Fraud Case}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<LOCATION>Singapore</LOCATION> implement global agreement swapping tax information, aimed ending offshore tax evasion, <DATE>2018</DATE>, provided conditions met, Finance Minister <PERSON>Tharman Shanmugaratnam</PERSON>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-11-04T00:02:31Z,[],281,"<LOCATION>Singapore</LOCATION> implement global agreement swapping tax information, aimed ending offshore tax evasion, <DATE>2018</DATE>, provided conditions met, Finance Minister <PERSON>Tharman Shanmugaratnam</PERSON>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/11/04/business/04reuters-singapore-tax.html,54585e35798810533a8de360,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Singapore<\/LOCATION> Says Will Adopt OECD Pact Tackle Tax Cheats 2018,print_headline:<LOCATION>Singapore<\/LOCATION> Says Will Adopt OECD Pact Tackle Tax Cheats 2018}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Technically, this monstrous natural-gas refinery is a “floating facility,” not a “ship,” but c’mon.",40,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Natural Gas},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>South Korea<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Royal Dutch Shell Plc},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Refineries},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Oil Petroleum Gasoline},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Ships Shipping},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:7,value:Indian Ocean}]",Magazine,"Photos <PERSON>Stephen Mallon</PERSON> document sheer size Prelude, offshore natural-gas refinery constructed <LOCATION>Shell South Korea</LOCATION> 530 yards long 80 yards wide.",The New York Times,[],Magazine,2014-11-02T00:00:00Z,[],666,"Technically, this monstrous natural-gas refinery is a “floating facility,” not a “ship,” but c’mon.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/11/02/magazine/the-biggest-ship-in-the-world-though-it-isnt-exactly-a-ship-.html,54539cf97988101196a59ae2,null,"{main:The Biggest Ship World Though It Isn’t Exactly a Ship,print_headline:The Biggest Ship in the World}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ROBERT SULLIVAN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Robert,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SULLIVAN}]}",article
<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> regulators plan deny proposals breed actively managed exchange-traded funds holdings secret months time.,null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-10-22T12:56:05Z,[],465,<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> regulators plan deny proposals breed actively managed exchange-traded funds holdings secret months time.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/10/22/business/22reuters-sec-etf-transparency.html,5447e2597988104f576eab95,null,"{main:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> SEC Plans Deny Proposals 'Non-Transparent' ETFs,print_headline:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> SEC Plans Deny Proposals 'Non-Transparent' ETFs}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The British Bankers' Association <ORGANIZATION>BBA</ORGANIZATION>, lobby group 240 UK overseas firms, held annual conference <DATE>Thursday</DATE>, attended politicians, regulators bank executives staff.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-10-16T08:04:47Z,[],1017,"The British Bankers' Association <ORGANIZATION>BBA</ORGANIZATION>, lobby group 240 UK overseas firms, held annual conference <DATE>Thursday</DATE>, attended politicians, regulators bank executives staff.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/10/16/business/16reuters-britain-banks.html,543fb6a379881001751bff2c,null,"{main:Comments From British Bankers' Association Conference,print_headline:Comments From British Bankers' Association Conference}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
