snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
<LOCATION>Australia</LOCATION> captain Mile Jedinak confident Socceroos blend players win month's Asian Cup home soil younger members squad strong handle pressure.,null,[],Sports,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T22:00:49Z,[],364,<LOCATION>Australia</LOCATION> captain Mile Jedinak confident Socceroos blend players win month's Asian Cup home soil younger members squad strong handle pressure.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/sports/soccer/01reuters-soccer-asia-australia-jedinak.html,54a60ac37988102023c952a3,Soccer,"{main:<LOCATION>Australia<\/LOCATION> Have Right Blend Win Asian Cup-Jedinak,print_headline:<LOCATION>Australia<\/LOCATION> Have Right Blend Win Asian Cup-Jedinak}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Starting 2015 themelesses, <PERSON>David Steinberg</PERSON>.",null,"[{name:subject,rank:1,value:Crossword Puzzles}]",Crosswords/Games,"Starting 2015 themelesses, <PERSON>David Steinberg</PERSON>.",The New York Times,[],Business,2015-01-01T22:00:33Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/crosswords/0101cardinaljpg/0101cardinaljpg-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/crosswords/0101cardinaljpg/0101cardinaljpg-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/crosswords/0101cardinaljpg/0101cardinaljpg-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:399},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/crosswords/0101cardinaljpg/0101cardinaljpg-articleLarge.jpg,height:399},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/crosswords/0101cardinaljpg/0101cardinaljpg-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/crosswords/0101cardinaljpg/0101cardinaljpg-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",711,null,Blog,http://wordplay.blogs.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/burning-sensation/,54a60a407988102023c9529b,null,"{main:Burning Sensation,kicker:Wordplay}","{original:By <PERSON>DEB AMLEN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Deb,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:AMLEN}]}",blogpost
"Fresh <LOCATION>New Zealand</LOCATION>'s successful test year, captain Brendon <PERSON>McCullum</PERSON> urging team start <DATE>2015</DATE> fashion face <LOCATION>Sri Lanka</LOCATION> game two-match series <DATE>Saturday</DATE>.",null,[],Sports,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T21:58:08Z,[],425,"Fresh <LOCATION>New Zealand</LOCATION>'s successful test year, captain Brendon <PERSON>McCullum</PERSON> urging team start <DATE>2015</DATE> fashion face <LOCATION>Sri Lanka</LOCATION> game two-match series <DATE>Saturday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/sports/cricket/01reuters-cricket-zealand.html,54a60a087988102023c95292,Cricket,"{main:Forget Last Year, <LOCATION>New Zealand<\/LOCATION> Need Keep Improving-McCullum,print_headline:Forget Last Year, <LOCATION>New Zealand<\/LOCATION> Need Keep Improving-McCullum}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<PERSON>Mario Cuomo</PERSON>, son Italian immigrants eloquent spokesman generation liberal Democrats terms governor <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> bring run president, died. He 82.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T21:15:05Z,[],1240,"<PERSON>Mario Cuomo</PERSON>, son Italian immigrants eloquent spokesman generation liberal Democrats terms governor <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> bring run president, died. He 82.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/us/ap-us-obit-mario-cuomo-.html,54a600187988102023c951b2,null,"{main:Ex-NY Gov. <PERSON>Mario Cuomo<\/PERSON>, Famed Oratory, Dies 82,print_headline:Ex-NY Gov. <PERSON>Mario Cuomo<\/PERSON>, Famed Oratory, Dies 82}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
<PERSON>Kate Catherine Keener</PERSON> has a lot on her mind. Theres the ethics problem of buying furniture on the cheap at estate sales and marking it up at her trendy <LOCATION>Manhattan</LOCATION> store and how much markup can she get away with?. Theres the materialism problem of,null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T17:23:05Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-please-give/video-please-give-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-please-give/video-please-give-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-please-give/video-please-give-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-please-give/video-please-give-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-please-give/video-please-give-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-please-give/video-please-give-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",45,<PERSON>Kate Catherine Keener</PERSON> has a lot on her mind. Theres the ethics problem of buying furniture on the cheap at estate sales and marking it up at her trendy <LOCATION>Manhattan</LOCATION> store and how much markup can she get away with?. Theres the materialism problem of,Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003364510/please-give.html,54a5c8cd7988102023c94c9f,null,{"main":"Please Give"},"{original:Sony Pictures Classics,person:[{firstname:Sony,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Pictures,rank:1,lastname:Classics}]}",multimedia
"Captain <PERSON>Craig McKenzie Christian Slater</PERSON>, <LOCATION>US</LOCATION> special forces soldier, hired protect group millionaires experience firsthand kicks thrills war. However, mission horribly wrong, men lot",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T17:22:23Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-soldiers-of-fortune/video-soldiers-of-fortune-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-soldiers-of-fortune/video-soldiers-of-fortune-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-soldiers-of-fortune/video-soldiers-of-fortune-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-soldiers-of-fortune/video-soldiers-of-fortune-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-soldiers-of-fortune/video-soldiers-of-fortune-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-soldiers-of-fortune/video-soldiers-of-fortune-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",42,"Captain <PERSON>Craig McKenzie Christian Slater</PERSON>, <LOCATION>US</LOCATION> special forces soldier, hired protect group millionaires experience firsthand kicks thrills war. However, mission horribly wrong, men lot",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003375386/soldiers-of-fortune.html,54a5c8a37988102023c94c92,null,{"main":"Soldiers Of Fortune"},"{original:Roadside Attractions,person:[{firstname:Roadside,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Attractions}]}",multimedia
<ORGANIZATION>Connor Cook Michigan State Spartans</ORGANIZATION> role playoff talk season.,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T17:01:41Z,[],832,<ORGANIZATION>Connor Cook Michigan State Spartans</ORGANIZATION> role playoff talk season.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/sports/ncaafootball/ap-fbc-t25-cotton-bowl.html,54a5c4567988102023c94c0a,College Football,"{main:No. 7 MSU Shocks No. 4 Baylor 42-41 Cotton Bowl,print_headline:No. 7 MSU Shocks No. 4 Baylor 42-41 Cotton Bowl}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
<LOCATION>Wisconsin</LOCATION> hoisted <PERSON>Barry Alvarez</PERSON> air victory ride.,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T16:05:01Z,[],1046,<LOCATION>Wisconsin</LOCATION> hoisted <PERSON>Barry Alvarez</PERSON> air victory ride.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/sports/ncaafootball/ap-fbc-t25-outback-bowl.html,54a5b6f27988102023c94adb,College Football,"{main:Gordon Leads Wisconsin Past Auburn 34-31 OT,print_headline:Gordon Leads Wisconsin Past Auburn 34-31 OT}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Meet <PERSON>Hank Mike</PERSON>, blue-collar Easter Bunnies fired hand assortment odd jobs, failing.  Fighting depression, debt eventually, longtime pals set mission recapture",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T14:12:29Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-hank-and-mike/video-hank-and-mike-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-hank-and-mike/video-hank-and-mike-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-hank-and-mike/video-hank-and-mike-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-hank-and-mike/video-hank-and-mike-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-hank-and-mike/video-hank-and-mike-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-hank-and-mike/video-hank-and-mike-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",43,"Meet <PERSON>Hank Mike</PERSON>, blue-collar Easter Bunnies fired hand assortment odd jobs, failing.  Fighting depression, debt eventually, longtime pals set mission recapture",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003329872/hank-and-mike.html,54a59c207988102023c9464b,null,{"main":"<PERSON>Hank And Mike<\/PERSON>"},"{original:Magnolia Pictures,person:[{firstname:Magnolia,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Pictures}]}",multimedia
The Alamo Bowl raises intriguing question UCLA: Is college farewell coach <PERSON>Jim Mora</PERSON>??,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T13:40:44Z,[],607,The Alamo Bowl raises intriguing question UCLA: Is college farewell coach <PERSON>Jim Mora</PERSON>??,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/sports/ncaafootball/ap-fbc-t25-alamo-bowl.html,54a5954d7988102023c9442c,College Football,"{main:Is Alamo Bowl Finale UCLA Coach <PERSON>Jim Mora<\/PERSON>??,print_headline:Is Alamo Bowl Finale UCLA Coach <PERSON>Jim Mora<\/PERSON>??}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
