snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Deals worth nearly <MONEY>$3.5 trillion</MONEY> were announced, a performance favored by low interest rates and high stock prices.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Mergers, Acquisitions Divestitures}]",Business Day,"Deals worth nearly <MONEY>$3.5 trillion</MONEY> were announced, a performance favored by low interest rates and high stock prices.",The New York Times,[],Business,2015-01-01T19:32:44Z,[],525,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/deal-makers-notched-nearly-3-5-trillion-worth-in-14-best-in-7-years/,54a5e7cc7988102023c94f8e,Dealbook,"{main:Deal Makers Notched Nearly <MONEY>$3.5<\/MONEY> <ORGANIZATION>Trillion Worth<\/ORGANIZATION> in &rsquo;14, Best in 7 Years,print_headline:Deal Makers Notched Nearly <MONEY>$3.5 Trillion<\/MONEY> Worth in ’14, Best in 7 Years,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>MICHAEL J. DE<\/PERSON> LA MERCED,person:[{firstname:Michael,role:reported,organization:,middlename:J.,rank:1,lastname:DE LA MERCED}]}",blogpost
"When <LOCATION>Missouri</LOCATION> played season, <ORGANIZATION>Tigers</ORGANIZATION> stopped run ran. <LOCATION>Minnesota</LOCATION> found Tigers successful.",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T16:33:05Z,[],703,"When <LOCATION>Missouri</LOCATION> played season, <ORGANIZATION>Tigers</ORGANIZATION> stopped run ran. <LOCATION>Minnesota</LOCATION> found Tigers successful.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/sports/ncaafootball/ap-fbc-t25-citrus-bowl.html,54a5be147988102023c94b7d,College Football,"{main:No. 16 <LOCATION>Missouri<\/LOCATION> Rumbles Past <LOCATION>Minnesota<\/LOCATION>, 33-17,print_headline:No. 16 <LOCATION>Missouri<\/LOCATION> Rumbles Past <LOCATION>Minnesota<\/LOCATION>, 33-17}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
<LOCATION>Wisconsin</LOCATION> hoisted <PERSON>Barry Alvarez</PERSON> air victory ride.,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T16:05:01Z,[],1046,<LOCATION>Wisconsin</LOCATION> hoisted <PERSON>Barry Alvarez</PERSON> air victory ride.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/sports/ncaafootball/ap-fbc-t25-outback-bowl.html,54a5b6f27988102023c94adb,College Football,"{main:Gordon Leads Wisconsin Past Auburn 34-31 OT,print_headline:Gordon Leads Wisconsin Past Auburn 34-31 OT}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Story  explorer's efforts gain support voyage arrival world triumphant return <LOCATION>Spain</LOCATION>.,null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T12:52:51Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-christopher-columbus-the-discovery/video-christopher-columbus-the-discovery-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-christopher-columbus-the-discovery/video-christopher-columbus-the-discovery-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-christopher-columbus-the-discovery/video-christopher-columbus-the-discovery-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-christopher-columbus-the-discovery/video-christopher-columbus-the-discovery-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-christopher-columbus-the-discovery/video-christopher-columbus-the-discovery-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-christopher-columbus-the-discovery/video-christopher-columbus-the-discovery-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",23,Story  explorer's efforts gain support voyage arrival world triumphant return <LOCATION>Spain</LOCATION>.,Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003311195/christopher-columbus-the-discovery.html,54a5897f7988102023c94084,null,{"main":"Christopher Columbus: The Discovery"},"{original:Warner Home Video,person:[{firstname:Warner,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Home,rank:1,lastname:Video}]}",multimedia
"The Snowy Peaks Ski Patrol takes evil land developer gain control mountain. From makers <ORGANIZATION>Police Academy</ORGANIZATION>, worth!",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T12:50:18Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-ski-patrol/video-ski-patrol-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-ski-patrol/video-ski-patrol-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-ski-patrol/video-ski-patrol-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-ski-patrol/video-ski-patrol-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-ski-patrol/video-ski-patrol-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-ski-patrol/video-ski-patrol-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",28,"The Snowy Peaks Ski Patrol takes evil land developer gain control mountain. From makers <ORGANIZATION>Police Academy</ORGANIZATION>, worth!",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003374377/ski-patrol.html,54a588fa7988102023c94054,null,{"main":"Ski Patrol"},"{original:Sony Pictures Home Entertainment,person:[{firstname:Sony,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Pictures,rank:1,lastname:Home}]}",multimedia
"A suicide bomber blew gates church <LOCATION>Nigeria</LOCATION>'s northeastern city <LOCATION>Gombe</LOCATION> New Year service, wounding people, official <LOCATION>Nigeria</LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>Red Cross</ORGANIZATION> told <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION> <DATE>Thursday</DATE>.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T12:28:27Z,[],198,"A suicide bomber blew gates church <LOCATION>Nigeria</LOCATION>'s northeastern city <LOCATION>Gombe</LOCATION> New Year service, wounding people, official <LOCATION>Nigeria</LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>Red Cross</ORGANIZATION> told <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION> <DATE>Thursday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/world/africa/01reuters-nigeria-violence.html,54a584787988102023c93ee9,<LOCATION>Africa</LOCATION>,"{main:Suicide Bomber Hits Church <LOCATION>Nigeria<\/LOCATION>'s <LOCATION>Gombe<\/LOCATION>, Wounding Eight,print_headline:Suicide Bomber Hits Church <LOCATION>Nigeria<\/LOCATION>'s <LOCATION>Gombe<\/LOCATION>, Wounding Eight}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"With 300 hours film shot <DATE>2010</DATE> tour, No Room For Rockstars documents true stories modern era rock roll angle. From kids van playing parking lots gain notice, veteran stage ma",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T09:29:46Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/20/movies/video-no-room-for-rockstars/video-no-room-for-rockstars-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/20/movies/video-no-room-for-rockstars/video-no-room-for-rockstars-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/20/movies/video-no-room-for-rockstars/video-no-room-for-rockstars-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/20/movies/video-no-room-for-rockstars/video-no-room-for-rockstars-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/20/movies/video-no-room-for-rockstars/video-no-room-for-rockstars-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/20/movies/video-no-room-for-rockstars/video-no-room-for-rockstars-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",47,"With 300 hours film shot <DATE>2010</DATE> tour, No Room For Rockstars documents true stories modern era rock roll angle. From kids van playing parking lots gain notice, veteran stage ma",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003359236/no-room-for-rockstars.html,54a559e979881011bed2c875,null,{"main":"No Room For Rockstars"},"{original:Cinedigm,person:[{firstname:Cinedigm,role:reported,organization:,rank:1}]}",multimedia
"Quarterback Cardale Jones accounted 305 yards scrimmage, defensive end <PERSON>Steve Miller</PERSON> returned interception 41 yards score, <ORGANIZATION>Ohio State</ORGANIZATION> led <LOCATION>Alabama</LOCATION> 34-28 quarter <ORGANIZATION>College Football Playoff</ORGANIZATION> semifinal...",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T01:04:31Z,[],583,"Quarterback Cardale Jones accounted 305 yards scrimmage, defensive end <PERSON>Steve Miller</PERSON> returned interception 41 yards score, <ORGANIZATION>Ohio State</ORGANIZATION> led <LOCATION>Alabama</LOCATION> 34-28 quarter <ORGANIZATION>College Football Playoff</ORGANIZATION> semifinal Sugar Bowl <DATE>Thursday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/sports/ncaafootball/ap-fbc-t25-playoff-sugar-bowl.html,54a4e44379881011bed2adee,College Football,"{main:<ORGANIZATION>Ohio State Leads Alabama<\/ORGANIZATION> 34-28 After 3 Quarters,print_headline:<ORGANIZATION>Ohio State Leads Alabama<\/ORGANIZATION> 34-28 After 3 Quarters}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Minimum wage increases go into effect in 20 states and the <LOCATION>District of Columbia</LOCATION> by <DATE>Jan. 1</DATE>, and, all told, 29 states will exceed the federal minimum of <MONEY>$7.25</MONEY> an hour at the beginning of <DATE>January</DATE>.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Minimum Wage},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:States US},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:3,value:United States}]",Business Day,"Minimum wage increases are set to take effect in 20 states, pushing number of states that exceed <MONEY>$7.25</MONEY> federal minimum to 29; changes will affect some <PERCENT>60 percent</PERCENT> of nation's work force, though difference will only be marginal in several states; battle to increase minimum wage has grown more intense amid rising income inequality, prompting <PERSON>Pres Obama</PERSON> to propose a new federal standard of <MONEY>$10.10</MONEY> per hour.",The New York Times,[],Business,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/business/jpWAGE/jpWAGE-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/business/jpWAGE/jpWAGE-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/business/jpWAGE/jpWAGE-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:424},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/business/jpWAGE/jpWAGE-articleLarge.jpg,height:424},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/business/jpWAGE/jpWAGE-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/business/jpWAGE/jpWAGE-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1017,"Minimum wage increases go into effect in 20 states and the <LOCATION>District of Columbia</LOCATION> by <DATE>Jan. 1</DATE>, and, all told, 29 states will exceed the federal minimum of <MONEY>$7.25</MONEY> an hour at the beginning of <DATE>January</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/business/hourly-minimum-wage-is-going-up-for-millions.html,54a4a6a279881011bed29fe2,null,"{main:States’ Minimum Wages Rise, Helping Millions of Workers,print_headline:Hourly Wage Is Going Up Millions}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>RACHEL ABRAMS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Rachel,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:ABRAMS}]}",article
"The relative importance genes shift years environment, study suggests.",,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Genetics Heredity},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Obesity},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Proceedings National Academy Sciences},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:4,value:<PERSON>Christakis<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Nicholas<\/PERSON> A},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Research}]",Science,null,The New York Times,[],Science,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/science/01zimmer/01zimmer-thumbWide-v2.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/science/01zimmer/01zimmer-thumbWide-v2.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/science/01zimmer/01zimmer-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:466},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/science/01zimmer/01zimmer-articleLarge.jpg,height:466},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/science/01zimmer/01zimmer-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/science/01zimmer/01zimmer-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",871,"The relative importance genes shift years environment, study suggests.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/science/gene-linked-to-obesity-hasnt-always-been-a-problem-study-finds.html,54a480b279881011bed29730,null,"{content_kicker:Matter,main:Gene Linked to Obesity Hasn’t Always Been a Problem, Study Finds,kicker:Matter}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>CARL ZIMMER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Carl,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:ZIMMER}]}",article
