snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
Is history remember??,null,[],Opinion,Is history remember??,The New York Times,[],OpEd,2014-12-26T11:08:26Z,[],558,null,Blog,http://krugman.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/26/1980-and-all-that/,549d884d7988103babf08bcf,null,"{main:<DATE>1980<\/DATE> And All That,kicker:<PERSON>Paul Krugman<\/PERSON>}","{original:By <PERSON>PAUL KRUGMAN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Paul,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:KRUGMAN}]}",blogpost
"Mr. <PERSON>Abe</PERSON>, leader <ORGANIZATION>Liberal Democratic Party</ORGANIZATION>, acknowledged faced battle persuading voters change Constitution renounces war.",10,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Japan<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:Abe, Shinzo},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Constitutions},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:World War II 1939-45}]",World,"Prime <LOCATION>Min Shinzo Abe Japan</LOCATION> begins term office; vows revise nation's Constitution, renounces war, opposition voters set deregulation policies part plan revive grow country's economy.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-25T00:00:00Z,[],525,"Mr. <PERSON>Abe</PERSON>, leader <ORGANIZATION>Liberal Democratic Party</ORGANIZATION>, acknowledged faced battle persuading voters change Constitution renounces war.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/25/world/asia/japan-shinzo-abe-begins-new-term-with-push-to-revise-constitution.html,549b06167988100306690de7,Asia Pacific,"{main:Shinzo Abe Has Eyes on Revising Constitution in <LOCATION>Japan<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:Abe Has Eyes Revising Constitution <LOCATION>Japan<\/LOCATION>}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>MARTIN<\/PERSON> FACKLER,person:[{firstname:Martin,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:FACKLER}]}",article
"Japanese Prime Minister <PERSON>Shinzo Abe</PERSON> unveiled cabinet <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>, appointing defense chief desire stronger pre-emptive strike capability rile neighbor <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-24T01:17:59Z,[],388,"Japanese Prime Minister <PERSON>Shinzo Abe</PERSON> unveiled cabinet <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>, appointing defense chief desire stronger pre-emptive strike capability rile neighbor <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/24/world/asia/24reuters-japan-politics.html,549a5ac67988102d96d56774,Asia Pacific,"{main:Japanese PM Unveils New Government, <ORGANIZATION>Defense Pick<\/ORGANIZATION> May Rile China,print_headline:Japanese PM Unveils New Government, Defense Pick May Rile China}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Japanese Prime Minister <PERSON>Shinzo Abe</PERSON>'s cabinet resigned <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>, setting stage launch government defense minister support <LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION> stronger pre-emptive strike capability rile <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-23T21:48:44Z,[],393,"Japanese Prime Minister <PERSON>Shinzo Abe</PERSON>'s cabinet resigned <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>, setting stage launch government defense minister support <LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION> stronger pre-emptive strike capability rile <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/23/world/asia/23reuters-japan-politics.html,549a2a3d7988102d96d55cc3,Asia Pacific,"{main:<LOCATION>Japan<\/LOCATION> PM Set Launch New Government, Defense Minister May Rile <LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:<LOCATION>Japan<\/LOCATION> PM Set Launch New Government, Defense Minister May Rile <LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION>}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The head Japanese energy start-up <ORGANIZATION>Eneres Co.</ORGANIZATION>, debuted <LOCATION>Tokyo</LOCATION>'s stock exchange amid fanfare <DATE>October 2013</DATE>, resigned independent investigation flagged concerns accounting practices.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-22T03:29:28Z,[],386,"The head Japanese energy start-up <ORGANIZATION>Eneres Co.</ORGANIZATION>, debuted <LOCATION>Tokyo</LOCATION>'s stock exchange amid fanfare <DATE>October 2013</DATE>, resigned independent investigation flagged concerns accounting practices.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/22/business/22reuters-eneres-ceo.html,5497d6ed7988104a1e0deda0,null,"{main:CEO <LOCATION>Japan<\/LOCATION> Energy Start-Up Steps Down After Accounting Probe,print_headline:CEO <LOCATION>Japan<\/LOCATION> Energy Start-Up Steps Down After Accounting Probe}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
Goldman names <PERSON>John E. Waldron</PERSON> co-head investment bank. | Regulators deem <ORGANIZATION>MetLife</ORGANIZATION> u201ctoo big fail.u201d | Another big whistle-blower reward <LOCATION>Bank America</LOCATION> case. | <LOCATION>London</LOCATION> tenants win battle <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> equity firm.| Regulators deem <ORGANIZATION>MetLife</ORGANIZATION> “too big to fail.” |Goldman names <PERSON>John E. Waldron</PERSON> co-head investment bank. | Regulators deem <ORGANIZATION>MetLife</ORGANIZATION> u201ctoo big fail.u201d | Another big whistle-blower reward <LOCATION>Bank America</LOCATION> case. | <LOCATION>London</LOCATION> tenants win battle <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> equity firm.| <LOCATION>London</LOCATION> tenants win battle over <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> equity firm.,null,[],Business Day,Goldman names <PERSON>John E. Waldron</PERSON> co-head of its investment bank. | Regulators deem <ORGANIZATION>MetLife</ORGANIZATION> “too big to fail.” | Another big whistle-blower reward in <ORGANIZATION>Bank of America</ORGANIZATION> case. | <LOCATION>London</LOCATION> tenants win battle over <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> equity firm.,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-19T13:56:02Z,[],2141,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/19/morning-agenda-goldman-promotes-star-deal-maker/,5494752d7988107c468004e2,Dealbook,"{main:Morning Agenda: Goldman Promotes Star Deal Maker,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By SYDNEY EMBER,person:[{firstname:<LOCATION>Sydney<\/LOCATION>,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:EMBER}]}",blogpost
"Japanese Prime Minister <PERSON>Shinzo Abe</PERSON>, brushing suggestions low turnout tarnished coalition's election win, vowed <DATE>Monday</DATE> stick reflationary economic policies, tackle painful structural reforms pursue muscular...",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-15T01:35:17Z,[],844,"Japanese Prime Minister <PERSON>Shinzo Abe</PERSON>, brushing suggestions low turnout tarnished coalition's election win, vowed <DATE>Monday</DATE> stick reflationary economic policies, tackle painful structural reforms pursue muscular security stance.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/15/world/asia/15reuters-japan-election.html,548e81a279881018ac4ba5ba,Asia Pacific,"{main:Abe Coalition Secures Big <LOCATION>Japan<\/LOCATION> Election Win With Record Low Turnout,print_headline:Abe Coalition Secures Big <LOCATION>Japan<\/LOCATION> Election Win With Record Low Turnout}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
How Masters Universe politicians bring back moral hazard.,null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Banking Financial Institutions},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Dodd-Frank Wall Street Reform Consumer Protection Act 2010},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Lobbying Lobbyists},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Regulation Deregulation Industry},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Federal Budget US},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Law Legislation},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:7,value:<ORGANIZATION>Citigroup Inc<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:8,value:Republican Party},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:9,value:Democratic Party}]",Opinion,"<PERSON>Paul Krugman</PERSON> Op-Ed column asserts Wall Street taking revenge tighter government oversight <ORGANIZATION>Congress</ORGANIZATION> roll back provision Dodd-Frank financial reform bill; charges lawmakers pockets, banking fat cats return risky wheeling dealing helped financial crisis.",The New York Times,[],Editorial,2014-12-15T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/11/12/opinion/krugman-circular/krugman-circular-thumbWide-v2.png},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/11/12/opinion/krugman-circular/krugman-circular-thumbWide-v2.png,height:126},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/11/12/opinion/krugman-circular/krugman-circular-thumbStandard-v2.png,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/11/12/opinion/krugman-circular/krugman-circular-thumbStandard-v2.png,height:75}]",788,How Masters Universe politicians bring back moral hazard.,Op-Ed,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/15/opinion/paul-krugman-dodd-frank-damaged-by-the-budget-bill.html,548e52d879881018ac4ba143,null,"{content_kicker:Op-Ed Columnist,main:Wall Street&#8217;s Revenge,seo:Dodd-Frank Damaged Budget Bill,print_headline:Wall Street’s Revenge,kicker:Op-Ed Columnist}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>PAUL KRUGMAN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Paul,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:KRUGMAN}]}",article
"Japanese Prime Minister <PERSON>Shinzo Abe</PERSON>'s coalition cruised big election win, ensuring stick reflationary economic policies muscular security stance, record low turnout pointed broad dissatisfaction performance.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-14T02:49:58Z,[],783,"Japanese Prime Minister <PERSON>Shinzo Abe</PERSON>'s coalition cruised big election win, ensuring stick reflationary economic policies muscular security stance, record low turnout pointed broad dissatisfaction performance.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/14/world/asia/14reuters-japan-election.html,548d41b8798810543aba5480,Asia Pacific,"{main:Abe Coalition Secures Big <LOCATION>Japan<\/LOCATION> Election Win With Record Low Turnout,print_headline:Abe Coalition Secures Big <LOCATION>Japan<\/LOCATION> Election Win With Record Low Turnout}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
<LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION>'s Prime Minister <PERSON>Shinzo Abe</PERSON> faces strong resistance promised economic political overhaul weekend election victory years power.,null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-14T02:14:13Z,[],788,<LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION>'s Prime Minister <PERSON>Shinzo Abe</PERSON> faces strong resistance promised economic political overhaul weekend election victory years power.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/14/world/asia/ap-as-japan-election.html,548d3989798810543aba53c1,Asia Pacific,"{main:<LOCATION>Japan<\/LOCATION> Abe Faces Battle Reforms Despite Vote Win,print_headline:<LOCATION>Japan<\/LOCATION> Abe Faces Battle Reforms Despite Vote Win}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
