snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Societe Generale's senior base metals trader, <PERSON>Mike Turek</PERSON>, <PERSON>Natasha Flora</PERSON>, energy trader, left bank <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> <DATE>Thursday</DATE>, part wider retrenchment French bank's takeover <ORGANIZATION>Newedge</ORGANIZATION>, sources told <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-11T17:24:06Z,[],333,"Societe Generale's senior base metals trader, <PERSON>Mike Turek</PERSON>, <PERSON>Natasha Flora</PERSON>, energy trader, left bank <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> <DATE>Thursday</DATE>, part wider retrenchment French bank's takeover <ORGANIZATION>Newedge</ORGANIZATION>, sources told <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/11/business/11reuters-newedge-socgen-commodities.html,548a19e17988102fcc1300ea,null,"{main:<ORGANIZATION>Newedge Metal<\/ORGANIZATION>, Energy Traders Leave SocGen Cuts Headcount,print_headline:<ORGANIZATION>Newedge Metal<\/ORGANIZATION>, Energy Traders Leave SocGen Cuts Headcount}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<ORGANIZATION>Merck KGaA</ORGANIZATION> aims to keep hold of its consumer healthcare unit, it said on <DATE>Friday</DATE>, pledging to develop a business that is expected to generate <DATE>2014</DATE> sales of <MONEY>$1 billion 0.63 billion pounds</MONEY> for the German drugs and chemicals company.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-11-28T09:24:55Z,[],375,"<ORGANIZATION>Merck KGaA</ORGANIZATION> aims to keep hold of its consumer healthcare unit, it said on <DATE>Friday</DATE>, pledging to develop a business that is expected to generate <DATE>2014</DATE> sales of <MONEY>$1 billion 0.63 billion pounds</MONEY> for the German drugs and chemicals company.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/11/28/business/28reuters-merck-consumers.html,5478867679881006dca8c3c1,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Germany<\/LOCATION>'s Merck Aims to Grow, Not Sell <MONEY>$1 Billion<\/MONEY> Consumer Health Arm,print_headline:<LOCATION>Germany<\/LOCATION>'s Merck Aims to Grow, Not Sell <MONEY>$1 Billion<\/MONEY> Consumer Health Arm}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"For good stock market bets, top investors bothered details corporate profits:, pick companies run founders.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-11-04T15:50:16Z,[],1004,"For good stock market bets, top investors bothered details corporate profits:, pick companies run founders.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/11/04/business/04reuters-stocks-investment-founders-insight.html,54593c6a79881027068435e0,null,"{main:Insight-Top Investors Stay Loyal Big Name Corporate Founders,print_headline:Insight-Top Investors Stay Loyal Big Name Corporate Founders}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Over-the-counter drugmaker Unipharm is up for sale and has hired advisory firm <PERSON>Houlihan Lokey</PERSON> to explore a deal that could value it at around <MONEY>$500 million 310.83 million pounds</MONEY>, three sources familiar with the matter told <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-10-24T14:04:20Z,[],563,"Over-the-counter drugmaker Unipharm is up for sale and has hired advisory firm <PERSON>Houlihan Lokey</PERSON> to explore a deal that could value it at around <MONEY>$500 million 310.83 million pounds</MONEY>, three sources familiar with the matter told <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/10/24/business/24reuters-unipharm-m-a-exclusive.html,544a9545798810574ee7c4c7,null,"{main:Exclusive-Unipharm Hires <PERSON>Houlihan Lokey<\/PERSON> to Explore <MONEY>$500 Million<\/MONEY> Sale - Sources,print_headline:Exclusive-Unipharm Hires <PERSON>Houlihan Lokey<\/PERSON> to Explore <MONEY>$500 Million<\/MONEY> Sale - Sources}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Italian drugmaker Sigma-Tau advanced talks sell part Italian operations domestic peer <PERSON>Alfa Wassermann</PERSON> create over-the-counter OTC powerhouse, sources familiar situation.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-10-20T15:47:17Z,[],653,"Italian drugmaker Sigma-Tau advanced talks sell part Italian operations domestic peer <PERSON>Alfa Wassermann</PERSON> create over-the-counter OTC powerhouse, sources familiar situation.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/10/20/business/20reuters-sigma-tau-m-a-alfa.html,54456766798810347c1a833f,null,"{main:Sigma-Tau, <PERSON>Alfa Wassermann<\/PERSON> Talks Combine Italian Operations- Sources,print_headline:Sigma-Tau, <PERSON>Alfa Wassermann<\/PERSON> Talks Combine Italian Operations- Sources}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Clearing houses make trading derivatives safer spell recover crisis needing taxpayer bailouts, rules global regulators <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-10-15T12:27:02Z,[],401,"Clearing houses make trading derivatives safer spell recover crisis needing taxpayer bailouts, rules global regulators <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/10/15/business/15reuters-clearing-derivatives-rules.html,543ea18579881001751bf4a4,null,"{main:New Rules Stop Clearers Becoming 'Too Big Fail',print_headline:New Rules Stop Clearers Becoming 'Too Big Fail'}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Women exploring conception aids option: The <ORGANIZATION>Stork OTC</ORGANIZATION>, over-the counter cervical cap designed collect sperm intercourse.",null,"[{name:subject,rank:1,value:Artificial Insemination},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Infertility},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Parenting},{name:subject,rank:4,value:Pregnancy Childbirth},{name:subject,rank:5,value:Sperm}]",<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,"Women exploring conception aids option: The <ORGANIZATION>Stork OTC</ORGANIZATION>, over-the counter cervical cap designed collect sperm intercourse.",The New York Times,[],Styles,2014-10-08T15:44:30Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/10/08/us/motherlode-stork/motherlode-stork-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/10/08/us/motherlode-stork/motherlode-stork-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/10/08/us/motherlode-stork/motherlode-stork-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:265},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/10/08/us/motherlode-stork/motherlode-stork-articleLarge.jpg,height:265},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/10/08/us/motherlode-stork/motherlode-stork-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/10/08/us/motherlode-stork/motherlode-stork-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",274,null,Blog,http://parenting.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/10/08/an-over-the-counter-at-home-conception-aid/,5435946b798810520e354ade,null,"{main:An Over-the Counter At-Home Conception Aid,kicker:Motherlode}","{original:By KJ.DELL'ANTONIA,person:[{firstname:Kj,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:DELL'ANTONIA}]}",blogpost
Swiss drugmaker <ORGANIZATION>Novartis AG</ORGANIZATION> members executive committee leave company completion transactions <ORGANIZATION>GlaxoSmithKline Eli Lilly</ORGANIZATION> divest units.,null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-10-08T01:34:56Z,[],244,Swiss drugmaker <ORGANIZATION>Novartis AG</ORGANIZATION> members executive committee leave company completion transactions <ORGANIZATION>GlaxoSmithKline Eli Lilly</ORGANIZATION> divest units.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/10/08/business/08reuters-novartis-moves.html,5434cd8c79881017f2d284d9,null,"{main:Novartis Says Three Executives Leave After <ORGANIZATION>GSK<\/ORGANIZATION>, <PERSON>Lilly<\/PERSON> Deals,print_headline:Novartis Says Three Executives Leave After <ORGANIZATION>GSK<\/ORGANIZATION>, <PERSON>Lilly<\/PERSON> Deals}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Fraud market penny stocks continues unabated, criminal cases filed week show, <PERSON>Peter J. Henning</PERSON> writes White Collar Watch column.",null,"[{name:organizations,rank:1,value:Cynk Technology Corp},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Frauds Swindling},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Regulation Deregulation Industry},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Securities Commodities Violations}]",Business Day,"Fraud market penny stocks continues unabated, criminal cases filed week show, <PERSON>Peter J. Henning</PERSON> writes White Collar Watch column.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-09-15T12:03:39Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/09/15/business/dealbook/dbpix-wolf/dbpix-wolf-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/09/15/business/dealbook/dbpix-wolf/dbpix-wolf-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/09/15/business/dealbook/dbpix-wolf/dbpix-wolf-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/09/15/business/dealbook/dbpix-wolf/dbpix-wolf-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/09/15/business/dealbook/dbpix-wolf/dbpix-wolf-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/09/15/business/dealbook/dbpix-wolf/dbpix-wolf-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1077,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/09/15/greed-continues-to-fuel-penny-stock-frauds/,54170e9d79881018c378ee16,Dealbook,"{main:Greed Continues Fuel Penny Stock Frauds,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>PETER J. HENNING<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Peter,role:reported,organization:,middlename:J.,rank:1,lastname:HENNING}]}",blogpost
Tensions growing regional regulators proposal collateral requirements make costly Asian companies trade European banks off-exchange derivatives -- complex financial products...,null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],null,2014-09-11T07:49:11Z,[],1140,Tensions growing regional regulators proposal collateral requirements make costly Asian companies trade European banks off-exchange derivatives -- complex financial products hedge price swings underlying assets ranging interest rates commodities.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/09/11/business/11reuters-financial-regulations-swaps.html,54118cd379881060c5af945d,null,"{main:<ORGANIZATION>EU<\/ORGANIZATION>'s OTC Derivatives Proposals Threaten Asian Regulatory Clash,print_headline:<ORGANIZATION>EU<\/ORGANIZATION>'s OTC Derivatives Proposals Threaten Asian Regulatory Clash}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
