snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Ms. <PERSON>Armstrong</PERSON> discusses book, examines relationship religion violence history.",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:Armstrong, <PERSON>Karen<\/PERSON>},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Books Literature},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Crusades Christianity},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Religion Belief}]",Arts,"Ms. <PERSON>Armstrong</PERSON> discusses book, examines relationship religion violence history.",The New York Times,[],Culture,2014-12-26T14:19:59Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/26/books/26armstrong/26armstrong-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/books/26armstrong/26armstrong-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/26/books/26armstrong/26armstrong-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:465},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/books/26armstrong/26armstrong-articleLarge.jpg,height:465},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/26/books/26armstrong/26armstrong-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/books/26armstrong/26armstrong-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1583,null,Blog,http://artsbeat.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/26/the-blame-game-karen-armstrong-talks-about-fields-of-blood/,549db4f17988105ced7885ca,null,"{main:The Blame Game: <PERSON>Karen Armstrong<\/PERSON> Talks About 'Fields Blood',print_headline:Challenging Critics Religion Who Blame It Violence,kicker:ArtsBeat}","{original:By <PERSON>JOHN WILLIAMS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:John,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:WILLIAMS}]}",blogpost
The <ORGANIZATION>Ohio House</ORGANIZATION> gave final approval week plan draw voting districts <ORGANIZATION>General Assembly</ORGANIZATION> bipartisan process intended make elections competitive.,28,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:State Legislatures},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:2,value:Ohio},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Elections, State Legislature},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Republican Party},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:5,value:Democratic Party},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Redistricting Reapportionment}]",<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,The New York Times,[],National,2014-12-21T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/21/us/21ohio1-web/21ohio1-web-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/21/us/21ohio1-web/21ohio1-web-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/21/us/21ohio1-web/21ohio1-web-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:450},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/21/us/21ohio1-web/21ohio1-web-articleLarge.jpg,height:450},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/21/us/21ohio1-web/21ohio1-web-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/21/us/21ohio1-web/21ohio1-web-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1019,The <ORGANIZATION>Ohio House</ORGANIZATION> gave final approval week plan draw voting districts <ORGANIZATION>General Assembly</ORGANIZATION> bipartisan process intended make elections competitive.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/21/us/politics/in-a-break-from-partisan-rancor-ohio-moves-to-make-elections-more-competitive.html,5495d3f179881029b367ddd3,Politics,"{main:In Break From Partisan Rancor, <LOCATION>Ohio<\/LOCATION> Moves Make Elections More Competitive,print_headline:In Break From Partisan Rancor, <LOCATION>Ohio<\/LOCATION> Moves Make Elections More Competitive}","{contributor:,original:By TRIP GABRIEL,person:[{firstname:Trip,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:GABRIEL}]}",article
The “Selma” director says viewers have turned to her for answers about the <PERSON>Michael Brown</PERSON> and <PERSON>Eric Garner</PERSON> cases.,null,"[{name:type_of_material,rank:1,value:News},{name:persons,rank:2,value:DuVernay, Ava},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Movies},{name:creative_works,rank:4,value:Selma Movie},{name:creative_works,rank:5,value:Zero Dark Thirty Movie}]",null,The “Selma” director says viewers have turned to her for answers about the <PERSON>Michael Brown</PERSON> and <PERSON>Eric Garner</PERSON> cases.,The New York Times,[],null,2014-12-12T10:00:55Z,[],501,"There plenty instances years Hollywood movies American politics, sociopolitical realities, intersect.",Blog,http://carpetbagger.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/12/selma-history-and-protests-today/,548b03797988102fcc13161f,null,"{main:‘Selma,’ History and Protests Today,kicker:Carpetbagger}","{original:By <PERSON>CARA BUCKLEY<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Cara,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BUCKLEY}]}",blogpost
"Because refereeing mistake late game Locust Grove <PERSON>Frederick A. Douglass</PERSON> high schools, <LOCATION>Oklahoma</LOCATION>&#8217;s Class 3A playoffs hinge judge&#8217;s decision.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Football},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Interscholastic Athletics},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:3,value:<LOCATION>Oklahoma<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Officiating Sports}]",Sports,"Class 3A football playoffs <LOCATION>Oklahoma</LOCATION>'s midsize schools delayed district judge upholds invalidates <LOCATION>Locust Grove</LOCATION>'s disputed quarterfinal victory Nov 28 Frederick A <ORGANIZATION>Douglass High School</ORGANIZATION> <LOCATION>Oklahoma City</LOCATION>; <PERSON>Douglass</PERSON> game partly replayed critical, admitted error made referees negating late touchdown.",The New York Times,[],Sports,2014-12-09T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/09/sports/Y-FOOTBALL-1/Y-FOOTBALL-1-thumbWide-v2.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/09/sports/Y-FOOTBALL-1/Y-FOOTBALL-1-thumbWide-v2.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/09/sports/Y-FOOTBALL-1/Y-FOOTBALL-1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:399},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/09/sports/Y-FOOTBALL-1/Y-FOOTBALL-1-articleLarge.jpg,height:399},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/09/sports/Y-FOOTBALL-1/Y-FOOTBALL-1-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/09/sports/Y-FOOTBALL-1/Y-FOOTBALL-1-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",1321,"Because refereeing mistake late game Locust Grove <PERSON>Frederick A. Douglass</PERSON> high schools, <LOCATION>Oklahoma</LOCATION>&#8217;s Class 3A playoffs hinge judge&#8217;s decision.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/09/sports/court-weighs-intervening-in-oklahoma-high-school-football-playoffs.html,54860faf7988101981f9ea6d,null,"{main:After Referees Blunder, Next Call Is Judge&#8217;s,seo:Court Weighs Intervening Oklahoma High School Football Playoffs,print_headline:After Referees Blunder, Next Call Is a Judge’s}","{contributor:,original:By JERÉ LONGMAN,person:[{firstname:Jeré,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:LONGMAN}]}",article
"Lawyers for <PERSON>Jason Puello</PERSON>, who, at 19, is too old to play for the basketball team, say that basing eligibility on when students’ birthdays fall means that the <ORGANIZATION>Education Department</ORGANIZATION> treats winter and <DATE>spring</DATE> sports differently.",23,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Education K-12},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:2,value:Education Department NYC},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Interscholastic Athletics},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:4,value:Puello, <PERSON>Jason<\/PERSON> <DATE>1995<\/DATE>-},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:5,value:Age, Chronological},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:Public Schools Athletic League},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:7,value:<LOCATION>Washington<\/LOCATION> Heights Expeditionary Learning School},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:8,value:<LOCATION>Washington Heights Manhattan<\/LOCATION>, NY},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:9,value:Athletics Sports}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"<PERSON>Jim Dwyer</PERSON> About <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> column focuses plight 19-year-old <LOCATION>Washington Heights</LOCATION> high school athlete <PERSON>Jason Puello</PERSON>, deemed ineligible play basketball senior year age; lawyers Puello suing <ORGANIZATION>Education Dept</ORGANIZATION>, arguing basing eligibility students' birthdays fall calendar inequity athletes depending sports season.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-11-21T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/11/21/nyregion/21ABOUT/21ABOUT-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/11/21/nyregion/21ABOUT/21ABOUT-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/11/21/nyregion/21ABOUT/21ABOUT-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/11/21/nyregion/21ABOUT/21ABOUT-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/11/21/nyregion/21ABOUT/21ABOUT-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/11/21/nyregion/21ABOUT/21ABOUT-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",789,"Lawyers for <PERSON>Jason Puello</PERSON>, who, at 19, is too old to play for the basketball team, say that basing eligibility on when students’ birthdays fall means that the <ORGANIZATION>Education Department</ORGANIZATION> treats winter and <DATE>spring</DATE> sports differently.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/11/21/nyregion/set-back-by-hardship-a-student-athlete-runs-up-against-an-age-restriction.html,546e9c4e7988106ad45c685a,null,"{content_kicker:About <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION>,main:Set Back Hardship, Student Athlete Runs Up Against Age Restriction,print_headline:Set Back Hardship, Student Athlete Runs Up Against Age Restriction,kicker:About <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION>}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>JIM DWYER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Jim,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:DWYER}]}",article
The prospects <LOCATION>Atlantic City</LOCATION>'s crumbling casino market worsening.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-11-20T10:58:07Z,[],531,The prospects <LOCATION>Atlantic City</LOCATION>'s crumbling casino market worsening.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/11/20/us/ap-us-atlantic-city-casino-closings.html,546e0fca79881016298c7aad,null,"{main:Future Dim Taj Mahal, Former Revel Casinos,print_headline:Future Dim Taj Mahal, Former Revel Casinos}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"A Toronto-based company abandoned plan buy Revel Casino Hotel <LOCATION>Atlantic City</LOCATION> <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>, dealing blow city reeling string casino closures disappearance thousands jobs.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-11-19T18:12:32Z,[],634,"A Toronto-based company abandoned plan buy Revel Casino Hotel <LOCATION>Atlantic City</LOCATION> <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>, dealing blow city reeling string casino closures disappearance thousands jobs.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/11/19/us/ap-us-revel-sale.html,546d24ac79881016298c77d8,null,"{main:Firm Cancels Plan Buy Closed Revel Hotel Casino,print_headline:Firm Cancels Plan Buy Closed Revel Hotel Casino}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Two agricultural companies sued <LOCATION>Maui County</LOCATION> <DATE>Thursday</DATE> challenge law banning cultivation genetically modified organisms.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-11-13T18:32:40Z,[],419,Two agricultural companies sued <LOCATION>Maui County</LOCATION> <DATE>Thursday</DATE> challenge law banning cultivation genetically modified organisms.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/11/13/us/ap-us-maui-gmo-ban.html,546635e079881049c19039af,null,"{main:<ORGANIZATION>Monsanto<\/ORGANIZATION>, Dow Unit Sue <LOCATION>Maui County<\/LOCATION> Over <ORGANIZATION>GMO<\/ORGANIZATION> Law,print_headline:<ORGANIZATION>Monsanto<\/ORGANIZATION>, Dow Unit Sue <LOCATION>Maui County<\/LOCATION> Over <ORGANIZATION>GMO<\/ORGANIZATION> Law}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Small cities <ORGANIZATION>Federal Communications Commission</ORGANIZATION> power override laws 19 states limit municipalities building expanding broadband networks.,null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Cooper<\/PERSON>, Mark},{name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Wheeler<\/PERSON>, Thomas E},{name:glocations,rank:1,value:Chattanooga Tenn},{name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>North Carolina<\/LOCATION>},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:Consumer Federation America},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:Federal Communications Commission},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Computers Internet}]",Technology,Small cities <ORGANIZATION>Federal Communications Commission</ORGANIZATION> power override laws 19 states limit municipalities building expanding broadband networks.,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-11-10T06:29:23Z,"[{legacy:{xlarge:images/2011/11/30/technology/bits-daily-report/bits-daily-report-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2011/11/30/technology/bits-daily-report/bits-daily-report-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2011/11/30/technology/bits-daily-report/bits-daily-report-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2011/11/30/technology/bits-daily-report/bits-daily-report-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",190,null,Blog,http://bits.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/11/10/daily-report-fighting-laws-that-can-limit-access-to-high-speed-web/,5460a30b7988106af1739a94,null,"{main:Daily Report: Fighting State Laws That Can Limit Access High-Speed Web,kicker:Bits}","{original:By THE <LOCATION>NEW YORK<\/LOCATION> TIMES,person:[],organization:The New York Times}",blogpost
Small cities F.C.C. power override laws 19 states forbid municipalities build expand broadband networks.,1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Computers Internet},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:2,value:Federal Communications Commission},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:States US},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:4,value:Wilson NC},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:5,value:Chattanooga Tenn},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Local Government}]",Technology,null,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-11-10T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/11/10/business/subbroadband/subbroadband-thumbWide-v2.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/11/10/business/subbroadband/subbroadband-thumbWide-v2.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/11/10/business/subbroadband/subbroadband-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:477},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/11/10/business/subbroadband/subbroadband-articleLarge.jpg,height:477},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/11/10/business/subbroadband/subbroadband-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/11/10/business/subbroadband/subbroadband-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",1350,Small cities F.C.C. power override laws 19 states forbid municipalities build expand broadband networks.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/11/10/technology/in-rural-america-challenging-a-roadblock-to-high-speed-internet.html,545ff6cd7988106af1739912,null,"{main:Communities Fight State Laws That Can Divide Broadband Access,print_headline:The Net’s Fallow Lands}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>EDWARD WYATT<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Edward,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:WYATT}]}",article
