snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"In <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Iowa</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>New Hampshire</LOCATION>, place talking <DATE>2016</DATE> campaign president, expects <PERSON>Hillary Rodham Clinton</PERSON> run president.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T12:21:40Z,[],1091,"In <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Iowa</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>New Hampshire</LOCATION>, place talking <DATE>2016</DATE> campaign president, expects <PERSON>Hillary Rodham Clinton</PERSON> run president.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/us/politics/ap-us-dem-2016-if-not-hillary.html,54a583047988102023c93e7c,Politics,"{main:What <PERSON>Hillary Clinton<\/PERSON> Doesn't Run President??,print_headline:What <PERSON>Hillary Clinton<\/PERSON> Doesn't Run President??}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<LOCATION>India</LOCATION> scrapped 65-year-old <ORGANIZATION>Planning Commission</ORGANIZATION>, Prime Minister <PERSON>Narendra Modi</PERSON> accused stifling growth Soviet-style bureaucracy, replacing <DATE>Thursday</DATE> body involve regions.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T10:36:52Z,[],362,"<LOCATION>India</LOCATION> scrapped 65-year-old <ORGANIZATION>Planning Commission</ORGANIZATION>, Prime Minister <PERSON>Narendra Modi</PERSON> accused stifling growth Soviet-style bureaucracy, replacing <DATE>Thursday</DATE> body involve regions.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/world/asia/01reuters-india-politics.html,54a56a4979881011bed2cc20,Asia Pacific,"{main:<LOCATION>India<\/LOCATION> PM Replaces Soviet-Style Planning Body, Aiming Boost Growth,print_headline:<LOCATION>India<\/LOCATION> PM Replaces Soviet-Style Planning Body, Aiming Boost Growth}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"A group thieves arrive snowbound town Deadwood, <LOCATION>South Dakota</LOCATION> intention vacationing... planning giant gold heist.",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T10:22:41Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/06/movies/video-beast-from-haunted-cave/video-beast-from-haunted-cave-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/06/movies/video-beast-from-haunted-cave/video-beast-from-haunted-cave-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/06/movies/video-beast-from-haunted-cave/video-beast-from-haunted-cave-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/06/movies/video-beast-from-haunted-cave/video-beast-from-haunted-cave-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/06/movies/video-beast-from-haunted-cave/video-beast-from-haunted-cave-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/06/movies/video-beast-from-haunted-cave/video-beast-from-haunted-cave-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",26,"A group thieves arrive snowbound town Deadwood, <LOCATION>South Dakota</LOCATION> intention vacationing... planning giant gold heist.",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003290732/beast-from-haunted-cave.html,54a5664c79881011bed2cb3a,null,{"main":"Beast From Haunted Cave"},"{original:Synapse Films,person:[{firstname:Synapse,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Films}]}",multimedia
Documentary-style chronicle days lives young men <LOCATION>Brooklyn</LOCATION> planning heist.,null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T04:21:16Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-laws-of-gravity/video-laws-of-gravity-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-laws-of-gravity/video-laws-of-gravity-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-laws-of-gravity/video-laws-of-gravity-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-laws-of-gravity/video-laws-of-gravity-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-laws-of-gravity/video-laws-of-gravity-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-laws-of-gravity/video-laws-of-gravity-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",17,Documentary-style chronicle days lives young men <LOCATION>Brooklyn</LOCATION> planning heist.,Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003348799/laws-of-gravity.html,54a511e679881011bed2b846,null,{"main":"Laws Of Gravity"},"{original:Triboro,person:[{firstname:Triboro,role:reported,organization:,rank:1}]}",multimedia
Bundled-up revelers planning usher <DATE>2015</DATE> Las Vegas Strip watch flower-decorated floats <ORGANIZATION>Rose Parade Southern California</ORGANIZATION> dealing near-freezing temperatures early <DATE>Thursday</DATE> blustery winter storm dumped show...,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T03:13:03Z,[],704,Bundled-up revelers planning usher <DATE>2015</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>Las Vegas Strip</ORGANIZATION> watch flower-decorated floats <ORGANIZATION>Rose Parade Southern California</ORGANIZATION> dealing near-freezing temperatures early <DATE>Thursday</DATE> blustery winter storm dumped show ice West.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/us/ap-us-new-years-storm.html,54a5024879881011bed2b4c4,null,"{main:Storm Brings Snow, Cold West New Year's,print_headline:Storm Brings Snow, Cold West New Year's}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Based <PERSON>David Mamet</PERSON>'s hit play, crooks spend long hours junk shop, bickering, bantering, waxing philosophical, planning small-time heist. Richly comic performances <PERSON>Franz Hoffman</PERSON>.",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T01:47:43Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-american-buffalo/video-american-buffalo-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-american-buffalo/video-american-buffalo-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-american-buffalo/video-american-buffalo-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-american-buffalo/video-american-buffalo-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-american-buffalo/video-american-buffalo-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-american-buffalo/video-american-buffalo-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",35,"Based <PERSON>David Mamet</PERSON>'s hit play, crooks spend long hours junk shop, bickering, bantering, waxing philosophical, planning small-time heist. Richly comic performances <PERSON>Franz Hoffman</PERSON>.",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003286444/american-buffalo.html,54a4ed9379881011bed2b014,null,{"main":"American Buffalo"},"{original:Hallmark Entertainment,person:[{firstname:Hallmark,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Entertainment}]}",multimedia
Chinese state media public criticized government police <DATE>Friday</DATE> failing prevent New Year's Eve stampede <LOCATION>Shanghai</LOCATION> killed 36 people dented city's image modern <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s global financial hub.,null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T01:07:17Z,[],435,Chinese state media public criticized government police <DATE>Friday</DATE> failing prevent New Year's Eve stampede <LOCATION>Shanghai</LOCATION> killed 36 people dented city's image modern <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s global financial hub.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/world/asia/01reuters-china-stampede.html,54a4e4b979881011bed2ae0d,Asia Pacific,"{main:<ORGANIZATION>China Demands Answers After Stampede Financial Hub Shanghai<\/ORGANIZATION>,print_headline:<ORGANIZATION>China Demands Answers After Stampede Financial Hub Shanghai<\/ORGANIZATION>}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"A million people crammed <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>'s Times Square ushered <DATE>2015</DATE> cheers, hugs kisses glittering New Year's Eve ball descended high ton confetti wafted revelers.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T00:41:00Z,[],539,"A million people crammed <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>'s Times Square ushered <DATE>2015</DATE> cheers, hugs kisses glittering New Year's Eve ball descended high ton confetti wafted revelers.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/us/ap-us-new-years-eve-nyc.html,54a4de7379881011bed2aca1,null,"{main:Crystal Ball Drops <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION>, Ushering 2015,print_headline:Crystal Ball Drops <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION>, Ushering 2015}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"A mysterious criminal <PERSON>Mullen Jr.</PERSON> rolls small town planning knock local bank, assuming hitch. But encounters retired poetry professor <PERSON>Sutherland</PERSON>, plans turn. With place",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T00:40:42Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/04/14/movies/video-man-on-the-train/video-man-on-the-train-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/04/14/movies/video-man-on-the-train/video-man-on-the-train-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/04/14/movies/video-man-on-the-train/video-man-on-the-train-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/04/14/movies/video-man-on-the-train/video-man-on-the-train-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/04/14/movies/video-man-on-the-train/video-man-on-the-train-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/04/14/movies/video-man-on-the-train/video-man-on-the-train-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",43,"A mysterious criminal <PERSON>Mullen Jr.</PERSON> rolls small town planning knock local bank, assuming hitch. But encounters retired poetry professor <PERSON>Sutherland</PERSON>, plans turn. With place",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003393086/man-on-the-train.html,54a4dde279881011bed2ac7f,null,{"main":"Man On The Train"},"{original:Tribeca Films,person:[{firstname:<LOCATION>Tribeca<\/LOCATION>,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Films}]}",multimedia
"Rigorous evidence should inform spending. Until lately, it hasn’t.",19,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:United States Politics Government},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:11,value:Research},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Federal Budget US},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:3,value:United States},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:4,value:<PERSON>Obama<\/PERSON>, Barack},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:5,value:House Representatives},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:Senate},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:7,value:Republican Party},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:8,value:Education K-12},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:9,value:Nurse-Family Partnership},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:10,value:Success All Foundation}]",Opinion,"Op-Ed article policy analyst <PERSON>Ron Haskins</PERSON> applauds <PERSON>Obama</PERSON> administration's long-term evidence-based results improving social policy; holds choice social welfare programs based rigorous evidence success; urges <ORGANIZATION>Congress</ORGANIZATION> reject Republican efforts cut <PERSON>Obama</PERSON> administration's evidence-based programs, social policy important left guesswork.",The New York Times,[],OpEd,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/opinion/01Haskins/01Haskins-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/opinion/01Haskins/01Haskins-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/opinion/01Haskins/01Haskins-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:486},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/opinion/01Haskins/01Haskins-articleLarge.jpg,height:486},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/opinion/01Haskins/01Haskins-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/opinion/01Haskins/01Haskins-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",919,"Rigorous evidence should inform spending. Until lately, it hasn’t.",Op-Ed,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/opinion/social-programs-that-work.html,54a4a21679881011bed29ed4,null,"{content_kicker:Op-Ed Contributor,main:Social Programs That Work,print_headline:Social Programs That Work,kicker:Op-Ed Contributor}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>RON HASKINS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Ron,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:HASKINS}]}",article
