snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
A scary bounty hunter young businessman <DATE>19th century</DATE> American West swap horror stories campfire.,null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T01:39:02Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-grim-prairie-tales/video-grim-prairie-tales-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-grim-prairie-tales/video-grim-prairie-tales-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-grim-prairie-tales/video-grim-prairie-tales-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:348},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-grim-prairie-tales/video-grim-prairie-tales-articleLarge.jpg,height:348},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-grim-prairie-tales/video-grim-prairie-tales-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-grim-prairie-tales/video-grim-prairie-tales-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",20,A scary bounty hunter young businessman <DATE>19th century</DATE> American West swap horror stories campfire.,Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003329114/grim-prairie-tales.html,54a4eb8b79881011bed2af9e,null,{"main":"Grim Prairie Tales"},"{original:Winstar,person:[{firstname:Winstar,role:reported,organization:,rank:1}]}",multimedia
"At Forest Ridge Mall, head security <PERSON>Ronnie Barnhardt</PERSON> patrols jurisdiction iron fist, combating skateboarders, shoplifters occasional unruly customer dreaming day swap flashlight badge",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2014-12-31T13:31:49Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-observe-and-report/video-observe-and-report-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-observe-and-report/video-observe-and-report-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-observe-and-report/video-observe-and-report-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-observe-and-report/video-observe-and-report-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-observe-and-report/video-observe-and-report-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-observe-and-report/video-observe-and-report-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",40,"At Forest Ridge Mall, head security <PERSON>Ronnie Barnhardt</PERSON> patrols jurisdiction iron fist, combating skateboarders, shoplifters occasional unruly customer dreaming day swap flashlight badge",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003360182/observe-and-report.html,54a4411979881011bed28908,null,{"main":"Observe And Report"},"{original:<ORGANIZATION>Warner Bros<\/ORGANIZATION>. Pictures,person:[{firstname:Warner,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Bros}]}",multimedia
"After swap Sgt. <PERSON>Bowe Bergdahl</PERSON> Taliban fighters provoked criticism, <ORGANIZATION>White House</ORGANIZATION> officials told <LOCATION>Cuba</LOCATION> deal release <PERSON>Alan P. Gross</PERSON> quid pro quo.",7,"[{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Bergdahl<\/PERSON>, Bowe R},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>Cuba<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:Gross, <PERSON>Alan Phillip 1949<\/PERSON>-},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Taliban},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:5,value:Prisons Prisoners},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:United States International Relations}]",<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,Diplomatic Memo; <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> prisoners swap Taliban release Sgt <PERSON>Bowe Bergdahl</PERSON> affected secret negotiations <LOCATION>Cuba US</LOCATION> release Alan P Gross exchange Cubans imprisoned <LOCATION>US</LOCATION>; deal include re-establishment ties <LOCATION>Cuba</LOCATION> negative domestic reaction exchange <PERSON>Taliban Bergdahl</PERSON>.,The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-31T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/world/31prexy-2/31prexy-2-thumbWide-v2.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/world/31prexy-2/31prexy-2-thumbWide-v2.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/world/31prexy-2/31prexy-2-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:387},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/world/31prexy-2/31prexy-2-articleLarge.jpg,height:387},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/world/31prexy-2/31prexy-2-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/world/31prexy-2/31prexy-2-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",1131,"After swap Sgt. <PERSON>Bowe Bergdahl</PERSON> Taliban fighters provoked criticism, <ORGANIZATION>White House</ORGANIZATION> officials told <LOCATION>Cuba</LOCATION> deal release <PERSON>Alan P. Gross</PERSON> quid pro quo.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/us/how-cuba-talks-were-reshaped-by-the-release-of-bergdahl.html,54a2f7aa7988102761d6cea4,Politics,"{content_kicker:Listening Post,main:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Swap <PERSON>Bergdahl<\/PERSON> Shook Up Secret Talks With <LOCATION>Cuba<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Swap <PERSON>Bergdahl<\/PERSON> Shook Up Secret Talks With <LOCATION>Cuba<\/LOCATION>,kicker:Listening Post}","{contributor:,original:By MARK LANDLER,person:[{firstname:Mark,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:LANDLER}]}",article
"The <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> called <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> release <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> citizens held <LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION>, denied report <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION> proposed prisoner exchange <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Marine.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T13:53:49Z,[],284,"The <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> called <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> release <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> citizens held <LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION>, denied report <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION> proposed prisoner exchange <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Marine.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/world/middleeast/30reuters-iran-us-prisoners-americans.html,54a2f50f7988102761d6ce9e,Middle East,"{main:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Calls Release Americans <LOCATION>Iran<\/LOCATION>, Denies Swap Deal,print_headline:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Calls Release Americans <LOCATION>Iran<\/LOCATION>, Denies Swap Deal}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Cuban police detained dissidents <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> thwarted unauthorized political protest, dissidents, major test <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON>'s policy shift normalizing relations communist-ruled island.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T13:42:19Z,[],626,"Cuban police detained dissidents <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> thwarted unauthorized political protest, dissidents, major test <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON>'s policy shift normalizing relations communist-ruled island.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/world/americas/30reuters-cuba-usa-dissidents.html,54a2f2347988102761d6ce97,Americas,"{main:Cuban Open Mic Protest Thwarted After Dissidents Detained,print_headline:Cuban Open Mic Protest Thwarted After Dissidents Detained}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> proposed exchange Iranian prisoners <LOCATION>U.S. U.S.</LOCATION> Marine prison <LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION>, semiofficial <ORGANIZATION>ISNA</ORGANIZATION> news agency reported <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> &#8212; report immediately denied <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION>.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T12:34:44Z,[],337,"The <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> proposed exchange Iranian prisoners <LOCATION>U.S. U.S.</LOCATION> Marine prison <LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION>, semiofficial <ORGANIZATION>ISNA</ORGANIZATION> news agency reported <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> &#8212; report immediately denied <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/world/middleeast/ap-ml-iran-us-prisoner-swap.html,54a2e2d77988102761d6ce68,Middle East,"{main:Lawyer: US Offers Prisoner Exchange Detained Ex-Marine,print_headline:Lawyer: US Offers Prisoner Exchange Detained Ex-Marine}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"The <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> called <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> release <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> citizens held <LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION>, denied report <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION> proposed prisoner exchange <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Marine.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T10:40:45Z,[],421,"The <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> called <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> release <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> citizens held <LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION>, denied report <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION> proposed prisoner exchange <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Marine.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/world/middleeast/30reuters-iran-us-prisoners.html,54a2c8067988104803cc8acf,Middle East,"{main:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Calls Release Americans <LOCATION>Iran<\/LOCATION>, Denies Swap Deal,print_headline:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Calls Release Americans <LOCATION>Iran<\/LOCATION>, Denies Swap Deal}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s top two trainmakers said on <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> that they will merge, creating a <MONEY>$26 billion 17 billion pounds</MONEY> company able to compete with the likes of <LOCATION>Germany</LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>Siemens</ORGANIZATION> and <LOCATION>Canada</LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>Bombardier</ORGANIZATION> for global rail deals.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T10:16:18Z,[],413,"<LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s top two trainmakers said on <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> that they will merge, creating a <MONEY>$26 billion 17 billion pounds</MONEY> company able to compete with the likes of <LOCATION>Germany</LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>Siemens</ORGANIZATION> and <LOCATION>Canada</LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>Bombardier</ORGANIZATION> for global rail deals.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/business/30reuters-china-cnr-m-a-csr-corp.html,54a2c2687988104803cc8ac0,null,"{main:Rival China Trainmakers Merge Boost High-Speed Rail Push Abroad,print_headline:Rival China Trainmakers Merge Boost High-Speed Rail Push Abroad}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Gazprom agreed buy European partners, <ORGANIZATION>Wintershall</ORGANIZATION>, <ORGANIZATION>EDF Eni</ORGANIZATION>, scrapped South Stream gas pipeline project.",2,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Pipelines},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:2,value:Gazprom},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Wintershall},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Electricite de <LOCATION>France<\/LOCATION> EDF},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:5,value:ENI S.p.A},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:6,value:<LOCATION>Russia<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:7,value:<LOCATION>Ukraine<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:8,value:European Union}]",Business Day,"Gazprom buy European partners <ORGANIZATION>Wintershall</ORGANIZATION>, <ORGANIZATION>EDF Eni</ORGANIZATION> abandoned South Stream gas pipeline project.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-30T00:00:00Z,[],156,"Gazprom agreed buy European partners, <ORGANIZATION>Wintershall</ORGANIZATION>, <ORGANIZATION>EDF Eni</ORGANIZATION>, scrapped South Stream gas pipeline project.",Brief,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/business/gazprom-to-buy-out-allies-in-scrapped-gas-pipeline.html,54a213c77988104803cc8939,null,"{content_kicker:Business Briefing,main:Gazprom Buy Out Allies Scrapped Gas Pipeline,print_headline:Gazprom Buy Out Allies Scrapped Gas Pipeline}","{contributor:,original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"English Premier League strugglers West <ORGANIZATION>Bromwich Albion</ORGANIZATION> sacked head coach <PERSON>Alan Irvine</PERSON>, club announced website late <DATE>Monday</DATE>.",null,[],Sports,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-29T19:28:03Z,[],317,"English Premier League strugglers West <ORGANIZATION>Bromwich Albion</ORGANIZATION> sacked head coach <PERSON>Alan Irvine</PERSON>, club announced website late <DATE>Monday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/29/sports/soccer/29reuters-soccer-england-westbrom.html,54a1f2437988104803cc88e2,Soccer,"{main:West Brom Axe Coach Irvine After Poor Start,print_headline:West Brom Axe Coach Irvine After Poor Start}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
