snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
He ran chance.,null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T19:05:25Z,[],2584,He ran chance.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/world/asia/ap-as-skorea-slave-islands.html,54a5e1337988102023c94ef7,Asia Pacific,"{main:'A Living Hell' Slaves Remote South Korean Islands,print_headline:'A Living Hell' Slaves Remote South Korean Islands}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"A <LOCATION>Chatham</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Massachusetts</LOCATION>, police cruiser ran killed college lacrosse player lying unlit road early <DATE>Thursday</DATE>, authorities.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T18:20:55Z,[],182,"A <LOCATION>Chatham</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Massachusetts</LOCATION>, police cruiser ran killed college lacrosse player lying unlit road early <DATE>Thursday</DATE>, authorities.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/world/asia/01reuters-usa-massachusetts-accident.html,54a5d6ba7988102023c94e05,Asia Pacific,"{main:Police Car Strikes, Kills Student Lying Massachusetts Road,print_headline:Police Car Strikes, Kills Student Lying Massachusetts Road}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Smugglers bring migrants <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION> sea adopted, dangerous tactic: cramming hundreds large cargo ship, setting automated crash coast, abandoning helm.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T18:17:23Z,[],782,"Smugglers bring migrants <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION> sea adopted, dangerous tactic: cramming hundreds large cargo ship, setting automated crash coast, abandoning helm.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/world/europe/ap-eu-italy-migrants-stranded-at-sea.html,54a5d6057988102023c94df5,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:New Tactic: Smugglers Put Ships Autopilot,print_headline:New Tactic: Smugglers Put Ships Autopilot}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"The investigation shooting death black 12-year-old  boy white <LOCATION>Cleveland</LOCATION> police officer agency, media report.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T17:34:38Z,[],190,"The investigation shooting death black 12-year-old  boy white <LOCATION>Cleveland</LOCATION> police officer agency, media report.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/us/01reuters-usa-police-cleveland.html,54a5cc067988102023c94d02,null,"{main:Sheriff Could Probe Police Death Cleveland Boy: Report,print_headline:Sheriff Could Probe Police Death Cleveland Boy: Report}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"A bit sunshine filled sky opening faceoff Winter Classic, seat cushions rained winning goal scored final whistle.",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T16:31:42Z,[],908,"A bit sunshine filled sky opening faceoff Winter Classic, seat cushions rained winning goal scored final whistle.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/sports/hockey/ap-hkn-winter-classic.html,54a5bd4a7988102023c94b6a,Hockey,"{main:Capitals Top Blackhawks 3-2 Winter Classic,print_headline:Capitals Top Blackhawks 3-2 Winter Classic}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
A <LOCATION>Florida</LOCATION> man charged first-degree murder mother found decapitated home New Year's Eve.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T15:45:23Z,[],254,A <LOCATION>Florida</LOCATION> man charged first-degree murder mother found decapitated home New Year's Eve.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/us/ap-us-mother-slain.html,54a5b2b97988102023c94a76,null,"{main:Sheriff's Office: <LOCATION>Florida<\/LOCATION> Man Decapitates His Mother,print_headline:Sheriff's Office: <LOCATION>Florida<\/LOCATION> Man Decapitates His Mother}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
A call girl hires ex-con recover money stolen pimp.,null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T14:38:54Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/01/26/movies/video-sex-love-and-cold-hard-cash/video-sex-love-and-cold-hard-cash-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/01/26/movies/video-sex-love-and-cold-hard-cash/video-sex-love-and-cold-hard-cash-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/01/26/movies/video-sex-love-and-cold-hard-cash/video-sex-love-and-cold-hard-cash-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/01/26/movies/video-sex-love-and-cold-hard-cash/video-sex-love-and-cold-hard-cash-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/01/26/movies/video-sex-love-and-cold-hard-cash/video-sex-love-and-cold-hard-cash-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/01/26/movies/video-sex-love-and-cold-hard-cash/video-sex-love-and-cold-hard-cash-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",14,A call girl hires ex-con recover money stolen pimp.,Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003372889/sex-love-and-cold-hard-cash.html,54a5a2537988102023c94832,null,"{main:Sex, Love And Cold Hard Cash}","{original:Universal Studios Home Entertainment,person:[{firstname:Universal,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Studios,rank:1,lastname:Home}]}",multimedia
"<PERSON>Thomas Piketty</PERSON>, the author of “Capital in the <ORGANIZATION>Twenty-First Century</ORGANIZATION>,” says he does not think “it is the government’s role to decide who is honorable.”",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Piketty<\/PERSON>, Thomas},{name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>France<\/LOCATION>},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Awards, Decorations Honors}]",Arts,"<PERSON>Thomas Piketty</PERSON>, the author of “Capital in the <ORGANIZATION>Twenty-First Century</ORGANIZATION>,” says he does not think “it is the government’s role to decide who is honorable.”",The New York Times,[],Culture,2015-01-01T14:22:25Z,[],215,null,Blog,http://artsbeat.blogs.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/piketty-turns-down-the-legion-of-honor/,54a59f0e7988102023c94724,null,"{main:Piketty Turns Down Legion Honor,print_headline:<PERSON>Piketty<\/PERSON> Says &#8216;Non&#8217; To Legion Honor,kicker:ArtsBeat}","{original:By <PERSON>JENNIFER SCHUESSLER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Jennifer,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SCHUESSLER}]}",blogpost
"In <PERSON>Werner Herzog</PERSON>'s film BAD LIEUTENANT: PORT OF CALL <LOCATION>NEW ORLEANS</LOCATION>, <PERSON>Nicolas Cage</PERSON> plays rogue detective devoted job scoring drugs --  playing fast loose law.  He wields badge wiel",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T14:11:53Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-bad-lieutenant-port-of-call-new-orleans/video-bad-lieutenant-port-of-call-new-orleans-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-bad-lieutenant-port-of-call-new-orleans/video-bad-lieutenant-port-of-call-new-orleans-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-bad-lieutenant-port-of-call-new-orleans/video-bad-lieutenant-port-of-call-new-orleans-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-bad-lieutenant-port-of-call-new-orleans/video-bad-lieutenant-port-of-call-new-orleans-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-bad-lieutenant-port-of-call-new-orleans/video-bad-lieutenant-port-of-call-new-orleans-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-bad-lieutenant-port-of-call-new-orleans/video-bad-lieutenant-port-of-call-new-orleans-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",49,"In <PERSON>Werner Herzog</PERSON>'s film BAD LIEUTENANT: PORT OF CALL <LOCATION>NEW ORLEANS</LOCATION>, <PERSON>Nicolas Cage</PERSON> plays rogue detective devoted job scoring drugs --  playing fast loose law.  He wields badge wiel",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003289810/bad-lieutenant-port-of-call-new-orleans.html,54a59bfa7988102023c94641,null,{"main":"Bad Lieutenant: Port Of Call <LOCATION>New Orleans<\/LOCATION>"},"{original:First Look Studios,person:[{firstname:First,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Look,rank:1,lastname:Studios}]}",multimedia
"Working night shift toll collector lonely stretch highway <LOCATION>Buffalo</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>, <PERSON>Henry KEANU REEVES</PERSON> man seemingly ambition, dreams purpose; man sleepwalking life. He wakeup call early",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T14:10:41Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-henrys-crime/video-henrys-crime-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-henrys-crime/video-henrys-crime-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-henrys-crime/video-henrys-crime-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-henrys-crime/video-henrys-crime-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-henrys-crime/video-henrys-crime-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-henrys-crime/video-henrys-crime-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",44,"Working night shift toll collector lonely stretch highway <LOCATION>Buffalo</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>, <PERSON>Henry KEANU REEVES</PERSON> man seemingly ambition, dreams purpose; man sleepwalking life. He wakeup call early",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003331853/henrys-crime.html,54a59bcf7988102023c9462c,null,{"main":"Henry's Crime"},"{original:Moving Pictures Film Television,person:[{firstname:Moving,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Pictures,rank:1,lastname:Film},{firstname:Television,role:reported,organization:,rank:2}]}",multimedia
