snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Low oil prices paradoxically world reach international agreement fight global warming, French ambassador charged organizing key climate conference <LOCATION>Paris</LOCATION>.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T11:02:55Z,[],665,"Low oil prices paradoxically world reach international agreement fight global warming, French ambassador charged organizing key climate conference <LOCATION>Paris</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/world/europe/ap-eu-france-climate-talks.html,54a41e7b7988102761d6e439,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:French Climate Envoy Sees Hope Low Oil Prices,print_headline:French Climate Envoy Sees Hope Low Oil Prices}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Grain futures lower <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>Chicago Board Trade</ORGANIZATION>.,null,[],Business Day,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T10:50:10Z,[],98,Grain futures lower <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>Chicago Board Trade</ORGANIZATION>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/business/ap-financial-markets-board-of-trade.html,54a41bab7988102761d6e343,null,"{main:Grain Lower, Livestock Mostly Lower,print_headline:Grain Lower, Livestock Mostly Lower}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Grain futures lower <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>Chicago Board Trade</ORGANIZATION>.,null,[],Business Day,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T15:45:19Z,[],98,Grain futures lower <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>Chicago Board Trade</ORGANIZATION>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/business/ap-financial-markets-board-of-trade.html,54a30fc87988102761d6cee4,null,"{main:Grain Mostly Lower, Livestock Mostly Lower,print_headline:Grain Mostly Lower, Livestock Mostly Lower}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Grain futures mixed <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> early trading <ORGANIZATION>Chicago Board Trade</ORGANIZATION>.,null,[],Business Day,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-29T10:52:23Z,[],94,Grain futures mixed <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> early trading <ORGANIZATION>Chicago Board Trade</ORGANIZATION>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/29/business/ap-financial-markets-board-of-trade.html,54a179287988101f98e3efe9,null,"{main:Grain Mixed, Livestock Mixed,print_headline:Grain Mixed, Livestock Mixed}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Asian stocks lower <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> concern Greek politics shaky Russian ruble dented confidence global economy.,null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-29T04:51:00Z,[],339,Asian stocks lower <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> concern Greek politics shaky Russian ruble dented confidence global economy.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/29/world/asia/ap-financial-markets.html,54a124be7988101f98e3ef49,Asia Pacific,"{main:Asian Stocks Lower New Fears Over <LOCATION>Greece<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:Asian Stocks Lower New Fears Over <LOCATION>Greece<\/LOCATION>}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Asian stocks higher <DATE>Monday</DATE> report <LOCATION>China</LOCATION> change banking rules apparent effort boost lending economic growth oil prices rebounded.,null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-28T23:31:13Z,[],347,Asian stocks higher <DATE>Monday</DATE> report <LOCATION>China</LOCATION> change banking rules apparent effort boost lending economic growth oil prices rebounded.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/28/world/asia/ap-financial-markets.html,54a0d9827988101f98e3eee6,Asia Pacific,"{main:Asian Stocks Up Oil Price Rebounds,print_headline:Asian Stocks Up Oil Price Rebounds}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Grain futures mixed <ORGANIZATION>Friday Chicago Board Trade</ORGANIZATION>.,null,[],Business Day,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-26T10:57:17Z,[],97,Grain futures mixed <ORGANIZATION>Friday Chicago Board Trade</ORGANIZATION>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/26/business/ap-financial-markets-board-of-trade.html,549d85fe7988103babf08bc8,null,"{main:Grain Mixed, Livestock Mostly Higher,print_headline:Grain Mixed, Livestock Mostly Higher}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Shares higher quiet trading <LOCATION>Friday Asia</LOCATION>, markets region globe closed Christmas holidays. <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>Shanghai Composite Index</ORGANIZATION> extended gains day rebound week's earlier...",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-25T22:19:07Z,[],287,"Shares higher quiet trading <LOCATION>Friday Asia</LOCATION>, markets region globe closed Christmas holidays. <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>Shanghai Composite Index</ORGANIZATION> extended gains day rebound week's earlier sell-off.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/25/world/asia/ap-financial-markets.html,549cd41c7988103babf08ad7,Asia Pacific,"{main:Shares Mostly Higher Quiet Holiday Trading,print_headline:Shares Mostly Higher Quiet Holiday Trading}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Grain futures lower <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>Chicago Board Trade</ORGANIZATION>.,null,[],Business Day,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-24T10:54:59Z,[],96,Grain futures lower <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>Chicago Board Trade</ORGANIZATION>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/24/business/ap-financial-markets-board-of-trade.html,549ae2457988102d96d5683b,null,"{main:Grain Lower, Livestock Mostly Lower,print_headline:Grain Lower, Livestock Mostly Lower}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Global oil markets fell <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> holiday-thin trade, extending week see-saw volatility traders jousted growing supply glut fully priced.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-24T00:48:22Z,[],406,"Global oil markets fell <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> holiday-thin trade, extending week see-saw volatility traders jousted growing supply glut fully priced.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/24/business/24reuters-markets-oil.html,549a546f7988102d96d5667a,null,"{main:Oil Slides, Brent Tests <MONEY>$60<\/MONEY> as Data Shows Glut Building,print_headline:Oil Slides, Brent Tests <MONEY>$60<\/MONEY> as Data Shows Glut Building}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
