snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Corrections appearing print <DATE>Thursday</DATE>, <DATE>January 1, 2015</DATE>.",2,[],Corrections,null,The New York Times,[],Summary,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,[],542,"Corrections appearing print <DATE>Thursday</DATE>, <DATE>January 1, 2015</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/pageoneplus/corrections-january-1-2015.html,54a4e89b79881011bed2aef3,null,"{main:Corrections: <DATE>January 1, 2015<\/DATE>,print_headline:Corrections}",[],article
Leaders <ORGANIZATION>Senate Judiciary Committee</ORGANIZATION> <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> seeking answers <PERSON>Obama</PERSON> administration federal law enforcement's surveillance technology sweeps basic cellphone data.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T15:18:06Z,[],372,Leaders <ORGANIZATION>Senate Judiciary Committee</ORGANIZATION> <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> seeking answers <PERSON>Obama</PERSON> administration federal law enforcement's surveillance technology sweeps basic cellphone data.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/politics/ap-us-fbi-cell-phone-surveillance.html,54a45af479881011bed28e94,Politics,"{main:Senators Seek Information FBI Cell Tracking,print_headline:Senators Seek Information FBI Cell Tracking}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<LOCATION>New Orleans</LOCATION>, post-Katrina. As leader elite Street Crimes task force squad, <LOCATION>New Orleans</LOCATION> Detective <PERSON>Sean Reilly</PERSON> Strong cope death young son abandonment wife. But routine warrant serve",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2014-12-31T13:13:37Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-sinners-and-saints/video-sinners-and-saints-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-sinners-and-saints/video-sinners-and-saints-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-sinners-and-saints/video-sinners-and-saints-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-sinners-and-saints/video-sinners-and-saints-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-sinners-and-saints/video-sinners-and-saints-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-sinners-and-saints/video-sinners-and-saints-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",44,"<LOCATION>New Orleans</LOCATION>, post-Katrina. As leader elite Street Crimes task force squad, <LOCATION>New Orleans</LOCATION> Detective <PERSON>Sean Reilly</PERSON> Strong cope death young son abandonment wife. But routine warrant serve",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003374255/sinners-and-saints.html,54a43cd579881011bed28794,null,{"main":"Sinners And Saints"},"{original:Anchor Bay Entertainment,person:[{firstname:Anchor,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Bay,rank:1,lastname:Entertainment}]}",multimedia
House Republicans are ending the year on a defensive note over Representative <PERSON>Steve Scalise</PERSON>’s <DATE>2002</DATE> speech to a white supremacist group.,null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Bush<\/PERSON>, Jeb},{name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Obama<\/PERSON>, Barack},{name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Scalise<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Steve<\/PERSON>},{name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Florida<\/LOCATION>},{name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>Louisiana<\/LOCATION>},{name:glocations,rank:3,value:United States},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:House Representatives},{name:subject,rank:1,value:United States Politics Government}]",false,House Republicans are ending the year on a defensive note over Representative <PERSON>Steve Scalise</PERSON>’s <DATE>2002</DATE> speech to a white supremacist group.,The New York Times,[],null,2014-12-31T07:03:46Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/us/politics/31firstdraft-white-house/31firstdraft-white-house-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/us/politics/31firstdraft-white-house/31firstdraft-white-house-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/us/politics/31firstdraft-white-house/31firstdraft-white-house-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/us/politics/31firstdraft-white-house/31firstdraft-white-house-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/us/politics/31firstdraft-white-house/31firstdraft-white-house-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/us/politics/31firstdraft-white-house/31firstdraft-white-house-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1616,null,Blog,http://www.nytimes.com/politics/first-draft/2014/12/31/today-in-politics-67/,54a3e66f7988102761d6dc53,false,"{main:Today Politics,kicker:First Draft}","{original:By THE <LOCATION>NEW YORK<\/LOCATION> TIMES,person:[],organization:The New York Times}",blogpost
"A man shot killed police run officers car <LOCATION>Philadelphia</LOCATION> suburb posted online video threatening kill police <ORGANIZATION>FBI</ORGANIZATION> agents previously committed mental health facility mother,...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T02:48:38Z,[],651,"A man shot killed police run officers car <LOCATION>Philadelphia</LOCATION> suburb posted online video threatening kill police <ORGANIZATION>FBI</ORGANIZATION> agents previously committed mental health facility mother, authorities.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/ap-us-killings-by-police-threats.html,54a3ab397988102761d6d57d,null,"{main:Threats, Hospitalization Preceded Police Shooting,print_headline:Threats, Hospitalization Preceded Police Shooting}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Police <LOCATION>Pennsylvania</LOCATION> shot killed man <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> car run officers attempted arrest charges making online terroristic threats law enforcement, officials.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T00:19:45Z,[],233,"Police <LOCATION>Pennsylvania</LOCATION> shot killed man <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> car run officers attempted arrest charges making online terroristic threats law enforcement, officials.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/us/31reuters-usa-pennsylvania-shooting.html,54a387f77988102761d6d16e,null,"{main:Police Kill <LOCATION>Pennsylvania<\/LOCATION> Man He Tried Run Down Officers,print_headline:Police Kill <LOCATION>Pennsylvania<\/LOCATION> Man He Tried Run Down Officers}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Corrections appearing print <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>, <DATE>December 31, 2014</DATE>.",2,[],Corrections,null,The New York Times,[],Summary,2014-12-31T00:00:00Z,[],566,"Corrections appearing print <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>, <DATE>December 31, 2014</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/pageoneplus/corrections-december-31-2014.html,54a394967988102761d6d2ea,null,"{main:Corrections: <DATE>December 31, 2014<\/DATE>,print_headline:Corrections}",[],article
"Cho Hyun-ah, daughter of the airline’s chairman, may face charges of assaulting the crew of a flight she disrupted.",9,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>South Korea<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Airlines Airplanes},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:Cho Hyun-ah},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Korean Air Lines}]",World,"<LOCATION>Seoul</LOCATION> court orders arrest <ORGANIZATION>Korean Airlines</ORGANIZATION> executive Cho Hyun-ah assaulting flight attendants disrupting duties flight <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> <DATE>December</DATE>; reports episode stirred public anger <LOCATION>South Korea</LOCATION>, Cho scion wealthy family.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-31T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/world/31korea/31korea-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/world/31korea/31korea-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/world/31korea/31korea-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:416},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/world/31korea/31korea-articleLarge.jpg,height:416}]",464,"Cho Hyun-ah, daughter of the airline’s chairman, may face charges of assaulting the crew of a flight she disrupted.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/world/asia/court-orders-arrest-of-ex-executive-at-korean-airlines-over-nut-rage.html,54a35d457988102761d6cf8b,Asia Pacific,"{main:Court Orders Arrest of Ex-Executive at <ORGANIZATION>Korean Airlines<\/ORGANIZATION> Over ‘Nut Rage’,print_headline:<LOCATION>South Korea<\/LOCATION>: Former Executive’s Arrest Is Ordered in Airline ‘Nut Rage’ Episode}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>MARTIN<\/PERSON> FACKLER,person:[{firstname:Martin,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:FACKLER}]}",article
"In ways anti-Warren, <LOCATION>Rhode Island</LOCATION>&#8217;s female governor dynamo dissident forces tough conversations party.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:1,value:Raimondo, <PERSON>Gina<\/PERSON> M},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>Rhode Island<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:Warren, Elizabeth},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Governors US},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:United States Politics Government},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Income Inequality},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:7,value:Democratic Party},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:8,value:Pensions Retirement Plans}]",Opinion,"Frank <PERSON>Bruni</PERSON> Op-Ed column calls attention <LOCATION>Rhode Island</LOCATION> Gov-elect <PERSON>Gina Raimondo</PERSON>, noting female Democratic governors country; contrasts <PERSON>Raimondo</PERSON>'s political approach Sen <PERSON>Elizabeth Warren</PERSON>, excited left wing party.",The New York Times,[],OpEd,2014-12-31T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/opinion/31BRUNI/31BRUNI-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/opinion/31BRUNI/31BRUNI-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/opinion/31BRUNI/31BRUNI-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/opinion/31BRUNI/31BRUNI-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/opinion/31BRUNI/31BRUNI-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/opinion/31BRUNI/31BRUNI-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",807,"In ways anti-Warren, <LOCATION>Rhode Island</LOCATION>&#8217;s female governor dynamo dissident forces tough conversations party.",Op-Ed,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/opinion/frank-bruni-gina-raimondos-approach-to-income-inequality.html,54a337d37988102761d6cf49,null,"{content_kicker:Op-Ed Columnist,main:A Democrat Watch 2015,seo:<PERSON>Gina Raimondo<\/PERSON>'s Approach Income Inequality,print_headline:A Democrat Watch 2015,kicker:Op-Ed Columnist}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>FRANK BRUNI<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Frank,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BRUNI}]}",article
"Activity <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s factory sector shrank time months <DATE>December</DATE>, private survey showed <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>, highlighting urgency series surprise easing moves <LOCATION>Beijing</LOCATION> past months.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T21:13:48Z,[],484,"Activity <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s factory sector shrank time months <DATE>December</DATE>, private survey showed <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>, highlighting urgency series surprise easing moves <LOCATION>Beijing</LOCATION> past months.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/business/30reuters-china-economy-pmi.html,54a35c617988102761d6cf88,null,"{main:China Factory Activity Contracts <DATE>December<\/DATE> Slowdown Deepens,print_headline:China Factory Activity Contracts <DATE>December<\/DATE> Slowdown Deepens}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
