snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
Bundled-up revelers planning usher <DATE>2015</DATE> Las Vegas Strip watch flower-decorated floats <ORGANIZATION>Rose Parade Southern California</ORGANIZATION> dealing near-freezing temperatures early <DATE>Thursday</DATE> blustery winter storm dumped show...,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T03:13:03Z,[],704,Bundled-up revelers planning usher <DATE>2015</DATE> <ORGANIZATION>Las Vegas Strip</ORGANIZATION> watch flower-decorated floats <ORGANIZATION>Rose Parade Southern California</ORGANIZATION> dealing near-freezing temperatures early <DATE>Thursday</DATE> blustery winter storm dumped show ice West.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/us/ap-us-new-years-storm.html,54a5024879881011bed2b4c4,null,"{main:Storm Brings Snow, Cold West New Year's,print_headline:Storm Brings Snow, Cold West New Year's}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Fans lined Rose Parade route <DATE>Thursday</DATE> bundled blankets, hats gloves sipped steaming cups coffee cocoa day dawned unusually frigid.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T02:38:47Z,[],603,"Fans lined Rose Parade route <DATE>Thursday</DATE> bundled blankets, hats gloves sipped steaming cups coffee cocoa day dawned unusually frigid.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/us/ap-us-rose-parade.html,54a4f9d679881011bed2b2d7,null,"{main:Cold Snap Across West Chills Rose Parade,print_headline:Cold Snap Across West Chills Rose Parade}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"&#8220;Ways Modernism,&#8221; exhibition <LOCATION>Vienna</LOCATION>, contrasting styles early Modernist architects.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Hoffmann<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Josef<\/PERSON>},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:Loos, Adolf},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Architecture},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Austrian Museum of Applied Arts / Contemporary Art <LOCATION>Vienna<\/LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Austria<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Art}]",Arts,"<PERSON>Alice Rawsthorn</PERSON> Critic's Notebook on exhibit Ways to Modernism: <PERSON>Josef Hoffmann</PERSON>, <PERSON>Adolf Loos</PERSON> and Their Impact at <ORGANIZATION>MAK</ORGANIZATION>, Austrian Museum of Applied Arts/Contemporary Art in <LOCATION>Vienna</LOCATION>; exhibit compares competing visions of modernist architects <PERSON>Hoffman</PERSON> and Loos at time when new generation is paying attention to their work.",The New York Times,[],Culture,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/arts/MODERNISM/MODERNISM-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/arts/MODERNISM/MODERNISM-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/arts/MODERNISM/MODERNISM-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:448},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/arts/MODERNISM/MODERNISM-articleLarge.jpg,height:448},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/arts/MODERNISM/MODERNISM-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/arts/MODERNISM/MODERNISM-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1061,"&#8220;Ways Modernism,&#8221; exhibition <LOCATION>Vienna</LOCATION>, contrasting styles early Modernist architects.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/arts/design/josef-hoffmann-and-adolf-loos-contrasting-modernist-architects.html,54a46a4279881011bed2920d,Art & Design,"{content_kicker:Critic’s Notebook,main:Two Architects, Two Visions, One Diptych Early Modernism,seo:<PERSON>Josef Hoffmann Adolf Loos<\/PERSON>, Contrasting Modernist Architects,print_headline:Two Architects, Two Modernist Visions,kicker:Critic’s Notebook}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ALICE RAWSTHORN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Alice,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:RAWSTHORN}]}",article
"A blustery winter storm dumped snow ice West <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>, making driving treacherous mountains <LOCATION>California Rockies</LOCATION>, forcing residents party-goers sun-soaked cities bundle frosty...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T16:12:40Z,[],643,"A blustery winter storm dumped snow ice West <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>, making driving treacherous mountains <LOCATION>California Rockies</LOCATION>, forcing residents party-goers sun-soaked cities bundle frosty New Year's.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/us/ap-us-new-years-storm.html,54a467b379881011bed29177,null,"{main:Storm Brings Snow, Cold West New Year's,print_headline:Storm Brings Snow, Cold West New Year's}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
A South Korean activist <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> launch balloons carrying DVDs <ORGANIZATION>Sony</ORGANIZATION>'s The <LOCATION>Interview North Korea</LOCATION> break personality cult built dictator Kim Jong Un.,null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T23:07:21Z,[],434,A South Korean activist <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> launch balloons carrying DVDs <ORGANIZATION>Sony</ORGANIZATION>'s The <LOCATION>Interview North Korea</LOCATION> break personality cult built dictator Kim Jong Un.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/world/asia/ap-as-nkorea-sony-hacking-.html,54a377217988102761d6cfd6,Asia Pacific,"{main:South Korean Drop <ORGANIZATION>Sony<\/ORGANIZATION> Film North Balloon,print_headline:South Korean Drop <ORGANIZATION>Sony<\/ORGANIZATION> Film North Balloon}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Canary Wharf owner <ORGANIZATION>Songbird Estates Plc</ORGANIZATION> has told shareholders to take no action on a Qatari-led <MONEY>$4 billion 2.57 billion pounds</MONEY> takeover bid, reiterating that the <MONEY>350 pence</MONEY> per share cash offer undervalued the company.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T11:16:01Z,[],410,"Canary Wharf owner <ORGANIZATION>Songbird Estates Plc</ORGANIZATION> has told shareholders to take no action on a Qatari-led <MONEY>$4 billion 2.57 billion pounds</MONEY> takeover bid, reiterating that the <MONEY>350 pence</MONEY> per share cash offer undervalued the company.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/business/30reuters-songbird-m-a-qatar.html,54a2d0787988104803cc8ae2,null,"{main:Songbird Tells Shareholders to Take No Action on <MONEY>$4 Billion<\/MONEY> Bid,print_headline:Songbird Tells Shareholders to Take No Action on <MONEY>$4 Billion<\/MONEY> Bid}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"As the search for <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION>’s Flight 8501 continued, aviation experts said the difficulty in locating it underscored the limitations in how planes are tracked.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Aviation Accidents, Safety Disasters},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:2,value:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:<ORGANIZATION>Malaysia Airlines<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight 370}]",Business Day,Search missing <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501 complicated delay declaring emergency contact plane lost fact planes stream data location satellite; <ORGANIZATION>International Civil Aviation Organization</ORGANIZATION> slow change flight-tracking requirements system change loss <ORGANIZATION>Malaysia Airlines</ORGANIZATION> 370.,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-30T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/30/world/JP-SEARCH/JP-SEARCH-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/world/JP-SEARCH/JP-SEARCH-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/30/world/JP-SEARCH/JP-SEARCH-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/world/JP-SEARCH/JP-SEARCH-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/30/world/JP-SEARCH/JP-SEARCH-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/world/JP-SEARCH/JP-SEARCH-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1112,"As the search for <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION>’s Flight 8501 continued, aviation experts said the difficulty in locating it underscored the limitations in how planes are tracked.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/business/hurdle-in-hunt-for-missing-jet-tracking-system.html,54a20c307988104803cc8918,null,"{main:Hurdle Hunt Missing Jet: Tracking System,print_headline:Hurdle Hunt Lost Plane: Poor Tracking}","{contributor:<PERSON>Thomas Fuller<\/PERSON> contributed reporting <LOCATION>Jakarta<\/LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Indonesia<\/LOCATION>, <PERSON>Nicola Clark<\/PERSON> contributed <LOCATION>Paris<\/LOCATION>.,original:By <PERSON>CHRISTOPHER<\/PERSON> DREW,person:[{firstname:Christopher,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:DREW}]}",article
"Rescue crews searching Indonesian waters <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia Indonesia</ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501, disappeared <DATE>Sunday</DATE> 162 passengers crew onboard. The plane flying <LOCATION>Surabaya</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Indonesia</LOCATION>'s second-largest city, halfway...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-29T08:13:06Z,[],1490,"Rescue crews searching Indonesian waters <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia Indonesia</ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501, disappeared <DATE>Sunday</DATE> 162 passengers crew onboard. The plane flying <LOCATION>Surabaya</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Indonesia</LOCATION>'s second-largest city, halfway destination, <LOCATION>Singapore</LOCATION>, vanished radar.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/29/us/ap-as-travel-indonesia-plane-questions.html,54a153db7988101f98e3ef9c,null,"{main:Q&A What Might Have Happened <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight,print_headline:Q&A What Might Have Happened <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Countries <LOCATION>Asia</LOCATION> <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> stepped search <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> plane carrying 162 people presumed crashed shallow waters Indonesian coast, <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION> sending warship find missing jet.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-29T00:02:07Z,[],949,"Countries <LOCATION>Asia</LOCATION> <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> stepped search <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> plane carrying 162 people presumed crashed shallow waters Indonesian coast, <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION> sending warship find missing jet.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/29/world/asia/29reuters-indonesia-airplane.html,54a0e08a7988101f98e3eeeb,Asia Pacific,"{main:<LOCATION>Indonesia<\/LOCATION> Expands Search Missing <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Jet, <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Sends Warship,print_headline:<LOCATION>Indonesia<\/LOCATION> Expands Search Missing <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Jet, <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Sends Warship}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Rescue crews searching Indonesian waters <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia Indonesia</ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501, disappeared <DATE>Sunday</DATE> 162 passengers crew onboard. The plane flying <LOCATION>Surabaya</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Indonesia</LOCATION>'s second-largest city, halfway...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-28T11:13:21Z,[],1490,"Rescue crews searching Indonesian waters <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia Indonesia</ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501, disappeared <DATE>Sunday</DATE> 162 passengers crew onboard. The plane flying <LOCATION>Surabaya</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Indonesia</LOCATION>'s second-largest city, halfway destination, <LOCATION>Singapore</LOCATION>, vanished radar.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/28/us/ap-as-indonesia-plane-questions.html,54a02c8f79881001534d20c2,null,"{main:Q&A What Might Have Happened <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight,print_headline:Q&A What Might Have Happened <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
