snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"A senior Chinese diplomat sacked investigation suspected corruption, foreign ministry <DATE>Friday</DATE>, time top diplomat fallen victim sweeping campaign graft.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T23:21:45Z,[],273,"A senior Chinese diplomat sacked investigation suspected corruption, foreign ministry <DATE>Friday</DATE>, time top diplomat fallen victim sweeping campaign graft.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/world/asia/01reuters-china-corruption.html,54a61da47988102023c9543f,Asia Pacific,"{main:Senior Chinese Diplomat Sacked Corruption,print_headline:Senior Chinese Diplomat Sacked Corruption}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<ORGANIZATION>Hyundai Motor Co</ORGANIZATION> affiliate <ORGANIZATION>Kia Motors Corp</ORGANIZATION> forecast sales year grow slowest pace <DATE>2003</DATE>, hampered capacity constraints weaker yen give Japanese rivals edge key markets.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T18:11:36Z,[],387,"<ORGANIZATION>Hyundai Motor Co</ORGANIZATION> affiliate <ORGANIZATION>Kia Motors Corp</ORGANIZATION> forecast sales year grow slowest pace <DATE>2003</DATE>, hampered capacity constraints weaker yen give Japanese rivals edge key markets.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-hyundai-motor-kia-motors-sales.html,54a5d48a7988102023c94dd6,null,"{main:Hyundai-Kia See <DATE>2015<\/DATE> Sales Growth Weakest 12 Years,print_headline:Hyundai-Kia See <DATE>2015<\/DATE> Sales Growth Weakest 12 Years}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Falling world oil prices hurt countries <LOCATION>Middle East Saudi Arabia</LOCATION>, world's biggest crude exporter,  takes action reverse slump, <LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION>'s deputy foreign minister told <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION>.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T11:22:27Z,[],678,"Falling world oil prices hurt countries <LOCATION>Middle East Saudi Arabia</LOCATION>, world's biggest crude exporter,  takes action reverse slump, <LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION>'s deputy foreign minister told <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/world/middleeast/01reuters-iran-saudi.html,54a5750779881011bed2ce82,Middle East,"{main:<LOCATION>Iran<\/LOCATION> Says Saudi Arabia Should Move Curb Oil Price Fall,print_headline:<LOCATION>Iran<\/LOCATION> Says Saudi Arabia Should Move Curb Oil Price Fall}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<PERSON>Britt Reid Seth Rogen</PERSON>, son heir <LOCATION>Los Angeles</LOCATION>' largest newspaper fortune, rich, spoiled playboy happy maintain direction-less existence. When father <PERSON>James Reid Tom Wilkinson</PERSON> dies, <PERSON>Britt</PERSON> meets impressive res",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T08:53:45Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/03/04/movies/video-the-green-hornet/video-the-green-hornet-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/03/04/movies/video-the-green-hornet/video-the-green-hornet-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/03/04/movies/video-the-green-hornet/video-the-green-hornet-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/03/04/movies/video-the-green-hornet/video-the-green-hornet-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/03/04/movies/video-the-green-hornet/video-the-green-hornet-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/03/04/movies/video-the-green-hornet/video-the-green-hornet-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",41,"<PERSON>Britt Reid Seth Rogen</PERSON>, son heir <LOCATION>Los Angeles</LOCATION>' largest newspaper fortune, rich, spoiled playboy happy maintain direction-less existence. When father <PERSON>James Reid Tom Wilkinson</PERSON> dies, <PERSON>Britt</PERSON> meets impressive res",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003388612/the-green-hornet.html,54a5517279881011bed2c696,null,{"main":"The Green Hornet"},"{original:Columbia Pictures,person:[{firstname:Columbia,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Pictures}]}",multimedia
"<PERSON>Drayton Jackson</PERSON> consummate ladies' man.... But scheming sister decides throw party invite girlfriends, <PERSON>Drayton</PERSON>'s maintain cool attempts world-class juggling act.",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T03:51:53Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-how-to-be-a-player/video-how-to-be-a-player-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-how-to-be-a-player/video-how-to-be-a-player-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-how-to-be-a-player/video-how-to-be-a-player-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-how-to-be-a-player/video-how-to-be-a-player-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-how-to-be-a-player/video-how-to-be-a-player-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-how-to-be-a-player/video-how-to-be-a-player-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",38,"<PERSON>Drayton Jackson</PERSON> consummate ladies' man.... But scheming sister decides throw party invite girlfriends, <PERSON>Drayton</PERSON>'s maintain cool attempts world-class juggling act.",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003339412/how-to-be-a-player.html,54a50aab79881011bed2b6b2,null,{"main":"How To Be A Player"},"{original:PolyGram Video,person:[{firstname:Polygram,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Video}]}",multimedia
"As <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> combat operations formally ended, military families sensed forgotten.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Afghanistan War 2001-14},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:United States Defense Military Forces},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Veterans},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:4,value:Afghanistan},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:5,value:Fort Hood Tex},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:6,value:Killeen Tex},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:7,value:<PERSON>Morris<\/PERSON>, Ramon S 1977-2014}]",<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,"Many American troops remain involved operations <LOCATION>Afghanistan</LOCATION>, official end war, soldiers families continue grapple injuries, mental trauma loss loved ones; scaled-down Operation Resolute Support continue bringing troops overseas train advise Afghan forces, sense mission fades; troops, veterans close feel forgotten.",The New York Times,[],National,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/us/JP-SOLDIER1/JP-SOLDIER1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/us/JP-SOLDIER1/JP-SOLDIER1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/us/JP-SOLDIER1/JP-SOLDIER1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/us/JP-SOLDIER1/JP-SOLDIER1-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/us/JP-SOLDIER1/JP-SOLDIER1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/us/JP-SOLDIER1/JP-SOLDIER1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1428,"As <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> combat operations formally ended, military families sensed forgotten.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/us/mission-ends-but-sacrifices-are-not-over-for-us-soldiers.html,54a4ac7f79881011bed2a13b,null,"{main:Mission Ends <LOCATION>Afghanistan<\/LOCATION>, Sacrifices Are Not Over <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Soldiers,print_headline:Mission Ends, Sacrifices Not Over}","{contributor:<PERSON>Andy Lehren<\/PERSON> contributed reporting <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION>.,original:By <PERSON>DAVE PHILIPPS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Dave,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:PHILIPPS}]}",article
Distrust countries resurfaced search 300 kidnapped girls lost momentum.,1,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Nigeria<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:2,value:Boko Haram},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Kidnapping Hostages},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:United States Defense Military Forces},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Women Girls},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:<LOCATION>United States Africa<\/LOCATION> Command},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:United States International Relations}]",World,"Tensions risen <LOCATION>United States Nigeria</LOCATION> failed attempt rescue girls kidnapped militant <PERSON>Boko Haram</PERSON>, countries accusing failure; distrust countries hindered rescue effort, <LOCATION>Nigeria</LOCATION> claiming lack American support <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> pointing <LOCATION>Nigeria</LOCATION>'s poor human rights record.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/world/ALT-INTEL/ALT-INTEL-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/world/ALT-INTEL/ALT-INTEL-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/world/ALT-INTEL/ALT-INTEL-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/world/ALT-INTEL/ALT-INTEL-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/world/ALT-INTEL/ALT-INTEL-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/world/ALT-INTEL/ALT-INTEL-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1155,Distrust countries resurfaced search 300 kidnapped girls lost momentum.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/world/with-schoolgirls-still-missing-fragile-us-nigeria-ties-falter.html,54a4a54179881011bed29f8c,<LOCATION>Africa</LOCATION>,"{main:With Schoolgirls Taken Boko Haram Still Missing, <LOCATION>U.S.-Nigeria<\/LOCATION> Ties Falter,print_headline:With Schoolgirls Still Missing, Fragile U.S.-Nigeria Ties Falter}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ERIC SCHMITT<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Eric,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SCHMITT}]}",article
"After <PERSON>Braxton Miller</PERSON> injured season, quarterbacks stepped lead <ORGANIZATION>Ohio State</ORGANIZATION>. All back season, make things interesting Coach Urban <PERSON>Meyer</PERSON>.",8,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Football College},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Meyer<\/PERSON>, Urban},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Miller<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Braxton<\/PERSON>},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:4,value:<PERSON>Barrett<\/PERSON>, J T},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:5,value:Jones, Cardale},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:6,value:Burrow, Joe <DATE>1996<\/DATE>-},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:7,value:<ORGANIZATION>Ohio State University<\/ORGANIZATION>}]",Sports,"<ORGANIZATION>Ohio State University</ORGANIZATION> quarterbacks <PERSON>Braxton Miller</PERSON>, J T <PERSON>Barrett Cardale Jones</PERSON> performed year considered coach Urban <PERSON>Meyer</PERSON> starting position.",The New York Times,[],Sports,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/sports/01JONES1/01JONES1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/sports/01JONES1/01JONES1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/sports/01JONES1/01JONES1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/sports/01JONES1/01JONES1-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/sports/01JONES1/01JONES1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/sports/01JONES1/01JONES1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",2401,"After <PERSON>Braxton Miller</PERSON> injured season, quarterbacks stepped lead <ORGANIZATION>Ohio State</ORGANIZATION>. All back season, make things interesting Coach Urban <PERSON>Meyer</PERSON>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/sports/ncaafootball/for-ohio-state-an-abundance-of-riches-and-intrigue-at-quarterback-.html,54a395f77988102761d6d315,College Football,"{main:At <ORGANIZATION>Ohio State<\/ORGANIZATION>, Overabundance Lines Up Under Center,print_headline:Overabundance Under Center}","{contributor:<PERSON>Elisa Cho<\/PERSON> contributed research.,original:By <PERSON>TIM ROHAN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Tim,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:ROHAN}]}",article
"A family living <LOCATION>England</LOCATION> World War II struggles maintain normal existence. Multi-Oscar winner, including Best Picture!",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2014-12-31T22:17:35Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/04/24/movies/video-mrs-miniver/video-mrs-miniver-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/04/24/movies/video-mrs-miniver/video-mrs-miniver-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/04/24/movies/video-mrs-miniver/video-mrs-miniver-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/04/24/movies/video-mrs-miniver/video-mrs-miniver-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/04/24/movies/video-mrs-miniver/video-mrs-miniver-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/04/24/movies/video-mrs-miniver/video-mrs-miniver-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",20,"A family living <LOCATION>England</LOCATION> World War II struggles maintain normal existence. Multi-Oscar winner, including Best Picture!",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003356496/mrs-miniver.html,54a4bc5379881011bed2a4d9,null,{"main":"Mrs. <PERSON>Miniver<\/PERSON>"},"{original:Warner Home Video,person:[{firstname:Warner,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Home,rank:1,lastname:Video}]}",multimedia
"Turns Buffalo Bills stuck coach <PERSON>Doug Marrone</PERSON>,.",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T18:29:55Z,[],762,"Turns Buffalo Bills stuck coach <PERSON>Doug Marrone</PERSON>,.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/sports/football/ap-fbn-bills-marrone.html,54a4874179881011bed298a9,Pro Football,"{main:<PERSON>Doug Marrone<\/PERSON> Steps Down Coach Bills,print_headline:<PERSON>Doug Marrone<\/PERSON> Steps Down Coach Bills}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
