snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"<LOCATION>Singapore</LOCATION>'s economic growth slowed expected fourth quarter manufacturing sector contracted face erratic global demand, raising concerns outlook <DATE>2015</DATE>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T21:50:49Z,[],507,"<LOCATION>Singapore</LOCATION>'s economic growth slowed expected fourth quarter manufacturing sector contracted face erratic global demand, raising concerns outlook <DATE>2015</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-singapore-economy-gdp.html,54a607eb7988102023c95265,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Singapore<\/LOCATION>'s Slower-Than-Expected Fourth-Quarter Growth Signals Weaker Outlook 2015,print_headline:<LOCATION>Singapore<\/LOCATION>'s Slower-Than-Expected Fourth-Quarter Growth Signals Weaker Outlook 2015}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Deals worth nearly <MONEY>$3.5 trillion</MONEY> were announced, a performance favored by low interest rates and high stock prices.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Mergers, Acquisitions Divestitures}]",Business Day,"Deals worth nearly <MONEY>$3.5 trillion</MONEY> were announced, a performance favored by low interest rates and high stock prices.",The New York Times,[],Business,2015-01-01T19:32:44Z,[],525,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/deal-makers-notched-nearly-3-5-trillion-worth-in-14-best-in-7-years/,54a5e7cc7988102023c94f8e,Dealbook,"{main:Deal Makers Notched Nearly <MONEY>$3.5<\/MONEY> <ORGANIZATION>Trillion Worth<\/ORGANIZATION> in &rsquo;14, Best in 7 Years,print_headline:Deal Makers Notched Nearly <MONEY>$3.5 Trillion<\/MONEY> Worth in ’14, Best in 7 Years,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>MICHAEL J. DE<\/PERSON> LA MERCED,person:[{firstname:Michael,role:reported,organization:,middlename:J.,rank:1,lastname:DE LA MERCED}]}",blogpost
"According recent studies, half Americans prospect good job home white picket fence, existed unachievable.",null,"[{name:type_of_material,rank:1,value:News}]",Opinion,"According recent studies, half Americans prospect good job home white picket fence, existed unachievable.",The New York Times,[],null,2015-01-01T19:32:18Z,[],2347,,Blog,http://www.nytimes.com/roomfordebate/2015/01/01/is-the-modern-american-dream-attainable,54a5e8887988102023c94f9e,Room For Debate,"{main:Is Modern American Dream Attainable??,kicker:Room For Debate}",null,blogpost
"The euro started year 29-month lows <LOCATION>Asia</LOCATION> head head <ORGANIZATION>European Central Bank</ORGANIZATION> fanned expectations bolder steps stimulus month, underlining <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> dollar's rate advantage.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T19:10:02Z,[],546,"The euro started year 29-month lows <LOCATION>Asia</LOCATION> head head <ORGANIZATION>European Central Bank</ORGANIZATION> fanned expectations bolder steps stimulus month, underlining <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> dollar's rate advantage.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-markets-global.html,54a5e2847988102023c94f13,null,"{main:Euro Starts New Year New Lows, Oil Tries Bounce,print_headline:Euro Starts New Year New Lows, Oil Tries Bounce}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<LOCATION>South Korea</LOCATION>'s manufacturing activity shrank fourth consecutive month <DATE>December</DATE> slower pace, private-sector survey showed <DATE>Friday</DATE>, adding signs economy slowly regaining footing heading <DATE>2015</DATE>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T19:03:32Z,[],250,"<LOCATION>South Korea</LOCATION>'s manufacturing activity shrank fourth consecutive month <DATE>December</DATE> slower pace, private-sector survey showed <DATE>Friday</DATE>, adding signs economy slowly regaining footing heading <DATE>2015</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-southkorea-economy-pmi.html,54a5e0717988102023c94ee3,null,"{main:<LOCATION>South Korea<\/LOCATION> <DATE>December<\/DATE> Factory Activity Shrinks Fourth Month Slower Pace-PMI,print_headline:<LOCATION>South Korea<\/LOCATION> <DATE>December<\/DATE> Factory Activity Shrinks Fourth Month Slower Pace-PMI}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<ORGANIZATION>Hyundai Motor Co</ORGANIZATION> affiliate <ORGANIZATION>Kia Motors Corp</ORGANIZATION> forecast sales year grow slowest pace <DATE>2003</DATE>, hampered capacity constraints weaker yen give Japanese rivals edge key markets.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T18:11:36Z,[],387,"<ORGANIZATION>Hyundai Motor Co</ORGANIZATION> affiliate <ORGANIZATION>Kia Motors Corp</ORGANIZATION> forecast sales year grow slowest pace <DATE>2003</DATE>, hampered capacity constraints weaker yen give Japanese rivals edge key markets.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-hyundai-motor-kia-motors-sales.html,54a5d48a7988102023c94dd6,null,"{main:Hyundai-Kia See <DATE>2015<\/DATE> Sales Growth Weakest 12 Years,print_headline:Hyundai-Kia See <DATE>2015<\/DATE> Sales Growth Weakest 12 Years}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"European Central Bank President <PERSON>Mario Draghi</PERSON> risk central bank fulfilling mandate preserving price stability higher half year ago, reiterated readiness act early year...",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T15:13:24Z,[],437,"European Central Bank President <PERSON>Mario Draghi</PERSON> risk central bank fulfilling mandate preserving price stability higher half year ago, reiterated readiness act early year.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-ecb-policy-draghi.html,54a5aaf87988102023c949cd,null,"{main:Draghi: Risk <ORGANIZATION>ECB<\/ORGANIZATION> Failing Its Mandate Higher Than Six Months Ago-Paper,print_headline:Draghi: Risk <ORGANIZATION>ECB<\/ORGANIZATION> Failing Its Mandate Higher Than Six Months Ago-Paper}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
<LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>'s President <PERSON>Dilma Rousseff</PERSON> began term <DATE>Thursday</DATE> vowing rein government spending curb inflation pull <LOCATION>Latin America</LOCATION>'s largest economy four-year slump.,null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T14:39:40Z,[],597,<LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>'s President <PERSON>Dilma Rousseff</PERSON> began term <DATE>Thursday</DATE> vowing rein government spending curb inflation pull <LOCATION>Latin America</LOCATION>'s largest economy four-year slump.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/world/americas/01reuters-brazil-rousseff.html,54a5a35e7988102023c9487a,Americas,"{main:<LOCATION>Brazil<\/LOCATION>'s Rousseff Vows Budget Cuts, Anti-Corruption Push Second Term,print_headline:<LOCATION>Brazil<\/LOCATION>'s Rousseff Vows Budget Cuts, Anti-Corruption Push Second Term}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<PERSON>Thomas Piketty</PERSON>, the author of “Capital in the <ORGANIZATION>Twenty-First Century</ORGANIZATION>,” says he does not think “it is the government’s role to decide who is honorable.”",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Piketty<\/PERSON>, Thomas},{name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>France<\/LOCATION>},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Awards, Decorations Honors}]",Arts,"<PERSON>Thomas Piketty</PERSON>, the author of “Capital in the <ORGANIZATION>Twenty-First Century</ORGANIZATION>,” says he does not think “it is the government’s role to decide who is honorable.”",The New York Times,[],Culture,2015-01-01T14:22:25Z,[],215,null,Blog,http://artsbeat.blogs.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/piketty-turns-down-the-legion-of-honor/,54a59f0e7988102023c94724,null,"{main:Piketty Turns Down Legion Honor,print_headline:<PERSON>Piketty<\/PERSON> Says &#8216;Non&#8217; To Legion Honor,kicker:ArtsBeat}","{original:By <PERSON>JENNIFER SCHUESSLER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Jennifer,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SCHUESSLER}]}",blogpost
"<LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>'s President <PERSON>Dilma Rousseff</PERSON> sworn term office <DATE>Thursday</DATE>, confronting expanding kickback scandal state-run oil company, moribund economy congressional support ruling coalition.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T13:02:25Z,[],334,"<LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>'s President <PERSON>Dilma Rousseff</PERSON> sworn term office <DATE>Thursday</DATE>, confronting expanding kickback scandal state-run oil company, moribund economy congressional support ruling coalition.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/world/americas/ap-lt-brazil-inauguration.html,54a58c127988102023c94152,Americas,"{main:<LOCATION>Brazil<\/LOCATION>'s Leader Sworn In 2nd Term,print_headline:<LOCATION>Brazil<\/LOCATION>'s Leader Sworn In 2nd Term}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
