snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"<ORGANIZATION>Hyundai Motor Co</ORGANIZATION> affiliate <ORGANIZATION>Kia Motors Corp</ORGANIZATION> forecast sales year grow slowest pace <DATE>2003</DATE>, hampered capacity constraints weaker yen give Japanese rivals edge key markets.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T18:11:36Z,[],387,"<ORGANIZATION>Hyundai Motor Co</ORGANIZATION> affiliate <ORGANIZATION>Kia Motors Corp</ORGANIZATION> forecast sales year grow slowest pace <DATE>2003</DATE>, hampered capacity constraints weaker yen give Japanese rivals edge key markets.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-hyundai-motor-kia-motors-sales.html,54a5d48a7988102023c94dd6,null,"{main:Hyundai-Kia See <DATE>2015<\/DATE> Sales Growth Weakest 12 Years,print_headline:Hyundai-Kia See <DATE>2015<\/DATE> Sales Growth Weakest 12 Years}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
The naive son <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Senator makes lightening-fast climb corporate ladder big conglomerate. Script wastes terrific cast!,null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T03:43:42Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-head-office/video-head-office-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-head-office/video-head-office-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-head-office/video-head-office-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-head-office/video-head-office-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-head-office/video-head-office-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-head-office/video-head-office-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",24,The naive son <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Senator makes lightening-fast climb corporate ladder big conglomerate. Script wastes terrific cast!,Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003331142/head-office.html,54a508c179881011bed2b642,null,{"main":"Head Office"},"{original:HBO Video,person:[{firstname:Hbo,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Video}]}",multimedia
A pair zany fast-food counter dudes stop giant evil conglomerate making mincemeat dinky burger joint.,null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T03:35:59Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-good-burger/video-good-burger-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-good-burger/video-good-burger-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-good-burger/video-good-burger-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-good-burger/video-good-burger-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-good-burger/video-good-burger-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-good-burger/video-good-burger-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",23,A pair zany fast-food counter dudes stop giant evil conglomerate making mincemeat dinky burger joint.,Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003328340/good-burger.html,54a506f779881011bed2b5d9,null,{"main":"Good Burger"},"{original:Nickelodeon/Paramount,person:[{firstname:Nickelodeon,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Paramount}]}",multimedia
"The actions <PERSON>Tony Fernandes</PERSON>, chief executive Malaysian company, compared favorably response <ORGANIZATION>Malaysia Airlines</ORGANIZATION> earlier <DATE>2014</DATE>.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Aviation Accidents, Safety Disasters},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:Fernandes, Tony <DATE>1964<\/DATE>-},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:4,value:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:5,value:<LOCATION>Indonesia<\/LOCATION>}]",Business Day,"Handling latest fatal <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> crash chief executive <PERSON>Tony Fernandes</PERSON> received public response <ORGANIZATION>Malaysia Airlines</ORGANIZATION> management disaster earlier <DATE>2014</DATE>; Fernandes addressed situation compassionate, hands-on approach won praise turnaround <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION>, deeply debt state control 13 years earlier.",The New York Times,[],Business,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/business/01airaisa1/01airaisa1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/01airaisa1/01airaisa1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/business/01airaisa1/01airaisa1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:438},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/01airaisa1/01airaisa1-articleLarge.jpg,height:438},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/business/01airaisa1/01airaisa1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/01airaisa1/01airaisa1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1272,"The actions <PERSON>Tony Fernandes</PERSON>, chief executive Malaysian company, compared favorably response <ORGANIZATION>Malaysia Airlines</ORGANIZATION> earlier <DATE>2014</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/business/international/airasia-tony-fernandes-responds-to-crisis-with-quick-compassion.html,54a45a2879881011bed28e64,International Business,"{main:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION>’s Chief Responds to Crisis With Quick Compassion,print_headline:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION>’s Chief Responds Quickly and With Compassion}","{contributor:<PERSON>Austin Ramzy<\/PERSON> contributed reporting <LOCATION>Hong Kong Michael Forsythe Putrajaya<\/LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Malaysia<\/LOCATION>.,original:By <PERSON>ALEXANDRA STEVENSON NEIL GOUGH<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Alexandra,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:STEVENSON},{firstname:Neil,role:reported,organization:,rank:2,lastname:GOUGH}]}",article
"The aging, embittered <PERSON>Michael Corleone</PERSON> reluctantly reverts violence preserve family honor cement European conglomerate involving <ORGANIZATION>Catholic Church</ORGANIZATION>. Not acclaimed predecessors great film.",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2014-12-31T22:02:24Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/05/01/movies/video-the-godfather-part-3/video-the-godfather-part-3-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/05/01/movies/video-the-godfather-part-3/video-the-godfather-part-3-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/05/01/movies/video-the-godfather-part-3/video-the-godfather-part-3-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/05/01/movies/video-the-godfather-part-3/video-the-godfather-part-3-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/05/01/movies/video-the-godfather-part-3/video-the-godfather-part-3-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/05/01/movies/video-the-godfather-part-3/video-the-godfather-part-3-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",37,"The aging, embittered <PERSON>Michael Corleone</PERSON> reluctantly reverts violence preserve family honor cement European conglomerate involving <ORGANIZATION>Catholic Church</ORGANIZATION>. Not acclaimed predecessors great film.",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003388032/the-godfather-part-3.html,54a4b8c579881011bed2a40d,null,{"main":"The Godfather Part 3"},"{original:Paramount Home Entertainment,person:[{firstname:Paramount,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Home,rank:1,lastname:Entertainment}]}",multimedia
"In RoboCop, the year is <DATE>2028</DATE> and multinational conglomerate <ORGANIZATION>OmniCorp</ORGANIZATION> is at the center of robot technology. Overseas, their drones have been used by the military for years– and it’s meant billions for <ORGANIZATION>OmniCorp</ORGANIZATION>’s bottom line. Now <ORGANIZATION>OmniCorp</ORGANIZATION> wants...",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2014-12-31T13:33:36Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-robocop/video-robocop-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-robocop/video-robocop-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-robocop/video-robocop-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-robocop/video-robocop-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-robocop/video-robocop-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/05/12/movies/video-robocop/video-robocop-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",41,"In RoboCop, the year is <DATE>2028</DATE> and multinational conglomerate <ORGANIZATION>OmniCorp</ORGANIZATION> is at the center of robot technology. Overseas, their drones have been used by the military for years– and it’s meant billions for <ORGANIZATION>OmniCorp</ORGANIZATION>’s bottom line. Now <ORGANIZATION>OmniCorp</ORGANIZATION> wants to br",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003369552/robocop.html,54a4418579881011bed28927,null,{"main":"Robocop"},"{original:Sony Pictures,person:[{firstname:Sony,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Pictures}]}",multimedia
"The Chinese company has agreed to acquire the <ORGANIZATION>Meadowbrook Insurance Group</ORGANIZATION> of <LOCATION>Southfield</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Mich.</LOCATION>, for <MONEY>$433 million</MONEY> in cash.",null,"[{name:glocations,rank:1,value:China},{name:glocations,rank:2,value:Southfield Mich},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:Fosun International},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:<ORGANIZATION>Meadowbrook Insurance Group<\/ORGANIZATION>},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Insurance},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Mergers, Acquisitions Divestitures}]",Business Day,"The Chinese company has agreed to acquire the <ORGANIZATION>Meadowbrook Insurance Group</ORGANIZATION> of <LOCATION>Southfield</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Mich.</LOCATION>, for <MONEY>$433 million</MONEY> in cash.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-31T10:20:50Z,[],250,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2014/12/31/fosun-of-china-in-u-s-insurance-deal/,54a414be7988102761d6e1a9,Dealbook,"{main:Fosun <LOCATION>China U.S.<\/LOCATION> Insurance Deal,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By DEALBOOK,person:[{firstname:Dealbook,role:reported,organization:,rank:1}]}",blogpost
"Chinese conglomerate <ORGANIZATION>Fosun International Ltd</ORGANIZATION> making foray <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> insurance market buying  property casualty insurer Meadowbrook, deal secure funds acquisitions.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T21:57:57Z,[],400,"Chinese conglomerate <ORGANIZATION>Fosun International Ltd</ORGANIZATION> making foray <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> insurance market buying  property casualty insurer Meadowbrook, deal secure funds acquisitions.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/business/30reuters-meadowbrook-ins-m-a-fosun-intl.html,54a366ef7988102761d6cfa1,null,"{main:<LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION>'s Fosun Buy <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Insurer Help Finance Acquisition Spree,print_headline:<LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION>'s Fosun Buy <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Insurer Help Finance Acquisition Spree}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
<LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>'s state-run oil company Petrobras <DATE>Monday</DATE> growing corruption scandal implicate employee pension fund led freeze payments 23 contractors allegedly involved scheme.,null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-29T22:19:36Z,[],326,<LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>'s state-run oil company Petrobras <DATE>Monday</DATE> growing corruption scandal implicate employee pension fund led freeze payments 23 contractors allegedly involved scheme.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/29/business/29reuters-brazil-petrobras.html,54a21a547988104803cc8945,null,"{main:Petrobras Says Probe May Implicate Pension Fund; Cuts Off Contractors,print_headline:Petrobras Says Probe May Implicate Pension Fund; Cuts Off Contractors}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501 disappeared part world <ORGANIZATION>Malaysia Airlines</ORGANIZATION> Flight 370 differs important ways.,null,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Aviation Accidents, Safety Disasters},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:<ORGANIZATION>Malaysia Airlines<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight 370},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501}]",World,null,The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-29T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/29/world/29plane/29plane-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/world/29plane/29plane-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/29/world/29plane/29plane-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/world/29plane/29plane-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/29/world/29plane/29plane-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/world/29plane/29plane-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",961,<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501 disappeared part world <ORGANIZATION>Malaysia Airlines</ORGANIZATION> Flight 370 differs important ways.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/29/world/asia/questions-about-flight-8501.html,54a067057988101f98e3edfd,Asia Pacific,"{main:Two Flights Go Missing, Their Stories Are Not Same,seo:The Facts <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>NICOLA CLARK<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Nicola,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:CLARK}]}",article
