snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"<LOCATION>Libya</LOCATION> made progress extinguishing fire oil storage tanks country's biggest oil port, <PERSON>Es Sider</PERSON>, raging week, member firefighting crew <DATE>Thursday</DATE>.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T17:22:06Z,[],285,"<LOCATION>Libya</LOCATION> made progress extinguishing fire oil storage tanks country's biggest oil port, <PERSON>Es Sider</PERSON>, raging week, member firefighting crew <DATE>Thursday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/world/africa/01reuters-libya-security.html,54a5c9337988102023c94cc1,<LOCATION>Africa</LOCATION>,"{main:<LOCATION>Libya<\/LOCATION> Sees More Progress Extinguishing Fire Eastern Oil Terminal,print_headline:<LOCATION>Libya<\/LOCATION> Sees More Progress Extinguishing Fire Eastern Oil Terminal}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Uber, Facebook, Instagram &#8212;, rage, <DATE>2014</DATE> winds ready fresh. From ride-hailing photo sharing, up-and coming apps startups watch <DATE>2015</DATE>. Which...",null,[],Technology,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T13:09:18Z,[],840,"Uber, Facebook, Instagram &#8212;, rage, <DATE>2014</DATE> winds ready fresh. From ride-hailing photo sharing, up-and coming apps startups watch <DATE>2015</DATE>. Which breakout hit year??",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/technology/ap-us-tec-startups-to-watch-in-2015.html,54a58e407988102023c941fb,null,"{main:In With New: Snappy Apps 2015,print_headline:In With New: Snappy Apps 2015}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"A city girl, moved small town <ORGANIZATION>Pacific Northwest</ORGANIZATION>, makes friends woodsy tomboy. Following clues legend, venture treacherous mountain cavern, search long lost treasure.",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T12:53:31Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-gold-diggers-the-secret-of-bear-mountain/video-gold-diggers-the-secret-of-bear-mountain-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-gold-diggers-the-secret-of-bear-mountain/video-gold-diggers-the-secret-of-bear-mountain-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-gold-diggers-the-secret-of-bear-mountain/video-gold-diggers-the-secret-of-bear-mountain-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-gold-diggers-the-secret-of-bear-mountain/video-gold-diggers-the-secret-of-bear-mountain-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-gold-diggers-the-secret-of-bear-mountain/video-gold-diggers-the-secret-of-bear-mountain-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-gold-diggers-the-secret-of-bear-mountain/video-gold-diggers-the-secret-of-bear-mountain-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",40,"A city girl, moved small town <ORGANIZATION>Pacific Northwest</ORGANIZATION>, makes friends woodsy tomboy. Following clues legend, venture treacherous mountain cavern, search long lost treasure.",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003328178/gold-diggers-the-secret-of-bear-mountain.html,54a589a97988102023c94091,null,{"main":"Gold Diggers: The Secret Of Bear Mountain"},"{original:Universal Studios Home Entertainment,person:[{firstname:Universal,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Studios,rank:1,lastname:Home}]}",multimedia
"Six months introduction, Kindle Unlimited proving controversial disruptive, <LOCATION>Amazon</LOCATION> innovations.",null,"[{name:organizations,rank:1,value:Amazon.com Inc},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Amazon Kindle},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Book Trade Publishing},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Books Literature},{name:subject,rank:4,value:E-Books Readers},{name:subject,rank:5,value:Writing Writers}]",Technology,"Six months introduction, Kindle Unlimited proving controversial disruptive, <LOCATION>Amazon</LOCATION> innovations.",The New York Times,[],Business,2015-01-01T07:00:48Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/technology/31bits-amazon/31bits-amazon-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/technology/31bits-amazon/31bits-amazon-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/technology/31bits-amazon/31bits-amazon-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/technology/31bits-amazon/31bits-amazon-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/technology/31bits-amazon/31bits-amazon-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/technology/31bits-amazon/31bits-amazon-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1026,null,Blog,http://bits.blogs.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/writers-are-mixed-over-amazon-unlimited/,54a5380c79881011bed2c0e5,null,"{main:Writers Are Mixed Over Amazon Unlimited,kicker:Bits}","{original:By <PERSON>DAVID STREITFELD<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:David,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:STREITFELD}]}",blogpost
With year plenty sales.,4,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Fashion Apparel},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:E-Commerce},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Shopping Retail}]",Fashion & Style,null,The New York Times,[],Styles,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/fashion/31SCOUT/31SCOUT-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/fashion/31SCOUT/31SCOUT-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/fashion/31SCOUT/31SCOUT-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:600},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/fashion/31SCOUT/31SCOUT-articleLarge.jpg,height:600},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/fashion/31SCOUT/31SCOUT-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/fashion/31SCOUT/31SCOUT-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",379,With year plenty sales.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/fashion/end-of-season-sales.html,54a4717f79881011bed293bc,null,"{content_kicker:Scouting Report,main:End-of-Season Sales,print_headline:End-of-Season Sales,kicker:Scouting Report}",[],article
"<PERSON>Michael Swier</PERSON>&#8217;s <LOCATION>Los Angeles</LOCATION> music club, Teragram Ballroom, big leap businessman made name <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:1,value:Teragram Ballroom <LOCATION>Los Angeles<\/LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Calif<\/LOCATION>, Music Venue},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Music},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Swier<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Michael<\/PERSON>},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:4,value:Los Angeles Calif},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:5,value:Bars Nightclubs}]",Arts,"<PERSON>Michael Swier</PERSON>, who opened rock clubs the <ORGANIZATION>Mercury Lounge</ORGANIZATION> and the <ORGANIZATION>Bowery Ballroom</ORGANIZATION> in <LOCATION>New York City</LOCATION> in the <DATE>1990s</DATE>, is set to open <ORGANIZATION>Teragram Ballroom</ORGANIZATION> in <LOCATION>Los Angeles</LOCATION>; venture, which involved <MONEY>$2 million</MONEY> renovation of former silent movie theater, is <PERSON>Swier</PERSON>'s first West Coast project.",The New York Times,[],Culture,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2015/01/01/arts/swier/swier-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/arts/swier/swier-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2015/01/01/arts/swier/swier-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:390},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/arts/swier/swier-articleLarge.jpg,height:390},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2015/01/01/arts/swier/swier-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2015/01/01/arts/swier/swier-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",930,"<PERSON>Michael Swier</PERSON>&#8217;s <LOCATION>Los Angeles</LOCATION> music club, Teragram Ballroom, big leap businessman made name <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/arts/music/bowery-ballroom-leader-plans-music-club-in-los-angeles.html,54a470d979881011bed29394,Music,"{main:A Bowery Titan Puts Down <LOCATION>L.A.<\/LOCATION> Roots,seo:Bowery Ballroom Leader Plans Music Club <LOCATION>Los Angeles<\/LOCATION>,print_headline:A Bowery Titan Puts Down <LOCATION>L.A.<\/LOCATION> Roots}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>BEN SISARIO<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Ben,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SISARIO}]}",article
"The actions <PERSON>Tony Fernandes</PERSON>, chief executive Malaysian company, compared favorably response <ORGANIZATION>Malaysia Airlines</ORGANIZATION> earlier <DATE>2014</DATE>.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Aviation Accidents, Safety Disasters},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:3,value:Fernandes, Tony <DATE>1964<\/DATE>-},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:4,value:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:5,value:<LOCATION>Indonesia<\/LOCATION>}]",Business Day,"Handling latest fatal <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> crash chief executive <PERSON>Tony Fernandes</PERSON> received public response <ORGANIZATION>Malaysia Airlines</ORGANIZATION> management disaster earlier <DATE>2014</DATE>; Fernandes addressed situation compassionate, hands-on approach won praise turnaround <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION>, deeply debt state control 13 years earlier.",The New York Times,[],Business,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/31/business/01airaisa1/01airaisa1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/01airaisa1/01airaisa1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/31/business/01airaisa1/01airaisa1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:438},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/01airaisa1/01airaisa1-articleLarge.jpg,height:438},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/31/business/01airaisa1/01airaisa1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/31/business/01airaisa1/01airaisa1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1272,"The actions <PERSON>Tony Fernandes</PERSON>, chief executive Malaysian company, compared favorably response <ORGANIZATION>Malaysia Airlines</ORGANIZATION> earlier <DATE>2014</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/business/international/airasia-tony-fernandes-responds-to-crisis-with-quick-compassion.html,54a45a2879881011bed28e64,International Business,"{main:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION>’s Chief Responds to Crisis With Quick Compassion,print_headline:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION>’s Chief Responds Quickly and With Compassion}","{contributor:<PERSON>Austin Ramzy<\/PERSON> contributed reporting <LOCATION>Hong Kong Michael Forsythe Putrajaya<\/LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Malaysia<\/LOCATION>.,original:By <PERSON>ALEXANDRA STEVENSON NEIL GOUGH<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Alexandra,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:STEVENSON},{firstname:Neil,role:reported,organization:,rank:2,lastname:GOUGH}]}",article
"Former <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Democratic Senator <PERSON>Mike Gravel</PERSON>, represented <LOCATION>Alaska</LOCATION> <DATE>1970s</DATE>, <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> head <LOCATION>Nevada</LOCATION> company develops markets cannabis throat lozenges products states steps legalize weed.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T19:23:20Z,[],303,"Former <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Democratic Senator <PERSON>Mike Gravel</PERSON>, represented <LOCATION>Alaska</LOCATION> <DATE>1970s</DATE>, <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> head <LOCATION>Nevada</LOCATION> company develops markets cannabis throat lozenges products states steps legalize weed.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/us/politics/31reuters-usa-marijuana-alaska.html,54a493e679881011bed29b9b,Politics,"{main:Former Alaska Senator Gravel Named Chief Executive Cannabis Products Company,print_headline:Former Alaska Senator Gravel Named Chief Executive Cannabis Products Company}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Three cops join investigate brutal multiple murder local diner. In case, uncover layers deceit political corruption venture glamorous seedy worlds <LOCATION>Tinseltown</LOCATION>.",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2014-12-31T14:58:59Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/05/06/movies/video-la-confidential/video-la-confidential-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/05/06/movies/video-la-confidential/video-la-confidential-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/05/06/movies/video-la-confidential/video-la-confidential-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/05/06/movies/video-la-confidential/video-la-confidential-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/05/06/movies/video-la-confidential/video-la-confidential-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/05/06/movies/video-la-confidential/video-la-confidential-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",40,"Three cops join investigate brutal multiple murder local diner. In case, uncover layers deceit political corruption venture glamorous seedy worlds <LOCATION>Tinseltown</LOCATION>.",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003347745/la-confidential.html,54a4558a79881011bed28d52,null,{"main":"<LOCATION>L.A.<\/LOCATION> Confidential"},"{original:Warner Home Video,person:[{firstname:Warner,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Home,rank:1,lastname:Video}]}",multimedia
"As Americans trimmed tree week hung stockings care, viewers turned TV screens. During week reruns, total prime-time viewership Big Four networks dipped <PERCENT>25 percent</PERCENT> week.",null,[],Business Day,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-31T13:15:13Z,[],336,"As Americans trimmed tree week hung stockings care, viewers turned TV screens. During week reruns, total prime-time viewership Big Four networks dipped <PERCENT>25 percent</PERCENT> week.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/31/business/ap-us-nielsens.html,54a43e3279881011bed28802,null,"{main:A Week Reruns, Christmas Saw Dip TV Viewing,print_headline:A Week Reruns, Christmas Saw Dip TV Viewing}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
