snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
Palestinian President <PERSON>Mahmoud Abbas</PERSON> entered confrontation <LOCATION>Israel</LOCATION> signing <ORGANIZATION>International Criminal Court</ORGANIZATION>.,null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T10:40:03Z,[],846,Palestinian President <PERSON>Mahmoud Abbas</PERSON> entered confrontation <LOCATION>Israel</LOCATION> signing <ORGANIZATION>International Criminal Court</ORGANIZATION>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/world/middleeast/01reuters-palestinians-israel-abbas.html,54a56b0279881011bed2cc49,Middle East,"{main:Abbas Trades Stalemate Confrontation ICC Move,print_headline:Abbas Trades Stalemate Confrontation ICC Move}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION> criticized latest <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> sanctions targets <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION> helped <LOCATION>Tehran</LOCATION> avoid existing sanctions commit human rights abuses, contravened spirit international talks <LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION>'s nuclear program.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T07:18:10Z,[],325,"<LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION> criticized latest <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> sanctions targets <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION> helped <LOCATION>Tehran</LOCATION> avoid existing sanctions commit human rights abuses, contravened spirit international talks <LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION>'s nuclear program.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/world/middleeast/31reuters-usa-iran-sanctions.html,54a3e9b97988102761d6dcb0,Middle East,"{main:<LOCATION>Iran<\/LOCATION> Says <LOCATION>New U.S.<\/LOCATION> Sanctions Violate Spirit Nuclear Talks,print_headline:<LOCATION>Iran<\/LOCATION> Says <LOCATION>New U.S.<\/LOCATION> Sanctions Violate Spirit Nuclear Talks}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> imposed sanctions targets, entities people targeted supported <LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION>'s efforts avoid sanctions backed government's human rights abuses, including censorship.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T11:27:11Z,[],270,"The <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> imposed sanctions targets, entities people targeted supported <LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION>'s efforts avoid sanctions backed government's human rights abuses, including censorship.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/world/middleeast/30reuters-usa-iran-sanctions.html,54a2d2957988104803cc8ae7,Middle East,"{main:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Names More Iran Targets Sanctions,print_headline:<LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Names More Iran Targets Sanctions}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"A dozen employees of Radio Free Europe/Radio Liberty, including an anchor and the cleaning woman, were arrested and detained for up to 12 hours over the <DATE>weekend</DATE>, as prosecutors intensified a crackdown on journalists.",4,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Azerbaijan<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:News News Media},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Radio Free Europe-Radio Liberty},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Radio},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:5,value:Radio Free <LOCATION>Europe<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Espionage Intelligence Services},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:False Arrests, Convictions Imprisonments}]",World,"Azerbaijani authorities arrest detain 12 employees Radio Free Europe-Radio Liberty, radio station backed <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION>, 12 hours, prosecutors increase crackdown journalists nongovernmental organizations.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-29T00:00:00Z,[],501,"A dozen employees of Radio Free Europe/Radio Liberty, including an anchor and the cleaning woman, were arrested and detained for up to 12 hours over the <DATE>weekend</DATE>, as prosecutors intensified a crackdown on journalists.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/29/world/middleeast/radio-station-backed-by-us-is-raided-in-azerbaijan.html,54a0adfd7988101f98e3ee6d,Middle East,"{main:Radio Station Backed <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Is Raided Azerbaijan,print_headline:Radio Station Backed <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Is Raided Azerbaijan}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>DAVID M. HERSZENHORN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:David,role:reported,organization:,rank:1}]}",article
"<LOCATION>Colombia</LOCATION>'s Marxist <ORGANIZATION>FARC</ORGANIZATION> rebels freed soldier captured attack military patrol week troops killed, group <DATE>Friday</DATE>.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-26T15:28:32Z,[],409,"<LOCATION>Colombia</LOCATION>'s Marxist <ORGANIZATION>FARC</ORGANIZATION> rebels freed soldier captured attack military patrol week troops killed, group <DATE>Friday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/26/world/americas/26reuters-colombia-soldier.html,549dc53c7988105ced7885e9,Americas,"{main:<LOCATION>Colombia<\/LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>FARC<\/ORGANIZATION> Rebels Free Soldier Captured During Attack,print_headline:<LOCATION>Colombia<\/LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>FARC<\/ORGANIZATION> Rebels Free Soldier Captured During Attack}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
A selected guide dance performances <LOCATION>New York City</LOCATION>.,24,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Dancing}]",Arts,null,The New York Times,[],Weekend,2014-12-26T00:00:00Z,[],747,A selected guide dance performances <LOCATION>New York City</LOCATION>.,Schedule,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/26/arts/dance/dance-listings-for-dec-26-jan-1.html,549c97b27988103babf08a76,Dance,"{main:Dance Listings <DATE>Dec. 26-Jan<\/DATE>. 1,print_headline:The Listings: Dance}",[],article
"<LOCATION>Colombia</LOCATION>'s Marxist <ORGANIZATION>FARC</ORGANIZATION> rebels free soldier captured week ambush military patrol killed colleagues, online statement <DATE>Thursday</DATE>.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-25T19:20:49Z,[],405,"<LOCATION>Colombia</LOCATION>'s Marxist <ORGANIZATION>FARC</ORGANIZATION> rebels free soldier captured week ambush military patrol killed colleagues, online statement <DATE>Thursday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/25/world/americas/25reuters-colombia-soldier.html,549caa937988103babf08a99,Americas,"{main:<LOCATION>Colombia<\/LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>FARC<\/ORGANIZATION> Rebels Free K.dnapped Soldier Peace Gesture,print_headline:<LOCATION>Colombia<\/LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>FARC<\/ORGANIZATION> Rebels Free Kidnapped Soldier Peace Gesture}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
Television highlights.,9,[],Arts,null,The New York Times,[],Culture,2014-12-24T00:00:00Z,[],755,Television highlights.,Schedule,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/24/arts/television/whats-on-tv-wednesday.html,549a56687988102d96d566ec,Television,"{main:What’s on TV <DATE>Wednesday<\/DATE>,print_headline:What’s On TV <DATE>Wednesday<\/DATE>}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>BRANDON K. THORP<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Brandon,role:reported,organization:,middlename:K.,rank:1,lastname:THORP}]}",article
"Between <DATE>2003</DATE> and <DATE>2012</DATE>, <MONEY>$6.6 trillion</MONEY> was secretly and illegally funneled out of developing and emerging economies by entities that may have been involved in crime, corruption and tax evasion, according to one study.",null,"[{name:glocations,rank:1,value:China},{name:glocations,rank:2,value:United States},{name:organizations,rank:1,value:International Monetary Fund},{name:organizations,rank:2,value:World Trade Organization},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Frauds Swindling},{name:subject,rank:2,value:International Trade World Market},{name:subject,rank:3,value:Tax Evasion}]",World,"Between <DATE>2003</DATE> and <DATE>2012</DATE>, <MONEY>$6.6 trillion</MONEY> was secretly and illegally funneled out of developing and emerging economies by entities that may have been involved in crime, corruption and tax evasion, according to one study.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-23T21:45:01Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/23/world/23sino-BAKER/23sino-BAKER-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/23/world/23sino-BAKER/23sino-BAKER-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/23/world/23sino-BAKER/23sino-BAKER-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:840},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/23/world/23sino-BAKER/23sino-BAKER-articleLarge.jpg,height:840},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/23/world/23sino-BAKER/23sino-BAKER-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/23/world/23sino-BAKER/23sino-BAKER-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",933,null,Blog,http://sinosphere.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/23/q-and-a-raymond-w-baker-on-financial-fraud-in-china/,549a28d77988102d96d55c73,Asia Pacific,"{main:Q. A.: <PERSON>Raymond W. Baker<\/PERSON> Financial Fraud <LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION>,kicker:Sinosphere}","{original:By <PERSON>DAVID BARBOZA<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:David,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BARBOZA}]}",blogpost
"A group <LOCATION>Milwaukee</LOCATION> aldermen pushing host police reforms prosecutors declined charge officer shot man 14 times, including equipping police body cameras identifying officers prone violence.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-23T02:24:34Z,[],744,"A group <LOCATION>Milwaukee</LOCATION> aldermen pushing host police reforms prosecutors declined charge officer shot man 14 times, including equipping police body cameras identifying officers prone violence.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/23/us/ap-us-killings-by-police-milwaukee.html,549918f7798810035238e784,null,"{main:Police Reforms Proposed After Milwaukee Shooting,print_headline:Police Reforms Proposed After Milwaukee Shooting}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
