snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"A currency printing mold <PERSON>Benjamin Franklin</PERSON>, mighty precious hardware.",31,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Antiques},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Franklin<\/PERSON>, Benjamin},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Printing Allied Trades},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Counterfeit Money Financial Instruments},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:5,value:<LOCATION>Philadelphia<\/LOCATION> Pa},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Architecture},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:Furniture},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:8,value:<PERSON>Aalto<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Alvar<\/PERSON>},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:9,value:Library Company <LOCATION>Philadelphia<\/LOCATION>}]",Arts,Eve M <PERSON>Kahn</PERSON> Antiques column; metal currency printing mold made <PERSON>Benjamin Franklin</PERSON>'s printing shop discovered exhibited Library Company; hardware pieces designed acclaimed architects artisans selling tens thousands dollars auctions.,The New York Times,[],Weekend,2014-12-12T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/12/arts/12ANTIQUES3/ANTIQUES3-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/12/arts/12ANTIQU.S./ANTIQUES3-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/12/arts/12ANTIQUES3/ANTIQUES3-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:793},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/12/arts/12ANTIQUES3/ANTIQUES3-articleLarge.jpg,height:793},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/12/arts/12ANTIQUES3/ANTIQUES3-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/12/arts/12ANTIQUES3/ANTIQUES3-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",950,"A currency printing mold <PERSON>Benjamin Franklin</PERSON>, mighty precious hardware.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/12/arts/design/how-franklin-thwarted-counterfeiters-.html,548b166e7988102fcc1317ff,Art & Design,"{content_kicker:Antiques,main:How Franklin Thwarted Counterfeiters,print_headline:How Franklin Thwarted Counterfeiters,kicker:Antiques}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>EVE M. KAHN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Eve,role:reported,organization:,rank:1}]}",article
A small <LOCATION>Virginia</LOCATION> city lose city hall police station dream municipal golf economic driver bust.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-11T12:39:47Z,[],406,A small <LOCATION>Virginia</LOCATION> city lose city hall police station dream municipal golf economic driver bust.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/11/us/11reuters-usa-virginia-default.html,5489d74c7988102fcc12f8e5,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Virginia Town Could Lose City Hall<\/LOCATION>, Police Station Amid Default,print_headline:<LOCATION>Virginia Town Could Lose City Hall<\/LOCATION>, Police Station Amid Default}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
Retirees covered financially troubled multiemployer pensions benefits cut congressional spending deal government running.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-11T03:26:53Z,[],903,Retirees covered financially troubled multiemployer pensions benefits cut congressional spending deal government running.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/11/us/politics/ap-us-congress-pensions-qa.html,548956047988104c1745a912,Politics,"{main:Multiemployer Pensions Could Face Cuts,print_headline:Multiemployer Pensions Could Face Cuts}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Swapping crisis for compromise, the <ORGANIZATION>House</ORGANIZATION> narrowly approved <MONEY>$1.1 trillion</MONEY> in government-wide spending <DATE>Thursday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME> after President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON> and Republicans joined forces to override Democratic complaints that the bill would also ease bank...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-11T03:11:41Z,[],978,"Swapping crisis for compromise, the <ORGANIZATION>House</ORGANIZATION> narrowly approved <MONEY>$1.1 trillion</MONEY> in government-wide spending <DATE>Thursday</DATE> <TIME>night</TIME> after President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON> and Republicans joined forces to override Democratic complaints that the bill would also ease bank regulations imposed after the economy's near-collapse in <DATE>2008</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/11/us/politics/ap-us-congress-rdp.html,548952747988104c1745a878,Politics,"{main:House Approves <MONEY>$1.1<\/MONEY>T Bill Financing Government,print_headline:House Approves <MONEY>$1.1<\/MONEY>T Bill Financing Government}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Retirees covered financially troubled multiemployer pensions benefits cut congressional spending deal government running.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-10T17:59:42Z,[],903,Retirees covered financially troubled multiemployer pensions benefits cut congressional spending deal government running.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/10/us/politics/ap-us-congress-pensions-qa.html,5488d1317988104c17459eee,Politics,"{main:Deal Allow Multiemployer Pension Benefits Cuts,print_headline:Deal Allow Multiemployer Pension Benefits Cuts}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Time running short, Republicans and Democrats agreed <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> on a <MONEY>$1.1 trillion</MONEY> spending bill to avoid a government shutdown and delay a politically-charged struggle over President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON>'s new immigration policy until the new year.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-09T03:05:59Z,[],978,"Time running short, Republicans and Democrats agreed <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> on a <MONEY>$1.1 trillion</MONEY> spending bill to avoid a government shutdown and delay a politically-charged struggle over President <PERSON>Barack Obama</PERSON>'s new immigration policy until the new year.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/09/us/politics/ap-us-congress-rdp.html,5486ad987988101981f9f472,Politics,"{main:Lawmakers Agree on <MONEY>$1.1 Trillion<\/MONEY> Spending Bill,print_headline:Lawmakers Agree on <MONEY>$1.1 Trillion<\/MONEY> Spending Bill}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
<ORGANIZATION>Congress</ORGANIZATION> prepared on <DATE>Monday</DATE> to scale back <PERSON>Michelle Obama</PERSON>&#8217;s school-lunch nutrition mandates and curtail some clean water regulations in a <MONEY>$1 trillion</MONEY> spending bill that would avert a government shutdown.,19,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:United States Politics Government},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:11,value:<PERSON>Boehner<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>John<\/PERSON> A},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Federal Budget US},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Lunch Breakfast Programs},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Law Legislation},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Shutdowns Institutional},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:Republican Party},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:7,value:Senate Committee Appropriations},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:8,value:House Committee Appropriations},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:9,value:<PERSON>Obama<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Michelle<\/PERSON>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:10,value:<PERSON>Mikulski<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Barbara<\/PERSON> A}]",<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,"<ORGANIZATION>Congress</ORGANIZATION> prepares to scale back <PERSON>Michelle Obama</PERSON>’s school-lunch nutrition mandates and curtail some clean water regulations in a <MONEY>$1 trillion</MONEY> spending bill that would avert a government shutdown, but extract policy price from Democratics.",The New York Times,[],National,2014-12-09T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/09/us/SUB-CONG/SUB-CONG-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/09/us/SUB-CONG/SUB-CONG-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/09/us/SUB-CONG/SUB-CONG-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:390},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/09/us/SUB-CONG/SUB-CONG-articleLarge.jpg,height:390},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/09/us/SUB-CONG/SUB-CONG-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/09/us/SUB-CONG/SUB-CONG-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1000,<ORGANIZATION>Congress</ORGANIZATION> prepared on <DATE>Monday</DATE> to scale back <PERSON>Michelle Obama</PERSON>&#8217;s school-lunch nutrition mandates and curtail some clean water regulations in a <MONEY>$1 trillion</MONEY> spending bill that would avert a government shutdown.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/09/us/politics/gop-extracts-price-for-averting-shutdown.html,548656047988101981f9ee56,Politics,"{main:G.O.P. Extracts Price Averting Shutdown,print_headline:G.O.P. Extracts Price Averting Shutdown}","{contributor:<PERSON>Julia Preston<\/PERSON> contributed reporting <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION>.,original:By <PERSON>JONATHAN WEISMAN ASHLEY PARKER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Jonathan,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:WEISMAN},{firstname:Ashley,role:reported,organization:,rank:2,lastname:PARKER}]}",article
Congressional officials key lawmakers change multiemployer pension plans cut benefits current retirees hopes avoiding future bankruptcies.,null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-08T18:24:43Z,[],131,Congressional officials key lawmakers change multiemployer pension plans cut benefits current retirees hopes avoiding future bankruptcies.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/08/us/politics/ap-us-congress-pensions.html,548633ff7988101981f9ee12,Politics,"{main:AP Sources: Congress Eyes Pension Plan Changes,print_headline:AP Sources: Congress Eyes Pension Plan Changes}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Key lawmakers weighed legislation to permit a reduction of benefits for up to 1 million retirees at economically distressed multiemployer pension plans, officials said late <DATE>Monday</DATE> as <ORGANIZATION>Congress</ORGANIZATION> labored over a <MONEY>$1.1 trillion</MONEY> measure to keep the...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-08T12:29:06Z,[],861,"Key lawmakers weighed legislation to permit a reduction of benefits for up to 1 million retirees at economically distressed multiemployer pension plans, officials said late <DATE>Monday</DATE> as <ORGANIZATION>Congress</ORGANIZATION> labored over a <MONEY>$1.1 trillion</MONEY> measure to keep the government operating past midnight <DATE>Thursday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/08/us/politics/ap-us-congress-rdp.html,5485e1157988101981f9e4a9,Politics,"{main:Key Lawmakers Seek Pension Changes,print_headline:Key Lawmakers Seek Pension Changes}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Multiemployer pension plans, involving unionized workers, common industries coal mining, trucking construction. But they&#8217;re running money.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Pensions Retirement Plans},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Retirement},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:401k, 403b 457 Plans},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Labor Jobs}]",Business Day,"<ORGANIZATION>Floyd Norris High & Low Finance</ORGANIZATION> column notes annual report released <ORGANIZATION>Pension Benefit Guaranty Corporation</ORGANIZATION> shows multiemployer pension plans run money years; warns absent legislation, pensions retired workers eliminated; laments political system unwilling taxpayer-supported solution.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-05T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/05/business/Norris/<ORGANIZATION>Norris-thumbWide<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/05/business/Norris/<ORGANIZATION>Norris-thumbWide<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/05/business/Norris/Norris-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:833},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/05/business/Norris/Norris-articleLarge.jpg,height:833},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/05/business/Norris/<ORGANIZATION>Norris-thumbStandard<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/05/business/Norris/<ORGANIZATION>Norris-thumbStandard<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg,height:75}]",1194,"Multiemployer pension plans, involving unionized workers, common industries coal mining, trucking construction. But they&#8217;re running money.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/05/business/without-new-laws-endangered-pensions-may-die.html,5480e8ae7988103739e172c4,null,"{content_kicker:High & Low Finance,main:A Strategy Pensions Risk Extinction,print_headline:A Strategy Pensions Risk Extinction,kicker:High &amp; Low Finance}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>FLOYD NORRIS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Floyd,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:NORRIS}]}",article
