snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"According recent studies, half Americans prospect good job home white picket fence, existed unachievable.",null,"[{name:type_of_material,rank:1,value:News}]",Opinion,"According recent studies, half Americans prospect good job home white picket fence, existed unachievable.",The New York Times,[],null,2015-01-01T19:32:18Z,[],2347,,Blog,http://www.nytimes.com/roomfordebate/2015/01/01/is-the-modern-american-dream-attainable,54a5e8887988102023c94f9e,Room For Debate,"{main:Is Modern American Dream Attainable??,kicker:Room For Debate}",null,blogpost
"With retail chains offering drop-off bins, certifying boards hold recyclers high standards, easier properly dispose devices.",6,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Recycling Waste Materials},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:11,value:<LOCATION>San Francisco Bay Area Calif<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:12,value:G.eenCitizen},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Waste Materials Disposal},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Electronics},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Environment},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:5,value:Best BUY Company Inc},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:<ORGANIZATION>Dell Inc<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:7,value:Environmental Protection Agency},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:8,value:Gazelle.com},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:9,value:United Nations Environment Program},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:10,value:eBay Inc}]",Technology,"Molly Wood Machine Learning column observes electronics fastest growing source waste world, million tons electronics ending trash yearly; welcomes fact easier consumers properly dispose electronics, retailers offering drop-off bins regulators holding recyclers higher standards.",The New York Times,[],Business,2015-01-01T00:00:00Z,[],1083,"With retail chains offering drop-off bins, certifying boards hold recyclers high standards, easier properly dispose devices.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/technology/personaltech/recycling-electronic-waste-responsibly-excuses-dwindle.html,54a48b3a79881011bed29993,Personal Tech,"{content_kicker:Machine Learning,main:Recycling Electronic Waste Responsibly: Excuses Dwindle,print_headline:Recycling Tech Waste Responsibly: Excuses Dwindle,kicker:Machine Learning}","{contributor:,original:By MOLLY WOOD,person:[{firstname:Molly,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:WOOD}]}",article
"A national animal rights group suing owner <LOCATION>Pennsylvania</LOCATION> ice cream shop force release female bear caged store public attraction 18 years, group <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-31T15:42:53Z,[],280,"A national animal rights group suing owner <LOCATION>Pennsylvania</LOCATION> ice cream shop force release female bear caged store public attraction 18 years, group <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/31/us/31reuters-usa-pennsylvania-bear.html,54a4608c79881011bed28fd7,null,"{main:Group Sues Free Bear Caged 18 Years <LOCATION>Pennsylvania<\/LOCATION> Sweets Shop,print_headline:Group Sues Free Bear Caged 18 Years <LOCATION>Pennsylvania<\/LOCATION> Sweets Shop}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The police investigating death <PERSON>Hock Ma</PERSON>, <LOCATION>Forest Hills</LOCATION>, found hot tub Spa Castle pronounced dead hospital.",null,"[{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:1,value:Ma, Hock},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Accidents Safety},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:3,value:Spa Castle},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:4,value:College Point <LOCATION>Queens<\/LOCATION>, NY},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Deaths Fatalities}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,null,The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-30T00:00:00Z,[],228,"The police investigating death <PERSON>Hock Ma</PERSON>, <LOCATION>Forest Hills</LOCATION>, found hot tub Spa Castle pronounced dead hospital.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/nyregion/man-84-dies-after-being-found-unresponsive-at-queens-spa.html,54a23ae97988104803cc89ad,null,"{main:Man, 84, Dies After Being Found Unresponsive Queens Spa}","{original:By <PERSON>EMMA G. FITZSIMMONS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Emma,role:reported,organization:,middlename:G.,rank:1,lastname:FITZSIMMONS}]}",article
"Rescue crews searching Indonesian waters <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia Indonesia</ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501, disappeared <DATE>Sunday</DATE> 162 passengers crew onboard. The plane flying <LOCATION>Surabaya</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Indonesia</LOCATION>'s second-largest city, halfway...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-29T08:13:06Z,[],1490,"Rescue crews searching Indonesian waters <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia Indonesia</ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501, disappeared <DATE>Sunday</DATE> 162 passengers crew onboard. The plane flying <LOCATION>Surabaya</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Indonesia</LOCATION>'s second-largest city, halfway destination, <LOCATION>Singapore</LOCATION>, vanished radar.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/29/us/ap-as-travel-indonesia-plane-questions.html,54a153db7988101f98e3ef9c,null,"{main:Q&A What Might Have Happened <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight,print_headline:Q&A What Might Have Happened <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
The head of the agency searching for Flight 8501 said that he believed the aircraft was “at the bottom of the sea” and warned that the country lacked adequate equipment for an underwater search.,1,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Indonesia<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Aviation Accidents, Safety Disasters},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:<ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION>},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:5,value:Surabaya <LOCATION>Indonesia<\/LOCATION>}]",World,"<PERSON>Bambang Soelistyo</PERSON>, head <ORGANIZATION>Indonesian National Search Rescue Agency</ORGANIZATION>, investigators missing <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> jet Flight 8501 sunk ocean warns <LOCATION>Indonesia</LOCATION> equipment suitable underwater search; <LOCATION>Malaysia</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Singapore Australia</LOCATION> offered search operation, effort evokes distressingly familiar mix grief mystery <ORGANIZATION>Malaysia Airlines</ORGANIZATION> aircraft missing Indian Ocean.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-29T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/29/world/asia/Indonesia/Indonesia-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/world/asia/Indonesia/Indonesia-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/29/world/asia/Indonesia/Indonesia-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:393},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/world/asia/Indonesia/Indonesia-articleLarge.jpg,height:393},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/29/world/asia/Indonesia/Indonesia-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/29/world/asia/Indonesia/Indonesia-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1295,The head of the agency searching for Flight 8501 said that he believed the aircraft was “at the bottom of the sea” and warned that the country lacked adequate equipment for an underwater search.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/29/world/asia/airasia-jet.html,549fc8c979881001534d205c,Asia Pacific,"{main:Indonesian Agency Says Missing <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Jet Probably Sank,print_headline:Jet Likely Sank, <LOCATION>Indonesia<\/LOCATION> Says}","{contributor:Reporting contributed <PERSON>Jeffrey Hutton Surabaya<\/PERSON>, <LOCATION>Indonesia<\/LOCATION>; <PERSON>Nicola Clark<\/PERSON> <LOCATION>Paris<\/LOCATION>; <PERSON>Poypiti Amatatham Muktita Suhartono<\/PERSON> <LOCATION>Bangkok<\/LOCATION>; <PERSON>Michael S. Schmidt<\/PERSON> <LOCATION>Honolulu<\/LOCATION>; <PERSON>Eric Schmitt<\/PERSON> <LOCATION>Washington<\/LOCATION>.,original:By <PERSON>THOMAS FULLER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Thomas,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:FULLER}]}",article
"Rescue crews searching Indonesian waters <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia Indonesia</ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501, disappeared <DATE>Sunday</DATE> 162 passengers crew onboard. The plane flying <LOCATION>Surabaya</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Indonesia</LOCATION>'s second-largest city, halfway...",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-28T11:13:21Z,[],1490,"Rescue crews searching Indonesian waters <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia Indonesia</ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501, disappeared <DATE>Sunday</DATE> 162 passengers crew onboard. The plane flying <LOCATION>Surabaya</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Indonesia</LOCATION>'s second-largest city, halfway destination, <LOCATION>Singapore</LOCATION>, vanished radar.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/28/us/ap-as-indonesia-plane-questions.html,54a02c8f79881001534d20c2,null,"{main:Q&A What Might Have Happened <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight,print_headline:Q&A What Might Have Happened <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia<\/ORGANIZATION> Flight}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
Readers react editorial British study showing uncomplicated pregnancies handled midwives.,16,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Midwives},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Pregnancy Childbirth},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Research}]",Opinion,null,The New York Times,[],Letters,2014-12-27T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/27/opinion/26LETTERSmidwife/26LETTERSmidwife-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/opinion/26LETTERSmidwife/26LETTERSmidwife-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/27/opinion/26LETTERSmidwife/26LETTERSmidwife-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:761},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/opinion/26LETTERSmidwife/26LETTERSmidwife-articleLarge.jpg,height:761},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/27/opinion/26LETTERSmidwife/26LETTERSmidwife-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/opinion/26LETTERSmidwife/26LETTERSmidwife-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",676,Readers react editorial British study showing uncomplicated pregnancies handled midwives.,Letter,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/27/opinion/the-role-of-midwives-in-american-births.html,549dea9e7988105ced788639,null,"{content_kicker:Letters,main:The Role Midwives American Births,print_headline:The Role Midwives American Births,kicker:Letters}",[],article
"Retirees flocking join fellow artists, letter carriers, <LOCATION>R.V.</LOCATION> enthusiasts places stay active needed care.",1,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Retirement},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Retirement Communities Assisted Living},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Elder Care},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:4,value:Nursing Homes}]",Your Money,"Retiring column; retirement communities cater people interests, passions, ways life, artists, homosexuals car enthusiasts, popular.",The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-27T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27retiring-pic/27retiring-pic-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27retiring-pic/27retiring-pic-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27retiring-pic/27retiring-pic-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27retiring-pic/27retiring-pic-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27retiring-pic/27retiring-pic-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/your-money/27retiring-pic/27retiring-pic-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1328,"Retirees flocking join fellow artists, letter carriers, <LOCATION>R.V.</LOCATION> enthusiasts places stay active needed care.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/27/your-money/finding-communities-that-connect-and-nurture-the-like-minded.html,549dbcba7988105ced7885d5,null,"{content_kicker:Retiring,main:Finding Communities That Connect Nurture Like-Minded,print_headline:Choosing Home Stay Connected,kicker:Retiring}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ABBY ELLIN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Abby,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:ELLIN}]}",article
"Issues handled federal tax system include health insurance exemptions, penalties, repayment excess subsidies.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Tax Preparers Preparation},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Patient Protection Affordable Care Act 2010},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Tax Credits, Deductions Exemptions},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:4,value:Health Insurance Managed Care},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Income Tax}]",Your Money,<PERSON>Tara Siegel Bernard</PERSON> Your Money column observes Affordable Care Act reconciled tax returns <DATE>2015</DATE>; notes means millions taxpayers deal tax forms calculations unexpected financial impacts; outlines biggest ways tax law affect taxpayers.,The New York Times,[],Business,2014-12-26T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/26/business/Penalty/Penalty-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/business/Penalty/Penalty-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/26/business/Penalty/Penalty-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/business/Penalty/Penalty-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/26/business/Penalty/<ORGANIZATION>Penalty-thumbStandard<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/business/Penalty/<ORGANIZATION>Penalty-thumbStandard<\/ORGANIZATION>.jpg,height:75}]",1396,"Issues handled federal tax system include health insurance exemptions, penalties, repayment excess subsidies.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/26/your-money/affordable-care-acts-tax-effects-now-loom-for-filers.html,549cb9cc7988103babf08ab1,null,"{content_kicker:Your Money,main:Affordable Care Act’s Tax Effects Now Loom for Filers,print_headline:Health Law Tax Effects Now Loom Filers,kicker:Your Money}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>TARA SIEGEL BERNARD<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Tara,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Siegel,rank:1,lastname:BERNARD}]}",article
