snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"<LOCATION>Indonesia</LOCATION>'s manufacturing activity contracted straight month <DATE>December</DATE>, falling weakest level early <DATE>2011</DATE> due declining output export orders, HSBC Markit purchasing managers' index PMI survey showed <DATE>Friday</DATE>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T22:01:32Z,[],240,"<LOCATION>Indonesia</LOCATION>'s manufacturing activity contracted straight month <DATE>December</DATE>, falling weakest level early <DATE>2011</DATE> due declining output export orders, HSBC Markit purchasing managers' index PMI survey showed <DATE>Friday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-indonesia-economy-pmi.html,54a60ac57988102023c952a4,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Indonesia<\/LOCATION> Manufacturing Contracts Record Low December-PMI,print_headline:<LOCATION>Indonesia<\/LOCATION> Manufacturing Contracts Record Low December-PMI}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<LOCATION>Singapore</LOCATION>'s economic growth slowed expected fourth quarter manufacturing sector contracted face erratic global demand, raising concerns outlook <DATE>2015</DATE>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T21:50:49Z,[],507,"<LOCATION>Singapore</LOCATION>'s economic growth slowed expected fourth quarter manufacturing sector contracted face erratic global demand, raising concerns outlook <DATE>2015</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-singapore-economy-gdp.html,54a607eb7988102023c95265,null,"{main:<LOCATION>Singapore<\/LOCATION>'s Slower-Than-Expected Fourth-Quarter Growth Signals Weaker Outlook 2015,print_headline:<LOCATION>Singapore<\/LOCATION>'s Slower-Than-Expected Fourth-Quarter Growth Signals Weaker Outlook 2015}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Deals worth nearly <MONEY>$3.5 trillion</MONEY> were announced, a performance favored by low interest rates and high stock prices.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Mergers, Acquisitions Divestitures}]",Business Day,"Deals worth nearly <MONEY>$3.5 trillion</MONEY> were announced, a performance favored by low interest rates and high stock prices.",The New York Times,[],Business,2015-01-01T19:32:44Z,[],525,null,Blog,http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2015/01/01/deal-makers-notched-nearly-3-5-trillion-worth-in-14-best-in-7-years/,54a5e7cc7988102023c94f8e,Dealbook,"{main:Deal Makers Notched Nearly <MONEY>$3.5<\/MONEY> <ORGANIZATION>Trillion Worth<\/ORGANIZATION> in &rsquo;14, Best in 7 Years,print_headline:Deal Makers Notched Nearly <MONEY>$3.5 Trillion<\/MONEY> Worth in ’14, Best in 7 Years,kicker:DealBook}","{original:By <PERSON>MICHAEL J. DE<\/PERSON> LA MERCED,person:[{firstname:Michael,role:reported,organization:,middlename:J.,rank:1,lastname:DE LA MERCED}]}",blogpost
"<LOCATION>South Korea</LOCATION>'s manufacturing activity shrank fourth consecutive month <DATE>December</DATE> slower pace, private-sector survey showed <DATE>Friday</DATE>, adding signs economy slowly regaining footing heading <DATE>2015</DATE>.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T19:03:32Z,[],250,"<LOCATION>South Korea</LOCATION>'s manufacturing activity shrank fourth consecutive month <DATE>December</DATE> slower pace, private-sector survey showed <DATE>Friday</DATE>, adding signs economy slowly regaining footing heading <DATE>2015</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-southkorea-economy-pmi.html,54a5e0717988102023c94ee3,null,"{main:<LOCATION>South Korea<\/LOCATION> <DATE>December<\/DATE> Factory Activity Shrinks Fourth Month Slower Pace-PMI,print_headline:<LOCATION>South Korea<\/LOCATION> <DATE>December<\/DATE> Factory Activity Shrinks Fourth Month Slower Pace-PMI}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Images bodies wreckage floating Indonesian waters gave relatives lost aboard <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501 anguish grief, provided answers families sought vain 10 months.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T09:13:29Z,[],869,"Images bodies wreckage floating Indonesian waters gave relatives lost aboard <ORGANIZATION>AirAsia</ORGANIZATION> Flight 8501 anguish grief, provided answers families sought vain 10 months.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/world/asia/ap-as-china-mh370-waiting-for-closure.html,54a5569c79881011bed2c7be,Asia Pacific,"{main:MH370 Relatives View <LOCATION>Indonesia<\/LOCATION> Crash With Empathy, Envy,print_headline:MH370 Relatives View <LOCATION>Indonesia<\/LOCATION> Crash With Empathy, Envy}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"After serving prison term revolutionary activity, simple honest man build life. His peaceful plans put test <ORGANIZATION>IRA</ORGANIZATION> buddies ex-girlfriend.",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T06:36:34Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-the-boxer/video-the-boxer-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-the-boxer/video-the-boxer-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-the-boxer/video-the-boxer-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-the-boxer/video-the-boxer-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-the-boxer/video-the-boxer-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/03/21/movies/video-the-boxer/video-the-boxer-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",35,"After serving prison term revolutionary activity, simple honest man build life. His peaceful plans put test <ORGANIZATION>IRA</ORGANIZATION> buddies ex-girlfriend.",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003383530/the-boxer.html,54a5314579881011bed2bf63,null,{"main":"The Boxer"},"{original:Universal Pictures,person:[{firstname:Universal,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Pictures}]}",multimedia
"Cuban police detained dozen dissidents <LOCATION>Havana</LOCATION> prison demand fellow opponents government released, dissidents <DATE>Thursday</DATE>.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T04:57:09Z,[],358,"Cuban police detained dozen dissidents <LOCATION>Havana</LOCATION> prison demand fellow opponents government released, dissidents <DATE>Thursday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/world/americas/01reuters-cuba-usa-dissidents.html,54a51a2179881011bed2ba2d,Americas,"{main:Cuban Police Detain Protesters Outside Prison, Dissidents Say,print_headline:Cuban Police Detain Protesters Outside Prison, Dissidents Say}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"The latest installment SCARY MOVIE franchise includes send ups PARANORMAL ACTIVITY, MAMA, SINISTER, THE EVIL DEAD, INCEPTION, BLACK SWAN pop culture featuring <PERSON>Ashley Tisdale</PERSON>, <PERSON>Charlie Sheen</PERSON>, <PERSON>Lindsay Lohan</PERSON>, <ORGANIZATION>Snoop Dogg</ORGANIZATION>, <PERSON>Katt Williams</PERSON>, <ORGANIZATION>Mol</ORGANIZATION>",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T01:38:40Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-scary-movie-v/video-scary-movie-v-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-scary-movie-v/video-scary-movie-v-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-scary-movie-v/video-scary-movie-v-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-scary-movie-v/video-scary-movie-v-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-scary-movie-v/video-scary-movie-v-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/03/28/movies/video-scary-movie-v/video-scary-movie-v-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",37,"The latest installment SCARY MOVIE franchise includes send ups PARANORMAL ACTIVITY, MAMA, SINISTER, THE EVIL DEAD, INCEPTION, BLACK SWAN pop culture featuring <PERSON>Ashley Tisdale</PERSON>, <PERSON>Charlie Sheen</PERSON>, <PERSON>Lindsay Lohan</PERSON>, <ORGANIZATION>Snoop Dogg</ORGANIZATION>, <PERSON>Katt Williams</PERSON>, <ORGANIZATION>Mol</ORGANIZATION>",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003371738/scary-movie-v.html,54a4eb7479881011bed2af99,null,{"main":"Scary Movie V"},"{original:Dimension Films,person:[{firstname:Dimension,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Films}]}",multimedia
"Growth <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s services sector picked slightly <DATE>December</DATE>, government study showed <DATE>Thursday</DATE>, helping offset weakness manufacturing weighing world's second-largest economy.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T00:37:48Z,[],141,"Growth <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s services sector picked slightly <DATE>December</DATE>, government study showed <DATE>Thursday</DATE>, helping offset weakness manufacturing weighing world's second-largest economy.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-china-economy-pmi-services.html,54a4ddbb79881011bed2ac77,null,"{main:China Service Sector Growth Picks Up <DATE>December<\/DATE>,print_headline:China Service Sector Growth Picks Up <DATE>December<\/DATE>}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s factory activity sputtered <DATE>December</DATE>, underlining challenges facing country's manufacturers fight rising costs softening demand cooling economy.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T00:37:48Z,[],762,"<LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s factory activity sputtered <DATE>December</DATE>, underlining challenges facing country's manufacturers fight rising costs softening demand cooling economy.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/business/01reuters-china-economy-pmi.html,54a4ddba79881011bed2ac73,null,"{main:China <DATE>December<\/DATE> Factory PMIs Suggest Economy Cooling Further, More Stimulus Expected,print_headline:China <DATE>December<\/DATE> Factory PMIs Suggest Economy Cooling Further, More Stimulus Expected}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
