snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"<LOCATION>Greece</LOCATION>'s radical leftist Syriza party cancel austerity <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION> erase big chunk Greek debt free country dark spell fallen, leader <PERSON>Alexis Tsipras</PERSON> told <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION> <DATE>Thursday</DATE>.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-18T09:29:27Z,[],661,"<LOCATION>Greece</LOCATION>'s radical leftist Syriza party cancel austerity <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION> erase big chunk Greek debt free country dark spell fallen, leader <PERSON>Alexis Tsipras</PERSON> told <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION> <DATE>Thursday</DATE>.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/18/world/europe/18reuters-greece-vote-tsipras.html,5492e5a379881005eed9d551,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:Tsipras Vows Break <LOCATION>Greece<\/LOCATION>'s 'Bad Spell',print_headline:Tsipras Vows Break <LOCATION>Greece<\/LOCATION>'s 'Bad Spell'}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Officials soliciting bids <ORGANIZATION>Park Service</ORGANIZATION>'s largest lucrative contracts, run iconic hotels restaurants Grand Canyon's South rim.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-14T22:39:48Z,[],420,"Officials soliciting bids <ORGANIZATION>Park Service</ORGANIZATION>'s largest lucrative contracts, run iconic hotels restaurants Grand Canyon's South rim.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/14/us/ap-us-travel-grand-canyon-contract.html,548e58e479881018ac4ba1d7,null,"{main:Grand Canyon Contract Offer Fails Attract Bids,print_headline:Grand Canyon Contract Offer Fails Attract Bids}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Officials soliciting bids <ORGANIZATION>Park Service</ORGANIZATION>'s largest lucrative contracts, run iconic hotels restaurants Grand Canyon's South rim.",null,[],<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-12T16:11:36Z,[],420,"Officials soliciting bids <ORGANIZATION>Park Service</ORGANIZATION>'s largest lucrative contracts, run iconic hotels restaurants Grand Canyon's South rim.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/12/us/ap-us-grand-canyon-contract.html,548b5adf79881004157bb56a,null,"{main:Grand Canyon Contract Offer Fails Attract Bids,print_headline:Grand Canyon Contract Offer Fails Attract Bids}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"The <ORGANIZATION>European Union</ORGANIZATION> banned <LOCATION>Libya</LOCATION>'s airlines operating European skies, citing safety concerns linked ongoing fighting.",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-11T11:18:50Z,[],123,"The <ORGANIZATION>European Union</ORGANIZATION> banned <LOCATION>Libya</LOCATION>'s airlines operating European skies, citing safety concerns linked ongoing fighting.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/11/world/europe/ap-eu-europe-libyan-airline-ban.html,5489c4777988104c1745bb62,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:<LOCATION>Libya<\/LOCATION>'s Airlines Banned From <ORGANIZATION>EU<\/ORGANIZATION> Skies,print_headline:<LOCATION>Libya<\/LOCATION>'s Airlines Banned From <ORGANIZATION>EU<\/ORGANIZATION> Skies}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Demonstrations end police whittle main protest area students, pro-democracy lawmakers academics wrangle proceed.",4,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Hong Kong<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Demonstrations, Protests Riots},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:3,value:China}]",World,"News analysis; thousands young people university student <PERSON>Manni</PERSON> Ng <LOCATION>Hong Kong</LOCATION> learned firsthand daunting highly organized, uncompromising government <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>; student protesters left wondering proceed failure demonstrators surround city government complex public support movement wanes.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-02T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/02/world/02hongkong/02hongkong-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/02/world/02hongkong/02hongkong-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/02/world/02hongkong/02hongkong-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/02/world/02hongkong/02hongkong-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/02/world/02hongkong/02hongkong-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/02/world/02hongkong/02hongkong-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",1121,"Demonstrations end police whittle main protest area students, pro-democracy lawmakers academics wrangle proceed.",An Analysis; News Analysis,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/02/world/asia/hong-kong-protests.html,547c7b1f798810629fb0d520,Asia Pacific,"{content_kicker:News Analysis,main:For <LOCATION>Hong Kong<\/LOCATION> Protesters, Spark Keep Alive,print_headline:For <LOCATION>Hong Kong<\/LOCATION> Protesters, Spark Keep Alive,kicker:News Analysis}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>MICHAEL FORSYTHE CHRIS BUCKLEY<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Michael,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:FORSYTHE},{firstname:Chris,role:reported,organization:,rank:2,lastname:BUCKLEY}]}",article
"Swiss voters overwhelmingly rejected proposals <DATE>Sunday</DATE> boost gold reserves impose strict curbs immigration, averting potential nightmare policymakers struggling popular backlash country's open borders.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-11-30T06:41:51Z,[],542,"Swiss voters overwhelmingly rejected proposals <DATE>Sunday</DATE> boost gold reserves impose strict curbs immigration, averting potential nightmare policymakers struggling popular backlash country's open borders.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/11/30/world/europe/30reuters-swiss-vote-projection.html,547b02c57988101f1558b2d4,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:Swiss Voters Reject Gold, Immigration Proposals, Salvaging <ORGANIZATION>EU<\/ORGANIZATION> Ties,print_headline:Swiss Voters Reject Gold, Immigration Proposals, Salvaging EU Ties}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"President <PERSON>Obama</PERSON>, in a television interview broadcast <DATE>Sunday</DATE>, called differences in talks between <LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION> and the <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> over <LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION>’s nuclear program “significant.”",,"[{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:1,value:Nuclear Weapons},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:United States International Relations},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Obama<\/PERSON>, Barack},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:4,value:Iran}]",<LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>,null,The New York Times,[],National,2014-11-24T00:00:00Z,[],399,"President <PERSON>Obama</PERSON>, in a television interview broadcast <DATE>Sunday</DATE>, called differences in talks between <LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION> and the <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> over <LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION>’s nuclear program “significant.”",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/11/24/us/politics/obama-acknowledges-broad-gaps-between-2-sides-in-iran-nuclear-talks-.html,547207de79881070464780ac,Politics,{"main":"Obama Acknowledges Broad Gaps Between 2 Sides Iran Nuclear Talks"},"{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>BRIAN KNOWLTON<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Brian,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:KNOWLTON}]}",article
"<LOCATION>China</LOCATION> cut interest rates time years <DATE>Friday</DATE> spur economy sliding slowest growth 24 years, signalled financial reforms cards freeing rates market.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-11-21T09:32:06Z,[],392,"<LOCATION>China</LOCATION> cut interest rates time years <DATE>Friday</DATE> spur economy sliding slowest growth 24 years, signalled financial reforms cards freeing rates market.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/11/21/business/21reuters-china-economy-rates-highlights.html,546f4db97988106ad45c6a33,null,"{main:<LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION> Explains Its First Rate Cut Over Two Years,print_headline:<LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION> Explains Its First Rate Cut Over Two Years}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"<LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s economy growing reasonable speed aggressive measures stimulate growth, Chinese central bank <DATE>Friday</DATE> cutting interest rates time years.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-11-21T06:27:57Z,[],86,"<LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s economy growing reasonable speed aggressive measures stimulate growth, Chinese central bank <DATE>Friday</DATE> cutting interest rates time years.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/11/21/business/21reuters-china-economy-policy.html,546f22287988106ad45c69a5,null,"{main:China Rules Out Strong Economic Stimulus After Rate Cut,print_headline:China Rules Out Strong Economic Stimulus After Rate Cut}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"Performing overseas <LOCATION>India</LOCATION>'s top priority test squad smart preparation time embark tour, <LOCATION>India</LOCATION> batsman VVS Laxman.",null,[],Sports,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-11-13T04:34:10Z,[],390,"Performing overseas <LOCATION>India</LOCATION>'s top priority test squad smart preparation time embark tour, <LOCATION>India</LOCATION> batsman VVS Laxman.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/11/13/sports/cricket/13reuters-cricket-india-laxman.html,54647c087988104000b1a957,Cricket,"{main:Laxman Implores <LOCATION>India<\/LOCATION> Focus Overseas Improvement,print_headline:Laxman Implores India Focus Overseas Improvement}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
