snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Two clueless, would-be bank robbers mixed wacky sting flush brains money-laundering scheme.",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T11:15:47Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-curse-of-inferno/video-the-curse-of-inferno-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-curse-of-inferno/video-the-curse-of-inferno-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-curse-of-inferno/video-the-curse-of-inferno-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-curse-of-inferno/video-the-curse-of-inferno-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-curse-of-inferno/video-the-curse-of-inferno-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-curse-of-inferno/video-the-curse-of-inferno-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",21,"Two clueless, would-be bank robbers mixed wacky sting flush brains money-laundering scheme.",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003385222/the-curse-of-inferno.html,54a573a079881011bed2ce06,null,{"main":"The Curse Of Inferno"},"{original:Orion Home Video,person:[{firstname:Orion,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Home,rank:1,lastname:Video}]}",multimedia
"When <PERSON>Vladimir Putin</PERSON> handed power unexpectedly ailing <PERSON>Boris Yeltsin</PERSON> day century, move television guarantee <LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION> freedoms needed civilised society.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-30T16:04:28Z,[],978,"When <PERSON>Vladimir Putin</PERSON> handed power unexpectedly ailing <PERSON>Boris Yeltsin</PERSON> day century, move television guarantee <LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION> freedoms needed civilised society.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/30/world/europe/30reuters-russia-crisis-putin.html,54a313f97988102761d6ceed,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{main:After 15 Years Power, <PERSON>Putin<\/PERSON> Risks Running Out Luck,print_headline:After 15 Years Power, <PERSON>Putin<\/PERSON> Risks Running Out Luck}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
<LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>'s state-run oil company temporarily suspending country's biggest builders engineering firms bidding contracts amid investigations massive corruption scandal.,null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T14:57:26Z,[],129,<LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>'s state-run oil company temporarily suspending country's biggest builders engineering firms bidding contracts amid investigations massive corruption scandal.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/world/americas/ap-lt-brazil-petrobras.html,54a304987988102761d6cec7,Americas,"{main:Petrobras Bans Firms Amid Kickback Probe,print_headline:Petrobras Bans Firms Amid Kickback Probe}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Chen Shui-bian, serving 20-year prison sentence, health problems include mild brain atrophy, severe depression Parkinsonism.",null,"[{name:persons,rank:1,value:Chen Shui-Bian},{name:persons,rank:2,value:Ko Wen-je},{name:persons,rank:3,value:Lu, Annette},{name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Taipei Taiwan<\/LOCATION>},{name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>Taiwan<\/LOCATION>},{name:subject,rank:1,value:Probation Parole},{name:subject,rank:2,value:Sentences Criminal}]",World,"Chen Shui-bian, serving 20-year prison sentence, health problems include mild brain atrophy, severe depression Parkinsonism.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-30T05:27:03Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/30/world/30sino-chen01/30sino-chen01-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/world/30sino-chen01/30sino-chen01-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/30/world/30sino-chen01/30sino-chen01-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:731},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/world/30sino-chen01/30sino-chen01-articleLarge.jpg,height:731},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/30/world/30sino-chen01/30sino-chen01-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/30/world/30sino-chen01/30sino-chen01-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",355,null,Blog,http://sinosphere.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/30/taiwan-considers-medical-parole-for-jailed-former-president/,54a27e0f7988104803cc8a47,Asia Pacific,"{main:<LOCATION>Taiwan<\/LOCATION> Considers Medical Parole Jailed Former President,kicker:Sinosphere}","{original:By <PERSON>AUSTIN RAMZY<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Austin,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:RAMZY}]}",blogpost
"<LOCATION>China</LOCATION> signing agreement <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> target assets illegally <LOCATION>China</LOCATION> corrupt officials, state-run newspaper <DATE>Monday</DATE>, government tightens screws anti-graft battle.",null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-29T02:29:36Z,[],422,"<LOCATION>China</LOCATION> signing agreement <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> target assets illegally <LOCATION>China</LOCATION> corrupt officials, state-run newspaper <DATE>Monday</DATE>, government tightens screws anti-graft battle.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/29/world/asia/29reuters-china-corruption.html,54a103017988101f98e3ef1c,Asia Pacific,"{main:<LOCATION>Beijing Looks U.S.<\/LOCATION> Deal Recover Dirty Assets: <LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION> Daily,print_headline:<LOCATION>Beijing Looks U.S.<\/LOCATION> Deal Recover Dirty Assets: <LOCATION>China<\/LOCATION> Daily}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"From dawn dusk, social historian sees intricacies life Victorian England.",19,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Books Literature},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:2,value:<PERSON>Goodman<\/PERSON>, Ruth <DATE>1963<\/DATE>-},{is_major:Y,name:creative_works,rank:3,value:How Be Victorian Book}]",Books,<PERSON>Judith Newman</PERSON> reviews book How Be Victorian: A Dawn-to-Dusk Guide Victorian Life <PERSON>Ruth Goodman</PERSON>.,The New York Times,[],BookReview,2014-12-28T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/28/books/review/28NEWMAN/28newman-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/books/review/28NEWMAN/28newman-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/28/books/review/28NEWMAN/28newman-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:574},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/books/review/28NEWMAN/28newman-articleLarge.jpg,height:574},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/28/books/review/28NEWMAN/28NEWMAN-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/books/review/28NEWMAN/28NEWMAN-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",1237,"From dawn dusk, social historian sees intricacies life Victorian England.",Review,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/books/review/how-to-be-a-victorian-by-ruth-goodman.html,549da00b7988105ced78859f,<DATE>Sunday</DATE> Book Review,"{main:‘How to Be a Victorian,’ by <PERSON>Ruth Goodman<\/PERSON>,print_headline:A Mile Her Corset}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>JUDITH NEWMAN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Judith,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:NEWMAN}]}",article
"President <PERSON>Vladimir V. Putin</PERSON> <LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION>, wields virtually unchallenged power reward class oligarchs, instrument punish oppose.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:1,value:<PERSON>Putin<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Vladimir<\/PERSON> V},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:2,value:<LOCATION>Russia<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Series},{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:4,value:Yevtushenkov, <PERSON>Vladimir<\/PERSON> P},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:Political Prisoners},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:6,value:Bashneft OAO},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:7,value:<PERSON>Lebedev<\/PERSON>, Aleksandr Y},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:8,value:Pugachev, <PERSON>Sergei<\/PERSON>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:9,value:<PERSON>Sechin<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Igor<\/PERSON> I},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:10,value:Rosneft}]",World,"Russian Pres Vladimir V <PERSON>Putin</PERSON> developed political economic system rewards class oligarchs severely punishes challenge <ORGANIZATION>Kremlin</ORGANIZATION>'s interests; latest case fate <PERSON>Vladimir P Yevtushenkov</PERSON>, longstanding loyalty <PERSON>Putin</PERSON>, punished public humiliating manner, lifetime fortune oil company <ORGANIZATION>Bashneft</ORGANIZATION> returned state Series: <PERSON>Putin</PERSON>'s Way.",The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-27T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/27/world/JP-PUTIN-1/JP-PUTIN-1-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/world/JP-PUTIN-1/JP-PUTIN-1-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/27/world/JP-PUTIN-1/JP-PUTIN-1-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:394},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/world/JP-PUTIN-1/JP-PUTIN-1-articleLarge.jpg,height:394},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/27/world/JP-PUTIN-1/JP-PUTIN-1-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/world/JP-PUTIN-1/JP-PUTIN-1-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",2855,"President <PERSON>Vladimir V. Putin</PERSON> <LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION>, wields virtually unchallenged power reward class oligarchs, instrument punish oppose.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/27/world/even-loyalty-no-guarantee-against-putin.html,549e10cd7988105ced788670,<LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>,"{content_kicker:<PERSON>Putin<\/PERSON>'s Way,main:Even Loyalty No Guarantee Against Putin,print_headline:Even Loyalty No Guarantee Against Putin,kicker:<PERSON>Putin<\/PERSON>'s Way}","{contributor:<PERSON>Steven Lee Myers<\/PERSON> reported <LOCATION>Moscow<\/LOCATION>, <PERSON>Jo Becker<\/PERSON> <LOCATION>Paris New York<\/LOCATION>. <PERSON>Andrew Roth<\/PERSON> contributed reporting <LOCATION>Moscow<\/LOCATION>, <PERSON>Masha Goncharova<\/PERSON> <LOCATION>New York<\/LOCATION>.,original:By <PERSON>STEVEN LEE MYERS JO BECKER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Steven,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Lee,rank:1,lastname:MYERS},{firstname:Jo,role:reported,organization:,rank:2,lastname:BECKER}]}",article
"Standard Chartered Plc hired prosecutors police transactions criminal activity, spokesman <DATE>Friday</DATE>, British bank wrestles series legal compliance problems.",null,[],Business Day,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-26T15:12:19Z,[],376,"Standard Chartered Plc hired prosecutors police transactions criminal activity, spokesman <DATE>Friday</DATE>, British bank wrestles series legal compliance problems.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/26/business/26reuters-standardchartered-compliance.html,549dc1b67988105ced7885df,null,"{main:Standard Chartered Hires Ex <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Prosecutors Amid Sanctions Probe,print_headline:Standard Chartered Hires Ex <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Prosecutors Amid Sanctions Probe}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
<LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>'s state-run oil company <ORGANIZATION>Petroleo Brasileiro SA</ORGANIZATION> and some of its executives were hit with a <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> class action lawsuit by investors in <MONEY>$98 billion</MONEY> of the company's securities over an alleged kickback and bribery scheme.,null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2014-12-26T07:20:22Z,[],406,<LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>'s state-run oil company <ORGANIZATION>Petroleo Brasileiro SA</ORGANIZATION> and some of its executives were hit with a <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> class action lawsuit by investors in <MONEY>$98 billion</MONEY> of the company's securities over an alleged kickback and bribery scheme.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2014/12/26/world/americas/26reuters-brazil-petrobras.html,549d52a07988103babf08b7e,Americas,"{main:Petrobras Hit With <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Class Action Suit Over <MONEY>$98 Billion<\/MONEY> in Securities,print_headline:Petrobras Hit With <LOCATION>U.S.<\/LOCATION> Class Action Suit Over <MONEY>$98 Billion<\/MONEY> in Securities}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"More 30 Israeli politicians public figures detained questioning connection corruption probe, police <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>.",12,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Israel<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Corruption Institutional},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:3,value:<PERSON>Yisrael Beiteinu<\/PERSON>},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:4,value:<PERSON>Lieberman<\/PERSON>, Avigdor}]",World,Israeli police report 30 Israeli politicians public officials questioned connection corruption probe; wide-ranging investigation affect <DATE>March 2015</DATE> elections.,The New York Times,[],Foreign,2014-12-25T00:00:00Z,[],99,"More 30 Israeli politicians public figures detained questioning connection corruption probe, police <DATE>Wednesday</DATE>.",Brief,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/25/world/middleeast/israel-politicians-are-detained-in-a-broad-corruption-inquiry.html,549b5d72798810030669106d,Middle East,"{content_kicker:World Briefing,main:<LOCATION>Israel<\/LOCATION>: Politicians Are Detained Broad Corruption Inquiry,print_headline:<LOCATION>Israel<\/LOCATION>: Politicians Are Detained Broad Corruption Inquiry}","{contributor:,original:By ISABEL KERSHNER,person:[{firstname:Isabel,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:KERSHNER}]}",article
