snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
He ran chance.,null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T19:05:25Z,[],2584,He ran chance.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/world/asia/ap-as-skorea-slave-islands.html,54a5e1337988102023c94ef7,Asia Pacific,"{main:'A Living Hell' Slaves Remote South Korean Islands,print_headline:'A Living Hell' Slaves Remote South Korean Islands}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
He ran chance.,null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T19:05:25Z,[],1135,He ran chance.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/world/asia/ap-as-skorea-slave-islands-abridged.html,54a5e12d7988102023c94ef5,Asia Pacific,"{main:'A Living Hell' Disabled Slaves South Korean Islands,print_headline:'A Living Hell' Disabled Slaves South Korean Islands}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
<ORGANIZATION>Connor Cook Michigan State Spartans</ORGANIZATION> role playoff talk season.,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T17:01:41Z,[],832,<ORGANIZATION>Connor Cook Michigan State Spartans</ORGANIZATION> role playoff talk season.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/sports/ncaafootball/ap-fbc-t25-cotton-bowl.html,54a5c4567988102023c94c0a,College Football,"{main:No. 7 MSU Shocks No. 4 Baylor 42-41 Cotton Bowl,print_headline:No. 7 MSU Shocks No. 4 Baylor 42-41 Cotton Bowl}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"<PERSON>Peter Carey</PERSON> accepts staff position staid <LOCATION>Boston</LOCATION> hospital, direction Dr. <PERSON>J.D. Randall Dan O'Herlihy</PERSON>. When Dr. <PERSON>Randall</PERSON>'s daughter <PERSON>Karen</PERSON> dies illegal abortion, <PERSON>Carey</PERSON>'s colleague <PERSON>David Tao</PERSON> prolific character great Jam",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T13:12:33Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-carey-treatment/video-the-carey-treatment-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-carey-treatment/video-the-carey-treatment-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-carey-treatment/video-the-carey-treatment-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-carey-treatment/video-the-carey-treatment-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-carey-treatment/video-the-carey-treatment-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-the-carey-treatment/video-the-carey-treatment-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",38,"<PERSON>Peter Carey</PERSON> accepts staff position staid <LOCATION>Boston</LOCATION> hospital, direction Dr. <PERSON>J.D. Randall Dan O'Herlihy</PERSON>. When Dr. <PERSON>Randall</PERSON>'s daughter <PERSON>Karen</PERSON> dies illegal abortion, <PERSON>Carey</PERSON>'s colleague <PERSON>David Tao</PERSON> prolific character great Jam",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003384161/the-carey-treatment.html,54a58e147988102023c941f0,null,{"main":"The Carey Treatment"},"{original:Warner Home Video,person:[{firstname:Warner,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Home,rank:1,lastname:Video}]}",multimedia
"A group unemployed theater actors survive working illegal money collectors. The loan shark working owns Off-Broadway theater. As decided play '<ORGANIZATION>American Buffalo</ORGANIZATION>', bloody battle favorite roles begins.",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T12:28:54Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-frogs-for-snakes/video-frogs-for-snakes-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-frogs-for-snakes/video-frogs-for-snakes-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-frogs-for-snakes/video-frogs-for-snakes-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-frogs-for-snakes/video-frogs-for-snakes-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-frogs-for-snakes/video-frogs-for-snakes-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-frogs-for-snakes/video-frogs-for-snakes-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",41,"A group unemployed theater actors survive working illegal money collectors. The loan shark working owns Off-Broadway theater. As decided play '<ORGANIZATION>American Buffalo</ORGANIZATION>', bloody battle favorite roles begins.",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003325675/frogs-for-snakes.html,54a583fc7988102023c93ec2,null,{"main":"Frogs For Snakes"},"{original:Artisan Entertainment,person:[{firstname:Artisan,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Entertainment}]}",multimedia
"<LOCATION>Israel</LOCATION>'s finance minister <DATE>Thursday</DATE> government's rush allot <MONEY>tens millions dollars</MONEY> <LOCATION>West Bank</LOCATION> settlements month amounted corruption, sought link secretive spending spree growing wave scandals...",null,[],World,null,AP,[],None,2015-01-01T11:52:11Z,[],344,"<LOCATION>Israel</LOCATION>'s finance minister <DATE>Thursday</DATE> government's rush allot <MONEY>tens millions dollars</MONEY> <LOCATION>West Bank</LOCATION> settlements month amounted corruption, sought link secretive spending spree growing wave scandals ahead <DATE>March</DATE> elections.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2015/01/01/world/middleeast/ap-ml-israel-palestinians.html,54a57c3979881011bed2d016,Middle East,"{main:<LOCATION>Israel<\/LOCATION> Ex-Minister: Settlement Funding Is Corrupt,print_headline:<LOCATION>Israel<\/LOCATION> Ex-Minister: Settlement Funding Is Corrupt}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Sex, politics American culture mixed combustible combination <ORGANIZATION>Now&Later</ORGANIZATION>. AngelaShari Solanis illegal Latina immigrant living <LOCATION>Los Angeles</LOCATION> stumbles <PERSON>Bill JamesWortham</PERSON>, disgraced banker run. She ta",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T10:59:22Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-later/video-later-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-later/video-later-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-later/video-later-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-later/video-later-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-later/video-later-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-later/video-later-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",37,"Sex, politics American culture mixed combustible combination <ORGANIZATION>Now&Later</ORGANIZATION>. AngelaShari Solanis illegal Latina immigrant living <LOCATION>Los Angeles</LOCATION> stumbles <PERSON>Bill JamesWortham</PERSON>, disgraced banker run. She ta",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003359891/later.html,54a56ee079881011bed2cd2a,null,{"main":"Later"},"{original:Cinema Libre Studio,person:[{firstname:Cinema,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Libre,rank:1,lastname:Studio}]}",multimedia
Palestinian President <PERSON>Mahmoud Abbas</PERSON> entered confrontation <LOCATION>Israel</LOCATION> signing <ORGANIZATION>International Criminal Court</ORGANIZATION>.,null,[],World,null,Reuters,[],None,2015-01-01T10:40:03Z,[],846,Palestinian President <PERSON>Mahmoud Abbas</PERSON> entered confrontation <LOCATION>Israel</LOCATION> signing <ORGANIZATION>International Criminal Court</ORGANIZATION>.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/reuters/2015/01/01/world/middleeast/01reuters-palestinians-israel-abbas.html,54a56b0279881011bed2cc49,Middle East,"{main:Abbas Trades Stalemate Confrontation ICC Move,print_headline:Abbas Trades Stalemate Confrontation ICC Move}","{original:By REUTERS,person:[],organization:REUTERS}",article
"It's fast, funny, outrageously illegal - granddaddy cross-country speed spectacles raced movie screens past generations. Put pedal metal The <ORGANIZATION>Gumball Rally</ORGANIZATION>. <LOCATION>New York City</LOCATION> starting poin",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T10:24:48Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/05/movies/video-the-gumball-rally/video-the-gumball-rally-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/05/movies/video-the-gumball-rally/video-the-gumball-rally-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/05/movies/video-the-gumball-rally/video-the-gumball-rally-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/05/movies/video-the-gumball-rally/video-the-gumball-rally-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/05/movies/video-the-gumball-rally/video-the-gumball-rally-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/05/movies/video-the-gumball-rally/video-the-gumball-rally-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",42,"It's fast, funny, outrageously illegal - granddaddy cross-country speed spectacles raced movie screens past generations. Put pedal metal The <ORGANIZATION>Gumball Rally</ORGANIZATION>. <LOCATION>New York City</LOCATION> starting poin",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003388874/the-gumball-rally.html,54a566c779881011bed2cb53,null,{"main":"The Gumball Rally"},"{original:Warner Home Video,person:[{firstname:Warner,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Home,rank:1,lastname:Video}]}",multimedia
"Lion Ark vivid scenes account ambitious animal rescue undertaken, finale sees 25 lions rescued illegal traveling circuses <LOCATION>Bolivia</LOCATION> flown safety USA.A shocking unde",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video Archive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T09:43:04Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/20/movies/video-lion-ark/video-lion-ark-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/20/movies/video-lion-ark/video-lion-ark-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/20/movies/video-lion-ark/video-lion-ark-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/20/movies/video-lion-ark/video-lion-ark-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/20/movies/video-lion-ark/video-lion-ark-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/20/movies/video-lion-ark/video-lion-ark-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",41,"Lion Ark vivid scenes account ambitious animal rescue undertaken, finale sees 25 lions rescued illegal traveling circuses <LOCATION>Bolivia</LOCATION> flown safety USA.A shocking unde",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003350214/lion-ark.html,54a55cfb79881011bed2c927,null,{"main":"Lion Ark"},"{original:ADI Films,person:[{firstname:Adi,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:Films}]}",multimedia
