snippet,print_page,keywords,section_name,abstract,source,blog,news_desk,pub_date,multimedia,word_count,lead_paragraph,type_of_material,web_url,_id,subsection_name,headline,byline,document_type
"Okay, movie fans. To nuke corn, dim lights settle cinematic mutations gargantuan 'gators, fearsome frogs, awesome ants monstrous moths, quote film: Ladies gentleme",null,[],Movies,null,Internet Video A.chive,[],Movies,2015-01-01T12:54:06Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-night-of-the-lepus/video-night-of-the-lepus-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-night-of-the-lepus/video-night-of-the-lepus-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-night-of-the-lepus/video-night-of-the-lepus-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:338},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-night-of-the-lepus/video-night-of-the-lepus-articleLarge.jpg,height:338},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-night-of-the-lepus/video-night-of-the-lepus-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/02/03/movies/video-night-of-the-lepus/video-night-of-the-lepus-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",42,"Okay, movie fans. To nuke corn, dim lights settle cinematic mutations gargantuan 'gators, fearsome frogs, awesome ants monstrous moths, quote film: Ladies gentleme",Video,http://www.nytimes.com/video/movies/100000003358727/night-of-the-lepus.html,54a589d57988102023c9409c,null,{"main":"Night Of The Lepus"},"{original:Warner Home Video,person:[{firstname:Warner,role:reported,organization:,middlename:Home,rank:1,lastname:Video}]}",multimedia
"As fresh starts, celebrate. <LOCATION>Iowa</LOCATION> coach <PERSON>Fran McCaffery</PERSON> step.",null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-30T15:11:50Z,[],732,"As fresh starts, celebrate. <LOCATION>Iowa</LOCATION> coach <PERSON>Fran McCaffery</PERSON> step.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/30/sports/ncaabasketball/ap-bkc-t25-iowa-ohio-st.html,54a307627988102761d6cecf,College Basketball,"{main:Uthoff, <LOCATION>White Lead Iowa<\/LOCATION> Past No. 20 <LOCATION>Ohio<\/LOCATION> St 71-65,print_headline:Uthoff, <LOCATION>White Lead Iowa<\/LOCATION> Past No. 20 <LOCATION>Ohio<\/LOCATION> St 71-65}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
"Every time I write about anonymous sourcing, I emphasize that it is sometimes both necessary and important. These examples don’t measure up.",null,[],Opinion,"Every time I write about anonymous sourcing, I emphasize that it is sometimes both necessary and important. These examples don’t measure up.",The New York Times,[],null,2014-12-29T11:33:09Z,[],684,null,Blog,http://publiceditor.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/12/29/anonywatch-department-of-ridiculous-reasons/,54a1829e7988101f98e3effc,The Public Editor,"{main:AnonyWatch: Department Ridiculous Reasons,kicker:The Public Editor&#039;s Journal}","{original:By <PERSON>MARGARET SULLIVAN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Margaret,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:SULLIVAN}]}",blogpost
"SCHECHTER--<PERSON>Aaron</PERSON>, born <DATE>March 19, 1926</DATE> Brooklyn, NY passed peacefully <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> <DATE>December 22nd</DATE>. Aaron wonderful life regrets; quote <PERSON>Frank Sinatra</PERSON>, I. An entertainment CPA, hand holder...",28,"[{name:persons,value:SCHECHTER, AARON}]",Paid Death Notices,null,The New York Times,[],Classified,2014-12-28T00:00:00Z,[],240,"SCHECHTER--<PERSON>Aaron</PERSON>, born on <DATE>March 19, 1926</DATE> in <LOCATION>Brooklyn</LOCATION>, NY passed away peacefully in <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> on <DATE>December 22nd</DATE>. Aaron had a wonderful life with no regrets; to quote <PERSON>Frank Sinatra</PERSON>, I did it my way. An entertainment CPA, hand holder and most importantly a genuinely nice man for his career of sixty-five plus years. His wife, <PERSON>Elaine</PERSON>, served as his right hand through it all. They had an unshakeable bond that later generations hope to emulate. He leaves his wife, <PERSON>Elaine Abrams</PERSON> and three wonderful daughters --<PERSON>Annie Kasper Tom</PERSON>, <PERSON>Sarah Gill Tony</PERSON> and <ORGANIZATION>Betsy Waters Andrew</ORGANIZATION> along with the great joys of his life --<PERSON>Rebecca</PERSON>, <PERSON>Caroline</PERSON> and <PERSON>Priscilla Kasper</PERSON>, <PERSON>Maxwell</PERSON> and <ORGANIZATION>Sammy Waters</ORGANIZATION> and <PERSON>Oliver Gill</PERSON>. He often quipped; We should have had the grandchildren first. Also survived by his sailing buddies <PERSON>Ellen</PERSON> and <PERSON>Marty Abrams</PERSON>, brother <PERSON>Mike Shepherd</PERSON>, <PERSON>Alex Rooks</PERSON> and <PERSON>Jules Alexander</PERSON> and their families. In <DATE>2000</DATE>, after enjoying <LOCATION>Compo Beach</LOCATION> in <LOCATION>Westport</LOCATION>, CT for thirty-seven years, <PERSON>Aaron</PERSON> and <PERSON>Elaine</PERSON> returned to <LOCATION>Manhattan</LOCATION> where he enjoyed his backyard, <LOCATION>Central Park</LOCATION>, as a visitor and volunteer. Donations in his honor may be made to the <PERSON>Aaron Schechter Baruch</PERSON> College Scholarship Fund, c/o Baruch College Fund, One <PERSON>Bernard Baruch Way</PERSON>, Box A-1063, NY NY 10010. A memorial celebration will be held on <DATE>Friday January 30, 2015</DATE> at 6pm at the <ORGANIZATION>Baruch Performing Arts Center Nagelberg Theater</ORGANIZATION>. Entrance on south side East 25th Street between Third and Lex. Bowtie Optional. 1/3",Paid Death Notice,http://query.nytimes.com/gst/fullpage.html?res=9F04E4D91F3AF93BA15751C1A9629D8B63,54aa0cb479881040cba0f4a8,null,"{main:Paid Notice: Deaths  SCHECHTER, AARON}",null,article
"Our constellations upside, stars shine brighter.",null,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Stars Galaxies},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:Space Astronomy},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Milky Way Galaxy},{is_major:N,name:glocations,rank:4,value:South America},{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:5,value:Latin America}]",Opinion,"Op-Ed | <PERSON>Vanessa Barbaraarticle</PERSON> Brazilian newspaper columnist <PERSON>Vanessa Barbara</PERSON> submits, exception <ORGANIZATION>Big Dipper Northern Lights</ORGANIZATION>, southern hemisphere offers earth's views starry sky.",The New York Times,[],Editorial,2014-12-28T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/28/sunday-review/28BARBARA-1419444549163/28BARBARA-1419444549163-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/sunday-review/28BARBARA-1419444549163/28BARBARA-1419444549163-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/28/sunday-review/28BARBARA-1419444549163/28BARBARA-1419444549163-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:401},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/sunday-review/28BARBARA-1419444549163/28BARBARA-1419444549163-articleLarge.jpg,height:401},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/28/sunday-review/28BARBARA-1419444549163/28BARBARA-1419444549163-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/sunday-review/28BARBARA-1419444549163/28BARBARA-1419444549163-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",804,"Our constellations upside, stars shine brighter.",Op-Ed,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/opinion/sunday/stargazing-is-better-in-the-southern-hemisphere.html,549efbe579881001534d1f69,<DATE>Sunday</DATE> Review,"{content_kicker:Contributing Op-Ed Writer,main:The Dazzle Southern Sky,seo:Stargazing Is Better Southern Hemisphere,print_headline:The Dazzle Southern Sky,kicker:Op-Ed | <PERSON>Vanessa Barbara<\/PERSON>}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>VANESSA BARBARA<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Vanessa,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:BARBARA}]}",article
Companies highlighting heritage attract shoppers value ritual tradition.,6,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Shopping Retail},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Trademarks Trade Names},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Advertising Marketing},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Zady Inc},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:5,value:E-Commerce},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Fashion Apparel},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:7,value:Factories Manufacturing}]",Business Day,"Companies spotlighting heritage effort gain customers value ritual tradition; studies authenticity--real perceived--can affect company's sales profits; online retailer Zady sells clothing, jewelry items companies stories shares site.",The New York Times,[],SundayBusiness,2014-12-28T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/28/business/28-ORIGINS-5/28-ORIGINS-5-thumbWide-v2.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/business/28-ORIGINS-5/28-ORIGINS-5-thumbWide-v2.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/28/business/28-ORIGINS-5/28-ORIGINS-5-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:751},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/business/28-ORIGINS-5/28-ORIGINS-5-articleLarge.jpg,height:751},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/28/business/28-ORIGINS-5/28-ORIGINS-5-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/business/28-ORIGINS-5/28-ORIGINS-5-thumbStandard-v2.jpg,height:75}]",1477,Companies highlighting heritage attract shoppers value ritual tradition.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/business/quenching-consumers-thirst-for-authentic-brands.html,549ed0327988105ced788716,null,"{main:Quenching Consumers&#8217; Thirst &#8216;Authentic&#8217; Brands,print_headline:Quenching Consumers’ Thirst for ‘Authentic’ Brands}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>MATTHEW HUTSON<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Matthew,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:HUTSON}]}",article
"From Doors Ramones, <ORGANIZATION>Danny Fields</ORGANIZATION> witnessed revolution inside, records.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:persons,rank:1,value:Fields, Danny},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Movies},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Archives Records},{is_major:Y,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Yale Beinecke Rare Book Manuscript Library},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:5,value:Music},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Rock Music},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:7,value:Ramones Music Group},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:8,value:Stooges, The Music Group}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"<PERSON>Danny Fields</PERSON>, music industry executive, photographer, DJ and journalist who was instrumental to formation of punk rock movement, has sold part of his extensive archives to <ORGANIZATION>Yale University’s Beinecke Rare Book & Manuscript Library</ORGANIZATION> and is subject of <PERSON>Brendan Toller</PERSON>'s upcoming documentary film <PERSON>Danny</PERSON> Says.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-28T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/28DANNYweb/28DANNYweb-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/28DANNYweb/28DANNYweb-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/28DANNYweb/28DANNYweb-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:405},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/28DANNYweb/28DANNYweb-articleLarge.jpg,height:405},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/28DANNYweb/28DANNYweb-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/28/nyregion/28DANNYweb/28DANNYweb-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1410,"From Doors Ramones, <ORGANIZATION>Danny Fields</ORGANIZATION> witnessed revolution inside, records.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/nyregion/iggy-lou-joey-and-danny.html,549d1e1b7988103babf08b3b,null,"{main:He Was Present Birth Punk, He Took Notes,print_headline:Iggy, <PERSON>Lou<\/PERSON>, <PERSON>Joey<\/PERSON> — and Danny}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>CHARLES CURKIN<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Charles,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:CURKIN}]}",article
D'Angelo Russell Big Ten. He excited finally finding.,null,[],Sports,null,AP,[],None,2014-12-27T21:15:26Z,[],741,D'Angelo Russell Big Ten. He excited finally finding.,News,http://www.nytimes.com/aponline/2014/12/27/sports/ncaabasketball/ap-bkc-t25-wright-st-ohio-st.html,549f685f79881001534d1fd3,College Basketball,"{main:Russell Has 24, Leads No. 21 <ORGANIZATION>Ohio State<\/ORGANIZATION> Win,print_headline:Russell Has 24, Leads No. 21 <ORGANIZATION>Ohio State<\/ORGANIZATION> Win}","{original:By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS,person:[],organization:THE ASSOCIATED PRESS}",article
They lost battle Republican stronghold.,17,"[{is_major:Y,name:glocations,rank:1,value:<LOCATION>Nebraska<\/LOCATION>},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:2,value:United States Politics Government},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:3,value:Politics Government},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:4,value:Republican Party},{is_major:N,name:organizations,rank:5,value:Democratic Party},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:6,value:Keystone Pipeline System},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:7,value:<PERSON>Hassebrook<\/PERSON>, Chuck},{is_major:N,name:persons,rank:8,value:Domina, <PERSON>David<\/PERSON> A},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:9,value:Midterm Elections 2014},{is_major:N,name:subject,rank:10,value:Elections, <ORGANIZATION>Senate<\/ORGANIZATION>}]",Opinion,"Op-Ed article psychologist author <PERSON>Mary Pipher</PERSON> argues importance progressives heavily conservative states home <LOCATION>Nebraska</LOCATION>; pushing progressive agenda <LOCATION>Nebraska</LOCATION> exhausting disheartening work, continues quit hand state single political view.",The New York Times,[],OpEd,2014-12-27T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/27/opinion/27oped-img/27oped-img-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/opinion/27oped-img/27oped-img-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/27/opinion/27oped-img/27oped-img-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/27/opinion/27oped-img/27oped-img-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",904,They lost battle Republican stronghold.,Op-Ed,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/27/opinion/nebraskas-lonely-progressives.html,549dfc727988105ced78864e,null,"{content_kicker:Op-Ed Contributor,main:<LOCATION>Nebraska<\/LOCATION>&#8217;s Lonely Progressives,print_headline:<LOCATION>Nebraska<\/LOCATION>’s Lonely Progressives,kicker:Op-Ed Contributor}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>MARY PIPHER<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Mary,role:reported,organization:,rank:1,lastname:PIPHER}]}",article
"Without guidance, students easily make poor decisions, families college, national ratio 500 students counselor.",1,"[{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:1,value:Guidance Counselors},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:2,value:Education K-12},{is_major:Y,name:subject,rank:3,value:Colleges Universities}]",<LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> / Region,"Large public high schools country, <LOCATION>Brooklyn</LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>Midwood High School</ORGANIZATION>, struggling lack guidance counselors, time students apply college; national ratio students counselors 500 1, proportion remained unchanged 10 years; students make poor decisions attending college absence guidance counselor.",The New York Times,[],Metro,2014-12-26T00:00:00Z,"[{legacy:{wideheight:126,widewidth:190,wide:images/2014/12/26/nyregion/y-COUNSELOR/y-COUNSELOR-thumbWide.jpg},subtype:wide,width:190,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/nyregion/y-COUNSELOR/y-COUNSELOR-thumbWide.jpg,height:126},{legacy:{xlarge:images/2014/12/26/nyregion/y-COUNSELOR/y-COUNSELOR-articleLarge.jpg,xlargewidth:600,xlargeheight:400},subtype:xlarge,width:600,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/nyregion/y-COUNSELOR/y-COUNSELOR-articleLarge.jpg,height:400},{legacy:{thumbnail:images/2014/12/26/nyregion/y-COUNSELOR/y-COUNSELOR-thumbStandard.jpg,thumbnailwidth:75,thumbnailheight:75},subtype:thumbnail,width:75,type:image,url:images/2014/12/26/nyregion/y-COUNSELOR/y-COUNSELOR-thumbStandard.jpg,height:75}]",1235,"Without guidance, students easily make poor decisions, families college, national ratio 500 students counselor.",News,http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/26/nyregion/little-college-guidance-500-high-school-students-per-counselor.html,549ccc607988103babf08ac8,null,"{main:Little College Guidance: 500 High School Students Per Counselor,print_headline:Little Guidance: 500 Students Per Counselor}","{contributor:,original:By <PERSON>ELIZABETH A. HARRIS<\/PERSON>,person:[{firstname:Elizabeth,role:reported,organization:,middlename:A.,rank:1,lastname:HARRIS}]}",article
